okay here we are we're live
trying out a new system right now anyway
tonight we're talking about
supplements this is a really important
live and i want to cover a lot of
information as much as i can
there's a lot of information out there
about supplements first of all there's a
lot of people out there that think they
don't need any supplementation
they don't need anything they can get
everything from their food
okay so that's that's what a lot of
people believe they can just get it all
from their food
and you know and they're covered right
and then you got people that believe
they do need some supplements and that
it may be a sound thing to do and it may
be important to do
glad to see you guys here in the
comments coming up here um
and you know there's there's people that
will do that too well they'll be like
you know what i kind of need some
supplements and
but there's a lot of people that you
know like i said they believe they could
get it all from their food and
and can we get everything from our food
can we get every chemical compound can
we get every nutrient
can we get all the things we need from
just our
food that's really important all on its
own like that's an important critical
thing to like think about
if we can get everything
from our food think about this you guys
check this out okay if we can get
everything from our food
all right well then what about the food
we eat
all these years what about the food we
ate 20 years ago what about the food we
ate 10 years ago what about the food we
ate five years ago
what about the processed food we might
have eaten what about the gras
the greasy uh fast food we might have
eaten right
what about that all in its own think
about that so
you know there's a lot to really
consider here
and did we eat poor food in the mean
like very poorly in the past
so even if we're on the most amazing
diet right now even if you think you're
on this great balanced diet or you're on
this
in a food combining diet someone sold
you into or you're on a
you're on a intuitive eating diet which
really you know
isn't really much of anything in many
ways and say you're on a paleo diet or
say you're on a plant-based diet or
whatever you're doing
what was the last 20 years was it all
organic
were you eating have you been eating
organic food since birth
and i'm going to tell you something
about even organic
farms organic soil i mean the farm
soil and organic farming is depleted
so even farms that are growing organic
food
you know are are depleted of many
trace minerals many nutrients and that's
organic
so if you if so say you're somebody who
didn't eat didn't eat organic your whole
life because how
come on like who who's eating organic
their whole life not a lot of people i'm
not a lot of people and was there soil
the most
richest and nutritious you know it's you
know like whatever
but i mean i've known people that they
grow their own food okay
and their soil is so rich
their compost that they use everything
they do
and trace minerals that they add through
all kinds of different options right
and they're using rock dust and they're
using all these different options and
it's soaked but
but organic farming it doesn't really do
that that's not how it's done
so and then conventional farming really
depleted conventional farming really
depleted so
here's the deal here's the question i
want to ask you you know and no big deal
it's just an interesting question
um were you eating a lot of wild foods
throughout your life if you're someone
that believes you can get every single
thing from your food and you don't need
supplements and you don't need
supplementation
on any level and you think you can get
anything everything and anything from
your food
were you eating a lot of wild foods your
whole life how much dolls have you eaten
throughout your whole life how many wild
blueberries have you eaten throughout
your whole life
how much aloe have you been eating
throughout your whole life because i'm
going to talk about aloe i'm actually
going to cut it open
show you how i eat aloe every single day
how much wild
food are you getting
in your diet right so that's one thing
how about this one
um how many herbs have you gotten in
your diet throughout your whole life how
much oregano how much sage how much time
how much you know margarine how much how
many how many how many herbs have you
gotten
how much lemon balm tea have you
consumed your whole life
you know think about it or how about
this how many leafy greens have you been
eating your whole life okay if you're
somebody that thinks i don't need to get
any supplementation
i don't need any supplements i don't
need nothing like that i could get it
all from my food
how many leafy greens have you been
consuming four cups of spinach every
single day two cups of spinach every
single day
how about mosh how about lots of kale
have you been consuming leafy greens
lettuces every single day
and a decent amount of them are you
doing all these leafy greens for your
whole life
no i doubt it and how about this one how
much fruit have you eaten throughout
your life
how much fruit all the fruit that you
that we need
to get the nutrition we need and get all
the things we need how much fruit
think about that one right there on his
out and with the trace minerals the
antioxidants the antiviral compounds in
fruit the antibacterial compounds in
fruit
right the phytochemical compounds in
fruit that actually
de-age us in the berries and the apples
and cleanse our liver
and get in and feed our liver all kinds
of glucose and nutrients
how much fruit are we doing our whole 20
30 years
but wait a minute you probably had pizza
of course you had pizza
i'm sure right well those pizza days
means you weren't eating all wild foods
and even if you weren't doing pizza that
day you probably wouldn't be doing wild
foods i'm not
shaming anybody i'm not at all
this is life this is normal like
exactly you might be somebody that had
pizza on and off your whole life but you
can get everything you could get all the
nutrition you want out of your food
uh well okay that's interesting because
man
in order to get everything we need out
of food man we got to be like
on it we have to be like just wild foods
the herbs
the greens the leafy greens lots of
fruit
all organic oh my god and that's that's
not something that's obtainable
normally or something that's so easy or
something we've done our whole life no
so
yes we need supplementation absolutely i
mean
i'm not one of those it's like you gotta
have supplementation no
if you feel good and you don't have any
symptoms and you don't have a condition
you guys
and you're not battling something and
you're not dealing with something
then fine you know fine if you're not
dealing with something living with
something suffering from something then
maybe you can do your foods and
clean that diet up and make sure you're
doing stuff by the way cleanse the heel
16.99 dirt cheap on sale amazon us
so i'm just letting you know and you can
get it free at the library by the way so
tonight we're going to talk about
powerful information because i'm going
to read out a cleanse to heal
i'm going to read out of here i'm going
to read excerpts i'm going to talk about
chapter 27 the supplements chapter and
i'm going to go through there a little
bit i'm going to answer questions too
uh really important so we're going to
talk about
all of this and it's really interesting
information if you really think about it
because
i run into people all the time and
they're like i don't need
any b12 and i don't need anything
because i get everything from my food
it's not really possible even though i
want people to get as much as they can
get out of foods but
no one's going to keep up with the wild
foods no one's going to keep on it with
all that no one's going to do aloe vera
every single day no one's going to do
aloe every day
you know it's not going to happen so you
know and so supplementation is important
and then
if you're suffering with a symptom or a
condition like
the over 200 different symptoms and
conditions plus more in here
and you're suffering and then
supplementation
is an option to to go as far as you want
to go
you can start with the foods you can
start with the cleanses and a lot of
people they just get rid of their
conditions with cleanses with the
cleanses
in in cleansing heal but you can go as
far as you want to and you could really
crank because that's the whole point
and go as far as you need to go powerful
information you won't hear anywhere else
i'm going to talk about tonight like all
medical medium information
if you did hear a word or two about
medical and medium information you're
like oh no wait a minute i heard about
metal
somewhere else focus you know consider
the details pay attention to the details
the details matter
because you'll know that that
information isn't
medical medium and you'll know that
medical medium information has all the
details like
how toxic heavy metals oxidize in our
brain and what
symptoms and conditions they cause that
never existed anywhere else so if you
hear something about it now it
originated from here
most people in the medical medium
community they started their journeys uh
seeing specialists
and doctors 10 doctors 15 doctors 20
doctors
i was known as the guy many years before
the books were published as a guy people
brought their bizarre symptoms to
and they couldn't get answers during the
course of sickness and they'd be seeing
all these different
doctors and everything and what happened
is that you know over the years of the
last 35 years i've worked with lots of
doctors that wanted answers wanted to
help troubleshooting cases
whole reason why this community grew so
big anyway throughout the years and
millions of medical medium books have
gone around the world and have sold
like that one right there the reason why
is because people got answers for the
first time and that was important so
people in the medical medium community
they've been there they've done that
a lot of people come here who haven't
been there and done that yet they get
here early and they start doing stuff
and
and they don't have that experience of
going around for you know five years
with symptoms and conditions and not
having answers they don't have that
experience yet
but most people they've been there
they've done that so it's been really
kind of a great thing to offer the
information so people can move forward
and real compassionate doctors lots of
them have the medical media books
in their doctor's offices they're
helping people every day with them it's
really incredible thing that's happening
so feel free feel free to bring what
you've learned what you learn here
tonight
to your medical doctor to your health
care provider to your practitioner
you know feel free to bring the book
show them the symptoms and conditions in
here this is a medical textbook is what
it is
so if if it's overwhelming some parts of
it you see
so much information because it's a thick
medical textbook you can bring
the book to your doctor's 51 off by the
way 16.99 at amazon.com
and and i mean you can get it so cheap
right now which is really great
by the way tonight's not an infomercial
on
supplementation supplements and all that
very important to know i know that a lot
of doctor authors they sell their own
supplement lines
and because they sell their own
supplement lines it's all about
it's all about their supplements it's
all about all that stuff that's not what
this
is i don't own thorn which is a
supplement company i like that i have
on my directory you know here's another
thorn supplement here
i don't own traditional medicinals i
don't own vimergy which you guys know
the bimergy products this is my favorite
the favorite line that i take every day
um so so really important to know there
so this is not
one of those infomercials what you'll
see out there is is there's a lot of
guys out there now they
they sell a book just so they can build
their brand and then sell
their supplementation and they put like
a million to two million dollars a month
in advertising you see their pop-up ads
left and right all through social media
they're bankrolling you know 100 million
dollars a year
and and it's really just garbage
supplements i see that all the time out
there that's not what this
is um basically what it is here is
go to library get the book for free how
about that okay i'm an infomercial for
going to the library isn't that great
and then learn and then learn what
supplementation you can bring to your
doctor and talk to
and you can go to medicalmedium.com and
see the best stuff that i use
fine uh but i'm not sponsored by the
company it's really important to know
and um so anybody who's jumping on here
that's
it's important to know because i get it
that's done all the time out there about
the
infomercials just everywhere people
selling their crap it's just
it's incredible so look you guys i'm
going to be reading part six and cleanse
the heel
that's where i'm going right now it's
part six
it's in the section there with over 200
symptoms and conditions
it's page 472
it's part six knowing the cause
and the protocols that's the first time
i've seen it not backwards on here
knowing the cause and the protocols you
guys might be able to read
read the book from here now for the
first time this is a really cool system
i got set up i'm trying a new system
so that you guys can read it
from the book i hope that's how it is on
your side
um all right so that's where i am
in this section there's over 200
symptoms and conditions
with protocols now there's
supplements and dosages what to do okay
the book is designed to take you as far
as you need to go
so when you do the 369 cleanse you're
healing
one side of everything you're dealing
with you can also work with supplements
too
on another side of it you can be
somebody that's just doing the mono
eating cleanse
it's the 369 you could be doing the
morning clench you could do the heavy
metal detox
cleanse you could do the anti-bug
cleanse there's lots of cleanses in the
book you do 369 original simplified and
advanced
the book is really designed for someone
to customize
their entire system
and that's what's amazing there isn't
just medical medium protocol
and i tried it and it didn't work you
know what you'll find out there
someone would be like oh i tried medical
medium it didn't work um oh
that's interesting oh my god did you do
the 369 advance
three times in a row did you do um
the mono eating cleanse did you try that
for a month did you do the supplements
and dosages
did you do that always keep that in mind
you know because what happens is the
book is designed with thousands of
protocols so
if someone says i tried medical media it
didn't work i tried fruits and
vegetables
that's pretty funny because there's
thousands of customized protocols in
medical medium books
thousands so there's a reason for that
there's
over a thousand combinations in here so
you can actually
heal and move yourself forward there's a
reason for that you can do
three of the supplement recommendations
you can do
two of the cleanses you can customize it
you can get yourself to a place
and you can take it all the way that's
how the book's designed
so all these points are really important
so let's get moving here a little bit
i'm in chapter 27 what you need to know
about supplements right here
i get asked questions all the time just
hundreds and hundreds of questions
especially thousands of questions
i mean it's ongoing okay like uh
the questions come all different sizes
and shapes like
do i need supplements do i not how do i
go about it where do i start
i'm sensitive you know that's a question
too you'll get like
i'm sensitive what do i do how do i go
about this
so there's just there's there's so much
of that and i completely understand
the thing is is that if you actually
read
the book cleanse the heel first of all
if i notice with all the different
questions i get
about supplementation or about cleansing
or however
i realize that the person a doesn't have
the book or never got the book
and that happens so if you're if you're
one of those
you you can get it first it's on sale 51
off right now in amazon us i mean
you can't go wrong with that or get it
free at the library if you're
and i noticed that i'll get a question
like you know
um i don't you know like what do i do
for this what do i do for that condition
well
sounds like you didn't read this chapter
what you need to know about supplements
and then true cause of symptoms and
conditions so it's either someone
doesn't have the book or they never read
it
it's one or the other if they have it
they haven't read it yet so let's cover
this
so what i want to do is i want to walk
through some of the
pieces of it now i won't be able to
cover every single aspect the book has
too much information
it's never too much but tremendous
amounts of information
that walks you through so this this
is your guide and that's what it is it's
like me
i i put the book together with spirit of
compassion to make it like
you got me there with you as far as like
taking that to that place so
i'm starting on page 472 right here and
i'm just going to read a little bit some
excerpts in between this and i'm going
to help you like
like guide you to through understanding
some of this information right now and
all that
um so just the first line in here why is
the world of nutraceuticals exploding
and
why is the whole thing with stuff why is
supplementation nutraceuticals exploding
that's because people are sick
they're sick no one wants to take
supplements who wants to take
gobble gobbles of pills and gobbles of
tablets and and liquids and all that
kind of stuff and powders
who wants to do that right you guys like
you know who who wants to go that i'm
glad you guys are all here i'm seeing
your comments
um um darcy said you're so kind to do
these lives
thank you i'm honored you feel that way
truly bless your heart really you know
you can't wait to start your 369 cleanse
um jennifer said how do i
how do i heal hashimoto's jennifer to
begin with
that's a really good question it's going
to take us into here actually too
if you've been diagnosed with
hashimoto's thyroiditis
okay first thing is to learn the cause
learn the cause because the doctors
have to tell patients what science
research believes it is
which is your body attacking itself
which is your immune system tacking your
own thyroid
creates an autoantibody and attacks the
thyroid that's not accurate
because they've never proved it they've
never showed it there's no study that
can show it there's no
there's no peer review study that shows
it there's no technology developed yet
to show the body attacking its
its own gland so i talk about the true
cause
in cleanse to heal so the first thing is
you get the book you go to the library
and get the book for free okay and when
you have the book
go into the symptoms and conditions
section all right and find out what the
true cause
was of what is hashimoto's why you have
hashimoto's that's to begin with
then you'll see supplementation and
protocols there but i want you to read
the chapter and everything before you
even get there so i'm in chapter 27.
so the reason why nutrition
nutraceuticals are exploding you guys
is because people are sick literally
sick
that's the reason why really important
to know right there
um and so because no one wants to just
go and buy supplements purchase
supplements
spend all that money and that's one of
the problems and here's a question i get
all the time
how do i do this what i'm going to end
up spending all this money
and out there because that's what people
do i've had people come to my office for
years for decades
i spent ten thousand dollars in
supplements just this month
i spent all these supplements i bought
out there in the world i went to this
doctor that practitioner this healer
and i got treasure troves of supplements
in in my cabinets and then i would be
like well
does any of those practitioners or
people know what the true cause of your
condition was they're like no
they don't know what's causing my
fibromyalgia they don't know what's
causing this and that because nobody
knows
right and so be like let's find out the
true cause to what your fibromyalgia is
i'm just giving that as one example
and then let's look at your treasure
trove of supplements that are in your
cabinet
and find out if any of them are for your
fibro and then when you go into their
cabinet i've seen this with so many
clients over the years years and years
ago they'd go
i'd go in their cabinet with them and
they would have
thousands of dollars of supplements that
were not going to help their
fibromyalgia
because the practitioners and the
doctors did not know what the cause of
the fibro was
and so that's why the person wasn't
getting better and that's why the person
spent
thousands of dollars the whole reason
for medical medium information is why
i explode like the medical media book
one exploded when it did in 2014 15
2015.
whole reason why we got here is because
there were answers for conditions and
then when you take a supplement
for the answer you move forward
and that's what happens with medical
media information that's why it's so
important so
um so let's go into here a little bit
more of all this
let's see
you know this is interesting here
supplementation while cleansing it's an
important question
like do i take supplements while
cleansing okay
do i take supplements while cleansing
it's an important question
how do we integrate supplements with the
cleanse
we'll get a few keys let me give you a
few key steps and reasons let's start
with that right there say you're
somebody doing the 369
and you want to still take your
supplements so say you still want to
take your lemon balm right here
so it's you know like that your lemon
balm or say you still want to take your
b12 or something like that i'm just
saying so i'm going to show you some
supplements in a little while too
um just know that when you're cleansing
you're lowering your fats
when you're when you're doing medical
medium cleanses okay because you're
bringing your fats down
when you bring your fats down your blood
your blood
doesn't have to deal with all that fat
that's in the bloodstream
and any supplement you ever take in your
life doesn't matter what it is or
whatever it is if there's anything good
in that supplement like a nutrient of
some kind
no matter what supplement it is whether
it's a vitamin or an herb or a nutrient
of some kind
anything you're taking can only do as
good
if it enters the cells so it actually
enters
our cells and so the reason one of the
reasons why in the cleanse is too i mean
the fats get lowered
is because when you lower the fats you
can get more nutrients into cells
as well so that means that you won't
have to do
higher dosages on supplementation
when you're doing cleanses because you
got the glucose in there
the glucose attaches itself the glucose
of your bloodstream
attaches itself to nutrients keep that
in mind
so the glucose you know in your
bloodstream okay
attaches to nutrients and drives it into
cells
always keep that in mind so when you're
doing a
three six nine cleanse minor weeding
cleanse you're doing you know heavy
metal
detox smooth cleanse the medical medium
heavy metal detox cleanse
morning cleanse your supplements are
going to be more effective
more powerful and then when you use a
high quality supplement like at
medicalmedia.com i have the directory
there
and i have all the different supplement
companies i like i'm friends with so
many of the
the supplement companies that are good
because i like to know these people
to some degree so that they don't like
you know
put something terrible in something and
all of a sudden whatever but i don't own
any of the companies on there
the point is is that is that and i'm not
sponsored by them
but the point is with the supplements is
that you don't have well you could
cleanse and you can hold supplements off
if you want why cleansing there's
nothing wrong with that and if you want
to take your supplements
while cleansing they're going to be more
potent so you can bring the dosages down
too that's an important question i get
asked all the time and
the reason why you can bring your
dosages down because you're taking fats
out of your diet during those cleanses
and so that means all those nutrients go
right into cells much easier much faster
that's no one knows this information
this is medical medium information
this is why medical media books medical
medium cleanses and medical medium books
and protocols get people better than
most because when they take the right
supplements
for the right problem when they find out
what the cause is
and they actually also do the cleanse to
lower down the fats
what happens is all those powerful
nutrients go into cells
and they start coming out of their
diseases conditions and symptoms and
problems and all this other stuff
and if they go to their doctor and they
bring the information they get even
extra help and all they get all this
extra help so
it's important to note that's one thing
i want to cover right there so
i'm going to go into supplements to
avoid while cleansing so let's head in
there right now
so let's go into there and supplements
to avoid while cleansing
if you're on supplements that are not
medical medium recommended
that's when we can get in trouble so
let's talk about that a little bit
so i'm going to cleanse the heel right
here i'm reading excerpts out of here
we're talking about supplementation
if you just got on here i'm going to cut
open an aloe leaf and talk about how i
eat the aloe in a couple of minutes
we're going to cover that and we'll talk
about some different supplements and so
forth so reading out of cleanse to heal
so supplements to avoid while cleansing
you guys if you are on supplements that
are not medical medium recommended that
means medicalmedium.com
on my directory you know for instance
like you're on whey protein powder
then you can be held back with your
healing really important to know
probably one of the most important
questions out there because you'll see
out there like what about collagen
what about whey protein powder what
about something else
and what about nutritional yeast because
people use that as a supplementation
nutritional yeast will hold somebody
back from healing when they're really
sick
um because you know because of msg and
so when
when we run into this stuff this is
where it gets kind of dicey
because a lot of people are on
supplementation that feeds
pathogens without them knowing it whey
protein powder will feed
an epstein bar a shingles virus a herpes
simplex one
cold sores okay people think cold sores
are no big deal they just they're on
their lip for a minute and then they go
away and that's it no they they're
actually
actually a lot of neurotoxins are
produced by them it gives people a lot
of issues you can even get trigeminal
neuralgia
like peeking up a little even though
shingles is the number one thing for
trigeminal neuralgia but um and if
you've heard nutritional yeast isn't
good for you it originated here
no one thought nutritional yeast was bad
for you no one thought that was bad for
the msg the glutamic
acid that's naturally occurring in it
it's not even just that's just one
reason why it's not good there's a bunch
of reasons medical medium information
only
but um but this is how it works you guys
i just want to cover this
one second if medical medium information
says
nutritional yeast is bad and it's the
first place that says it right
it gets out there and it gets all around
and then
someone hears it out there and they'll
be like oh well wait a minute
i heard it out there so no anthony
doesn't know anything when it originated
here it's unbelievable
this is how it works it's not ego it's
just or anything like that
what it is is okay well don't you want
to know where all the information is so
someone can heal it's about getting
people help so they have a way back to
all of it
oh heavy metals are bad in our system um
but why are they bad in your system
you'll find all the information here
of why it's bad information no one's
ever heard before and how it
oxidizes in your brain and spreads into
brain tissue nobody knew that ever
nobody not one place so i say this stuff
because
if you hear about toxic heavy metals out
there somewhere and
know where all the information is so you
can actually get them out of your system
which leads to the next thing
corella so here so corella's a terrible
supplement for people to take but still
even now you'll see like influencers on
social media like
taking my corella right now it's like oh
my god it's just how does this keep on
happening how do we get here where it
keeps on happening it's
so painful and so it's it's really tough
because
corella is toxic bottom line it's just
toxic
i'm just going to say it outright first
of all most of them end up with bacteria
in them
i've seen people doubled over vomiting
for days and days and days because of
corella
you can hit anybody at any time that's
one thing corella also doesn't remove
toxic heavy metals corella has toxic
heavy metals in it
like it goes on and on and on and on so
all these things are important to know
so if you're someone and you're like
doing fish oil it's another one you
can't get the mercury out of fish oil
you cannot get the mercury out of fish
oil i'm sorry you can't
you can do a centrifuge chelation you
can do anything you want
on fish oil your guys you're not going
to get the toxic heavy metal residue out
the methyl mercury because the more you
take it out
of an oil fish oil the more more
dangerous it gets because homeopathic
and a homeopathic reaction occurs
where you keep on diluting and diluting
you keep on trying to get that mercury
out and then that fish oil becomes more
toxic and then the methyl mercury it
goes to the brain it's it's it's
less it's less toxic to eat a can of
tuna fish
than do fish oil supplements and we know
how bad a can of tuna fish is
so i mean there we go so fish oil is
another example
it's like i'm not getting better on a
medical mean protocol but i'm on whey
protein powder collagen fish oil
uh corella um protein powders
with msg in them glandular supplements
bovine supplements whatever i mean it's
it's it's the list goes on
it's like and that person's not doing
medical medium protocols it's just crazy
how it works so
um so the bottom line is one thing that
can hold people back
is supplementation not medical medium
recommended and there's a reason for it
i don't just pull this stuff
out of my hat okay or whatever
all right and it's like you know
there's a reason why these things don't
help people
and it's it's critical reasons so just
know this anyway if you just got on here
cleanse the heel 16.99 51 off amazon.com
the sale actually stopped the other day
and it went up to 20
and then it went back down to 16 as of
today it's like a miracle so
um take advantage of it or go to the
library get it for free
i don't have any control over the sale
of the book on any level amazon does all
that
that's just how it's done so let's go
into
let's go into some examples here i
talked about whey protein powder it'll
feed
pathogens it will feed pathogens i
talked about l-carnitine
also in the other medical medium books
that will feed
pathogens you can't get better while on
l-carnitine
you can't get better when you have a
real sickness a real issue
symptoms and conditions with whey
protein powder
you can't get better with these things
they feed bugs you can't get better with
natural flavorings and everything and
msg and everything you guys
this is critical and so like before i go
anywhere with supplements you got to
know this baseline
so important traces of mercury and fish
oil
mercury will feed pathogens that's why
people have the fibromyalgia the lyme
disease
the rheumatoid arthritis the hashimoto's
thyroiditis
psoriatic arthritis the sarcoidosis just
the list goes on
you know the vitiligo whatever i mean
all these different conditions
mercury will feed you know eczema
psoriasis
mercury will feed bugs keep bugs alive
not a good thing so fish oil is another
bomb right there
all on its own so i'm just covering a
few other things here too so
um it's a common mistake and prime
example of why it's best to hold off on
some supplements while you're doing
a medical medium recommended um
you know cleanse so if you're doing 369
if you're doing mono eating cleanse if
you're doing the morning cleanse if
you're doing
these powerful cleanses that are saving
lives every day out there
it's important to kind of hold off
supplements you're doing because chances
are
before you got the book and before you
started the cleanse
you got i'm just using some of these as
examples you got the corelli got the
fish oil you got the
you know you got the whatever and and
everything i was talking about there the
collagen the whey protein powder the
other protein powders have msg in it
that nobody knows
about you're going to be on something
and then you're going to go into the
cleanse and you're going to be on these
supplements that
aren't getting you better and then see
how it all works
so critical to read this chapter you
guys and cleanse the heel you've got to
have
by the way it's a it's a medical
textbook it's really heavy tremendous
amounts of information so we get it
don't be surprised when you can't
pick up the box so easily right off the
start when you're realizing how big the
book is
so let's go to let's go to where you
start right here um
let's here let's head here so if you're
dealing with
more than one symptom or condition at
the same time
pick the one that looms largest in your
life okay let's talk about that
critical okay if you're dealing with
more than one symptom you got three
symptoms four symptoms
dizziness fatigue anxiety depression
aches and pains floaters in the eyes
just
right list goes on um tingles and
numbness
uh pain in the neck pain in the jaw pain
in the back
uh swelling all these different things
okay
even weight weight gain weight issues
too much weight that you know you're
worried about
pick the symptom or the condition or a
condition that you were diagnosed with
pick the one that looms the most that's
the way to go
and when you pick that one and you head
back
into this book into all the symptoms and
conditions right
so when you head in here
okay you'll see i mean that's just
there's over 200 symptoms and conditions
in here and i just opened it up to every
pa
any pages methylation problems that's
one mononucleosis epstein-barr
mood swings irritability uh multiple
sclerosis
it just keeps on going on you know um
right here is neurological
symptoms cfs right here neurological
symptoms cfs
you'll see in here okay
so um and you'll see all the dosages
you'll see all the supplements in this
book so this book is
critical for for anyone to have when you
go in there you're like well wait a
minute my fatigue is really bad
my fatigue's the big problem that's what
i'm dealing with is my fatigue
i have anxiety i have some depression i
have some aches and pains but fatigue is
the most one that's looming over me
that's where i would go so i would go in
i would go in cfs right there
okay i would go in there and you'll see
all the different supplements and you'll
see all the different dosages in here
okay
so you'll see that and you start there
um to begin with so that's the first
important critical piece all right
so once you've found your symptom or
condition
here in the book if you're sensitive
you can try one supplement a day if
you're
sensitive you can try one supplement a
day you guys
if not you can put them all together
as your daily like regimen so you can
put them all together as your daily
regimen
or as a middle ground you can choose a
couple to start off with and then take
it from there
so that's the way to go you can easily
do that you can start with celery juice
that's one thing you can start with
celery juice that's an herb that's
herbal medicine
it's herbal medicine and so celery juice
is an herbal medicine you can start with
that herbal medicine
you guys just so you know that that's
what you can do
and that's a big deal and starting there
is just to start all on its own
if you're somebody sensitive work your
way up work your way up to 32 ounces of
it
that's what you can do and then well
okay
well another place you can go is b12
that's another place you go so
i'm gonna talk about like they're gonna
so anyone who goes in there
you're gonna see in here you're gonna
see a baseline you'll see b12
zinc vitamin c lemon balm okay
you'll see those four and you'll see a
list of most
important for somebody to start with
because you might be like well where do
i start
what's the most important supplement how
do i do this well let's go to anxiety
and anxiousness so i'm gonna head there
now so i'm in anxiety and anxiousness
right here
okay so
anxiety and anxiousness and you'll see
all the different supplements and
everything
and i marked on anxiety right here i
marked with a pen the number one
thing you can try for this which is b12
so if you have anxiety
you can try b12 as number one you know
my favorite b12 is the vimergy so it's
the vimergy v is in victor i
am as the mary ergy that's the vimerg
b12 it's adenosine cobalamin
methylcobalamin right
but it's the best and highest quality on
every level um
and that makes a difference because
crappy b12s don't really help i mean you
can try your best to try to get the best
that you can
and you might get help a little bit but
you know it's not easy out there i get
it but that's the one i would use that's
my favorite
so b12 and if b12 is showing high in
blood tests okay
doesn't mean you're getting enough b12
because b12 high in your blood means
that there's a methylation
issue so that means there's no reason to
stop taking b12 if you have it high in a
blood test
because methylation issues are are
what's happening when b12 does not
when the liver is stagnant and sluggish
and you have methylation lip
issues in the liver which most people
have then what will show up
is the b12 will float around in the
bloodstream and not enter into the
nervous system not enter into deep
places so when
when you get a blood test and it's
showing high on b12
it doesn't mean your nervous system is
high in b12 it doesn't mean your brain
is high in b12 it's just showing up in
bloodstream as high in b12
doesn't mean the methylation is working
properly to get it deep into the nervous
system
which takes time so what people do is
they'll make mistakes they'll stop b12
altogether because a test would say
it's high in b12 but they'll stop all
together or they were using the wrong
kind of b12
and that's another thing all on its own
so then they get cheated out of actually
healing anxiety
cheated out of healing um all kinds of
different neurological symptoms
ticks and spasms and aches and pains and
because you know
b12 is that critical for that so you got
to be cautious on that when it shows up
high the other thing is
science research doesn't know what kind
of b12 levels we're supposed to have
with all the pathogens
all the bugs all the toxins all the
stress we're under
science research doesn't govern all that
or factor all that in they don't factor
any of that in of what
level of b12 is whatever the right kind
of b12 or not
it's so many so many potholes it's
unbelievable
to the degree of potholes all
information that comes from medical
media and
all originates here i mean it just does
all this type of information
no one had any of this they don't it's
just it's just i have to say that
because
it's critical to to know where it comes
from so people can find their way
and if it didn't come from here i
wouldn't be saying it that's this
it is what it is um
so let's go into this a little bit so
okay
so where to start you have anxiety so
let's head in there
if someone has anxiety or anxiousness
okay
the best place to start when you look in
supplements supplements right here i got
i marked them
you'll see number one is b12 number two
is zinc
so let's see the zinc that i use as
example
um so i'm on page
491 for a second but we're really we're
i'm only showing this as an example on
page 491 where anxiety
and i'm just showing you that there's
there's there's
um but really 476 is where i am though
so i'm just gonna
show you guys if you go in page 476 and
cleanse the heel
it says where to start right here i got
all my little postage notes
i i got a new book and i'm because that
potions notes were on on the other book
they filled up the whole thing so i'm
just putting
i'm starting fresh so in here
it says celery juice is a good place to
start beyond that vitamin b12 i showed
you that guys
zinc is the next one to start right here
that's the vimergy zinc the one i love
it's the right kind of zinc it's a
liquid zinc sulfate but it's done right
which cry which is critical um
vitamin c is the third thing lemon bob's
the fourth thing so what i do is i'll
say hey
if i got an anxiety disorder and i can't
get rid of my anxiety and it's and i'm
struggling with it and i'm suffering
from it
um first thing i would do is start a
cleanse start when the cleanses and
medical medium cleanse the heal second
thing i would go i would read the
supplements chapter and i would go and
find anxiety in here this is what i
would do
and i would look and i would say well
since i read the chapter it said
start with just a few supplements if i
want i don't have to do the whole
protocol of everything
i can just start with a few supplements
and b12 is one of them
it says three dropper fulls twice
a day so for anxiety it says three
dropper fulls twice a day of b12 and you
go to your doctor
you go to your practitioner and you can
talk to them about that and that's what
you can do
so it's three dropper fulls twice a day
that's one dropper full right there
as an example and
if you're sensitive though i'm going to
read about that in a little bit if
you're sensitive
you can just do a few drops if you want
i mean you can just literally start with
a few drops one two three that's what
you can do
i mean if i was sensitive that's what i
would do and you can do just a few drops
um so the second thing i would go with
would be
zinc so that's the second thing right
there and i would do the same thing it
says
zinc one dropper full daily of zinc so
one dropper full daily of zinc
and everybody's zinc deficient we have
to understand that the soils are
zinc deficient our food is zinc
deficient organic food
organic produce and organic food is zinc
deficient
so that's just how it works and so what
happens is zinc
controls our immune system that's what
gives our immune system the power
to battle everything that's why zinc is
critical for what's going around now
but zinc is critical for all the viral
stuff all
of it the epstein bars the shingles
hhv-6s nobody talks about all these
things
critical for all of that so zinc is the
next one right you'll see that and this
is the vimergy zinc
v is in victor i am ergy it's it's a
liquid zinc sulfate but it's the right
way to do it in the right kind like i
said before
so we'll go into the third thing vitamin
c so that's the microc that i use right
here it's the vimergy microc
if you have a vitamin c you like it love
it and
and by all means try it and do that but
for
for anxiety you don't want one that
is that straight ascorbic acid no buffer
whatsoever because
that's going to be irritating with
anxiety if anything so
that's why it says micro c really
important on here it's the type of
buffered kind
so then we got the fourth is lemon balm
so i'm going to go into that for a
minute too you got the lemon balm
lemon balm is critical for anxiety it's
a great one right there i mean
and it'll stay for anxiety four dropper
fulls
four times a day now if you got really
mild anxiety
you can do a half a dropper full you can
do one dropper full
you can do two for a whole day you can
do
three tiny drops you can do lemon balm
tea
this is traditional medicinals it's my
favorite tea company so
they got that's a lemon balm that i
actually you know
i have lemon balm tea every single day i
like it because it's anti-viral
anti-bacterial i like to keep my immune
system strong
you know just in case you bump into
something or you're somewhere public
and you know pick up something so i love
the lemon bumps so
but if you're that's the whole great
thing is you look and you're like well
lemon balm
and they'll say four dropper holes twice
a day okay so that's
you know that's the lemon balm here but
you can do smaller dosages
if you if you're chemical sensitive if
you've got food sensitivities if you're
a really sensitive person
you've got so many options here you can
do one
supplement one day then the next day
do another one then the next day do
another one
and keep it just one at a time
or three tiny drops of one three tiny
drops of another and
you can do so much that's why there's
thousands of combinations
with the medical medium protocols that's
the whole point
but i walk you through when i answer
questions and i and i give you the
information in this book if you're
somebody that just got on
take advantage of the sale on this book
it's 16.99 on amazon.com if you want to
if you want to
in the us it it's 51 off but
go to the library for free if you want
to do that i mean if everybody goes to
the library i'm happy
i just want them to have the book it's
critical i just want you feeling better
it's about you getting better
that's what it's about um anyway so
i'm going to go to page 476 again and
here i am
i'm reading about this a little bit more
and if you're ready to move forward
beyond that
if your list if you have a symptom
condition that you find in back of the
book out of the 200 symptoms and
conditions
okay and you have a a symptom or a
condition back there
go to lysine i mean go to spirulina go
to curcumin go to cat's claw go to
lysine i'd give you
direction on the most important ones to
work with
if you're getting overwhelmed at the
amount of supplements in a list the
reason why there's more supplementation
in the list
some people have more difficult
pathogens they'll have a really stubborn
epstein bar
they'll have one of the over 60
varieties of epstein-barr or
two of them and they'll have two of them
in their liver one in their thyroid
and they'll and and they're really
struggling or they'll have shingles or
they'll have cytomegalovirus or they'll
have streptococcus causing
sibo or bloat or acne they'll have strep
causing
you know all those things or utis or
bladder infections or
urinary tract infections kidney
infections so i give you options to go
further and further and that's so
important
and that's how that's how you actually
get people better is you have the
choices and options
with the right information so they don't
have they don't just stop like oh i
tried medical medium protocol it didn't
work
what you tried you did 32 ounces of
celery juice twice a day
um you did the heavy metal detox cleanse
um
you you lowered your fat long enough um
you actually did supplementation in its
fullest extent if you wanted to
so and if you but like i said if you're
really sensitive you can do little drops
and i'm going to go to um
page 497 now
okay you can use this technique if
you're sensitive so i'm going to give
you a rundown on the technique if you're
sensitive
right and you can do little
drops small amounts so if i'm in if
you're truly chemical sensitive if you
have food sensitivities
you can use this food and chemical
sensitivity technique
if you feel you're sensitive you may be
somebody that's not chemical sensitive
you're not food sensitive but you're
sensitive you're just sensitive
and if you're sensitive and you can use
this technique
so you don't have to be under the guise
of food sensitivities or chemical
sensitivities to use this technique
so i'll show you this technique which is
really cool
everyone with chemical and food
sensitivities is different
and everyone with sensitivities is
different you're welcome to explore
any of the supplements in this chapter
the list here is simply a starting point
for some sensitive people okay the fresh
celery juice
that's one place you can start the raw
honey another place you can start is a
daily routine
for the other herbs and supplements in
this book take only one
supplement one day if you want take one
another day cycle that's one thing you
can do
you can do this on an eight day cycle
and i talk about it here really you need
to get the book and you need to read
that
so you can kind of like really digest
that because i'm i'm going to cover so
much ground here that
i can only spend so much time with each
powerful point um
so and okay here's a question i always
get all the time you guys can you
put supplements in a smoothie yes
but you don't have to here's what i like
to do okay
i like to do this first of all um with
vimergy supplements
because that's what i take myself
personally i i don't put it in my
smoothie i don't put
supplements really in my smoothie like
all like little tinctures all the herbs
and all that i don't normally do that
all right
so what i like to do is um
i like to get a little shot glass a
small little glass put an ounce of water
in it
that's what i like to do personally and
i put all my tinctures in there
and then i just send it down and i chase
it down with a little water if you don't
like the taste
that's what i like to do okay so um but
people like to put it all in their
smoothie but i don't like to put all the
different tinctures and all
all the subs in the smoothie because i
want my smoothie to taste more like food
and not herbal supplements
um so that that's what i personally
choose so you gotta dip you know a
couple different options and all that to
what you want to do
um and
so so that's just
this is a quick answer for that that
question and
but but also i i also take them straight
so i take all the liquid straight so
that's what i do too a lot of times like
i'll be
a little bit too lazy i'm i got too much
going on or i got so much on my plate
i'll just instead of getting a shot
glass and putting an ounce of water in
it
or small glass you know because you know
whatever and put put water in it
i just would do them straight to boom
boom boom take them straight then drink
right off you know glass of water
whatever send it on down too
so um that's what i that's what you can
do
when you see the term daily this is
interesting
that means to take the given dosage of
the supplements over the course of the
day you can take it
over the course of the day okay um
and and it's your choice on how you want
to do that so when you say when you see
daily you can
it means that to take the given dosages
of the supplement over the course of the
day
it's your choice on how to do that
you're welcome to take the whole dose
once a day when you see that whole
section back here and cleanse the heel
all right
if you're sensitive you may want to
break it up into multiple servings for
example if it says to take
two teaspoons of barley grass juice
powder daily
you may decide either to put both
teaspoons together in a smoothie
those work good in a smoothie by the way
because the heavy metal detox movie has
the
the uh barley grass juice powder that's
the bimrgy it has the spirulina
the incredible spirulina it's the best
carolina there's
the emergencies barely is best in the
world i put the wild blueberry powder in
there
you guys have seen that i did that the
other day that medical medium heavy
metal detox smoothie
and it'll say for example it takes two
you know it says two teaspoons of barley
grass juice powder daily
you may decide either to put both
teaspoons together in a smoothie
or have one teaspoon in the morning
smoothie and one teaspoon in your water
at night if you really wanted to i mean
you can do it in so many different ways
when you see the term twice a day that
means
two installments taking it taken at any
time of day
as long as they're at least four hours
apart
if you miss one of those installments on
any given day
try to start fresh the next day so
that's just a little something right
there to cover too
i want to talk about um children's
dosages in a minute
and all of that quality is critical
and i want to read that right now
first of all actually singles for a
reason it has something to do with
quality too
this is important someone cleans the
heal if you just got here
the book's on sale 16.99 51
off amazon.com in the us take advantage
of the sale
because if the sale was gone and then it
came back because they
control it at amazon i couldn't believe
it's back it's a medical textbook
and take advantage of it or go to the
library go to library and get it out for
free
i mean that's what i would do i'd be
like i'm heading to the library
and just going to grab the book for you
grab it out for free um
that's an option so singles for a reason
right here you'll notice that almost
every one of these items you come across
in the urban
supplement section you get ready guys
like in the
in this right here in the supplement
section of dosages
and conditions right here it's canker
sores
uh chemical and food sensitivities
cataracts
um uh bloating brain fog
when you're in here anxiety autoimmune
diseases and disorders when you're in
here
okay addiction adrenal problems
alzheimer's
um acne when you're in here
what you'll notice is that most of the
supplements recommended
are in single form individual single
form
and some of them might have a few things
in there
but most of them are in single form
you'll see spirulina
asparalina and that's how you
actually get better when you take a
powder form out there
that has 50 ingredients in there
30 ingredients in there 25 ingredients
in there
chances of getting better are slim to
none
because what happens is supplement
companies use a speck
of spirulina and a crappy one and they
throw it in there so you'll see
spirulina on the list
whoa alfalfa grass barley grass
spirulina
gorilla i mean what you mean you just
see whatever going down the list
collagen uh minerals trace minerals
amino acids um
and you're reading a whole list of these
things you can't get better on those
you can't that's what goes wrong so some
people like oh i did the medical medium
protocol i just i had lysine
they had a speck of lysine in a
amino acid formula that had 20 amino
acids
it's like throwing away money and not
getting better
and so you'll see that when you look in
here at lysine
i don't even know if i have a lysine
right here i do i have a vimergy lysine
right in front of me here
when you see lysine you're getting
enough lysine
and then you know why you're using
lysine because you're killing off
epstein-barr you're knocking back
epstein barr and when you knock down
epstein bar and shingles
often your tingles and numbness start to
get a little better off stir aches and
pains and your fatigue starts getting
better over time
and what happens is that supplement
companies
put 30 things in something 20 things in
something 15 things in something 10 or
more
and when you have 10 or more in all
these different supplements
they got fillers in the supplement then
you have a speck of dust of each thing
it's how they take advantage rip off and
scam
millions and millions and hundreds of
millions of people
it's the game see i talk to supplement
companies
i know the game i know all the crap
all the twists even the best vegan
company supplements starting out now
that think they're so great they'll have
like 15 things in there a little bit of
this a little bit of maca
a little bit of that little bit of this
and they're ripping you off and
just sending you down the river without
a paddle
and that's what they're doing so you
guys the reason why
it's singles in here it's advanced
information it's above the rest
a you know what's wrong b you know what
to take
c when you take natalie for a condition
because i'm looking at metal leaf right
here
um and what i'm looking at right now i'm
looking at nettle leaf
when you take nettle you're not taking a
speck of
nettle dust in something that has 20
ingredients
in a supplement form or 10 to 15 18
and you're taking you see nettle in
there you're not getting nettle
you're not going to get better from
nettle and it's a scam because
what they do is they get these
fulfillment centers and
all the companies they'll have a great
cool you know
a great cool earthy um label on the
bottle
you'll see an influencer some guy
influencer like yeah this is so
synergistic works with your body
of the highest ingredient source from
the amazon
they'll have all that but really it's
from a fulfillment center
that guy's just a bull crapper and you
have 15 different things in there plus
citric acid which is terrible
and all this other stuff this is
critical to healing
this is what matters this is how
everything like really
really this is how it happens here so
this is really important to know and
so you'll see singles in here by the way
if you just got on here cleanse the heel
take advantage of that so
you know there's so much to cover here
but take advantage of cleanse the heel
of being like
16.99 amazon but library go to the
library if you want
and because i can't cover it all here
the reason why i keep on showing the
book is what am i going to do
um you guys not have the book and then
not have all the information
i can only show so much each live i'm
trying to do as many as i can and do
three lives a week or six lives a week
really
um to get guilty library and get it for
free but it's critical to have the
information in the book i mean what am i
going to say
so the whole thing here with singles
for a reason is so critical
when you take the lemon balm by itself
or you drink the lemon balm tea
by itself in a potent form like
traditional medicinals
i do both personally i do both and
um when you do that it's not an herbal
mix
with a speck of dust and then and
literally you get ripped off
you look at your supplement that's what
that's what would happen all the people
i've seen over the years
thousands of dollars of supplements in
their cupboards all junk fillers
everything everything all packed and all
that in there
and and people not getting better with
all those different ingredients with
speck of dust and everything
so you can learn about supplements from
my directory medicalmedia.com if you
really want to know
but the point is is it's it's making
sure you don't get
cheated making sure you don't get
cheated it's critical to not get cheated
so
let's go into lyme disease because on
instagram too
i forgot i forgot that i didn't cover
lyme disease i want to just cover for a
couple seconds if you go into lyme
disease in here
um in uh cleanse the heel
just trying to find it right here
um do the owner of lyme disease i talk
about the true cause of lyme disease
which is critical to know you'll see
that here so if you go in here you'll
see lyme disease and you'll see a whole
section on the true cause and you can
read it
right there okay and
in lyme disease you'll see the
supplementation
right there okay you'll see the fresh
celery juice the reason why that's there
is because it's it's an herbal medicine
so it's not like why is celery juice
there you don't see other juices there
you don't see other juices there you
don't see a juice you don't see carrot
juice in there
that's not herbal medicine you don't see
and because medical medium information
is is the only place where we know
what celery juice does because it's a
herbal medicine so you'll see that there
say work up to 32 ounces
okay and then you go down the list
you'll see 5 mt at
5 5 mdhf you'll see the folate right
here
you'll see um um when you go down the
list you'll see the cat's claw in here
okay and you might be somebody with lyme
disease that's sensitive
to see the cat's that's the vimergy
cat's claw that's the best one
out there hands down cat's claws don't
work out there
and you'll see curcumin you'll see
glutathione you'll see lemon balm like i
was talking about there
now if you're sensitive if you're
sensitive you just do a tiny drop
use the technique i talked about use the
whole sensitive technique
you can take three tiny drops of cat's
claw
all right but you'll see the cat's claw
dosage is three dropper volts twice a
day
you don't have to go the three dropper
fulls twice a day
you can be three tiny drops of cat's
claw
a day and you can work your way up you
can
customize your protocol you can talk to
your doctor you can talk to your
practitioner
that's how incredible this is then
you'll see the licorice root
in in in lyme disease but why is that
there
why is that well first of all no one
used cat's glove for lyme disease until
medical medium information got out there
years ago
because cat's claw kills off viruses
that cause lyme disease and you'll read
about it
knowing the true cause of your condition
is how you recover
then knowing what to do and what to use
and how to do the cleanse there's the
tools so you can just
really get you there so then you'll see
the lysine because it's antiviral you'll
see the licorice root antiviral you see
the mullen leaf
and you go down here you'll see the raw
honey
that's another one you'll see the b12
for the nervous system
why b12 well nobody knew why medical
medium information taught people for the
central nervous system
b12 is for the central nervous system
because our central nervous systems get
beaten down by viruses and pathogens
from neurotoxins that's why we get the
chronic fatigue syndrome the rheumatoid
arthritis we get
the lyme disease we get all these
different conditions and we get the
brain fog all that are
we we get the colitis that's viral too
so
b12 is for nerves because of viruses
then you see the vitamin c right there
then you'll see the zinc
you'll see a working lyme disease
protocol
that doesn't exist anywhere else i don't
know how
more i can hold somebody's hand here you
can take this to your doctor and have
them work with you on everything in here
and maybe add to whatever they're doing
too
but the point is is that's what this
book
is designed for plus you could do you
can do cleanses and not even go into the
supplements
but you have opportunities and choices
to take it as far
as you want to go so let's talk about
children's dosages
i want to go into that a little bit
that's an important thing
so i'm in cold and flu and cleanse the
heel
supplements and dosages right there if
you don't have the book you might want
to have the book
um so
cold and flu and
in this section here have dosages so
it'll say
supplements for cold and flu for adults
now why is he talking about cold and flu
like who cares about cold and flu right
now right we're gonna care
we're gonna care because
there's gonna be another virus still
looming around
at the same time flu comes rolling in
and hammering in pretty rough because it
does
and so there's a lot to be concerned
about
children a lot to be concerned about
babies lots to be concerned about
adults too but that's why i put this in
here what spirit of compassion foresaw
was the virus hold the whole virus thing
spirit of compassion forced all that
i got 35 years of freaking out about
viruses
35 years of freaking out about viruses
to get people safe and get them
recovered with all their conditions and
symptoms including flu viruses or
any other manufactured virus that hit
some scene
okay whatever all of it and that's the
whole
thing medical media information is about
protecting people about protecting with
the viral
viral issues and all of that so when it
comes down to it
there's supplements for cold and flus
for adults but for
children which is critical because when
flu season comes and you got
you got the flu's pounding away in
december
and everything else and all that it's
critical
i want to talk about lyme disease back
to lyme disease for one question because
i saw something there
lyme is not bacterial just want to cover
that right there
and you'll you'll know first of all
medical medium information pushed lyme
disease out of the bacterial category
it's not even in that category anymore
so lyme disease the lyme labs they don't
want to lose their their
billionaire their their empires so the
lyme labs want to still say it's a
bacterial because they don't want to
lose their empires
lyme labs have been bankrolling
and they're not going to break that but
science research
took it out of the bacterial category
and they put it in the autoimmune
category that was because medical medium
books millions of medical media books
got around the world
and people stopped thinking that lyme
disease is bacterial anymore
so people actually know it's viral
because of the medical medium books if
you're new to that get the books and
learn
and so that's why i was talking about
that so anyway we'll go back to the cold
and flu supplements
so here it is supplements were cold and
flu
in children ages one to two
all right supplements for colds and flu
in children ages three to four with
dosages and protocols
dosages and protocols for instance
supplements
for cold and flu in children ages one to
two it'll say
elderberry syrup one teaspoon three
times a day
uh goldenseal four tiny drops
not dropper falls three times a day
you're saying the list goes on and on
and on
um and then um and
and then you got what supplements were
cold in flu in children from
ages five to eight years old supplements
for cold and flu in children
ages nine through twelve supplements for
colds and flus at ages 13 and up
so you'll see that's here okay which is
really uh
which really powerful information take
it to your pediatrician
when cold and flu comes or whatever or
or have your pediatrician have the book
too
so and you can take to your doctor
pediatrician
and um and ask them if it's okay for
your child to have those amounts and
these dosages
so that's something that's in here as
well which is really incredible
um but the bottom line is it's it's all
about
so many options and i walk you through
it
to empower you empowerment
is having an answer to why you're sick
that's number one
why am i sick because
leaky gut is not an answer because
leaky gut isn't even a real thing i know
that's like
hard for people to hear but if someone
had a leaky gut they would be in the
hospital with with the temperature of
dying of sepsis see
what happens is leaky gut isn't wall
people isn't white people say people
with diverticulitis
that almost have like a hole in their in
their colon going to the outside of
their bloodstream
they don't even they don't even suffer
from
like there's people that have
diverticulitis with holes in their colon
almost to the other side and they don't
have symptoms people have they could
diagnose a leaky gut
so you have to understand it doesn't
work that way if you even had a
puncture even the sl a passageway
you'd be like so sick it would be insane
so i want to go into um
so leaky gut is just a theory they have
no proof there's never been a peer
review study that actually
showed it happening it's not seeable
it's not visionable it's not
known it's it's not even no it's there's
no science research to back it up
alternatively
conventionally there's ammonia
permeability
so i talk about ammonia permeability
that's different that's when you have so
much stuff
rotting that's impacted in your
intestinal tract like rancid fats rancid
proteins on the linings of the
intestinal tract
and it's creating ammonia gas and that
ammonia gas will go through everything
it'll go through your bones it goes up
to your teeth and rot your teeth at
night
people are like well why am i losing
teeth well all that stuff's been
impacted in them for 30 years 20 years
15 years
and their teeth start going that's
ammonia permeability that's different
let's go into aloe a little bit
um and when teeth have problems it's not
from what you're doing that day or that
time period when teeth have problems
they develop teeth problems
that's from 10 years ago what were you
doing 10 years ago
what were you doing 15 years ago what
were you doing did you come into this
world mineral deficient
you know lemon water does not hurt teeth
um at all because people never did lemon
water but everybody's in a dentist chair
getting their teeth drilled
what did you do in your life in the past
was it deficiencies what kind of foods
were you eating 10 years ago because our
teeth problems don't develop in the
moment from what we're doing right now
our teeth problems develop from 10 years
ago five years ago from eight years ago
so and dentist chairs are filled with
with people that are eating animal
protein
so it's not about plant protein it's
it's filled with everybody and everybody
so it's really important to know that so
here's an aloe leaf right here
um i talk about i'll leave protocols in
cleanse to heal the symptoms and
conditions area
really important to know there's alola
leaf so what i like to do is i cut off
this end because it's extra bitter
i mean i still dig a spoon in there but
you know i cut off this end right here
so i mean personally i dig a spoon in
there and kind of dig
that out but it's really bitter because
it's right close to the plant because
when they pluck the aloe
they pluck it right off the plant and
this part right here is really bitter
that that's really bitter but so i cut
it off for you guys i figured it's the
best thing for you guys to
you know to do too um you can eat the
aloe
and you can eat it straight i eat it
straight okay even though i got the
medical medium recipes where you can put
it in a blender and blend it with water
and drink it down because that's that's
an amazing way to do it it's an
incredible way to do it
i've always talked about that for
decades but i like to eat it straight
it's quicker for me too you know and and
so what i do is i cut off a section
about so big
just showing you right here
i just cut off a section of the aloe
um don't add to food don't don't add
food in your blender with it or anything
else you can
you can you can put your aloe with what
you're eating and blend it up of course
you can you can do that i just like to
do it
alone because it's more potent as the
medicine it does it brings down the
acids
um it gets to the digestive tract on its
own by itself
which i really love it's an herb i like
like to take
by itself is what it is a wild food i
like to take by itself
it's a wild food i like to take by
itself and so
um what i do is what i just did now i
have it right here what i did just
i took a knife right here and i cut it
like this
trying to show you in a different way
here oh there you go
okay and i open it up like that then i
fillet it
i hope i'm not going too fast this
aloe in in um in supplementation
i hate i hate aloe in supplementation i
hate aloe and drinks
meaning not not like making your own
fresh
aloe vera water i hate aloe in bottles
with preservatives because they put
preservatives in it
it sits on the shelf in the health food
store hey i'm going to grab a bottle of
aloe if that's the only way you can do
it and that's the only thing you can get
you can try that but but i personally
like trying to get a hold of a leaf if
you can
that's my favorite thing to do and um
so i just laid it back like this i just
did this
just trying to show you guys i just
played it played it back like that
tripping everywhere right now so
um and then i flayed this piece right
here
i'm going to flay it again
so i just laid it again with the knife
i'm probably not doing a great job in
front of you guys
as always
what else do you expect right i'm always
uh messing something up on here
and then you i eat this i just put it in
my mouth and just gobble it down right
that's one side there just knocked it
off so here's the other side
and i just flay the other side like this
i play the skin back
try not to get it on the computer too
the camera there you go
i do that and i flay it
and that's the next piece i take both
off and i eat it just like that
so that's right there
and i'll eat it fresh once a day but
the whole thing is it's great for
digestive problems i like it for the
mono eating person
than in the model eating plan in here so
when you get cleansed of heal
um you'll see the mono eating diets in
here um it's mono-eating
cleanse and you can do that mono-eating
cleanse for a long time gastroparesis is
incredible for
other different symptoms with your
digestive tract all of it the mono
eating cleansing here
it's really great but what
what i like those are like the aloe vera
kind of mixed in there for people doing
mono-eating people with digestive
problems
people with gut problems and gut issues
i like having the aloe in there so it's
something right there to think about
and i mean overall i mean you guys
cleanse a heel
i mean check it out these are some of
the supplement information i can cover
today i'll do another one
there's so much really to cover um
the books on sale and go to
medicalmeme.com to the supplement
directory so you know
like what is safe what is something that
i would take
because that's the whole point and of
having that there
because what happens in what people do
is they end up just getting lost out
there and then
how do you get better when you're taking
the wrong zinc you don't how do you get
better when you're taking
crella when you're supposed to be taking
the right kind of spirulina how do you
get better
when you're doing too much nutritional
yeast with all that msg you don't
nutritional yeast alone
can make or break somebody's healing it
can make or break them healing crossing
a finish line
and when you really think about so many
obstacles and so many problems that
could get in the way that's why these
books have
people who actually are able to read
these books focus
and actually just really take it
seriously and move forward with it or
take it to the doctor that really
cares about them and wants to help work
with them the people who move forward
they're the people who
who do um it's not just like oh i tried
celery juice for five days
and you ended up doing an hpp one on the
shelf of the of the
health food store that was like high pr
high
pressure pasteurization and doesn't work
and it wasn't even a fresh one and
you're like
next thing you know you go online you're
like sorry it just didn't work
it's like you know the whole bit i
answer i answer
questions and um but you guys are
incredible
um i'm reading some of the comments
right now
this is a new system i have set up so
i'm looking over to read the comments
jennifer said you're so great for us
thank you you're awesome
um what minnie says
what company do you get your supplements
from vimergy
that's where i buy them from uh
vimergy's v's and victor i
m e r g y that's that's the company
i use it's the best stuff ever
traditional medicinals is another one
for my teas
they're not my teas i buy them to drink
them
traditional medicinal's the best teas
okay good question
i like thorn that's thorin gaba
the camera's so weird on here that's
thorn gaba
i'm just saying sets thorin 5m thf
um once again vimergy vimergy has the
um amazing products they got the the
vegan
epa dha but the best one there is that's
vimorjee
vimergy has the spirulina incredible
stuff
all of it um yeah
so all of the whole thing is just
because i like
thorn doesn't mean i like all of their
products that's not it at all so
just know that i like their gaba and i
like their 5mthf
um i like their methylfolate but it
doesn't mean i like all their products
don't get confused at that
check my directory so you know because
my directory changes a lot at
medicalmedium.com
because if you go there you'll see that
you know i might like
one product from thorn or two products
but i don't like the rest of them
because of
all kinds of different pitfalls they
have in them it's the same thing with a
lot of products
vimergy i like all of their products
because they're like exceptionally above
board like vimergy that company right
there visa and victor i am ergy
they're exceptionally above board i like
every product they come out with
um they keep it so fair and so straight
and it's really unbelievable what
they've done
it's the quality and everything about it
you know here's the licorice from
vimergy right here
um but i like a few different companies
i like a bunch of companies but i only
like
certain things from some of these
companies because they blow it
in so many other ways with other
products they just blow it it's it's
it's incredible how it works
um alexandra says you're incredible
and soc thank you for everything you're
incredible too you rock
awesome um uh a you
are robinson says i do love energy i do
too
incredible company they're good people
they're incredible mom and pop company
they don't care about spending money on
the product
they'll spend money on the product when
other companies won't
venergy also gets every single product
individually tested for toxic heavy
metals other companies don't
because it costs too much money so you
have to understand what you're dealing
with when you're dealing with a really
good company
it's it's really amazing what happens
i love you too a you um
what can i do for it joseph says aw what
can i do for a hangover
uh try not to drink
try not to drink too much if you can is
it wine
is it hard liquor are you doing whiskey
are you doing tequila what are you doing
i mean
whatever i don't know too much about
liquor but are you doing rum
i don't know i probably sound like funny
about it because i don't really know
what drinks are out there
vodka and whatever you're doing or
whatever you're getting loaded on
be easy on your liver keep that in mind
but you don't need me lecturing you on
that you know about that you know about
that but i'm proud of you for asking
what to do over a hangover it's what
here's what you do
you when you beat yourself up by doing
something intense like that like hitting
your body hard with some alcohol
you want to do a lot of things to make
yourself stronger
yourself stronger you want to
do the vitamin c for your liver you want
to you want to drink the celery juice to
help restore yourself you want to
do the aloe vera you want to just do
everything you can
so that when you're knocking yourself
down with the with the alcohol overload
you want to be able to kind of you know
recover
but don't give that don't make it
permission to do more
um i'm just looking at some other things
how do i find the products you recommend
uh otta medicalmedium.com
check my supplement directory my
products directory okay
i'm not the owner of all those products
i'm not sponsored by those companies
check the check that out okay this isn't
an infomercial to sell supplements
it's not or it's not an infomercial to
get the book free at a library
it's not okay you could buy it also
amazon.com 16.99 51
off incredible really um
patty aw can i get these supplements
australia
vimergy yes you could get vimergy v as
in victor infector i-m-e-r-g-y
in australia definitely yes check the
vimergy website gotovimorgy.com
and check the vimergy website definitely
um
yeah australia
you know it's funny i mean i love
australia and
the australian like australian people
they they buy the medical medium books
out there they order them and get them i
hear i mean i've heard that like they're
they're they're out there i don't know
if they're in the libraries i don't know
how it works in australia if the medical
meeting books are in the libraries in
the u.s they're in the libraries
and i always tell people go in the
libraries and get it for free because
i'd rather have somebody do that
if they can but um but i know in
australia they're getting the books and
i just you know i hope that amazon is
running so i think they're running a
sale in australia right now
which would be great um
this because people in australia they
want what i notice is they care about
their health
like unbelievably and just it's
incredible and they want
answers oh my god
danielle said books are in libraries in
australia yeah
that tears me up books are in libraries
in australia so yeah
incredible that just really made my day
right there
it's like for real all right you guys
on that happy note the books are books
are in the libraries in australia
on that happy note i will probably let
you go for the night
um love you guys greatly thanks for
coming on tonight sorry i didn't answer
a lot of questions
um
amazing god i'm reading the comments you
guys
so all right heading off and
i hope you come to another life bless
your heart
and um just know that i care and i
believe in you guys and if you're
struggling
suffering with a symptom or condition
just know that i stand behind you stand
with you and
you know let's move forward together
i'm proud of everybody okay and know if
you've been through a lot just know that
my heart pours out to you
truly does okay god bless you and um
and be good and always pack yourself in
the back
okay have compassion for yourself and
know that you're a good person
no matter what no matter what you're a
good person
okay bye-bye