supplements that are bad for your brain
supplementation that's bad for the brain
so that's what we're talking about we're
in the brain saver books you guys I'm so
blown away right now because these books
are in your hands it's absolutely
incredible on all kinds of levels
the brain shot therapy so you guys doing
the brain shot therapies do you feel it
it's relief it's like
I'm just going to tell you right now
sometimes I mean they they just like hit
you like whoa like it's crazy you guys
I'm excited about this because I'm
talking about supplementation inside the
brain saver protocols book right here
now there's two books brainsaver brain
saver protocols 40 off which is utterly
insane these are massive books heavy
tons of information can't say enough
about them but 40 off amazon.com right
now take advantage of the sale for gifts
and for whatever holidays and everything
else I'm telling my friends that's what
you should do it's a really good chance
right now for that now I'm just reading
a little bit in here so this is really
an exciting moment for me because I'm in
a section
talking about supplementation that's bad
for the brain right so brain betrayer
supplements is what I call them they're
in the brain saver protocols cleanses
and healed uh and and recipes right so
here we go
these supplements fall into four main
categories so I'm going to take these
off right now
so these supplements fall into four main
categories let me read the categories to
you I'm so excited I'm going too fast
right here it's problematic and damaging
supplements that's the category we're
working in right now
problematic and damaging supplements so
that's the category then there's mildly
mildly problematic supplements it's
another category
and then overrated or overused
supplements another category and then
quality concerns supplements where it's
especially important to seek out high
quality forms because they're frequently
produced with low quality ingredients or
problematic additives such as
preservatives
so earlier today we were talking about a
few of them so I'm just going to list
out a few there's alkaline ionized or
water machines there's apple cider
vinegar products they're spent tonight
clay there's caffeine based supplements
there's charcoal there's chlorella
there's chlorine dioxide there's cod
liver oil shark liver oil there's
colostrum deer antler diatomaceous earth
does any of this ring a bell at all
digestive bitters essential oils taken
internally
fat burners fish oil and krill oil gut
powder Blends herbal tinctures and
alcohol hydrochloric acid HCL
supplements L-Carnitine L-Arginine
mineral oil mushroom coffee with
caffeine oyster supplements Pearl powder
sodium bicarbonate turpentine oil whey
protein powder zeolites does any of that
ring a bell at all you guys because
those are all problematic and damaging
supplements to the brain I'm going to
read a little on some of those right
there so I don't know if you guys have
taken those throughout your time or a
lot of people try everything they've
been there they've done that they've
tried so many different things so let's
hit it a little bit in some areas a
couple of areas where I didn't talk
about yet
let's hit zeolite I think that's a good
area right there so let's take it from
there okay
in recent years in edible varieties of
zeolites have been Unearthed and
manufactured in the same places as
edible zeolites so just digest that for
a second
just kind of grab on to that for a
moment
in recent years in edible varieties of
zeolites have been Unearthed and
manufactured in the same places as
edible zeolites just kind of grasp back
for a second very important causing
cross-contamination
so when you're doing zealots you can be
really understanding about how it works
and what's going on okay so I'm in the
brain saver books if you guys don't have
these you're missing out I don't even
know what to say greatest books of all
time hands down in health
you will see okay so let's keep on going
neither edible nor inedible zeolites
cross the blood-brain barrier so let's
just digest that for a second
if you hear zeolites cross a blood brain
Berry you're being scammed
there's no science or research that can
ever show that is the lights across the
blood-brain barrier it doesn't exist
so if you hear that so you hear all the
zeolite reps it's like oh crosses the
blood brain period oh really because it
doesn't
really important to know neither edible
nor inedible zeolites cross the
blood-brain barrier nor do they enter
the brain
zeolite cannot enter the brain another
complete misunderstanding in the scam
world of zeolites really important so
these are these are life-changing books
because you really become empowered
because you understand what's really
happening so you can protect yourself
and your brain
cross-contaminated zeolite varieties
stay in the intestinal tract and
irritate the lining
cross-contaminated zeolites which is all
of them
stay in the intestinal tract and
irritate the lining
causing dehydration and vagus nerve
sensitivities now we have to protect our
vagus nerves it's critical that we
understand our vagus nerves and protect
our vagus nerves coming out of a brain
stem our vagus nerves have a lot to do
with so many aspects of our internal
health here I've talked about that a lot
of times but the books are packed with
Vegas Urban for information loaded with
vagus nerves
and their information about them so
let's go a little bit further
so what happens is zeolites irritate the
intestinal lining
causing
nerve problem
your zeolite and you're literally
creating vagus nerve issues that means
anxiety that means all kinds of other
issues
ticks and spasms anxiety weird digestion
stuff stomach stuff gastroparesis
whatever a whole bunch of things that
medical medium information talks about
vagus nerve can be involved with okay
let's go a little bit further
edible zeolites which is do you like
products right edible zeolites even if
you have every assurance that they're
not cross-contaminated should not be
taken in high dosages or long term
because even edible zeolites they're
varieties of zeolites build up inside
the gut creating imbalances and
dehydration
which takes critical electrolytes and
water from the brain
it's even a really good feel like you're
taking a decent amount of it you're
stealing hydration from neurons and
brain tissue
large dosages of zeolite can create
Trace mineral imbalance because zeolites
don't have a discernment between get
ready for this oh my God
that's every line in this book is like
this
every line in these both these books is
exactly where it's mind-blown mind blown
it's one line after another check this
out
large dosages of zeolites can create a
trace mineral imbalance
get ready because zeolites don't have a
discernment between what's a toxic heavy
metal
get ready and what's a precious Trace
mineral the very thing we need in our
brain the very thing we need
neurotransmitter chemicals need
everything needs in the brain I talk
about it in the brain saver books
zeolite does not have a discernment
between trace minerals that are precious
for our brain in toxic heavy metals you
know what that means
when you take zeolites they they can
actually cage up
trace minerals and they do
zeolites do not travel into the
bloodstream so let's make this clear too
zeolites don't travel into the
bloodstream they stay in the intestinal
tract so it's another thing people just
get tricked by the holes of light talk
zeolites do not travel into the
bloodstream
and they do not bind onto toxic heavy
metals in the bloodstream critical to no
zeolites are not a reliable binder so I
love I love what I hear out there at
Albanian doesn't know anything about
binders what
I don't yeah you need to like oh you do
okay
keep on telling a whole bunch of people
that get them sicker chronically ill
just you know it's like you guys are one
big experiment out there
I've said that before the chronically
ill are just one big experiment for a
whole bunch of
not so smart people that tries to just
like do this do this it's like and then
the chronically ill who are really smart
they're just like they're just this one
big experiment
zeolites are not a reliable binder
zeolites only stay in the intestinal
tract just like clay it's just like clay
it stays in the intestinal tract it
doesn't go to your brain doesn't cross
the blood brain barrier and it doesn't
go into your bloodstream
as Elites sit inside the intestinal
tract they can interrupt trace minerals
from leaving the intestinal tract and
entering the liver so your trace
minerals that enter your body have to go
into your liver and brain with the
zeolite can stop that
so I think where people get confused
because at one point you recommended
them I understand why you do not now but
people
that haven't updated themselves on your
new information
well here's the thing and it's not even
just that
what it is is
there's a whole bunch of sharks the
sharks are on the outside of the medical
meeting communities medical meeting
communities
largest Health communities in the world
millions of people around the world
people that are not even on social media
or whatever and what happens is is it
became Feeding Frenzy have you noticed
the ads that you show up in all your in
all your feeds
those are hundreds of companies trying
to fish for medical medium people and
fish them out of the medical meaning
Community just so you understand it's a
dog eat dog world out there and it's all
about the money money money
and that you change so what happens is
that
they just the sharks
throw in everybody's feeds everybody all
your feeds all the stuff right and
they're fishing
and even if they never even saw that one
time there was this one zeolite and you
know small quantities one zeolite at one
time 10 15 years ago
that can act at least
as an absorbent through the intestinal
tract even if they didn't even see that
they're still hammering the zeolites
because the zeolite industry is still
going to take advantage of all the
health communities so they go into the
medical medium Health Community and they
fish and they fish and they fish
but all but you'll see that adds in your
feeds from everything from fishing into
like a fishing expedition to snag as
many people from the medical medium
communities they can snag and pull out
and draw out that's how it's done out
there
what is the name of the book He's
reading brain saver brain saver
protocols
so what happened though the zeolite
industry grew and then the
cross-contamination occurred which I've
been talking about for a very long time
so I've been talking about the cross can
contamination which is the mix of the
zeolite powers
being
farmed together
harvested together out of the Earth
and then process together and that
didn't exist back years ago
but that exists now so yeah absolutely
very important to know no really good
question though and I talk about that
all the time about that and I really
appreciate that awesome
so let's go into something else so we're
in problematic for the brain
problematic and damaging supplements
now keep in mind it's a large list
so we got colostrum let's hit colostrum
how many of you guys have tried the
whole colostrum bandwagon right get on
the colostrum bandwagon
which for a lot of reasons is terrible
we know that right
colostrum is a dairy product that feeds
pathogens so here you are your
chronically ill you're sick and then
you're told try the colostrum that's
going to build up your immunity
meanwhile colostrum itself in a human
body feeds the reason why you're sick so
any kind of pathogenic stuff it's the
feed that pathogen that's in you so if
you're sick with the chronic fatigue
syndrome which is Epstein-Barr and
that's mm info by the way going all the
way back our ra that's mm info or
thyroid thyroiditis it's mm info if
you're sick with Epstein-Barr virus and
you do the classroom what's happening is
you're feeding the very virus that's
actually causing the problem so
colostrum is the very product that feeds
pathogens
wrangling says wow it's so cool all
replays uploaded in the newsletters yeah
you got to check out the medical meme
those newsletter sign up when you can
there's no pay wall sign up for
newsletter we try to give just free free
free free free free everything's free
um I don't want to break this up into
big courses and all that stuff and
charge and don't want endless fees
charging subscription fees and
everything else I just want it free
anyway so colostrum is the dairy product
that feeds pathogens such as viruses and
bacteria accelerating chronic illness
classified this is interesting though
what you'll learn in the medical healing
books when you have these in your hand
what you're going to learn these brain
saver books is you're going to learn a
lot about classified medical research in
science
classified medical research and science
use dairy products colostrum included as
fuel source to feed and raise pathogens
in Labs that's why we're sick now it's a
hundred years
little over a hundred years
of science raising pathogens in labs and
feeding dairy products to those
pathogens and then slowly releasing
those pathogens into the
public
as each decade went back by from the 19
teens to 1920s to 1930s to 1940s to
1950s to 1960s until we got to Woodstock
and then since Woodstock was blamed for
all the free sex and all the free love
and everybody was just having sex they
were saying they're saying that was the
spread of all the herpes simplex one but
really it was already put out there for
everybody long before my classified
medical research and science
let's go choose something else another
area we talked about deer antler today
we talked about a bunch of charcoal
charcoal my favorite
charcoal's my favorite you're taking
your charcoal supplements everybody's
saying oh I got charcoal I was
recommended to do charcoal right the
whole bit so let's hit charcoal for a
little bit
okay
charcoal take it internally so remember
that says charcoal taken internally
we're in problematic and damaging
supplements for the brain and body we're
in the brain saver books you guys have
to get the books when you get a chance
charcoal including activated charcoal
activated charcoal
suffocates intestinal linings
interesting
suffocates the intestinal tract lining
not allowing nutrients to absorb
assimilate or easily pass through the
intestinal Linings to the hepatic portal
vein so what this means is when you take
charcoal
right
I'm going to move this over you guys
just bear with me for a second I'm just
very excited about the brain saver books
I made a lot of sacrifices to put these
out here
still making sacrifices and I feel that
knowing it's in your hands and starting
to get in your hands is just a relief
it's like a relief I don't even know
what else to say
so when you take charcoal
charcoal
has a spread out Factor
okay
it tends to spread out and blow up so
when charcoal gets into the intestinal
tract
it covers every single aspect of your
intestinal lining
not just part of your intestinal
lighting
and when it covers every aspect of your
intestinal lining it's so tiny and so
Nano in its form charcoal activated
charcoal
then it blocks uptake
you actually lose the ability to uptake
nutrients easy from your food so if
you're having your salads and you're
having your fruit you're having your
meat you're having your whatever you're
having your fish your chicken whatever
it is that you eat or want to eat if you
think there's a nutrient in any of it
you're not going to get those nutrients
readily accessible not going to get them
at all easily because of charcoal the
nutrients are going to get blocked and
you're not going to have nutrient uptake
at full satisfaction
just keep on going with the charcoal
charcoal is one of my favorites it's not
my favorite as far as liking it it's my
favorite as far as how ridiculous it is
so the causes of nutritional
deficiencies suffocating good this sorry
this causes
nutritional deficiencies suffocating
good bacteria and microorganisms while
allowing bad bacteria and microorganisms
to thrive check this out
a question there brain saver is a true
Masterpiece many thanks for everything
you do for all of all of us incredible
thank you
listen I just want you guys to have the
answers I want you guys to be able to
empower yourselves I want you guys to be
able to protect yourselves that's all I
care about
if I cared about me me me me you'd see
the Anthony Williams Show on Main Street
mainstream TV I've been asked to do it a
ton of times where it'd be like a series
working on people blah blah blah I've
turned down the Anthony Williams Show a
dozen dozens and dozens of times because
I need to make sure you get what you
need I can't make this about being a
star
and I'm not a star okay so this causes
nutritional deficiencies suffocating
good bacteria and microorganisms while
allowing bad bacteria microorganisms to
thrive so here's how it works
when you suffocate
the intestinal lining with charcoal
you're actually killing off good
bacteria
bad bacteria can be suffocated and
Thrive even become even stronger that's
how it works with bad bacteria charcoal
does not remove toxic heavy metals and
that's one of the biggest screw-ups in
Alternative Health right there
is is the misinformation of charcoal
getting Metals out who says they've
never seeded there's not one single
paper that shows
charcoal removing toxic heavy metals it
doesn't exist
it never did
but for some reason it became like
what is it now like concrete
Granite Stone
charcoal does not remove toxins heavy
metals charcoal is not a binder for
toxic heavy metals it's not a binder for
toxic heavy metals either
charcoal is the opposite so it does the
opposite so check this out
charcoal can keep toxic heavy metals
from leaving the intestinal tract with
an explanation here
because the metals get buried under the
charcoal As It Coats the intestinal
tract lining what I love about SOC is
the explanation after explanation after
explanation the details details that are
just mind-blowing to me all the time as
I was doing the books I was sitting
there I was like okay well give me the
explanation
charcoal even activated charcoal stains
the walls of the intestinal tract and
takes weeks to completely eliminate so
here's how it works when you take a
charcoal supplement
it stains the lining of the intestinal
tract in that stain doesn't leave for
weeks
I mean can you imagine what someone with
crohn's colitis IBS any kind of
intestinal tract disorders any kind of
intestinal tract problems gastroparesis
whatever it's serious
I know I'm running through a lot of
symptoms quick
because I want to get to the good stuff
charcoal is toxic to the body because it
keeps toxins inside the body
it is helpful to brush your teeth with
an activated charcoal so here's how cool
so if you look at me and you say hey aw
maybe you got a thing against charcoal
maybe you just don't like the charcoal
companies or someone did you wrong and
this is your way to get them back that's
not true but watch this
I'm Pro charcoal and this very thing I'm
reading
charcoal supplements periodically okay
brushing your teeth with them if you
brush your teeth with an activated
charcoal periodically
just make sure you don't swallow
and instead spit out the charcoal then
rinse your mouth really good as good as
you can
so you can brush your teeth with
activated charcoal Spirit compassion has
told me that that's that's okay
so I have it in there because it's okay
so let's do another one too
let's hit
gut powder blends
so let's hit that one you guys I'm
breathing out of brain saver protocols
and I'm back
today and this is brain saver right here
they're 40 off amazon.com us I'm mind
blown because they discounted it so much
which is like Angelic to me because it's
cost way more to make these books
um there's a 20 book every
section so it's like 20 book easy a 20
hour book a 20 book a twenty dollar book
I mean these books are like three four
they should be three four five hundred
dollars if you take all the information
and everything and then you look at
other health books out there
this is like
a dozen other health books that are
whatever twenty dollars a piece or more
or whatever okay gut powder blends
abrasive scratchy combinations of
irritants that do not balance the
microbiome and do quite the opposite
scramble up the microbiome see so here's
how it works no one's going to take a
look in here no one's got a microscope
as you drop a gut powder blend
from your functional guy or from
somewhere online or some ad or something
or this is good for your microbiome
no one's going to know what's happening
when that gut power plant goes down in
here there's no way to know
No One's Gonna have a camera
No One's Gonna Do an endoscopy and have
actually a camera in here watching the
gut powder blend in your intestinal
tract and see what it even does to even
help microbiome or not
it's all guessing games out of trends
but what happens when you drop a gut
powder blend
you scramble up your microbiome you
don't help it it breaks the natural
rhythm of a microbiome and does the
opposite and scrambles it all up
this worsens intestinal tract conditions
for sensitive people especially when
dealing with nervous system issues such
as vagus nerves
and phrenic nerve inflammation resulting
in increased anxiety and digestive
stress ego you're going to the person
that you need to go see it's like oh
your microbiome's off here here's
another gut powder here's another
probiotic with it here's a probiotic
powder mix with all this other stuff
let's just keep on taking it down and
meanwhile you're somebody that's already
going to the doctor because you have
anxiety you have depression you have
weird feelings you have Panic you have
different kinds of sensation in your
intestinal tract you have all these
issues that are vagus nerve related and
you're seeing your practice sure because
now you're taking the gut powder blends
and it's just scratching the heck out of
your intestinal lining uh irritating
your vagus nerves
gut powder Blends can throw an
intestinal tract into spasm and I've
seen it happen before
creating cramping gastrointestinal pain
gastro gastritis bloating Health
practitioners will often mistake these
reactions for a healing or detox of some
sort so here's where things go wrong
so you're doing your good powder blends
you think you're fixing your microbiome
and you're doing all this good stuff and
now you get thrown into intestinal tract
spasm and then you call your
practitioner friend healer and they go
you must be detoxing
when you're in spasm because of a gut
powder blend
Health practitioners will often mistake
these reactions for a healing detox of
some sort so
we're talking about the brain saver
books have you tried the brain shot
therapy
and there are seven brainchild therapy
cleanses
there's meditations but there's also
other things too there's seven heavy
metal detox cleanses in here as well
okay this is a funny one chicken
cartilage I don't know if you know about
chicken cartilage but people are saying
well it's good for you there's chicken
cartilage supplements out there
a friend of mine was telling me they
were watching a YouTube and the person's
like well I got my chicken cartilage
supplement here I got my other thing
here
hey guys try my chicken cartilage
supplement
all right I have here offers nothing for
the body
chicken cartilage raises blood acids so
it's like here you go and you're looking
for help you want good stuff and you're
thinking oh this chicken cartilage is
good for me let me take this product
raises blood acids supporting chronic
acidosis in all body systems and that's
what we don't want is chronic acidosis
Catherine Elizabeth
says I got choked up when you said you
were waiting for the info on eating
disorders and you asked SOC you're
getting me choked up right now and you
asked SOC if he was there
and he answered that he was looking at
all the people with the disorder because
yeah because what happened was let me go
find that
I wanna I wanna look for that right now
see
and we're still going to talk about
chicken cartilage for a second
right
I'm gonna find that right now so just
bear with me
here we are
you guys the books are so big
you think I would know my way perfectly
around these books but I gotta tell you
I mean
the amount of information
okay here we are
okay many times
if you guys got a second many times
as I was sitting at my desk receiving
the information that you found here in
these pages
I would enter a sphere of light to take
me out of my personal world and
surroundings
so that I could hear Spirit of
compassion perfectly clearly
and see any Vision that Spirit provided
one day as I was sitting here waiting to
transcribe words from Spirit about
eating disorders
I asked where are you getting choked up
like right here
ask where are you
Spirit of compassion said I'm here
I'm just opening up the plane
to get a reading from over a billion
Eating Disorders on this planet
so I can provide the information that
reaches everyone with eating struggles
I want it to be comprehensive so
everyone's included
that gets me to Catherine Elizabeth
because
he
you know I I don't usually you know I
don't
it's the kind of thing that when you
hear it and you put it in writing to the
words exact words that come through
and you put it in writing you realize
how many people are suffering when I
think about it how many eating disorders
and we know Eating Disorders can be hell
hell on Earth eating disorders
can
cut people down like trees just it's
just terrible
eating disorder chapter is so
mind-blowing and comprehensive that when
you do read the eating disorder chapter
and brain save or just be prepared
because it's got so much information
and we're talking about the eating
disorder chapter but when you read the
eating disorder chapter just be prepared
to take the information in
like just be prepared because it's so
much there's so much information about
eating disorders you have to almost it's
not even just about reading between the
lines it's every single line
foreign
it's going to change how people look at
eating disorders and how the industries
and people deal with eating disorders so
this is going to change this book is
going to change the fabric of eating
disorders and how the industry views and
looks at eating disorders
yeah take a few years but it's going to
change
probably even rapidly
foreign
here too
Spirit of compassion sees The Human
Condition on this planet and then
provides a deep understanding of how it
came to be
why and what to do with the resources we
have here on this planet we only have so
many resources on this planet to help
heal us and spirit of compassion has to
weed through it all right weed through
all the resources that that aren't good
and the resources that our answers and
are good
we see you
we know what you're up against
that's from Spirit of compassion in me
so I wrote that here the spirit of
compassion said you tell them that we
see you and that's what he said to me
and I remember sitting in my office
chair the one I burned a hole in the
seat cushion was just basically torn the
shreds
he said to me
right we see you
and I I said why he said say we see you
we know what you're up against you tell
them Spirit of compassion said to me
that that we know what you're up against
and then he said to me say this and I
said okay I'll write this he said write
this
and we don't want you to go through it a
moment longer
Holly's help said Eating Disorders were
so hard for me I struggled so bad
healing with your info thank you
eternally thank you for being here
my life's worth is my life's work is
when choked up my life's work is to
deliver this information to you
so that you can be elevated above the
Sea of confusion you see a confusion is
when you get sick
and you don't know why you have that
tingles numbness burning skin aches
pains confusion eating disorder pain in
the back of the head pain in the jaw
blurry vision brain fog confusion ticks
and spasms Tremors weakness fatigue
nodules cysts whatever it is
it's so that
you can be elevated above the Sea of
confusion and noise and rhetoric
of today's Health fads and trends
in order to regain your health and
navigate life on your own terms
[Music]
so I'm back in the supplements section
for a little bit here you guys
meaning this is a different Pro this is
you know the supplement section meaning
problematic and Mild mildly problematic
supplements to our brain and bodies
we're talking about charcoal then we're
going in the chicken cartilage
I didn't finish chicken cartilage these
acids forced the body to really to
release calcium storage to neutralize
the acid while depleting bones
can cause kidney stones and gallbladder
stones so
chicken cartilage supplements to a lot
and not good we can we can go into so
many things in here that are true let's
do sodium bicarbonate how many times
have you seen sodium bicarbonate sodium
bicarbonate
Lorraine L says I didn't feel seen or
understood before so reading that and
hearing that
let's talk about the sodium bicarbonate
I've watched a lot of people get
themselves in trouble over the years
with the sodium bicarbonate
the one thing you're going to get from
me
if if you want to know a little
something about medical media
is that consistency
when sodium bicarbonate blew up on the
scene I wasn't on the bandwagon I wasn't
saying you got to do all the sodium
bicarbonate
when charcoal blew up on the scene I
wasn't saying you got to do charcoal
here make sure you take your charcoal
when products blew up on the scene along
the way I didn't hop on that bandwagon
bandwagon when
anything like that happened there's
always consistency mm info's always been
mm info original Source going back and
then people withdraw from it out there
people in health would take from it
and kind of poach little pieces along
the way
but you'll find consistency and it won't
contradict itself
it's not like each podcast doctor writes
one book about something and three late
years later oops sorry for leading you
guys all down that road because I'm
writing another book that's going this
direction
so everybody's just one big experiment
great
oyster supplements I'm noticing oyster
supplements are big out there and
happening on the scene right
bottom dwellers such as oysters contain
mercury dioxins
strontium uranium
petrochemicals and other toxic heavy
metals not a good source of zinc that's
another thing get your zinc from oysters
oysters.zinc no they don't
they got the tiny bit the tiniest bit
you'd have to eat a barrel of oysters to
get zinc from oysters a barrel you'd
have to be doing oysters every night for
dinner to get zinc for moistures
I just love how this stuff happens it's
like oh no oysters are zinc you get your
zinc from oysters you do no you don't
you just get a tiny bit of zinc for
moisture so small in my meat you would
have to eat a lot of oysters and you
have to eat oysters so many oysters it
would be ridiculous you'd have to suck
down a dozen oysters twice a day
and that won't even do it
while oysters do contain some zinc
zinc gets diminished and depleted from
toxins zinc is the toxin
equalizer so what happens is when you've
got dioxins and mercury and an oyster it
cancels out the zinc automatically
the toxins
okay so while oysters do contain some
zinc zinc gets diminished and depleted
from toxins the toxins in oysters cancel
out the zinc that oysters provide
consuming oysters oyster supplements
because that's big right now is always
oyster supplements or oyster extracts
it's big right there I'm not making any
friends again
the kick me sign is on my back ready
who knows what I'm gonna get
soon tonight whatever tomorrow will kind
of BS comes my way
the toxins in oysters cancel out the
zinc that oysters provide consuming
oysters oyster supplements or oyster
extracts
does not restore zinc levels and clear
up zinc deficiencies you will never be
able to clear up a zinc deficiency
eating oysters
if your life depended on it
we can go on and on and on the books are
packed
and we I mean there's so much
information in here chlorophyll let's
just do a little chlorophyll for a sec
chlorophyll is big people call it the
green water
I'm taking my green water he's even see
it on social media you see when you see
YouTubers the problems might say like
YouTubers are like got my green water
here and then I got my other thing here
and hey you guys I'm making my avocado
toast and I'm taking my supplementation
my fish oil my green water my you know
my charcoal I'm taking my Pearl powder
oh my God
man when you get sick someday and you're
doing all that it's not going to be fun
climbing out of it okay
so we'll do the chlorophyll for a couple
of seconds all right because that's a
big one
get ready for this the body does not
utilize chlorophyll that's been
processed and singled out from its
original Source because the chlorophyll
is missing key components that are
intertwined when chlorophyll is part of
a complete Whole Food chlorophyll has to
be part of a complete Whole Food
chlorophyll cannot be isolated or
separated
it loses the rest of its constituents it
loses the rest of its chemical compounds
to actually make it work inside the body
anybody doing chlorophyll in a tincture
bottle or a liquid bottle that you buy
in the store is not getting anything
from it
I saw someone say Atlantic dolls is high
in Arsenic uh try again it's not
unbelievable
are you talking about Pacific dolls the
great garbage patch
because you might be talking about the
specific dolls
which
for decades now
we all know you ain't supposed to eat
you're not talking about Atlantic
dolls which doesn't have that but the
great garbage patch all the way over
there
anything's possible
and that's misinformation once again to
scare someone and you know what that
that actually happens because people out
there in the health movements the gurus
out there get so angry that they're
constantly hearing about medical media
and medical meeting info and medical
medium books and dolls and wild
blueberries they're so sick of it
that they'll just come up with anything
the adults is bad for you because of
this oh don't do that because of this
it's actually a sick world out there
when you think about it I can't tell you
how many people don't want people who
are sick to heal they have they would
rather have people suffer that on their
hands and knees
then ever heal
they don't care because they have so
much hatred in their heart
so much hatred in their evil little
heart
that don't let people just stay sick and
they'll spread terrible information
because there's there's they're mentally
sick with Darkness
and so they want people who are
chronically ill to stay safe that's the
kind of world we're on
we're in a world where there's good and
evil I'm sorry but it's true and someone
told me the other day that there's
people that don't believe there's any
evil that it's all just about your frame
of mind Dimension it's all about love
and everything else and it's not are you
kidding me
there's so much evil on this planet you
guys know you can
there's so much right and there's good
on this planet too but it's still the
battle still a spiritual battle good and
evil it's still happening it's here
all right so let's go into this a little
bit I think I was going to talk about
chlorophyll and I was I'm at your
service you guys
separating chlorophyll is a processing
method stripping other phytochemical
compounds that make chlorophyll usable
and potent when it enters the body as
part of a whole food the processing part
of chlorophyll stops it from even
working
chlorophyll cannot be isolated and still
serve a purpose so when you take
chlorophyll supplements it can't serve a
purpose it's throwing away money it's
throwing away Everything Medical mediums
book
um for 29 these massive volumes here is
way too much money I'm gonna buy a
seventy dollar bottle of chlorophyll
instead because this Guru over here in
this other platform says you should be
on chlorophyll
chlorophyll can only be utilized if
still in its natural source with other
phytochemical compounds and nutrients
it's becoming a trend to add a few drops
of chlorophyll to your water to turn it
green have you had your green water
as if you were adding food coloring
as a healing and beneficial alternative
add some drops of parsley juice or
barley grass juice powder to your water
anyway there's so much information in
here you guys it's packed I just want to
give you a reminder here how to clean
your books too so I want to show you
this really quick so I put a little
water on the tan towel they come greasy
from Amazon's conveyor belts plus other
Warehouse conveyor belts it's not from
it's not from the publisher these came
pristine they were these were minted
pristine and beautiful and clean and
then what happened is they got shipped
beautiful clean and pristine to like
Amazon so forth Amazon they take the
book and they throw it on the conveyor
belt conveyor belt is loaded with grease
there's grease fittings on the conveyor
belt and they grease them every other
day with the machine so the conveyor
belt just has all these metal rings
going down and the book goes travels
down the conveyor belt like this to be
processed for your order and then by the
time it gets to you it's grease here a
little grease here some brown stuff here
some Gunk here somebody working might
have been eating a little something or
drinking a little something got a little
something on there so what happens is
you take your towel with a little bit of
dish soap and some dampness damp cloth
and you clean your books off and they
come out so nice that's probably a
better thing instead of getting mad at
me and giving me a one star look out for
imposters
um some imposters just recently wanted
to ruin the medical medium book release
by by throwing a tremendous amount of
shade with misinformation there are
imposters out there right now
pretending to do some kind of
consultation or reading which I don't do
consultations consultations or readings
with
women
and taking them for a ride and taking
their money or taking their or with
breaking their trust or whatever they're
doing so there's imposters that are
actually trying to get people to say oh
aw is this bad person doing
consultations and taking advantage of
people their kindness and everything
else so and their money or whatever it
is so look out for imposters because
they're out and then that's making
people who have been hurt by the
imposters to spread against the stories
and posts
about how bad Anthony Williams is with
an S when it's Anthony William on top of
it or whatever so anyway I just want to
talk about the imposters as well sign up
for the medical media newsletter because
I got a whole bunch of Recaps and videos
and all kinds of cool stuff and emails
coming out and check out the recent
podcast at Apple podcast I just did
which is an incredible podcast because
it was so fun and so good
and if you can try to find a way to ask
Tick Tock to give me my platform back on
Tick Tock because they banned my Tick
Tock page because I showed my brain
saver books
which is kind of pretty funny there but
dog eat dog world
um
yeah so anyway good versus evil
it's what it is
okay so anyway you guys um I think oh if
you can
uh please leave a review on Amazon if
you like or Barnes and Nobles or Amazon
or whatever if you like the books
um leave a review for protocols and
brain saver for both of them if you like
the books
um
yeah so if you get a chance that would
be amazing 300 symptoms and conditions
the brain shot therapy cleanses the
brain shock Therapies
that's a whole other thing so if you
take a look at the books and I'll talk
about another day but the brain shock
therapies brain shot therapies as well
and
what else over a hundred recipes healing
recipes for the brain the list goes on
the information is vast I want to
prepare you each chapter is fully loaded
each section is fully loaded and if you
even get I dare you to get through these
books because if you even do you start
over from the beginning again because
you're there's so much to digest that
even me
as a mere human
like us all here
I
have to read these books myself again
now remember I'm a messenger I took the
information from Above This original
unique information I put them in the
books
and I had to learn it
all the same just like you guys have to
learn and I have to school myself
in reading them over and over again
if you can believe that
all right you guys
love you greatly
I would say get both
is what I would do
all right I'll see you guys tomorrow I'm
excited let's do some more reading let's
do some more fun
and have a good night please