out there about supplements and how it
works
so when we get a blood test it's just a
snapshot in time so we have to remember
that it's just a window in time that's
what it is it's like this one snapshot
and that's something to understand when
it comes down to blood work and stuff so
when someone says well
you know my b12 is fine in my blood test
then why are you sick
then why are you sick my blood test was
great my blood work is great doctor says
everything looks good then why are you
at the doctor's office
you know why are you sick why are you
breaking out with acne why do you have
severe depression why do you have skin
problems why do you have eczema why do
you have psoriasis why do you have some
other problem too so there's a lot of
confusion out there it's like no my
blood works fine looks good
you know everything looks good my
nutrients are good oh my b12 is great
yeah a year later
you got brain fog and you're at a
specialist
a year later you're getting an mri
two years later you're sick with
something else three years later you got
fatigue
four years later hairs falling out
fatigue skin problems more acne
depression everything else and that's
what we're up against it's so but your
blood work was fine
your blood test was great
your b12 was perfect
right
your b12 was perfect meanwhile
you're sick
it's like oh my blood works too my blood
work was great i'm great today three
years later you're sick
so let's talk about like how this works
to begin with and everything around it
so this is all important information
we're talking about supplements today a
little bit
specifically we're going to talk about
melatonin
that's a good one to talk about right
there
5mthf we're going to talk about that
cat's call i'm not sponsored by the way
cat's claw
we're going to talk about that a little
bit too maybe a little bit of
ashwagandha if we have time of course we
got the b12 here
and
i think liz had a question about
elderberry circle with 369 cleanses
right because there's honey in
elderberry in this elderberry syrup
which is incredible
because it's not it's not something else
that's in there it's not like it's not
like straight corn syrup or sugar or
anything like that so it's it's nothing
like that too and that's important to
know
so
when it so you can do the 369 with the
369 cleanse
okay
you can do the elderberry syrup with 369
cleanse that's that's not a problem it's
not a lot of honey to begin with and
it's okay
you're welcome liz
i mean if i was doing the 369 cleanse
right now and i want to take elderberry
syrup i would do it i'll take all the
berry syrup
all right so here we are so i want to go
back to the blood work a little bit
it's interesting how someone will say
that all checks out finding my blood
work my blood work was good my b12 was
good my calcium was good my other
nutrients were good and everything
but they're sick and they're dealing
with autoimmune they're dealing with all
kinds of other issues and everything so
what is it is it really good or not so i
just want to start out real quick with
the b12 for a couple of seconds when b12
is
high in your system so hey my b12 is
high i don't need b12
but if there's any kind of mental
illness mental health issues
if there's any kind of
autoimmune anything neurological on any
level nervous system brain and central
nervous system is if there's anything
like that anything brain
central nervous system
elevated b12
doesn't mean oh
that's it don't need to take b12 ever
again
that's not how it works a couple of
things happen a lot of people are on a
high fat diet when they're on a high fat
diet
the b12 suspends in their bloodstream so
if they get a blood test and the blood
test shows that their b12 is high
and they had fat the previous day
nuts seeds nut milks and which is fine
right chicken if someone wants to eat
chicken this isn't an anti-animal
protein anti-vegan whatever i'm just
talking about fats right
okay
cheese butter whatever which is not good
that's not good right so say they had
some kind of animal fat or say they had
some kind of plant fat or even avocado
the day before
it can suspend nutrients in the
bloodstream not allowing them to absorb
easy so when you get your blood test and
you're like oh my b12 is high i need to
stop my b12 meanwhile the fats in the
diet are suspending the nutrients in the
bloodstream so they don't enter into
cells
it's an important piece of information
so
um
yeah
we're here right now we're talking about
supplements
we're talking about the central nervous
system in the moment talking about b12
how it enters into the central nervous
system so this is this is critical
anybody with neurological lyme
that
gets
information about their blood work and
their b12 is high and i was telling a
doctor this the other day
the doctor said to me what do you
recommend anthony because i i give
information to doctors all the time i
say i recommend that your patient stays
on b12
because
they're having neurological symptoms
they got neurological lyme
they get all the symptoms associated
with it right
and even though their blood tests this
doctor was saying well their blood test
shows they got plenty of b12
but that doesn't mean the nervous system
has plenty of b12 your central nervous
system doesn't have enough b12 doesn't
mean your brain has enough b12
it's a snapshot in the bloodstream
most likely the b12 they're taking
is just suspended because of the fats
and oils and i said well what is your
neurological lyme patients on he said
well i got them on a keto diet
i'm like so you got them on a keto diet
so they're on a high fat diet so the
fats are suspending the nutrients in
their bloodstream and it's not even
getting to their central nervous system
so the details matter is what i'm saying
the details matter all about it right
so when someone's dealing with a
neurological symptom of any kind so what
is the neurological symptom
tightness of the chest anxiety
depression aches and pains tingles and
numbness ringing in the ears vertigo and
dizziness those are just some of them
restless leg syndrome creepy crawlies on
the skin sciatic nerve pain back pain
neck pain head pain migraines this is
all neurological ocd depersonalization
bipolar neurological adhd neurological
so
and that's just some of them you guys
that's some of the neurological symptoms
right there
so when it comes down to a central
nervous system issue like fatigue
severe fatigue or any kind of fatigue
that's neurological
we got to make sure that the b12 we get
we're getting enough b12 to the central
nervous system to the brain stem to the
brain to the vagus nerves
so
our vagus nerves require b12 it's what
keeps us alive
and so what happens is a lot of people
so let's go into like other problems
that happen so somebody be like well
i'm on a b12
and i'm like well what kind of b12
you're on so i'll tell the doctor well
the doctor be like the doctor i'll talk
to you will be like well i'm giving my
patients aw i'm giving my patients a b12
so can you get the b12 out
not sure sure i'll get the b12 out i
could can you send me a snapshot of that
b12 can you get it out and send a
snapshot of that b12
so the doctor will send
a photograph of the b12
okay
and then i'll look at it and then i'll
say can you take a snapshot on the back
with the ingredients
and in the back
it'll say everything there right
including some things that won't say
that are hidden that companies do all
the time vimrgy doesn't do that i'm not
sponsored but i'm just talking about the
b12 that i trust the most and
so i'll look in the back of the bottle
it'll be citric acid in there or you'll
see something crazy like a filler or
you'll see
all right you'll see a natural flavoring
in there
you'll see citric acid alcohol you'll
see alcohol in there
you'll see a hidden alcohol
you'll see all kinds of things in there
and i'll be like okay well and then you
won't see the right kind of b12 the
point i'm trying to say is all these
details matter to somebody healing to
somebody actually surviving and healing
and recovering
it's critical to have the right things
so that's one thing i wanted to talk
about the b12 thing another another
thing too people have reactions to b12
when it's all these bad b12s now
when someone had b12 shots i just got to
tell you guys when someone had b12 shots
they become sensitive to b12
so if they ever had a b12 shot in their
life they could become sensitive to b12
and that's when it's critical
to have the 5mthf right the methylfolate
so
because what happens is when someone had
b12 shots
a methylation problem occurs with the
b12
because they had it they had a shot of
b12 so when you have a shot of b12 the
body
starts to
start to identify it as not being a
positive thing
so then you have an allergic reaction
that happens where an antibody actually
gets built up it's that's really what
happens an antibody gets filled up
towards your b12 because if you had the
b12 shot when that happens you don't
methylate b12 and
so a lot of people have difficulties
methylating b12 one reason is because
their liver
is really dysfunctional another reason
is because they had the b12 shots
so when they had to when they had that
in their life and they end up taking b12
they feel like they might react
one of the reasons why the react is
they'll do the wrong b12 one with
alcohol citric acid and add things you
don't know about msg and all that so
they're reacting to the msg
there's no msg in this one this is the
vimergy b12 right v is in victor i m
ergy.com if you don't know the company
the point is is that they'll use a b12
somebody will use a b12 and have msg in
there and they'll react
that's one problem another two is they
had b12 shots before
if they had b12 shots before they get
sensitive to b12
so because they they end up having a
difficult
time
methylating their their liver has a
difficult time methylating so
that's why i like the 5mthf so
anybody who thinks they have a b12
problem whether they're using a bad b12
and that's one of the reasons why
they're having the problem and using one
that's not good
regardless it's good to take the
methylfolate so if someone thinks they
have a b12 issue it's good to take the
methylfolate at the same time if you
want or you can take it another time ask
your doctor it's right for you i'm just
telling you what i recommend the doctors
i talk to doctors about their patients
all the time
chris chris sage says vimergy b12 has
gotten me off mattress island
carissa
i i gotta tell you something right
all right and you're you're on facebook
okay
i can't tell you how many
people
i've seen stuck on mattress island with
neurological symptoms
their life is
limited the quality of life they've lost
they're on mattress island most of the
time in their life and the right kind of
b12
and the right dosage i've seen people
turn around in 10 days from being on
mattress island i've talked to doctors
who come to me and be like i got so many
people laying on mattress island what
you call mattress island aw i got so
many people on mattress island
and what do i need to do and i'm like
get b12 in every one of them while their
b12 is okay though aw
i checked their b12 their b12 seems to
be adequate enough in the blood work
why are they on mattress island
so get the b12 in them right the right
kind and then the doctor would be like
i'm seeing people rise up like from the
grave practically
10 days later 12 days later they're
rising up
they're able to function more they're
off a mattress island a little bit more
each day they're using their muscles a
little bit more now they're doing things
in their kitchen they're going they're
they're taking walks outside
these details matter
and that's what it's about the details
so that was a little bit about b12 we've
got more to talk about talking about the
central nervous system so here's the key
sugar
takes the nutrients
into our cells
right
insulin
insulin's job the hormone insulins job
is to take sugar
in your bloodstream
and bring it into the cells so you can
stay alive
because without sugar we die
you guys know that right without sugar
we die
if we don't have a sugar
that enters our cells
we die
our brain
has to have sugar
in 10
seconds without sugar passing 10 seconds
5 seconds 8 seconds 12 seconds our brain
starts to die
so glucose is critical this is how we
live right
it's important to know okay
why do you think a diabetic will go into
a diabetic coma
either something's wrong they don't have
the insulin or they're out of insulin
right or something's or they have
another malfunction right
the malfunction regardless is about
glucose getting to the brain the sugar
goes low to the brain
and that's why a diabetic will be on the
back of a bus or somewhere
or they'll be in a bus somewhere or
somewhere else and they're just going to
be there like this passed out and
they're seizuring
then their tongue's hanging out of their
mouth
and then you've got to put a little
orange juice in their mouth to just get
them out of it a little bit regardless
of where their insulin is i mean i've
seen that happen so many times right so
you have to get sugar to the brain
so nutrients nutrients enter our cells
through
sugars is what they do
a lot of people are so jacked up on high
fat diets
that they're throwing
they're they're they're not
like they're not getting the nutrients
where they need to be so the b12 is one
of them
now i recommend i was telling a doctor
the other day i still recommend even if
somebody's on a high fat diet to make
sure they get the right supplements in
because they can sneak some in some will
mean they'll sneak some of those
nutrients into their cells it'll get
there
but for maximum healing you take
somebody on mattress island with
neurological problems that are suffering
you lower their fats and you get the
right b12 in them
and
you got a chance now
every day i i think about it like how
does anybody stand a chance of healing
with the misinformation out there for
one
how many people are derailed
from getting the right information so
they don't even stand a chance to heal
they'll never stand a chance to heal
yeah you heard it from me they will
never heal
there's people out there that will never
heal because
the the information
it's derailed before it even gets to
them or they just don't learn it or
there's so much misinformation out there
they don't understand b12 or how it
works they don't know about the right
things they'll never heal
they'll go to doctor doctor specialist
especially should crown round around
forever and they will never get their
life back and that's sad
that happens all the time
so
you know someone said the other day i
think that they actually said the other
day in the comments section right like
oh there he goes with supplements again
okay well okay
okay
it's better
to know why you're sick and how to heal
and supplements are a critical way of
doing that
or do you want to just keep on going
around okay let me
buy a 50 000 oxygen hyperbaric oxygen
chamber which don't work they don't work
they've been around forever
and people pouring into my office for
years i tried everything
they purchased auction you know chambers
all of it it's cute it's a great idea
but no
it doesn't work
you know um go to another doctor and
keep on pumping ozone therapy inside of
you over and over and over again
which i don't recommend
you know
keep on going around okay let's go cold
punching now let's see if that can fix
it all right let's go try a rife machine
let's see if that will fix this how many
times those things just ended up in
people's closets it's
and
that crap gets expensive
real expensive and it still doesn't fix
things and that's what i mean over and
over again oh grab an alkaline ionizer
water machine and poison yourself it
doesn't work
let's get a 5 000 alkaline ionizer water
machine let's do that
right
and
people don't realize
you know it's their simple
strong basic details
of how to get people out of the muck and
out of the darkness and into the light
of healing there's ways to do it
and using the right supplementation is a
critical way to do it it's part of it
sabine said
on facebook vimrgy b12 is great it works
good i had a blood test after six months
supplementing i recovered from a lot of
problems with the heart right there
anthony you are the right you are right
with everything
you were telling back in 2020
i hope all listen good to what you and
spirit and compassion have to say i
recovered from diabetes type 2 sluggish
liver heavy metal poisoning hashimoto's
and epstein-barr
is asleep again god bless you really
sabine i'm so proud of you
i truly am
so we'll go into some more more about
the supplements a little bit
so cat's claw i want to talk about cat's
cloth for a little bit so
check this out you guys
years ago
years ago at different times in my life
when i had an office and people all
around the world came to see me
recommended by their doctors okay
right so let's just go back to any time
frame i've been doing this which is
decades since the 1990s people would
come to my office
right after seeing specialists after
specialist after specialist not have a
clue to why they were sick with their
neurological symptoms and sickness and
fatigue and everything right
and i would have all these herbs on my
shelf
all these herbs
and spirit of compassion would say they
need cat's claw
right
so i'd go and get the glass jar off the
shelf
like this
i would start up some tea
right there in my office
get some hot water going i'd get the
cat's claw out and the cat's claw would
be a dried cat's claw
sitting in a glass
jar
i would take the cat's claw out
and i would put it in the hot water and
steep it right in front of the person
and be like what's that okay it's cat's
claw
and then
have them sip it
right there
and i
i
and it wasn't the best cat's claw
it was survival
cat's claw
it helped
it was amazing
that i had some
no one knew about it
and when i think about where we are
today when like the cat's claw that's in
my hands right now
if i had this back then
i could have speeded up so many people's
healing processes
yeah it helped him when i took the cat's
claw out of the glass jar and i made
them a cat's claw tee right there in my
office whether it's 1994 or 1997 or 1999
at different times in different people
when spirit of compassion said this
would be really good for them and it was
beneficial
and their doctor would call me up their
doctor would come to my office the
doctor would sit there
and even as far as back as the 80s
right
and so the point is
that if i had something like this at my
ready
at their ready
i could have gotten so many more people
faster
and you know because it took more time
to use the dry cat's claw the best stuff
i could find at the time back all the
way decades ago
and
i didn't have the option so what i what
i realized in the supplement world is
there's so much crap out there and
there's so much
just junk and misinformation
and i think about it you know that
people they don't even know they just
take things for granted they don't even
know
like what what kind of blessings we have
that we're so lucky to have here if i
was suffering from neurological lyme
myself personally if i had all these
this fatigue and aches and pains and i
had tingles and numbness and i was
suffering and i had inflammation
throughout my body and i had
neurological symptoms because of the
epstein-barr virus because that's behind
that's actually behind neurological
lines shingles doesn't help either and
say i had all these viral issues
right
and i had something at the ready at this
my at my disposal like this and a
quality like this
i mean it's just a miracle is what i'm
trying to say
and that's that's the kind of thing that
counts that's the cat's claw right there
so with cat's claw
and i tell doctors all the time
is your patient on cat's claw
and they'll be like well well i don't
know there was a cat's call capsule that
i could always try to get them on or
something like that
be like
that's not that's not the answer
i want to hear your patience on cat's
claw
if you want to get your patients better
you know when it comes down to the
neurological line neurological symptoms
you don't even have to have a lyme tag
it's autoimmune
just autoimmune
right
and then it matters about the right kind
of cat's claw someone will have a cat's
claw it'll just have alcohol in it it'll
be ripped to shreds inside the nutrients
it can constitute all the nutrients
would be literally
damaged from the alcohol
and so you'll have all these issues
with the different cats claws out there
or dehydrated
capsulated
cat's claw it just doesn't work right
and the low potency and the low ratio
and the low low quality all of it
combined with the fillers and everything
else
basically what happens when we have
something at our disposal and
let me make something clear right here
right now
medical meeting information and tools is
as basic as just celery juice
and see how your problems go away
they're not going away and they're
sticking and you're only getting some
things better you stay with your celery
and then we move forward
and then it's now the heavy metal detox
smoothie i'm cleaning things up but if
you're somebody that's got
a lot of bugs and see you've got the
shingles and the cmv and you got the ebv
and you got the hh v6 and you're sick
and you got the streptococcus causing
all kinds of acne and crazy stuff and
utis with it all if you're sick
it may not just be celery juice being
enough for you
i've never been one to jump in heavy in
anything in the sense where you got to
do all these supplements and this is
what you got to do no start with celery
juice is fine
but just don't complain that you're not
getting better and you've tried mmm and
you did it all when you didn't and you
just did some celery juice because
there's so many more places you can go
so many more directions you can go into
customizing so it's like
you can start as at the beginning with
celery juice but you know the cat's
claws here if you're really struggling
let's see hannah says i take cat's claw
among other ones you have here they are
really moving the needle for me my fibro
has reduced immensely so what happens
with
lexi what happens with fibro is you're
dealing with the epstein-barr virus
right
i talk about that and i teach that to
doctors all the time see i've seen bar
virus creating fibromyalgia that's
original medical medium information now
science is talking about that now
and that's medical medium signs versus
that stuff out there so science is now
talking about hey epstein bars you know
creates fibromyalgia now
cat's claw
synapsing bar killer
epstein bar creates neurological lyme fc
bar creates multiple sclerosis
and just so you know all those articles
you see out there now about epstein-barr
creating ms i published it seven years
before
seven years before it was published okay
about the cause of multiple sclerosis
and taught years before that by me and
lectures
and and teaching doctors and so forth
about the cause of ms but the point is
with any symptoms you may be somebody
that's like i don't have ms aw i don't
have
neurological lyme a doctor says you know
i might have autoimmune
yeah
you got the autoimmune or you've got
your symptoms whatever symptoms those
are
so cat's cause one of those things where
i've always seen this as a miracle
i i saw it as a miracle going back years
ago in my office when i would take the
dried cat's claw out and make the person
a tea right there
and they would sit there and they'd be
sipping this cat's claw or they'd be
sitting there with their doctor and
they're both sipping the cat's claw
and
if i knew because you know everybody's
at their own free will the world has its
own free will
if i knew years and years later
that we'd have a cat's claw
at the ready in our hand
that's better than anything i've used
all these years i just i'd be blown away
and i am blown away
definitely now we have stronger bugs
today too than we did years before and
that's a problem we're up against we've
got stronger bugs we've got stronger
ebv's we got stronger shingles we got
more toxic heavy metals we cut more
chemicals we're up against all the time
so we're up against more than we ever
were up against before so what that
means is oh my blood tests just fine
with my b12 i don't need any b12
the doctor said my blood test is fine
the world has changed
did you know that the level that they
actually depict as being fine
the window of where the b12 needs to be
on the blood test is from the 1920s
did you know that the 1920s
so everybody's walking around now with
all kinds of different elevated al
epstein bars they got the herpes simplex
one and two they get cytomegalovirus
they got hpv they got hiv they got
aids
they're walking around with all this
stuff
toxic heavy metals lots of chemicals and
we're using the b12 level
that was a theory as being the right b12
level
in 1920. so what you see on your blood
work
is 1920s depiction of a group of doctors
in in the science world in 1920
that
believe that was where the b12 level
should be at and that's what we we rely
on we rely on something from 1920 from
guesswork to where your b12 needs to be
on blood on the blood test
not to what we're up against today in
the world we're up against fighting what
we're fighting against
trying to heal people on mattress island
everybody falling ill we know how
everybody's falling ill now and getting
there and so with all that in the flues
too that we're up against now and
everything else that we keep on getting
hit with
that we're going to then go by the
gold standard of 1920 from some
guesswork that that's where your b12
level is supposed to be at and if you do
go by that fine
but is it even getting into the cells
it's another thing too so anyways going
back to the 5mthf right
so that's the methylfolate right there
it helps with the methylation so
the incredible thing about like the
vimergy products like the vimergy b12 it
needs less of the
methylation that's what's amazing right
there right it needs less
of methylation other b12s that won't
even get into cells there's so many
b-12s out of there that won't even budge
into cells right the vimergy b12 is the
right blend of adenosine cobalamin and
methylcobalamin and then when you and
that alone
actually beats out methylation issues
but then if you're somebody that had all
these b12 shots and all these issues
you might want to ask your doctor hey
can i take the methyl methylfolate right
and this is the stuff that i recommend
friends and family people who come to me
doctors that talk to me about stuff like
that so let's move on to something else
so i'm just talking about a couple of
these things right there let's talk
about melatonin
right here
so on youtube
okay venislav says
i healed from a tough ear infection
after three months on medical medium
protocols and lifestyles lifestyle thank
you aw and soc this this is life saving
amazing honor to have you here truly and
i'm glad you're doing better and feeling
so much better so i'm talking about
melatonin right now
melatonin is really interesting okay
because first of all
it's an antioxidant and that's what it
is but an antioxidant that goes to the
brain
which is why i like melatonin right
so one of the things about melatonin
i'll show your brain right here
one of the things i like is it slows
down angiogenesis
right so it slows down
blood vessels growing from growths blood
vessels growing from tumors and cysts
and growths and stuff like that okay so
i really really love melatonin for that
reason alone but for mental health
conditions i love melatonin greatly
because it is an antioxidant
that has a different access to the brain
and brain stem so antioxidants all
antioxidants have a different pathway
into our body
an antioxidant from one source
a polyphenol anthocyanin from one source
will enter
the body in a different way organs in
the body and glands in a different way
than some other antioxidant source will
do when it comes down to a hormone
antioxidant like
melatonin
a brain hormone antioxidant it's easy
access through blood brain barrier it's
easy access and that's what i love about
it okay
audrey's antler says but doesn't
melatonin mess up your hormones it does
not has nothing to do with estrogen has
nothing to do
with anything of that sore has nothing
to do with testosterone
has nothing to do with epinephrine has
nothing to do with adrenal hormones has
nothing to do with thyroid hormones or
any of the sort or any of that there is
no
science
that has showcased that it does
okay that was an attack a while back on
melatonin because melatonin is very
helpful for a word i can't say on here
so
because melatonin is helpful for a word
that
sounds like answer
[Music]
because melatonin
is helpful for answer
it it has been attacked and some of the
sabotage has been things like that oh
it'll mess up your hormones which it
doesn't oh it'll do this which it
doesn't
because it's good for answer
you know answering the phone
it's good for answering the phone it's
good for answering questions it's good
for answer
all right
so the melatonin so that's the best
melatonin out there i take like six or
eight capsules a night do your doctor
says
do your doctor tells you you know
whatever i'm just saying that for me
personally i'll do six or eight capsules
every single night
last night i took a handful of capsules
that's what i did last night last night
right before bed that's what i did okay
and so
and it's not messing up my hormones
okay so last night i just did that
that's what i did i'll just show you on
the camera
i just did i didn't even count them
didn't count them didn't say 5 milligram
10 milligram 20 25 milligram 20 whatever
i just just poured them into my hand
like this last night like that
and i sent them down
i didn't count how many i didn't count
whatever that's what i did
you're somebody that
is interested in melatonin ask your
doctor what's right for you
don't do what i'm doing
do what's right for you
so anyway
mv doom said
geez that's a lot
caroline says l-m-a-o-o-o-o-o-o-o
that's a serious lmao
all right anyway you guys
so i'll talk about melatonin a little
bit more right
anxiety depression
ocd depersonalization bipolar
schizophrenia
right deep sadness so no one knows why
they're sad okay the feeling of being
lost a feeling of being kind of out of
it
a feeling of being like disconnected
like you need to be someplace else
a feeling of having anxiousness anxiety
all that with it
a feeling i feel like that you got meant
like memory loss like a feeling of like
am i losing my memory or sensation like
am i losing my memory
anything like that or if you have memory
issues adhd right autism all of it
sylvia says if you're healthy why would
you take that many melatonin because i
do something i don't recommend anybody
else to do
is
i am making a special surprise
an
announcement
i'm hoping
the beginning of this week coming up
and i'm excited so i got to surprise you
guys beginning this week but anyway
the point is is the reason why like why
would i take this much if i don't have a
health problem because i burn the candle
at four ends i work 20 hour days i work
22 hour days
i work 18 hour days 19 hour days i work
seven days a week i haven't taken a
vacation in decades
so
that's what i do
i work for god i work for the
chronically ill
i don't work for myself
i work for god and i work for the
chronically ill and when you do that
you don't put yourself first
so i don't do self-care i want everybody
else to do self-care i want you guys to
be into self-care i want you to take
care of yourselves it's critical okay
but
what i do is something different
so
i push
the pedal to the metal
i step on the gas
and i drive fast in life
not literally in a car because driving
fast is bad in a car don't do it
the bottom line is so what i like to do
is i like to protect myself because
if anybody actually looked at my
schedule and looked at my life and saw
in my personal life how hard i work and
how many years and how and what i do
they would be scared for my life
and so what i do because spirit
compassion says take care of yourself
make sure you're getting that
antioxidant in your brain make sure your
your b12 is cranked up because of what
you do make sure you take care of
yourself
so that's what i do i try to take care
of myself where i can like the easiest
way i can so what brand of melatonin
roxanne says that's vimergy
it's v is in victor i m as in mary
e-r-g-y you'll see the label right there
vimorji
vimorji.com i'm not sponsored
right
and i don't own vimergy i'm not the
owner of the company it's just the best
stuff there is
hands down it's the best does it make a
difference when you have good stuff
it makes a difference
huge one it moves the needle and that's
the difference right there
so
talk about ashwagandha for a couple of
minutes i know that
we have a crisis right now with women in
in hair loss
um samantha half says are you paid by
vibrancy
i am not sponsored i don't have that
thing where you know people get
sponsored so they get what is it like
they get paid because they're sponsored
and all that stuff so no i'm not paid by
the energy so um
yeah i'm not the owner of energy i don't
i'm not a uh
you know a part owner of energy or
nothing so
i'm not an ambassador
so
i'm not an ambassador so i don't get
paid as an ambassador i'm not a whatever
whatever the people are with all that
they get sponsored their ambassadors and
all that stuff to everything no
it's just the most powerful stuff that
i've found that i like for my friends
and family i recommend the doctors and
of course i tell you guys about it all
the time
elsie said you should be paid that's
funny so this is the ashwagandha in my
hands right now
so i want to tell you about the
ashwagandha so there's a wave right now
okay of hair loss for women
massive wave of hair loss for women and
that's where we're heading into this
world we're heading into a world where
that's going to be more and more
obvious happening in people's lives
doctors are going to be hearing about it
all the time
so
what i love about
ashwagandha is ashwagandha does help the
adrenals and it helps
the adrenals restore
which is a big part of why women have
hair loss
so
so when it comes down to your adrenals
they get weak and there's dosages in the
book on that too like if you know if you
have a cleanse to heal here's a cleanse
the heel right here i show you the
dosages and all that and cleanse the
heel
so in this life right here with the
stress that women are under
and men too and men too but the stress
that women are under
right
like women's hair follicles depend on
how strong their adrenals are because
there's a hormone in their adrenal blend
that keeps the hair follicle healthy and
alive
so
when
and you don't even have to have fatigue
to have an adrenal problem you could be
missing one of the adrenal hormones
or be really low on it and then the hair
starts falling out so if you're
especially if you're up against stress
or any kind of
any kind of emotional
so what happens is with a lot of women
is they'll have a difficult relationship
difficult friendship they'll have
you know financial stress they'll have
a divorce they'll have
all kinds of other issues that happen in
their life and then a year later the
hair just starts pouring off their head
like it's just coming out in droves it's
in the shower it's on the shower floor
it's everywhere it's in their hands and
they brush it they just brush their hair
and it's just filled and filling the
brush and it's this
it's like what feels to be like a
tragedy as they're pulling out all the
hair out of their brush and they have
hair all over their sink and it becomes
this thing where that all of a sudden
becomes tremendous amounts of ptsd and
stress as hair is just going everywhere
and falling everywhere so
family member reached out to me that has
a best friend the best friend's just
losing all their hair and she's just
losing it's everywhere and like aw what
do i do it's like ashwagandha that's the
first thing make sure you've got enough
ashwagandha
and she was like well no i tried
ashwagandha she tried ashwagandha well
what kind
and she was doing these ashwagandha
capsules
and then she switched and she used this
ashwagandha and the hair started to slow
down
so it does make a difference when it's
the right stuff right
that's one another thing i said are you
on b12
like well there's b12 in my multivitamin
so what this family member's friend said
to me is there's b12 in their
multivitamin and that should be enough
and there's b12 in their hair skin and
nails vitamin and that should be enough
i said it's not enough it's not enough
it's that much b12 and it's not even a
good quality one so the b12 in the
multivitamin is just only a smidgen it's
not even a good one
and it's just not enough
well what do you suggest a w
boom four dropper fulls of b12 a day two
dropper holes twice a day and you do
your ashwagandha
and then boom less hair was falling out
less hair was falling out and then it
stopped
and this person's hair was just falling
out for quite a while and they went to
all their functional medicine doctors
and they were trying this and they're on
hair skin nail formulas and they were
doing this and it wasn't enough
so anyway talking about ashwagandha for
the adrenals strengthening the adrenals
right
i take ashwagandha i take it every night
so what i do with ashwagandha
right
is do three dropper falls now with b12
you don't have to do it in your mouth
you can do it in water and have it in
shot glass i'm just letting you guys
know a lot of people are like well what
about the b12 just put it in your mouth
have it under your tongue you don't have
to it's a bunch of dropper folds right
there of ashwagandha
so
that's what i'll do at night
right
but i love that question why am i taking
anything if nothing's wrong with me
well
i think if someone and i had a doctor
tell me this a surgeon said that the
hours i work if they did those hours
they would literally need a sabbatical
a year off so what i like to do is i
like to keep the engine going so i use
all the good stuff to do it
i take all the good stuff away take away
the cleanses the the medical mean
cleanses that i like to do take away the
mono eating cleanse which i love to do
every now and then switch off and do
that take away
spirit of compassion's information
put me on
just whatever diet or keto diet or put
me on some just plant-based diet
or a keto diet animal protein take away
you know all all my access to all the
best stuff and supplements and yeah if
i'm doing 20 hours a day i could start
probably getting some problems
you know like adrenals can start getting
worn down and beat up central nervous
system needs fuel i mean you know so
it's all these things that are so
critical take away my celery juice and
yeah
i'm a human being and if you work 20
hours a day and you push
push
push it that hard you can actually get
yourself in trouble so i do my 32 ounces
of celery juice every single morning i
do my heavy metal detox smoothie because
we're always getting all kinds of
you know contamination with heavy metals
everywhere it's in the air it's
everywhere
you know if i stop doing my heavy metal
detox smoothie and my celery juice and i
stop doing the things that protect me
and the b12 that i take every day and
the propolis and the zinc
right
then yeah
there could be a problem that could
develop i'm a human being i'm not super
natural
human to superhuman or something you
know not a superhero
um
anna says anna says why does stomach get
upset when you take so many at one time
well i don't ever get an upset stomach
right
so i can take a whole bunch at once if
you're somebody you know you could be
somebody already
here's here's the thing too so be your
own detective
your stomach never gets upset ever
so only when you take a bunch of
supplements at once like it never gets
upset like you don't have a history like
ask yourself do i have a history of my
stomach getting upset when i
had popcorn and i ate this or i did this
do i get have i ever been to a doctor
about acid reflux have you ever been to
a doctor about my stomach being upset
like be your own detective and realize
that it's not the supplements
that make them upset
unless it's something like you took a
vitamin c that's straight ascorbic acid
which is like battery acid right so you
took a vitamin c i don't have the microc
right here in front of me but you took a
vitamin c that's like straight ascorbic
acid and you have a sensitive stomach
then yeah you're going to burn a hole in
your stomach from bad vitamin c's
there's vitamin c's in those packets you
know those little packets everybody goes
into the store they're like oh i'm going
to grab some of those vitamin c packets
right there that's straight battery acid
straight but i saw i actually saw a what
is a commercial on youtube for those
just recently or something like that
and i'm like oh great yeah
put 10 million dollars into advertising
advertising that battery acid in a
packet
right so you know
and if you got a sensitive stomach it's
things like that that can really
aggravate that stomach
but people that you know and you know
people have inflamed nerves in the
stomach so if they have inflamed nerves
in the stomach if they have
if someone has um
someone has a sensitive nervous system
nerves going to the stomach
if someone has
an ulcer and they don't know it right
they might have an ulcer and they
actually don't know it
okay
so
that means you're gonna be sensitive
with other things too so if you're
someone that never went to a doctor or
never complained about a stomach problem
ever and you're taking a bunch of
supplements and it's giving you a tummy
ache make sure they're the right kind
make sure they're high quality make sure
there's no alcohol in those supplements
make sure there's no
all the fillers and crazy fillers and
citric acid citric acid in a supplement
will just burn the burn the heck out of
the stomach lining
i mean the vimergy stuff's not like that
so i just want to make that clear so
that's not like that and if for some
reason you're somebody because you have
stomach problems then you take it slow
and you do a little bit at a time ask
your doctor what's right for you that's
what i would tell a family member
when someone's sensitive they could
think you know they can take less and
then have it with foods it's another
thing too like if someone's really
sensitive because they have sensitive
stomach issues and they want to take a
little bit of b12 or something you take
it with food and you take less
right
sherry joy green good to see you dr
sherry
so you guys this is some of the
information i want to talk about today
and
when it comes down to supplementation
there's so many bad versions out there
that they can create a scar in
somebody's life with supplements so then
someone is someone's taking so many bad
multivitamins and protein powders and
and you know bad hair skin and nail
supplements and bad herbal concoctions
that were with alcohol or herbal powders
that had all that clay in it and
they have these bad experiences and that
doesn't help right now you don't have to
take supplements to heal depending on
where you are like the medical medium
information is customizable like i said
you can start with celery juice i can't
tell you how many people in this world
are drinking celery juice right now and
they've gotten rid of their acid reflux
or whatever it is just from celery juice
angela says anthony please tell the
people if they can take them all
together or if they can space them out
do what's right
by you and your doctor but what i do is
i take them all together
just out of out of easiness for me right
so i'll take them all together okay you
can space them out if you want you can
take them all together you can do
anything you'd like to do just getting
them in is really important
stephanie crown says can you combine
drops of different things to take all at
the same time please or should be
separate help answer please i'm very ill
you know i tell doctors all the time
that their patients can put them all in
the same thing because a lot of people
are sick so what they'll do is they
don't have the energy to do it
differently so i just put some actual
god in there now i just put some b12 in
there you know do what your doctor tells
you to do i'm just showing you what i
would do personally or for my
friends or family right and then you add
water to this so there's some cat's claw
in there so i did some cat's claw i did
some b12 i did some ash reganda now i'm
going to go here
and do some licorice right so then i got
some licorice right here
and right or or if
i do some lemon balm right here
and here's some lemon balm
okay i'm gonna two dropper fulls of
lemon balm in here yeah and you could do
that and then you add a little bit of
water to it so let me go and add a
little bit of water
okay
and then i shoot that down and you can
chase it down with more water of course
you can
but that's what i do you know ask your
doctor if this is okay for you to do
right and see what he says or she says
joel says anthony i read in your book to
say i work for god
as an affirmation and it's helped me so
much
thank you thank you
well thank you for being here and i'm
honored that you're here
you guys i am going to
go on ig i'm going to put telegram on
i'm going to put tick tock back on we're
going to go to instagram and
we're going to talk about supplements
more and the whole bit i might talk
about another supplement i was going to
talk about olive leaf and i didn't get a
chance to talk about olive leaf on how
it's antiviral how it's antibacterial
how i love it for a lot of things so i
might talk about that then
anyway you guys i am heading over
and
thank you for being here today it's
incredible getting any time i can to
talk to you guys
april taft's asking about dr nesbit i'm
hoping he's doing good i haven't heard
from dr nesbit in a little while and
that scares me because he could be on a
drinking binge
and uh i know he said he had a tough
week of surgeries and sometimes he just
disappears and i hope he's not
slaying around with too much alcohol in
a system so i will check on dr nesbit
when i can i love you guys
and i am heading off to ig in a little
bit so i'll see you soon