about supplemental protocols medical
medium supplement protocols
this is an important live right here for
a lot of reasons because people
often get confused when it comes down to
supplementation when it comes down to
medical medium protocols
because there's so much information with
medical medium there's so much
leading information in the health world
that it's it is true
it's hard to keep track of it because
it's geared
so someone can go as far as they want to
heal
someone who's actually critically sick
or someone
who's not so sick who wants to improve
and heal and you know and get better
really quick right
so it's not just one
size fits all like all the other stuff
out there in the health field that's all
you know the stuff is just like oh take
some probiotics that will fix everything
it's like no it won't take some take
some of this that will fix everything
and you know and medical media protocol
is is
protocols are thousands of protocols
customizing it to yourself so you can
make it to the finish line
and there's something really special
about that you might be somebody that's
just hey you're doing celery juice
16 ounces on an empty stomach every
single day you're building up your hcl
you're cleaning up your liver you're
getting some
the critical electrolyte sodium
cholesterol mineral salts to your brain
right and then you might be somebody
that's
doing a whole bunch of different
supplementation dosages
knowing how to do supplement dosages
you're doing your celery juice you're
doing cleanses you might be somebody
who's doing the mono cleanse
or the 369 but
take comfort in something that there's
something in there for you
and where you are with your health and
what's happening with your health
and if and there's different levels of
conditions
here's one thing that confuses people a
lot you guys okay
somebody with bloating may just have a
little bit of bloating
maybe some mild acne and they do medical
medium protocol
and they get better and then they tell
somebody else what bloating
that all you needed is to do is just
this and then someone else
tries a little bit of that and they
don't get rid of their bloating
because they were more severe they were
more severe
so that someone else has to actually get
into the book
and learn how to use it in the protocol
so they can get their severe bloating
problem fixed we're going to talk about
bloating we're going to talk about
autoimmune we're going to talk about
neurological symptoms we're going to
talk about
eczema going to talk about brain fog
we're going to do that right here and
we're going to talk about protocols how
to take them including supplementation
i'm glad you guys are coming on we're
live on facebook live on youtube
live on tick tock live on clubhouse good
to see you guys
this is an important lie for anyone
that's seeking a way
out seeking a way out
there's the not so sick and then there's
the sick right
and they're not so sick they can afford
to play
reindeer games where's my reindeer ah
no reindeer they can afford to play the
reindeer games out there
they can they can dabble in this they
can dabble in that they're not so sick
it's okay you can play that game for a
while
right and then when you get that those
other
symptoms and you're really sick you're
fatigued you're bloating you've got the
gastroparesis
you've got the constipation you've got
the painful gut
you've got the the aches and pains
you've got the cranial nerve problems
that i always talk about
you got the cranial nerve problems you
got the severe adrenal
problems you're viral you got the
epstein-barr
you're getting different symptoms you're
going back and forth for do i have lyme
disease
do i have multiple sclerosis do i have
ra
hey where's what the doctor said i have
autoimmune
i'm showing i got autoimmune and
and i'm not well and i also got a
thyroid problem and i don't feel good
and i got anxiety that's creeping in
and all kinds of problems and there's a
difference there
there's a difference versus somebody
else it's like i got a little bit of
rosacea comes and goes i got a little
bit of rosacea
it comes and goes i break out with a
breakout once every
three months and i get a little tired if
i push myself too much
i got a little anxiousness that's a not
so sick person
right and then somebody that's like oh
my god i feel like i'm 100 years
old everything aches my joints are
cracking
don't feel good i got fatigue i got jaw
pain and the dentist says it's not my
tooth
oh and then i got this other problem my
neck pain back my neck pain
tightness in the chest and i got a lot
of
i got a cough that comes on at night i
just all of these things you're like
wait a minute
and so what do we do like what do we do
and well oftentimes
someone who's not so sick does medical
medium are like yeah
right cleaned up that acne boom cleaned
up that bloating boom all i needed was
16 ounces of celery juice
and heavy metal detox smoothie
and someone else is like i tried the
heavy metal detox smoothie
i was getting benefits but i need more
but they don't look and they don't find
it they don't
know where it's at they don't know where
that moor is at
you know and they don't know how to use
it so we're talking about this is more
of an
intimate little get-together here
and this intimate get-together is like
look i'm sitting here with you guys
all right for free for free
and i want to show you how to kind of
cut a little bit through this
chapter which is the supplements chapter
okay
and you'll see in this book right you'll
see something that says here
knowing the cause and the protocols
that's a huge that's a big deal
that's a big deal you guys i'm just
giving the 4-1-1 on that
because nowhere else in in the natural
medicine world unless you guys unless
you guys
tell me wrong when people are really
sick
they'll be uh they'll be at their tenth
neurologist
and they won't their neurologist won't
hand them this
this little note here the neurologist
won't say
we're going to give you knowing the
cause and the protocol
so you can recover they don't do that in
the neurologist's office
i know so this is really important right
there
so in here what you need to know about
supplements
is part of it very important stella
mono cleanse moves the needle for me
nice
and move the needle for you thank you so
much and i'm able to work out after
four years four years
weren't able to work out for four years
you see i understand that i know what
that is
right 35 years of people walking into my
office many of them being carried in
i know what that means not working out
you know
and and i i never took for granted any
time
ever was able to take a minute off and
do a run
you know run do do a jog
you know go running hop on a bicycle
never took it for granted because all
those years
i watched people crawl into my office
from all around the country and around
the world
and they came into that office and they
were just wounded soldiers
wounded soldiers working out
forget it they got it they were able if
they were able to take a shower
and not get exhausted after going the
bathroom
after going number two eliminating
after pooing and then and then getting
into a shower
that's it done for the day they were in
the bed done for the day
and then they'd get out of bed a couple
hours later after it just totally
exhausted them
and then they were just ready for a
doctor's appointment and that would that
would tank them
jessica was so sick liver failure in the
hospital january 1st 2021 i'm
completely healed my i've completely
healed my liver thanks to
mm i'm also completely cured of thyroid
disease
and off all meds i read the books
jessica you read the books
my god by the way congratulations
congratulations i'm so proud of you
guys are interested in the book if you
don't know the book cleanse the heel
51 off amazon.com
us or find it in other bookstores
uh it's everywhere target it's all over
the place
but um check it out if you can get at
the library if you need to get at the
library
so we're talking about bloating
neurological symptoms how to use the
protocols around that
we'll talk about autoimmune how to use
the protocols around that
even child liver child liver
what people don't realize is that people
who are sick
now had
what i call child liver when they were
a baby or a child yeah
when they were children they had a sick
liver
constipation bloating as a child
sick liver dark circles under the eyes
as a child
sick liver right
that even even other things too all
kinds of other things any kind of skin
rashing
skin issues dermatitis any kind of
eczema any kind of psoriasis for a child
sick liver child liver and so i want to
talk about that a little bit
so glad you came on ear infections too
sick liver infections as well
good to see you guys so here we are
we're live right now that's what we like
to be i'm going to show you guys a
couple things i'm gonna actually
if you guys hang in there i'm gonna
crack open an aloe leaf i'm gonna crack
open a melon
and some other things too so one thing i
love about cleansed heel and one thing i
love about medical medium information
is cold and flu information
and pandemic too so plague
because basically that's that's the flu
it's just
a different kind of engineered flu so
medical medium books or are for a lot of
that too and i'll go into the cold and
flu section which is important
so that's a great place place to go so
let's start
where to start when it comes down to
i'm going to find the page right now
julie says where does a sick child liver
come from is it genetic
no it's not genetic toxic heavy metals
are passed
in utero so that's one reason right
there low-grade viruses are passed in
utero
that's another reason right there and
then also a child can
get and pick up and contract strep also
get strep from the parents strap from
other sources
that's it that's a easy prime example of
how it's done
and other ways too those are just that's
just a couple of things
not to mention toxins lots of toxins
children get lots of toxins for lots of
reasons
so if you're dealing with more than one
symptom or condition at the same time
pick the one that looms largest in your
life did you guys
catch that right there if you're
suffering from more
than one symptom right with more than
one symptom
kelsey bach every time i see you uh
leave comments
on youtube you're like 47 symptoms i
healed so that's 47 symptoms
right many of you guys 20 symptoms 30
symptoms 50 symptoms
you know 10 symptoms right um
so what do you do when you have a lot of
symptoms
if you're dealing with more than one
symptom or condition if you got
ra and you got hashimoto's if you've got
eczema and hashimoto's
pick the one that looms larger in your
life largest right
if you've got fatigue is it a skin
condition
what is it anthony anything for enlarged
prostate i'll check the book and see if
we have anything in here
so you never know
it might be in here
might be under here it is reproductive
system section i know there's a prostate
something in here for sure i'll find it
in a little while but i know it's in
here
so for example if you're plagued by
fatigue focus on taking care of that
and don't worry about bloating if you're
plagued by fatigue
it's okay to just hold off the bloating
thing in the moment
that's all right and you focus on the
fatigue
chances are right over time you may find
that working on one
issue like the fatigue takes care of
another
takes care of another or you can switch
off after a while and focus
on a different supplement list for
another issue
once you've found your symptom or
condition here you don't need to take
every supplement listed
you don't have to take every supplement
listed
you can start with just the top four or
a couple of them
important to know if you're sensitive
you can try one supplement a day hey i'm
really sensitive
i'm super sensitive most likely because
you've had a lot of bad supplements
which
can cause problems but i'm super
sensitive so what do i do
well i can start with the b12 that's
what i can do
start with the b12 i'll just start with
that in the list
you might be super sensitive because
you're really toxic and really viral
you don't know it but you got a couple
of different a couple of different
epstein bars you've got
shingles virus sitting in there you've
got the fever blister virus the simplex
sitting in your body
your cranial nerves are hypersensitive
you've got vagus nerve issues you've got
trigeminal nerve issues you've got optic
nerve issues you've got the eye floaters
you have the ring in the ears you're
hypersensitive you got the tingles and
numbness maybe a little fatigue maybe
you got the brain fog
just really sensitive maybe your
digestive system sensitive
you feel everything that enters into it
right you guys
that's okay that's okay
because once you've found your symptom
or condition here you don't need to take
every supplement listed for it
if you're sensitive you can try one
supplement a day
if not you can put them all together as
your daily
regimen if you're not sensitive throw
them all together
throw them all together and that's okay
you want to throw them all together
right or as a middle ground you can
choose a couple
to start with so hey you know i found my
condition let me go in here what's wrong
with me
i got anxiety i got anxiousness that's
what's wrong so i'm in the book i'm
inclined to heal i got anxiety
i got anxiousness let me read the true
cause
when anxiety interferes with your life
it's caused by toxic heavy metals such
as mercury aluminum and copper
whoa whoa so that's what my crippling
anxiety
already i got an answer coming on
because i've been to five psychiatrists
i've been to ten doctors
i've been to all kinds of people and my
anxiety actually is toxic heavy metals i
just discovered what my anxiety is right
here
you don't have to do everything okay the
book is set up so someone really sick
can go all the way or take their time
and just knock things down a little bit
at a time
climb up that staircase to getting
better
so we're in the supplement section right
i'm in anxiety and anxiousness
so i'm i'm i'm struggling with that
anxiety and anxiousness
and i'm like been everywhere been there
done that
i've tried everything i've tried breath
work i've tried all kinds of things out
there i tried meditation with my anxiety
it just doesn't work
i'm on benzodiazepines
i mean i'm i'm sucking it out my anxiety
is really really bad
so i got the medical medium book i
decided to finally do it
i heard about it for years right
so i'm doing it and i'm seeing here when
anxiety interferes in your life yeah it
interferes with my life it's killing me
it's interfering with my life it's
caused by toxic heavy metals such as
mercury aluminum and copper
viruses such as one of the over 60
various epstein-barr you know i remember
having mono when i was younger
is that epstein-barr because i remember
it could even be over one of the old the
one of the over 30 varieties of shingles
that's funny i had a strange rash about
seven years ago i didn't know what it
was a doctor wasn't sure what it was
or a combination of both toxic heavy
metals and viruses so i can have
metal causing my anxiety and maybe even
viral issues
whoa most of the time it's both at once
with one cause more dominant depending
on individual case
that means i might have more toxic heavy
metals than i do viruses
check that out so here i am i already
been to 10 doctors
i got crippling anxiety i'm on benzos
and i'm actually learning right now for
the first time i'm getting an answer of
why i have crippling anxiety that's
interfering with my life
fancy that fancy that
seaweed hero fancy that might be a song
with that in there
anxiety okay so here's it most of the
times both at once right
with one dominating anxiety can also be
triggered accelerated or heightened by
emotional conflict
emotional conflict can heighten anxiety
okay we know that your anxiety might
crank up if you're triggered
emotionally ready although
toxic heavy metals and or virus must be
present for the anxiety to become
sustained and chronic
for the anxiety to be sustained and
chronic
it means it's these other physical
things
you know what's amazing about medical
mean information and i'm not saying this
because on the medical medium that's not
it because i'm just as astonished
as a lot of people are when they find
the true cause because
i'm a human being that hears the voice
the spirit of compassion since i was age
four
giving me the answers that nobody in
medicine could provide and nobody an
alternative alternative medicine can
provide ever
so i get blown away too and i don't take
it for granted i still wake up every
morning saying
it's incredible that you have the answer
it's incredible when it's not out there
let's go let's talk about anxiousness
you guys anxiousness that comes and goes
in a milder form can have the same toxic
metal or
viral causes or can result from mild
emotional injury or prolonged stress
on its own so i'm in anxiety for the
moment and that's a neurological symptom
and i want it to cover neurological
symptoms and we're going to go into
autoimmune as well in a little bit so
now i'm in the supplementation section
it says supplements for
anxiety fresh celery juice
work up to 32 ounces a day you guys if
that's all you do
nursing hi if that's all you do
is the celery juice that's incredible
incredible okay but don't just
do the celery juice and never read the
book
try it for a week and say it didn't work
and you tried medical medium
because you didn't you can go as far as
you need to go
just teaching you how a little bit
please can someone help and check if
gastroparesis is in this book yes it is
it's gastroparesis information in here
it's in the mono eating chapter
navid check it out when you can
so fresh celery juice we're there right
also in here it says celery forks three
capsules three times a day
that's the celery force right there
ask your doctor what's right for you
bring this to your doctor
say can i take the celery force there's
no celery in celery force
but it goes straight to the brain really
helps for anxiety
anxiousness i know because i've seen
friends and family take it
and experience it i use this every day
because i'm on this intense intense
schedule right now
so i use it every day try to give me as
much clarity as it possibly can get
so i'm just on it next one is 5mthf
for anxiety so 5 mthf so i got it
somewhere in here
there it is that's another one right
there it says one capsule daily
now you can do less
you can do five mthf one every other day
you can try different options
here's something interesting then it
goes into aloe vera
two or more inches of fresh gel skin
removed
how do you like that
is there anything on lupus lupus is is
autoimmune so if you don't find it here
directly this has lupus in it right here
okay but lupus is under autoimmune here
so yeah so it says autoimmune diseases
and disorders
that's if you don't find your label
because there's hundreds of autoimmune
disease titles right
if you don't find it you go under
autoimmune autoimmune disorders
so here i have an aloe leaf in front of
me
so i'm in here with anxiety and it says
aloe vera two or more inches of fresh
gel
skin removed daily
right so i'm just gonna cut this part
off right here
like that i'm gonna cut a two inch piece
like that
right i'm gonna try not to get it all
over the book
[Music]
guys welcome we're live right now
we're in the medical medium kitchen
having a little fun we're
reading cleanse the heel but we're
talking about all important pieces of
information
critical pieces of information you're
somebody that's not so sick you might
not care
if you ever get sick someday this stuff
is a godsend
so i'm cutting this information's
godsend so i'm cutting a piece of aloe
right there
so what does it say in the book so i'm
in anxiety
aloe vera two or more inches of fresh
gel
skin removed daily
so that's the aloe piece right there
right
here's a tip i might give you right here
which is really cool why
would aloe even be in here
a lot of people's nerves are jacked up
they're jacked up bad vagus nerves
attaching to the intestinal tract
are heightened in sensitivity because of
toxic heavy metals
and virus infections people walk around
with chronic viral infections every
single day and don't even know it and
they got crippling anxiety because of it
because of neurotoxins
created by the virus
so people walk around little bugs in
them is what they do
okay and those little bugs
pee and poo and they pee and poo
neurotoxins those neurotoxins get
released out of the viruses
like epstein-barr and shingles
those neurotoxins float around
and aggravate vagus nerve cells
any kind of vagus nerve issues so
what i like about aloe
and we just had a a piece of a two inch
piece right
maybe that's a little bit more than two
inches right there it's in the anxiety
section
because it's soothing to the linings of
the intestinal tract
it's antiviral but it's soothing to the
linings of the intestinal tract
which can calm the nerves and calm the
vagus nerve down ease
gastric cramping and spasms and
everything
so that's why it's there in the anxiety
part
i remember when i was younger and spirit
of compassion would always give me
the remedies and the information that
people needed i would always ask like
why
why why all the time
you know why spirit why why why
so we did the aloe right there next one
is ashwagandha
one dropper full twice a day
so the ashwagandha is next and these are
vimergy supplements right here
just so you know i'm gonna grab an
ashwagandha real quick so
actual gun is an important one
i think it's somewhere else i take the
ashwagandha and i might have taken it
into my office
i am looking at
got an ashwagandha right here you guys
sorry about doing this to you
it's all about being live so the
ashwagandha right here
it says one dropper full twice a day now
this is the vimergy products if you guys
don't know the vimergy products it makes
a difference
so i just gave you a quick rundown b is
in victor i am as
mary e rgy.com i'm not sponsored
but and it's important to have stuff
that doesn't have the alcohol it doesn't
have
the small percentage of of ingredients
you don't know about that exist in there
like msgs that are hidden in there or
the natural flavors
or anything like that or the citric acid
or all the junk and garbage or the bad
glycerin
all of that so
and most people will bat grab the bad
quality stuff they'll grab the wrong
stuff they'll be like okay
let me go grab something else it says
high quality but it's not
do the best you can but that's the one i
use friends and family that's the one
that i trust the most ashwagandha is one
dropper full twice a day so let's talk
about that why
why spirit why
and you can check out other supplements
on my directory medically dot com spirit
why
why ashwagandha for anxiety i don't get
that like i
i want to know okay so let's go there
that's why when you get the low-grade
viral infections
this important information when you've
got the low-grade vital infections in
the toxic heavy metals
and it's triggering off that vagus nerve
and it's triggering off those those
those cranial nerves and it's messing
you up
and you're getting the tightness of the
chest and the tightness of the throat
and you're getting all the issues that
are involved in you know you're getting
the heart palpitations and all this
other stuff that's happening vegas nerve
related
doctor doesn't know why you're having
this the adrenals are
pumping pumping sometimes that anxiety
can keep you up half the night sometimes
it can keep you up the whole night
some sometimes it keeps people up three
days straight
donna says ashwagandha unless you are
hyperthyroid correct
not correct it's a theory
here's here's my problem that i have out
there the theories when theories develop
in natural medicine
they're developing when they still don't
know why someone has hyperthyroid or
hypothyroid but do what your doctor
tells you if your doctor tells you stay
away from ashwagandha because the
hypothyroid stay away from it
to listen to your doctor but what
happens is that
theories that develop in natural
medicine
from people who don't know why someone
has a hypothyroid hypothyroid
hashimoto's thyroiditis cyst nodules
tumors and their thyroid problem
they don't know why they didn't know it
was epstein-barr
that information came later science
researcher linking epstein-barr down
because
medical media published it many years
ago talked about it for many years but
the cause of hyperthyroidism and
hypothyroidism you'll read in the books
is epstein-barr virus which can also amp
up anxiety for a lot of people too
without having a thyroid problem
moving right along our adrenals get
jacked up that's why
the ashwagandha so spirit why is this
so when i'm taking down the information
and and getting it out there for
everybody
i'm asking questions all the time i want
to know
because it helps to protect the adrenals
when your anxiety is cranking
rita gene says can you take a lot of the
supplements together or do you have to
take them at different times of the day
i take them all together a lot of times
you can do it different times a day
i explain it here too in the supplement
section of cleanse the heal you should
really check that out when you get a
chance because it's in this section
so right here knowing the cause of the
protocol
that's the section right there so let's
move to the next one barley grass juice
powder barley grass juice powder
right a lot of times i'll take barley
grass juice powder
i'll take it in a melon so this is
really cool best barley grass juice
powder on the market
is the vimergy b is in victor i
am e r yeah v-i-n-e-r-g-y
m-o-u-s-e no not that one
scooping out the melon right here
so let's do that i'm going to do a
little scoop out i just don't want to
dump
the center right there on the spot i
have to have the book you guys
want to keep it nice and clean
so what i do with honeydew melons i
watermelon too
watermelon too is i like to put the
barley grass juice powder
even on watermelon i'll do it too
absolutely
so i'm putting a little barley grass
juice powder right there inside the
melon
i like to have it that way you can also
have it so many other different ways
heavy metal detox movie is another way
to
put that right there
so i'm just anxiety right now anxiety is
a neurological symptom
we're going to talk about other stuff
too while we're here
so moving on down the line there's a lot
of supplements here one of the
best ones for this problem that people
deal with is
lemon balm so that's one of the better
ones right
there is lemon balm so it says lemon
balm
four dropper fulls four times a day
right
so let me get these four dropper fulls
right in here
four dropper fulls four times a day
you don't have to do that dosage because
if you read in here you can do
less just like i was talking about
before so if i go back
you guys just got here if i go back in
here
right if you're sensitive you can try
one supplement a day
vimrji supplements have flax oil in it
on tick tock you're saying no they don't
have flax oil in it
nope it's flax glycerin doesn't have
flax oil in it
just so you know it's advanced this flax
glycerin instead of palm glycerin
palm glycerin isn't the worst thing in
the world but it's not great
so vimergy has flax glycerin which
supersedes that's how advanced they are
it's incredible
you don't have flax oil in there that
flax glycerin though so there's no oil
in there
it's a good question though thanks for
asking
so what i love about the lemon balm is
it
calms the nerves down is what it does it
calms the nerves down if you guys want
to know what i'm doing
i'm going through supplementation
protocols i'm talking about you know all
kinds of different tips and things that
are really helpful important right there
in cleanse the heel
that's 51 off amazon.com us get a free
library
or other bookstores you can get it from
other stores too
so let's go into this a little bit
what i love about lemon balm is it's a
lifesaver for so many people
that i've recommended it for in high
dosages
do your doctor tells you i'm just
telling you what i would do for myself
if i had anxiety or
friends and family in high dosages like
four dropper fulls four
times a day it's constantly
keeping the nerves calm so it's helping
to feed the nerves
phytochemical compounds in lemon balm
relax nerves
they don't make you drowsy it you mean
lemon balm won't make you drowsy
but it calms the nerves is what it does
because phytochemical compounds
alkaloids and lemon bombs specifically
coat nerves
and stop them from wigging out
lemon balms also antibacterial antiviral
and that's a big deal too all on its own
so what's wigging out in our body
cranial nerves trigeminal nerve vagus
nerve right
all the different nerves in our body wig
out and
they're attached to all the different
organs too vagus nerve goes to some
lung lung activity vagus nerve goes to
the heart
vegas there goes the intestinal tract to
the stomach
and then people have all this anxiety or
symptoms that are neurological not just
anxiety and i love the lemon bomb
such a great great tool
okay if you grab lemon balm with alcohol
you're losing
you're losing you can't just burn the
alcohol off like people say well i'll
just burn the alcohol off i'll just boil
it
then yeah you're left over with now you
just boiled
something that was had a potential of
maybe helping inside the body but
but yet you're also boiling the heck out
of it
dispersing it in water like there's
there's no way out when you have alcohol
in the supplements it makes things
really difficult because a lot of people
will say no wait a minute
i got one it's got alcohol in it but i
know the trick you you
dump it into a pot of water and
and burn it off i'm like oh my god
and the alcohol already got into the
herb itself
so it's not about burning it off so what
i love about the vimergy is
there's no concern of that but yet
it's the flax glycerin
so it's even better than if you've
got another alcohol-free supplement that
had palm glycerin
and there's a lot of other reasons too
but that that's why it's good so
the vagus nerve runs into the different
organs
and the lemon bomb is helpful i can't
tell you how many people got off their
benzos
how many people got off their benzos
for using lemon balm like lemon balm
therapy spirit of compassion recommended
over the last 35 years
information is in this book take it to
your doctor
guys we're having fun
i'm gonna pop a little bit of water in
here
i'm gonna send this down
so good i love to taste the lemon balm
instantly instantly puts me in a really
good mood if i'm already in a good mood
it just puts me in even a better mood
so move on down the line a little bit
curcumin that's great for anxiety too
because curcumin is a natural like a
natural aspirin
so it's a natural anti-inflammatory not
because
it's killing off all the pathogens that
create inflammation
that's not why because it's
phytochemical compounds
and you know in turmeric and curcumin
is all part of that it's all bundled up
in there and those phytochemical
compounds
have an aspirin like effect so i like
curcumin because
it lowers inflammation in the body
even if doctors and practitioners and
people on you know doctors on youtubes
or whatever podcasts or
in magazines don't know why you're
inflamed
they don't know why you're inflamed
curcumin is good for inflammation well
it's true it is good for inflammation
but i like the best one so that's in
here too and that can calm anxiety down
a little bit
dr faun md
there's lots of low quality curcumins
out there with additives
keep that in mind and they don't even
tell you
when there's even more additives in
there that are not that are not even on
the
ingredient list but that are in it
because i told you about that whole
thing bemidji refuses to do
they refuse to let a certain percentage
of manufactured additives go into their
products that all the other supplement
companies let in
and people say well why is he always you
know pushing their stuff or talking
about their stuff
because it's the best i use it friends
and family use it but it's more than
that
not just the best it's because
they like put their foot down
and when you're chronically ill you need
somebody that's got your back you need
people that got your back that put their
foot
down i put my foot down all the time
because i'm just like i don't care if
the caffeine industry is pissed at me i
don't care if everybody's mad at me the
apple cider vinegar people are at my
front door with torches and and shovels
and pitchforks
i don't care if you know like whoever's
knocking on my door the charcoal people
and
the ionizer water machine people are mad
at me and everybody's mad at me because
i'm trying to protect the chronically
ill someone's got to put their foot down
and and have the chronic legs back it's
not just
it's that it's not just knowing the true
cause of why we're sick and how to heal
and how to do protocols it's more than
that it's about having your back too
it's all of it it's important
there's some i mean yeah
magnesium glycinate that's in the
anxiety section so what does it say
three capsules daily magnesium
relaxes muscles muscles get wigged out
because
nerves are wigged out all the nerves
going through all our muscles
get all wigged out because of toxins and
toxic heavy metals and viral neurotoxins
like i was talking about
creating anxiety and other problems so
then our muscles
get pushed to their limit not because
they're being used like a workout
they're being pushed to the limit on a
stress level
so i love magnesium glycinate
you'll see more magnesium glycinate out
there because
medical medium information is the most
advanced
and it leads the way in all of health if
you're somebody like that's not possible
i i don't even know why this guy's
saying this it's true and it's all fact
and it's true
the books don't lie they've been
published first it leads the way in
information
lectures i've done over the years leads
the way in information and glycinate now
magnesium glycine you'll see
it now out there and all the supplement
companies that made all these mistakes
they're now putting glycinate magnesium
glycinate and stuff it's like
medical medium information is upgrading
all the time
the world of natural medicine in
conventional medicine too and chronic
illness
glycinate's really important that
magnesium
so we got that that's of energy
magnesium i take a bunch of that
i take a bunch of that every single day
that's what i do
so vitamin c why is vitamin c important
for anxiety like
when i was younger i'd say the spirit of
compassion like why vitamin c
i hate having these annoying questions
but why
because your anxiety is spawned on
by low-grade viral infections
and that's what's happening to everyone
spirit combat should be like everybody's
anxiety spawned on by low-grade viral
infections
and free radicals such as toxic heavy
metals
vitamin c doesn't take out all the toxic
heavy metals that's not it at all
but at least it helps to neutralize
byproduct and runoff from toxic heavy
metals
the black stuff that
oxidizes the black oxidation
that material that oxidizes
it comes off of toxic heavy metals
vitamin c helps to neutralize that
that oxidation vitamin c
helps to lower low-grade viral
infections that are causing somebody's
anxiety this covers i'm talking about
all neurological symptoms too you guys
low-grade viral infections toxic heavy
metals a lot of that neurological lyme
people are jacked up in tons of mercury
they got mercury in them
they're loaded with mercury mercury in
the brain mercury in their nervous
system mercury in their liver when they
got neurological lyme
jacked up with mercury and low-grade
viral infections
yep i see there's a lot of trolls there
huh everybody's saying there's tons of
trolls
so we got the vitamin c that's the micro
c
it's of energy microc if you guys don't
know of energy i know you guys most of
you guys do let's be using victor i am
ergy dot com
i'm not sponsored by these guys so
we're in cleanse the heel if everybody
wants to know we're in the supplement
section
this is a different kind of live this is
a live showing you
an example if you find your symptom you
find your condition
if you're somebody with multiple
symptoms multiple conditions
pick the one that bothers you the most
you can pick another one too but if you
pick the one that's bothering you the
most chances are a lot of the other
symptoms will start going away as you're
healing which is really great
the best book marisa clenzie heel
yep so moving down the line a little bit
let's go into a couple other different
conditions so
um i want to talk about that as well
so if you're somebody that's like but i
don't want to do all these supplements
but i want to do medical medium i want
to know the protocols i want to know how
to heal
then you do the top four and i talk
about in here b12 is one of the top four
right there lemon balm vitamin c
one of the top four right or you can do
top eight you can do top eight zinc
right there it's important there too so
you do some zinc
you got your b12 you got your vitamin c
okay that's top three you could do top
two
maybe pick the b12 and the zinc right
there
you don't it's not about being
overwhelmed it's about knowing you're
heading in the right direction
and knowing a little bit at a time you
can chip away
and chip away and climb up that ladder
and heal
but then people pick the wrong
supplements they'll pick the wrong
supplement or the wrong kind or whatever
details matter when you gotta heal man
they matter it was complicated when we
got sick
it was complicated when we got sick
right complicated toxic heavy metals
from utero
complicated different viral infections
in streptococcus throughout the years
contracting it with just you know you
know on the dating scene
for some people got a new streptococcus
here got a new fever blister here
it gets complicated right
drank off of somebody's glass in high
school and got mono
jorah says medical medium healed my
cystic acne microc was a big help
it it is a big help for so many people
i'm honored to hear
thank you for being here getting sick is
is complicated we burn our adrenals out
we do years of caffeine
marissa says it's about understanding
what causes your symptoms and conditions
it really matters exactly
but when you understand your symptoms
and conditions it's a huge part about it
right
and that's what i love about this
knowing the cause and the protocol
matters it's complicated when we get
sick
we contract a lot of different viruses
throughout our life eating in
restaurants public bathrooms
through other people right that passed
down from our parents
and we get a lot of toxic heavy metals
from
medical treatments there's toxic heavy
metals and antibiotics
lots of it lots of it we take an
antibiotic there's toxic heavy metals in
there
it's toxic heavy metals and
pharmaceuticals
so we're do work but what happens is
that we get
over time we get a lot of different
toxin
toxins chemtrails other exposures metal
through
just aluminum foil whatever it is
drinking out of cans
the happy girl 99 thank you anthony
williams three years since discovering
you
medical medium is the only protocol that
has healed me
this is true healing this is a real
quality of life
being taught honored
the happy girl 99 honored there's
thousands of combinations so everybody
has a chance to heal he's just
and have faith have faith
that once you learn a little bit as
you're diving into it and understand
how it works just a little bit at a time
you can get there
you can customize it to the way you need
to customize it
so how do we heal
how we have to know what's wrong and we
have to know what to do
we have to know what's wrong and why it
happened and we have to know what to do
what to do this is what how it works
you can't heal entirely if you have a
problem if you don't know why you're
sick
you know what's crazy is someone who
gets sick today
it looks like it looks like everything
is all set for you to heal
out there well first go to my
conventional doctor i'll start with that
i'll get a whole bunch of blood work and
then i'll go to my next doctor
try that then i'll go to a specialist
now i'm gonna go to my functional doctor
now i'm gonna go to my chiropractor
now i'm gonna go to my naturopath and
i'm gonna go to my health coach whatever
it is my nutritionist
and you're gonna and you think it's all
there
and everybody's like uh you got candida
um you got it's
you're actually it's genetic or you got
autoimmune that's not an
answer like those aren't answers
you a gut health problem we got to
balance your flora that's not that's not
an answer
marianne says why is the glycerin needed
in the bemrg supplements
a lot of other supplements don't have
glycerin
so there's a reason why one of the
reasons why
is because you can't just
first of all you don't want it in a
powder when it comes down to
herbs number one you don't want it in
a powder absorption doesn't happen
it doesn't happen okay
number two all nutrients absorb into
your cells
through some type of glucose
some type of glucose by attaching
those phytochemical compounds to a
glucose you can absorb it
that's why all those powders and
formulas out there
that people take so dumping in it's not
attached to a glucose
it'll never absorb and they just poop it
out and poop it out poop it out
so and you don't want alcohol so you
have to have
the glycerin but the key is
when you use the glycerin the glycerin
is a glucose a form of glucose that
attaches itself to the nutrients and
then draws the nutrients into
your cells
it's really brilliant really it's just
it's it's brilliant how
our bodies work and what they need
so
so glycerin is glucose yeah the form
the form everything that's a
carbohydrate or sugar of any kind that
goes inside our body that's involved in
our body
floating around in her body is glucose
so the minute the glycerin enters your
mouth it
it's glucose boom it's glucose
christine thank you anthony you helped
me heal not just my symptoms but my
whole mind body and spirit
369 cleanse changed my entire life so
grateful
incredible christine so
let's go into another part let's go into
chemical food sensitivities which
which i really like talking about a
little bit even if it's just for a
couple of minutes let's head there now
rita is there anything about toddlers
being able to take these supplements in
your book yes there is
cold and flu section check it out
dosages for toddlers ask your doctor if
it's right for you ask your pediatrician
if it's okay
everyone with food and there's also a
section in there called child liver
because children when children are sick
their liver is involved
when they're sick with anything
excellent psoriasis vitiligo anything
like that when children are sick
it's liver related very important to
know so that's
in here too everyone with
chemical and food sensitivities is
different
it's different you're welcome to explore
any of the supplements in this chapter
the list here is simply a starting point
for some
sensitive people the fresh celery juice
you've got the chemical sensitivities
you start with this fresh celery juice
everybody's different because of what
they have going on some people have more
viral activity some people have more
toxic heavy metal
activity some people have more aluminum
some people have more mercury
some people have more copper some people
have more cadmium and lead and arsenic
some people have two epstein bars some
people have one epstein bar
some people have a different variety of
epstein-barr while they'll have a
different variety of shingles some
people have two different varieties of
shingles and a variety of hhh v6
some people have two types of cold sores
they won't know it but two types of
fever blisters
some people have fever blister cold sore
virus simplex virus
and they'll have a shingles virus all in
the same location someone's going to
have their shingles virus down here
right here they'll have it in their back
some people have the shingles virus on
their ass
they'll have it on their ass and it'll
break out every couple of months
the doctor will be perplexed everybody's
different
some people wore perfume for years some
people didn't
some people have air fresheners plugged
in some people don't some people have
sent the candles plugged in some people
don't
some people have two or three viruses
plus cytomegalovirus
plus hpv
and they'll also be covered in perfume
for 10 years
some people have copper pipes in their
house and they'll have lots of copper
in their brain and in their liver some
people have lots of aluminum in their
body because they took a lot of
different pharmaceuticals
everybody's different so your chemical
sensitivities are going to be different
see how it works you guys
the list here is simply a starting point
start with fresh celery juice
maybe celery force
it's not because your body is different
we're human beings
strike 77 wasn't that funny the other
day
strength good to see you turned out it
was a mistake
so anyway you guys
so you can do raw honey in some herbal
tea
like a lemon balm tea you can take it
gently you can do
you can just do little things it's not
because
your body is different
it's because of what's residing inside
someone could have had a big trigger
they could have mold exposure and they
got two viruses
and they got toxic heavy metals and they
had a fluoride treatment
too many one fluoride treatment too many
you guys had too many fluoride
treatments
some people got scented candles burning
in their house all day long
they go out and they get a fluoride
treatment right
and it pushes and they just have their
carpets cleaned some people love to get
their carpets cleaned by a conventional
carpet cleaning service every month
and they're getting saturated with
solvents and poisoned
everybody's different it's about what
you have inside of you that makes you
different
and that's that's how it works the
chemical sensitivities tammy winters
i've been doing celery force for six
weeks it already has helped my
split nails oh celery juice for six
weeks
it already has helped my split nails
lower blood pressure and chronic fatigue
incredible incredible and guess what
guess what if you go into the chronic
fatigue syndrome section
right here in the book you can look at
other things you can do
if celery juice isn't enough yet because
you may have
someone's fatigue can go away with
celery juice every day
somebody else's might be there a little
more stubborn because we've got some
other problems so we have to go a little
deeper we need to know the protocols
for the other urban supplements take one
take only one supplement one day
another the next so one of the
techniques for chemical sensitivity is
just take one supplement a day
the next day you take another supplement
the next day you take another one
that's a technique right there you can
read about in here if you decide to take
all of the supplements in this list it
means you'll be
on an eight day cycle a sensitivity is
yet
another reason to stay away from
supplements with 50 ingredients let's
talk about that right now this is really
important
one there's a way to move forward for
everybody there's just a way to move
forward
it exists been here for 35 years since i
started working with people and i worked
with people when i was a little
practical baby so
but the point is there is a way right
there is a way now there's something
really important what was just said in
here
right here in this book a sensitivity is
yet another reason to stay away from
supplements with 50 ingredients in a
bottle and i mean 20 ingredients too
not just 50
multivitamins multivitamin bottles
infamous for not only ripping people off
not only not helping because it's a
smidgen of a low quality thing in there
a smidgen smooth mission
but it's aggravating for people who are
sensitive
multivitamins are aggravating for people
who are sensitive
if you're somebody sensitive and you're
taking lemon balm and a multivitamin
you'll probably think the multivitamin
is great and the lemon balm is a problem
even though lemon balm's just one thing
one thing with the multivitamin you'd be
like no
multivitamins we get brainwashed we get
brainwashed about like multivitamins
well i need my multivitamin my
multivitamin
best multivitamin that i've ever
used for myself is what you're seeing
right here
barley grass juice powder right right in
to say this melon or in the heavy metal
detox smoothie
and spirulina combined okay for years
i heard it over and over again
uh what can i use for a prenatal what
can i use for prenatal i'd be like okay
a bunch of low-grade specks
of dust and and vitamins vitamins that
are just bulk
supplies of low-grade they use a speck
of each
some guys like i think what would be
really good for
women who are pregnant would be a
concoction of
this this this this this let's just put
it all together and slap it together and
have everybody think it's like okay
i mean if i was pregnant
if i was pregnant just get you guys
gonna tell you i was pregnant i got
pregnant
you guys i've been pregnant for
you guys are seeing an uh an ultrasound
right now
through my body right now and you're
seeing my baby
i didn't tell you guys i was pregnant
but what i have right now is a screen
sending out a giant ultrasound so you
guys can see
inside of me right now
um if i was pregnant i am pregnant
sorry guys i am pregnant not if i was
pregnant i am pregnant
i am pregnant so i'm gonna do some
spirulina
and some barley grass juice powder
that alone offers more phytochemical
compounds
for more micronutrients more vitamins
across
the board than any prenatal can ever
offer my baby and me
it's a renata it's a true miracle i got
pregnant
i know i didn't tell you guys right now
what you're seeing is an ultrasound
machine
sending a powerful blast through my body
so you guys can see my baby
do you think it's going to hurt my baby
we should turn that machine down i'm
going to have
we got to turn that machine down you
guys turn that machine down because it's
hurting my baby yep turn the machine
down good good
phew the ultrasound's off of me but
inside of me i got the baby
[Applause]
so anyway i just put spirulina inside a
half of a melon because i like to have
it that way you can have it in
half a papaya like dude i like do it on
watermelon too i do
so i got spirulina here i got barley
grass juice powder that's an incredible
multivitamin that'll low
you want to go a little further instead
of a speck of 5
mth
methylfolate can take a methylfolate
and spirulina
and barley grass and then add b12
not a spec something that can actually
help
you can customize with medical medium if
you're doing
spirulina the best spirulina there is in
the market today it's the vimera gvs and
victor imergy.com
barley grass juice powder i saw that
exactly not barley grass
that's the vimergy right and you're
doing that
and then you add in like the b12 you
make sure you're doing some
c you got some zinc already already
you got yourself moving forward already
just with that alone
you're looking at your symptoms you're
going through here and if you just say
you know what i'm going to do the
spirulina i'm going to do the barley
grass i'm going to do some c and some
zinc
boom some b12
if it was me though if i you know
now now that i'm pregnant i just turned
on the ultrasound
just turn the ultrasound back on machine
so you guys can see visually through my
body
if it was me i mean now now that i'm
pregnant
um i wouldn't take
a whole bunch of herbal concoctions
because i don't appreciate when
i go to my practitioner
and my practitioner gives me a whole
bunch of
herbs what if my baby reacts to one of
them i wouldn't know
you know like uh chinese medicine herb
herbal formula with 30 herbs in it
natural fat a gut health pro probiotic
with
20 30 herbs in it that's what i'm
talking about
like 30 herbs in it not just one herb
not like nettle leaf or
lemon balm that's different kim you can
ask your
practitioner your doctor if little metal
leaf is okay while you're pregnant you
can ask your
practitioner and doctor if a little um
if a lemon balm is okay while you're
pregnant
i've recommended that to friends and
family but ask your doctor what's right
for you
b12 but 40 50 herbs 30 herbs gut health
formulas probiotics with six or eight
herbs in it
how do you know what the baby is gonna
react to or not
react to so i just don't like that
happening
so i worry with my baby
so you guys have you just got here we're
talking about the medical medium cleanse
the heel book supplements and protocol
symptoms and conditions how to use it
how to work with it let's hit cold and
flu
page 498 are you guys hanging out
cold and flu you ready for this i'm
gonna read a little bit if you guys are
okay for this
what we call colds these days are
actually mild versions of the flu
colds are gone news flash
to all the doctors out there in the
world colds are gone
there are no cold cold bugs
that create colds you either have a mild
flu or you have a bad flu
or a moderate flu mild flu moderate flu
or bad flu
or mild plague moderate plague
or bad plague which is the flu family
by the way engineer flu family
many many years ago there were different
varieties of common cold viruses that
could give you the sniffles a scratchy
throat and sometimes a fever under 100
degrees
that was the cold virus for many many
years
a long time ago
in order for this to happen you would
really need to have a lowered immune
system
which most often occurred due to not
being clothed right
check this out you guys for damp weather
and experiencing temperature shock from
being exposed to the elements
these cold viruses never created what
we're up against in the present today
today if we experience those symptoms
and they're mild
we're really dealing with a mild
influenza strain
when the symptoms are worse we're still
dealing
with influenza
flus are going around right now be
prepared stomach flu is going around be
prepared
foods are going around this fall coming
up be prepared to what's to come
we're also dealing with the plague gonna
deal with the plague all fall we're
gonna deal with the flus
and the winter and there's gonna be some
pretty bad flus and stuff
people's immune systems are down more
than ever before
in our history and this year this year
people's immune systems are
just flat busted right now people are
going to be
contracting flus more than ever i'm not
trying to spook anybody i'm just saying
you might want to just be prepared talk
to your doctor if you want to
ask your doctor if it's okay you can
have a little zinc or you know some good
quality zinc like the best quality zinc
or something in some
micro sea or something so we're in
supplements and protocol section of cold
and flu
so let's just talk about this a little
bit this is important
even the stomach bugs that go around are
particular strains of the flu unless you
had food poisoning you guys
the flu can enter a family of five and
each individual can experience different
symptoms as the strain leaves one family
member and moves on to the next
the strain mutates from person to person
plus everybody's immune system reacts
differently
so the last family member's flu may be
very different from the first family
member's flu
for example one person may get a sore
throat runny nose
and cough for three days while the next
gets 103 degree temperature and a very
long lasting cough and sinus drainage
important information
yeah health liz health with liz everyone
is already getting sick you're seeing it
right
you help out people you're seeing it
totally it's insane actually
medical medium zinc shock therapy and
medical medium vitamin c shock therapy
see pages four 482 and 484. it's a
medical textbook you guys is so helpful
can we be very can can be very
helpful techniques to apply at the first
sign of contracting a bug
because the flu often starts in the
lungs throat and sinus cavities
medical medium zinc shock therapy is
geared to this region to try to head it
off at the pass
supplements for cold and flus in adults
it talks about the supplements well for
adults it has cat's claw
here where's the cat's claw
where are you
um oh of course we're right here
so for adults then ask your doctor
all the time you know about what you can
take or not assist cats cloth two
dropper fulls three times a day
elderberry syrup
one tablespoon three times a day and
then it moves on you got the golden seal
goldenseal even if you don't have
anything but golden seal
that's a great one for cold and flu for
adult
for adults
thyme that's a huge one right there two
sprigs of fresh thyme and hot water
as tea or four sprigs in room
temperature
water twice a day
got some time what book is this cleanse
the heel
on tick tock you're asking cleanse the
heel 51
off amazon.com us it's like a miracle
price right now
get free at the library if you want
you can make some time tea i just said
four sprigs
right
put some sprigs in there
medicalmedium.com there's a directory
just so you know for supplementation
that's
the safest or
above board quality at least the best we
can get out there
i mean nothing surpasses vimorgy yet but
there are companies that still offer
some good things
i got them listed at medicalmedium.com
bad supplements give supplements a bad
name
bad cleanses give cleanses a bad name
bad people give good people
a bad name i think does that make sense
so anything we're called supplements for
cold and flus in children
one to two
when people say they're not getting
better many times
if not all the time they're using
supplements that aren't the right ones
low quality supplements supplements are
colds and flus in children ages one to
two right you guys supplements for colds
and flus and children ages three to four
supplements for colds and flus in
children ages five to eight
supplements for colds influenced
children ages nine to twelve
supplements for cold and flu in children
ages 13 and
up
[Applause]
incredible book you guys
we're heading off to ig we're going to
turn tick tock back on
so glad you guys were here we're going
to put clubhouse back on too
um but we'll be on instagram we'll see
what kind of fun we're going to have
over there
you're doing time t now lizzie m amazing
incredible um you guys know the
supplements that i use friends and
family the ones that i used personally
it's a vimorjin
vimergy.com
i'm off to ig i hope i see you guys i
love you guys greatly california poppy
good to see you
i'll see you guys then