we're live on facebook we're live on
youtube we're live on clubhouse
sweet potato tacos is what i'm making
we're talking about
fear mongering versus
truth telling pretty interesting right
so anyway look at this lettuce i got
right here you guys
this is pretty awesome i'm gonna make
myself some lemon balm tea
too and right here i got these purple
sweet potatoes look at those right there
okay they're already steamed they're not
like steamed
completely because we're gonna also put
them in the oven do a little
toasting good to see you guys i'm glad
we're on
um we're live on youtube live on
facebook live on clubhouse all at the
same time great glad you guys are coming
on
making the sweet potato tacos talking
about fear-mongering
you guys bump into any fear-mongering
out there or
gas lighting is anybody trying to
gaslight you guys
because there's a lot of gas lighting
going out there
uh and peer pressuring intense peer
pressuring
gaslighting fear mongering
right the whole bit the thing is is you
ever run into anybody you guys have you
ever run into anybody that just they
weren't ready
and that's okay right they weren't ready
you know to do what they needed to do
you know they weren't ready to
take care of themselves like they needed
to do right you know
they're still doing the whole in
moderation
i could still have a pizza on the
weekends and that's fine i get it i'm
like you guys probably do that some of
you guys probably do that of course
i'm still doing my pizza i'm still doing
my chocolate i'm still doing
i'm still doing my gluten in between so
what it's just once in a while right
and they're not ready to take that next
step to free themselves right
and someone's gonna be like hey you
should be allowed to do whatever you
wanna do you should be allowed to do
and eat what you feel like eating you
should be allowed to have some gluten
you should be allowed to
have some pizza once in a while i should
be allowed to partake in things because
it only makes you stronger
it only makes you stronger you know that
exposure like what you're worried about
bugs
you're worried about whatever and what
happens is
you know we get told hey doing something
is going to make us
stronger getting exposure is going to
make us stronger
you know that's what we're told all the
time michelle says gaslighting is
his gas lighting is now wide right
widespread out there
it's all about gaslighting totally you
know i met you know i remember
a while back talking to somebody and
they were and they're like
yeah but wait a minute if i'm taking
care of myself and eating so good so
i'm eating so much good food and
i'm watching out for my dairy products
and i'm watching out for fried foods and
i'm watching out for canola oil
right i'm just i'm just making myself
weaker i'm just making myself weaker
because i was talking to somebody this
person was telling me i was talking to
somebody aw and they were like
yeah you can have a little bit of this
let your body experience a little bit of
that
you should have some chocolate who cares
if you get a little canola oil in you in
a treat
you know you should be having some kind
of chocolate treat you could have
coffee if you want you could have a
glass of wine you can have some alcohol
right
you could have a little bit of this in a
little bit of that makes you stronger
you get weaker if you
you know if you push that away
you get weaker if you you know if you
keep that stuff out
you become orthorexic right
so that's another gaslighting term right
so here you are you're trying to heal
you're trying to take care of yourself
because you don't feel good
because you're sick and you don't feel
good and you're trying to take care of
yourself you're trying to heal
and you're trying to eat right and
you're trying to keep the gluten out and
you're trying to keep the dairy products
out
and you're watching what you're eating
and all of a sudden
you know it's a lot of work to do that
right so it's a lot of work to watch
what you're eating we're really being
censored today
whoa so it's a it's like
um stephanie says hi aw
mono eating saved my life this week i
could not move
vertigo and inflamed vagus nerve thank
you soc
the mono eating and cleanse the heel is
critical for that
critical you guys need to get taken down
by something if you feel like
you're being taken down with something
exactly in that case it's vertigo it's a
mono eating
and cleanse the heel making the sweet
potato tacos we're talking about fear
mongering we're talking about
some interesting stuff i'm gonna i'm
gonna start making the dish get it in
the oven
too you guys but what you'll find is
someone will think you know hey like
i'm eating healthy i'm taking care of
myself and then someone's going to come
and sabotage them and say you're
orthorexic
and it's like wait what am i and they're
being gas lit
boom right there like the flames are
happening right there
like wait a minute what am i i'm i'm
what
orthorexic what's that you're obsessed
about healthy food you're obsessed about
eating healthy
you're obsessed about healthy food right
you know and you're just you're just
obsessed
that's a disease so now you've got the
eating healthy disease
so somebody will say that out there
really really
gas light the freaking hell out of
someone so bad
because that just clobbers you here you
are you're trying to take care of
yourself and it's hard job as it is
right
you don't feel good you got symptoms you
got conditions
you're working hard on trying to take
care of yourself and somebody comes
along and they got
like gasoline and a lighter and they're
just dumping it on you and they just
light the flame
is what they do and and they're doing it
with a couple of different ways
you'll either whether whether you're
called orthorexic or something or
if you're just like you're obsessed
about food why are you so obsessed about
food i don't need to be obsessed about
food i could just live my life and not
think about food and eat whatever i want
when i want
and then it makes you feel like a real
piece of crap too that's one right there
because a lot of people
who aren't sick they aren't sick or they
say they're sick
but they're really not they get a little
energy a little brain
touch of brain fog little acne they see
their
different functional medicine doctors
they stay out of the woods
because they're not eating so so
terrible
and they're not sick yet they're not
sick sick yet right
and then they'll be the ones to be like
i don't really think about food i don't
really focus about food i live my life
i'm a life liver not a food eater you
focus on food
you go focus on food there you know yeah
you go worry about everything you're
eating go worry about all your
your lettuces worry about your tomatoes
worried about all your stuff and
i'll go live my life and have a glass of
wine when i feel like it and i'll have a
little pizza when i feel like it and
you know you know i'll pick choices
intuitively to what feels good in the
moment but other than that i don't
really think about food so it's another
form of gas lighting right there
it's another thing here they bring the
gasoline container over and they got the
lighter and they're dumping gasoline on
you and they
they hit the flame and that's how it
works right and then the moderation gas
lighting
that that right there is a whole other
another thing all on its own
so it's like yeah you should be allowed
to do moderation
or you weaken your system i heard that
one pretty recently like
your system needs to be bombarded by all
this crap out there you need to go out
on the streets you need to breathe in
all the smog
you need to get exposed by germs
you need to be licking your hands after
you touch a hand door handle
a doorknob so you walk into a place you
touch the doorknob doesn't matter just
lick your hand that
that before the plague that's going
around right now
you know people just didn't even care
they didn't even care just touching
everything doesn't matter rub your eye
you know it's like get exposed because
it makes you stronger that is not true
that is not true right so
it's fear mongering saying look be
cautious about that door handle
you shouldn't have your finger in the
taste tester
at the grocery store you shouldn't be
going into the grocery store
and sticking your hand in the sample jar
at the grocery store
those little square pieces of cheese in
the sample jar that everybody else have
their hands in right before
the plague before the plague now because
they changed all the rules right
and you stick your hand in that sample
jar and you pop those little cheese
squares in your mouth and now you're
you're pushing your cart and you find
another sample jar
and you go and grab some of that right
there right
and next thing you know it right
you're you're you're exposed but if
someone said you shouldn't be sticking
your hands
truth-telling right truth-telling now
okay
truth-telling you shouldn't be sticking
your hands in that sample jar
at the grocery store all right and
putting that
stuff in your mouth you're gonna be
throwing other people's streptococcus in
your mouth you're gonna start be putting
in
other people's e coli you know someone
just went to the bathroom
and they wiped their butt they got feces
on their hand
and now they're reaching in that they're
reaching in that little sample jar
right there let me go in that sample let
me oh pineapple
with the pineapple with the toothpick
stuck in it and a little piece of cheese
there
let me go grab that in the grocery store
oh let me grab one too let me grab
another one too
meanwhile the person who prepared it
also came out of the bathroom
they wiped their butt who knows how good
they wash their hands or if they why why
they wash your hands at all and so
that's truth telling right there that's
true tally
right you should never put any pain you
should never put any paper on the toilet
seat
that's being totally obsessive totally
out of control
you should never have to put toilet
paper or any kind of paper
protection on the toilet paper toilet
seat in public restrooms
just sit on the seat sit on the seat get
exposed
makes you stronger makes you stronger
right
true telling is don't be sitting on that
toilet seat
that somebody else sat on okay
i can't tell you how many people have
herpes on their butt you guys have no
idea
30 plus years of doing the work that i'm
doing
doctors sending patients to me from all
over the world right
and and the amount of people that have
herpes on their butt
it's unbelievable right shingles breaks
breakouts on their butt simplex one
breakouts
on their butt simplex tube breakouts on
their butt
strap on their butt but
cheeks breakouts and pustules on their
butt
cheeks simplex and everything else dr
fun have you ever seen any of the
patients have that
doctor font any patients have that with
the breakouts on their butt right there
they're they're right their butt cheeks
the breakouts
so but you know but truth telling is
put paper down on that seat truth
telling medical medium information is
flush the toilet in the public restroom
before you sit on that seat
because whatever swimming around that's
left over one flush doesn't get rid of
it
did you know that you guys one flush
when somebody goes to the bathroom
okay and they flush the toilet it's
important information
and they flush the toilet right and that
toilet bowl goes down
oops oops all clean water that's not
clean there's still
it never gets rid of that seven gallons
that goes down
always leaves like a half a gallon
quarter of a gallon behind
so you all got you got all that germ all
sitting in there and then you go sit on
the toilet and you got that sitting
right there just
just ready for you ready for you right
so it's not only do you need
the cover like protection on the toilet
seat
but you got to worry about the splash
so if you're peeing sitting down
right you're going to have splash
coming up from that water it's just
going to be splashing
you see all these micro splashes right
so you wanna you in a public restroom
you wanna flush it
before you even sit on there even if the
water looks clean oh it obviously
flushed somebody flushed it will flush
it again
so then you have less of a chance of
exposure but
is this fear-mongering are you scared
now
are you scared like is everybody scared
are you scared out of your mind
right or is it truth-telling or can
someone handle truth-telling
what is it if they can't handle
truth-telling i understand
but what is it is it fear-mongering
right
ashley kevin says that's what the splash
is the worst um
now it's protecting it's having your
back
you know so it's either is it fear
mongering or is it having
your back or having your body's back how
about that
or you having your body's back you know
so when you look at all the different
levels you guys
we're live on youtube live on facebook
i'm about to make sweet potato tacos or
live on clubhouse
if you look at it all right you'll see
the traps everywhere
okay the moderation trap right there
okay
then you feel like well moderation
everybody's saying moderation
maybe that's the right way to go maybe
that's what i should do right
and but what no one realizes is you
poison yourself in moderation we poison
ourselves in moderation do you like
poisoning yourself
i mean we poison ourselves in moderation
and it's almost like pushing the body to
the limit pushing the body to the edge
will the body give yeah it does
it gives on everybody eventually right
chris you seem finding me good to see
you yeah and and so the whole thing is
we
we have this mechanism our body
that gets pushed to the edge all the
time
and it eventually starts to break down
one way or another
it just starts to break down it just
does some people saw it earlier
some people it's not narashini it's good
to see you glad you're on i'm gonna
start um
making some stuff here um let's do this
let's get these sweet potato pieces see
these beautiful
purple sweet potatoes right here uh
flamen says aw thank you for being solid
all these years really honored honored
you feel that way
truly truly truly jamie i call it making
an educated choice or decision that's a
that's said it better than i could said
it better than i could
amazing really these are some green
onions i'm gonna move over here right
you guys i got red bell peppers right
here
gonna make a hot sauce too so
that was really a good way of saying it
right don't you want a choice don't you
guys want a choice don't you guys want
want to know what's going on right i'm
cutting these in cubes right here
and it's going to go um in a i'm going
to marinade these and then they're going
to go in a baking
tray going to go in the oven in a little
bit okay look at this beautiful
green leaf lettuce i have right here
okay
um i'm gonna kind of cubes these up
these are these
beautiful purple sweet potatoes right
here
as i told you guys earlier i pre-steamed
them and
still left them kind of not completely
cooked but just about
and then i'm gonna give them a toast in
the oven for a little while
if you don't pre-steam them you gotta
you know bake them in the oven
for sure you got to give them that bake
time but this is going to be a faster
way of doing it for today
it's like how much do you guys want to
know
right how much do you want to know
how much can people handle that's
another thing too you know
did an alien spacecraft
right looking for a hand towel here here
it is didn't alien spacecraft
bring the human race here
we're not it's interesting question
right
um
take these little cubes here
is the toilet bowl
filled with a lot of bad bugs and we
have to be careful when we sit on it
publicly
yeah we do got to be cautious
before the plague very few people
no one i knew did
the the hand sanitizer before touching
the cart
at the grocery store do a couple more of
these
just grab the cart doesn't matter what
ha what was what's on the cart handles
rub your eye
spread the flue
everybody's got the flu in the winter
everybody's touching everything
touching doorknobs no one's thinking
about anything
doesn't matter just eat something grab a
sandwich don't wash your hands
right makes you stronger it doesn't i've
seen
i've seen it knock people down and knock
them down
i'm going to cut a couple more of these
so our immune system weakens
because it's bombarded by so many
different things so your immune system
is bombarded our immune system
is bombarded is it fear mongering or is
the truth telling
our immune system gets bombarded every
single day okay radiation
all right mercury falling out of the sky
okay
mosquito spray just so you know that the
chemical companies are trying to kill us
they just dump mosquito spray all over
the world
on top of us mosquito sprays okay that's
what they do
that's their favorite is that mosquito
spray right
we breathe in and we breathe in and we
get knocked down the point is
it's not about being in fear it's about
how do we fortify ourselves protect
ourselves make ourselves stronger
and then the perfumes colognes just so
you know that stuff is so toxic
the air fresheners the scented candles
are so toxic
so toxic it's unbelievable you guys have
got you don't know it's so bad
so bad um okay i'm gonna
i'm gonna do a little uh this is pretty
much right here
so i'm gonna put some lime juice in here
basically i'm gonna marinate these a
little bit
so let me put this down for a second
right here
all right
i'm gonna put this over here actually
let's add some lime juice
and
i think when people really they want to
live their life and they don't want to
be thinking anything so
they don't want to be thinking about
something
they have no control over but you really
do have control over so much got control
over the perfumes clones in your life
you got control over um scented candles
you got control over
right air fresheners
aftershaves right you got control over
those
that's a big deal on its own um that
just knocks people down
knocks them down bad right you got
control over how much fish you're eating
you got to worry about the mercury right
got control when you learn
that fish oil supplements will will
bring you so fast to alzheimer's and
dementia down the road
memory loss severe depression anxiety
right you got you got an ability to
avoid that okay
i'm adding in lime juice and putting a
little bit more lime juice in this so
i'm doing a little marinating
right and i got about two cups
more than two cups of sweet potatoes in
there that's right so you guys i'm
making this the sweet potato tacos right
here so let me use some cayenne half
teaspoon of cayenne
i got that all right
half teaspoon of cayenne in here do a
little bit of
ground cumin got a little bit of that
going
let's do some coriander half teaspoon of
cumin
coriander half teaspoon right so i got
those covered
um one one tablespoon of raw honey got
some raw honey here
one teaspoon or a tablespoon of honey or
maple syrup i'm gonna do maple syrup on
this one
if you guys are okay with that you guys
are okay with the maple syrup you can do
honey too
right so let me put a little bit of this
in here
all right we've got that going this is
gonna be really good okay
i'm gonna mix this up
i'm not gonna mix it up so much where i
damage them
and then i'm going to get them on the
baking tray and then we're going to talk
about some serious stuff
we're just having a little fun talk to
start with here
let me get this in the baking tray
got the oven on right now
here we go so let's drop these on here
like this
spread these out
i'm really excited about this dish you
guys this is just great
okay let's get this in the oven
and get down to business
400 degrees toasting those up
get rid of these
how many years have i heard if i only
need this if i only knew this
if i only knew that if someone only told
me
how come nobody told me i had
epstein-barr
how come the doctor didn't know i had
epstein-barr all these years
how come no one told me to be careful
about that medical treatment
how come nobody told me
to be cautious about all the different
toxins and poisons how come
no one told me you know to be cautious
in the airport with my luggage because
it's so loaded with
i wasn't told about it affecting my
children and
and having the right you know the
baggage right next to my children
nobody told me about perfumes colognes
and how toxic they are and how they
lower the immune system
and scented candles lower the immune
system they drop the immune system
you know if i only knew if i only knew
how to heal
all these years right
and you know there's a podcast episode
on that to you guys
no one about fragrances and all that you
should you can check that out medical
media podcast said
apple podcast killing you smelly is the
name of that episode
nobody told me about how caffeine's
damaging my adrenals
and and bringing on my depression even
worse
nobody told me it was a psychoactive
drug that was actually
not healthy for me right and then
creates birth problems and in conditions
with my children
too but no one talks about that okay
and i've had so many people tell me over
the years how come nobody knew any of
this
why do we have to trial and error you
know nobody told me that
it was important to be cautious about
exposure versus
thinking that exposure would make me
stronger and make my immune system
stronger because we're supposed to get
a stronger immune system due to exposure
because that's what we're told right
just every bit of exposure makes you
strong but no one's saying
anything about that like what to look
out for
okay and all these all these things
matter
you know and who's looking out for us in
the end
right so we have to look out for each
other but if we're not given that
information and we're not giving those
tools how do we look out for ourselves
how do we
look out for us how do we look out for
each other how do we look out for our
family members the whole bit
right and i'm going to make some tea
right now
so that's a good thing right there i got
i got a tea kettle going i'm just going
to turn it on for the moment
make some tea you guys which he should i
have i got lemon balm
metal leaf raspberry leaf
right traditional medicinal is the one i
use i'm not sponsored
but it's the one i use it's the best tea
tea company i feel in the world
um so i'm gonna have some lemon balm
maybe i'll do two bags are you guys cool
with that
everything okay with that right
mc educating myself good vibes
good to see emc
thanks for being here lorraine l
good to see you watching the comments
hey just drop a lemon balm
box nothing like being live
i love it jocelyn
i wish more people knew about how toxic
fragrances are
even after you tell them they keep on
using them absolutely
of course they do
one thing that happens that people don't
understand is that
fragrances are an
invasion upon us
perp it's purposeful
that the form of darkness no
that might be too far i might have gone
too far on that
i think you guys think i've gone too far
to that but
it's a form of darkness because the
chemical companies
who conjure up these dangerous chemicals
just laughing in our faces slapping in
our faces
right like creating fake wildflower
smells
and just fake toxic perfume smells
right and meanwhile really just laughing
at our face
i'm gonna put a little honey in there
you guys okay if i do that
a lot went in there
right then they make us afraid of bugs
they'll make us afraid of mosquitoes
they'll make us afraid of things and
then they'll just want us to wish we had
mosquito spray being dumped on us
you know it's like
they fear monger us into they fear
monger us
into wanting to be intoxicated
you know um
ticks cause lyme disease they'll say
which is not true ticks don't cause lyme
disease you guys
but you wouldn't believe in in places
where there are a lot of ticks
people getting tick spray all on their
properties all on their yards right
for their children to play so that's
that's what's happening right
so all like oh my god all in new england
on the east coast of the u.s other
places united states and
practically anywhere in the united
states now right is
parents are being told you know you
better have some
some chemical company come in a
pesticide company
come insecticide and spray for ticks in
your lawn your property
your your adjacent woods maybe to your
property or your house right
because you know your children you know
need to be
safe because they're going to get lyme
disease from tick bites right
children don't get lyme disease from
tick bites right i talk about that in
the medical medium book the new edition
children don't get lyme disease from
tick bites bites it's not tick bites
ticks don't do that so it's really
important to know this is a new addition
by the way
and mosquitoes don't spread disease
here in the united states and most other
places around the world right
malaria is the only thing that
mosquitoes have ever spread
and even that's questionable by the way
in certain for certain reasons
but the bottom line is they'll put you
in fear about these things and
in tick with ticks everybody sprays
their lawns they spray
all around their house they spray in
their houses
and now you're exposing your children to
a deadly
neurotoxic chemical right it does have
long-term
damage to the body and nervous system
and so so now your children are in the
yard they're playing in the grass that
was sprayed by the tick spray company
i mean it's the endless problems with
this
i mean with with the mistakes that are
made all the time but you get put
into fear about it so the gas lighting
comes around so the
end up bringing that big that big
gasoline can
over just jump it there we go they dump
it all over you and bring out the match
you gotta spray for ticks you gotta
spray for ticks you gotta spray for
ticks
and you get you get lit up again
are incense toxic yeah they are yvonne
um yeah they're toxic
incense is just as toxic i'm just going
to be straight up is the perfumes the
clones air fresheners and scented
candles
chemical companies got your number they
got your number
they got your number in your head your
mind they got your number in your head
in mind
um kim blocker says
are you against a cup of organic coffee
for fatty liver
look it's not that i'm against it like
hey he's against it
but if you have a fatty liver i mean i i
wouldn't drink coffee if you have a
fatty liver because the coffee the
caffeine
is what tires out a liver and keeps on
tiring out a liver
so if you have a fatty liver there's not
it's not going to be an easy road to
healing a fatty liver if you have any
caffeine going in there
should listen to the medical mean
podcast coffee matcha tea and
and chocolate um medical mean podcast
apple podcast
so what coffee does is and all caffeine
does is it stresses out the liver it
weakens it it beats it down and that's
what it does and
and that might be just a simple way of
saying it right there but if you want
the more detailed version
is caffeine prompts your adrenals to
flood a tremendous amount of epinephrine
into your bloodstream your liver has to
soak it up like a sponge in order to
protect your brain
and your heart from becoming damaged by
the caffeine's effects of
triggering off your adrenals and then
all that epinephrine is flooding into
your bloodstream so your liver has to be
the sponge that's your mop right do you
have a mop in your kitchen
you guys mop your kitchen at all do you
do that because that's your liver you
should see
on the end of that mop when you're
mopping right you're mopping
along right is that a new prop i have to
get the mop
and you know and you're mopping along
right
that's your liver attach the bottom of
that broom that handle that mop handle
that's your liver and it's got to mop up
the floor well that's what it's doing
with all that adrenaline
and it's all caffeine it's not just
coffee it's matcha tea it's
whatever type of green tea it's every 10
black tea it's energy drinks
it's caffeine pills destroys the liver
and destroys the liver by prompting all
that adrenaline that epinephrine from
being
you know surging out of your adrenals
and then your liver has to be like i
said that sponge and that's what it has
to do okay
cacao chocolate the same thing and if
you got a fatty liver it's not that i'm
against it it's like look i want to look
if you if you want chocolate if you want
coffee if you want
i get it but but what i'm against is
it's i'm against yeah
i'm against the industries you know i
mean they said the industries aren't
looking out for people
leslie says i would say sheila says what
about decaf coffee it's all the same
leslie says are coffee enemas safe
please say yes
they're far from safe i'm sorry to say
no
i'm sorry to say no it was a bad idea
there's no science behind it
and that's the thing everybody thinks
what's the science behind it no
it's it was a bad idea terrible idea
actually
people are so obsessed with their coffee
they're so obsessed with their caffeine
that it was a really bad idea to
to to um to do the enema the coffee
enema
it really hinders your liver your
stomach buffers
the poisonous effects of caffeine to a
to a degree
so your stomach has a thick skin your
stomach has a really thick skin you guys
and that's what your stomach has you see
i'm going to pull the stomach right out
of this
um right on my friend right there i'm
going to pull the stomach out okay
your stomach's got a really really
really
thick skin inside just so you know i'm
just letting you know okay
and it's there to buffer poison in case
we get
we accidentally swallow poison right
and i talked about this one time okay
humankind
didn't know what what to eat right it's
all about
wait a minute let me try that herb
or that root or that shoot and everybody
stood around somebody when they tried
something new
native american culture i had a native
american a friend of mine right tell me
about
what their ancestors say right back in
their ancestors said
back in the day it was everybody stood
around
why one brave native american tried
something new
just so you know tried something new
should i
can i eat that tuber or that shoot or
that rhizome
can i eat that rhizome from that shrub
and then eat it and see how sick they
get
do they get devastatingly sick are they
in fetal position and vomiting for two
days
do they completely shut down and go
unconscious do they
choke and their throat just swell up and
they can't breathe and they die
right and so um your stomach
is created is made to be that buffer
for for mistakes of survival or stupid
mistakes
or whatever so i'm checking the oven
right now you guys bear with me in a
second
um those are toasting up
they actually only need another minute
or so and i'm gonna make a sauce make a
hot sauce
so okay back to this again so when we
dump
coffee poisonous effects of caffeine get
buffered a little bit
from that thick skin inside the stomach
right they get buffered a little bit
from that thick skin
okay but when you put coffee up the back
end
there's no buffer it goes directly into
your bloodstream
to your heart into your brain and it
annihilates the central nervous system
if you're somebody with central nervous
system symptoms what does that mean i
don't have any central nervous system
symptoms
i don't have any what's he talking about
i got no nervous system symptoms
migraines anybody migraines neck pain
back pain leg pain insomnia
nervous system okay tinkles and numbness
ringing in the ears nervous system
vertigo dizziness balance issues
depression anxiety nervous system so
whatever what up burning skin
pain in your jaw pain in your teeth
unexplained nervous system
right floaters in the eyes nervous
system okay
black spots in your eyes white spots in
your eyes all nervous system
right so you got all these new all these
nervous system
conditions and symptoms out there right
the worst thing
ever is to put coffee up the back end
because when you put coffee that way
there's no buffer from that thick skin
from the stomach you guys
and even that still isn't good enough
right it just buffers it to some degree
so it slowly gets to the brain
and the heart versus you go the coffee
enema
that goes right into your bloodstream it
hits your liver right away bam
wax that liver not to cleanse it it
doesn't cleanse it
it shocks it and weakens it and disables
it
that's what it does when you do coffee
enema right and then
and then the caffeine gets into the
bloodstream and causes a big problem i'm
going to take that out i think that's
just about getting there
so let me just grab an oven mitt wrap it
up you guys
that's what i'm doing get these out
these are toasted up nice okay so i am
going to
let me make the sauce and let me find a
spot where this should go
okay so maybe we can put it over here
all right
okay it's gonna burn on that towel but
i'll put it there
all right i got it right there you guys
so i'm just i'm just gonna make a sauce
right now
let's do that i'm gonna sip a little tea
so good with honey and the lemon balm
tea it's so incredible
it's not that moringa is bad or anything
it just
doesn't do a whole lot
it there's a lot of things people say
what about this what about moreno what
about this what about that you know it's
not that it's bad
what about maca what about this what
about that right it's like
maca doesn't fix anyone right and
here's the thing all these things that
come out whether it's niem oil
moringa maca whatever that comes out
right dear antler whatever somebody
throws out next right
collagen whatever people don't realize
it all comes from a place of
no one knew why anybody's sick and why
someone's suffering and struggling
that's the health realm
all through the years the reason why i
got all the connections that
have happened in my life and most
powerful people in the world reaching
out to me is because
what happened was people said he has an
answer
because there's there was never any
answers in the health realm right
and he has answers to why i have
mysterious tingles and numbness
he has answers to why i have this jaw
pain that won't go away
right it's a shingles virus nobody knew
that he had answers to why
people are struggling with burning skin
right
or chronic etis you know he had answers
that's he got answers right nobody had
the answers okay so
but at the same time in the health room
everybody health health world right
everybody throws out like try this try
that try this
this will help you green tea will help
you this will help you
help you with what really with what
because nobody knows why anybody's
sick it's either people think it's your
genes or your body's attacking itself
or you you're making it up and you're
lying or
you're seeking out attention right
nobody knows why anybody was sick okay
um astrid said i thought maca is for
fertility
um then that's made up that's just made
up
there's no scientific study that could
definitively show
that maca can help with fertility right
there just isn't astrid so that's just
made up and that's what happens maca
maca came out during a time where where
anybody
looking for cool things neither you
needed a cool
name and it always took off you just
need a cool name like maka took off
because people were like maka what's
maka maka maka maka
everybody's like oh my god put it here
put it there same thing with neem oil
it's like neem oil
neem neem all through the internet
and then you know that's how it works
right but neem oil
doesn't fix your multiple sclerosis
lupus fibromyalgia ra
lyme disease aches and pains tingles and
numbness ringing in the ears depression
anxiety see
see how it works maca doesn't either so
it's like
if you want somebody to get better it
can't be
trendy things so to speak it has to be
something that actually works
and then when it finally works then it
takes off right
but maca took off because of money
money right there was no money in celery
juice
it was people actually healing okay and
that's why it still survives today
because there's not one dollar into
a massive campaign that celery juice is
something you need to do
not one dollar right and so and
it's out there healing people and
changing lives
because it works because celery works
it's in you know but maca never changed
any lives
but maca had millions of dollars behind
it
to convince people it's something you
should buy
right kombucha tea millions of dollars
in advertising to convince every yoga
mama they should be
on it right but it doesn't do anything
so you can still be a sick yoga mama
trying to go to yoga class
with fibro and aches and pains and
fatigue but
maca or kombucha tea aren't gonna fix it
see how it works
but the millions of dollars behind these
things the millions of dollars behind
collagen the millions of dollars behind
these things
is it's it's all like it's basically a
fake out
smoke and mirrors and it's bait and
switch it's constantly like this right
celery juice has all the odds stacked
against it
every the media trying to stop it every
single
in the health world tries to clobber the
crap out of it because it makes nobody
money it just heals people
and so it's end in medical mediums the
originator so that doesn't help all on
its own
because people just get all bent out of
shape about that alone right
but celery juice lives on its own
because it heals and heals and heals and
heals and saves lives and changes lives
and
moves people forward right with no money
can you imagine
if you put the money that was behind
kombucha tea and the money behind
probiotics and the money behind any of
this stuff right
in maca whatever if you put that kind of
money behind celery juice
not only would there be like 500 million
people drinking it right now
naturally around the world because it
works but you'd have six
billion people drinking it if five
billion people drinking it
it's just it's just it's incredible how
it works um let's make the sauce right
now you guys
i got a food processor right here just
going to flip this around
it's kind of a chill day we're just
we're talking about some cool things
guys you think it'd help if i can plug
this in
so which i'm gonna do
[Music]
so what i'm gonna do is get a little
extension cord in a second and plug this
food processor in so that's what i was
saying your stomach is designed to
handle poison
but only certain amounts of poison to a
certain degree
the stomach can buffer but other than
that we still get poisoned by things you
know
it's like it's like a dangerous poison
like cyanide right
if it goes into the stomach you'll live
a
half an hour longer or hour longer
than if it was put into an enema so
somebody put a dangerous dangerous
poison like cyanide in an enema you
would die
in seconds just set two seconds and
that's the difference if it went into
the stomach you'll be at the hospital
dying but you'll be a livestone that's
the difference in how the stomach works
so we'll go with a half cup
of chopped red bell pepper we're making
the hot sauce right now
so just taking out the center right
there there you go
put it over here
so i'm just going to chop this up
these are really sharp knives i'm
dealing with right now and like i said
before
be really careful with sharp knives
because you cut yourself real easily
um that's a massive mistake in the
culinary world would they say that dull
knives
cause more injuries that's not true
actually that's so not true
i've seen people chop their fingers off
with sharp knives
and and not get injured with in you know
with
with adult knife steak knives are
different
okay those are different that's a whole
nother story i'm talking about these
type of chopping knives let's put some
cherry tomatoes in here too
okay you can chop up the cherry tomatoes
pudding in there i'm just gonna throw
them right in
um third of a cup
see that that's probably it right there
there you go
nice cherry tomatoes okay um let's do a
clove of garlic
look you can do three cloves of garlic
you can do one clove of garlic
i'm gonna do one all right i'm making
the hot sauce the medical medium hot
sauce for this
this is the sweet potato tacos
so i'm gonna put one clove of garlic in
there
let's do that
all right so then put some lemon
in there some lemon juice in there too
let's see i got a lemon over here you
guys
nice okay and get some lemon juice in
here i think i'm gonna get a tiny
strainer real quick
so what i'm gonna do
i'm gonna look for that i think we're
down
anyway
here we go
so i'm going to put some lemon so this
is the hot sauce i'm making right here
you guys
so get that in there i'm gonna put some
lime juice in here too
let's cut a lime
that's not a lime that's actually juicy
enough
there we go some lime in here too so
making this hot
sauce while we're talking about some fun
stuff
you can do um a little less lime if you
want a lot i like more lime
there we go
put some raw honey in here you have the
option of maple syrup if you don't like
honey on any level
so you got the option of maple syrup
just move this over
so put some honey in here
all right and i'm going to put a hot
pepper
so i have a couple different hot peppers
here
i got these fresh super chilies i'm
gonna pop one in there
that's gonna be hot right there
let's go let's get this one here
i'm gonna get a plate
all right
so this is an incredible hot sauce i i
happen to make it a lot
people want to say what is what does aw
eat what is he eating what is he doing
you know and um
what i do is i make this hot sauce all
the time
that's what i do so we got a little bit
so that's my hot sauce so i'm gonna
plate these
tacos up so i'm gonna grab some nice big
leaves here
i think the hardest part about being
sick is not having an answer to why
you're sick
i think that's the hardest part right
so i'm getting these nice big leaves
here
so i'm making these tacos
so i put some leaves down so to start
with you see you guys see
okay and
now i'm gonna get the toasted
so i got these sweet potato beautiful
sweet potato pieces right here
these are these are incredible because
they are marinated remember you guys i
made that marinade
these are so good and i'm putting them
right in these little tacos
there we go and
put a couple more pieces here too
and you can put a little bit of that hot
sauce
there
let me get some green onion on there too
doing that
so let me put this in front of you guys
here
i've been in the mood to make some food
you know i i have lately it's it's just
like
it's it's actually really fun i'm going
to take the green parts of these
scallions
chop a little bit of it
a friend of mine said well that's all
you're doing is you're playing with food
i said well
what are you doing just eating out in
restaurants
during a plague
you know my friend said you're just
worried about food food food making food
food food i said that's funny because
you've been in and out of the hospital
for years with all kinds of problems i
said to a friend
right it's been in and out of the
hospital for years
and so okay i'm into food well you're in
the food too
you're you're picking all these dishes
in your restaurant every restaurant you
go to every minute
you're just all about food food food
he's like no you're about food food
i go that's kind of funny because i'm
scratching my head i said to my friend
no you're about food
you're wondering what restaurant you
want your palette to experience
like what restaurant dish what different
restaurant in the middle of a play
like right that's you're obsessed about
restaurants you're obsessed about people
serving you you know and that's the
other thing too so i told my friend
you're just obsessed about
people serving you yeah i like the
ambiance i like being served i'm like
yeah well
right anyway you guys this is a
beautiful dish right here so i got the
sweet potato tacos right here
um and what i like to do is put the
sauce right on there
okay
okay so that's what i like to do
is put it right on top like this
put a little bit over them
now you can put a lot more than that
but that's a dish right there i don't
know if you guys can see that
so and this is an incredible dish so i
like this one a lot so i eat it i eat it
a lot so
like every other day whatever
that's a great one it just there's
something about the taste of the sauce
with the sweet potato i like the purple
sweet potato that's the one i've been
using a lot lately you guys
it looks good right incredible
so the bottom line is look if you want
to heal you have to look out for like i
always say death by a thousand cuts the
pitfalls you got to worry about that
you got to not let people gaslight you
you have to you have to stay confident
right stay confident that you have the
answers
okay so confident that you know why
you're sick
number one that's a big part too if
you're if you're
if you're learning about medical medium
information then you're learning why you
actually are sick and what you've been
going through you know why you have
thyroiditis you want you know why you
have a thyroid nodule
you want you know why you have thyroid
cancer you know why you have etis and
bladder infections
right and you know why you have insomnia
and you know and hives you know why you
have hives
you know i have migraines you know why
your histamines are up
right you know why you're you you're
you've got food sensitivities and
chemical sensitivity so once you learn
these answers with medical medium
information
so it's it's it's not about being gaslit
anymore
so when the gas lighter comes by and
they just want to torch you
it's like no no i'm not buying that i'm
not buying that
i'm eating good for a reason i know what
to avoid
i know how to heal i know what to do i
know what supplements to do
too so that's another thing too you'll
be gas-lit in the supplement world
just so you know you guys in the
supplement world right
it is here's how it works in that world
all right
they're spending supplement companies
out there right they spend millions of
dollars
if they're not a mom and pop they spent
they spend
millions of dollars in advertising so
that it's shoved in your face
everywhere okay and they don't even have
a clue as to if you're why you're sick
or what you need to do
you know and so this is what people get
bombarded with out there robin says you
have the best recipes and should release
a cookbook
i am a naturopathic doctor and would buy
it and recommend it to my patients
thanks so much
um there's so many recipes in there i
put a cookbook
in all the books so just letting you
know so that's what i do
so there's an actual cookbook in all the
medical medium books
i've done that for a reason so that you
have it right there
inside the medical textbook too that's
the new addition right there
and there's 75 recipes in cleanse the
heel
okay so there's 75 recipes and cleanse
the heel which i don't know if you guys
can see that if i'm doing it this way
right incredible and that's inclined to
heel
and it's a cookbook 75 recipes i've
known people out there putting cookbooks
out and there's just
75 recipes 50 recipes in a cookbook
dr faun his books are four and one
thanks that's coming from a medical
doctor incredible
so guys i wanted to make some food with
you guys today i'm heading off to
instagram and i'm heading off to um
yeah instagram i'm gonna put clubhouse
back on let's do that
so yes i'm looking forward to it i'm
heading over there now i can't wait
i'll see you in what five minutes or
something let me just straighten out the
kitchen a little bit
and then we'll be back we'll be back on
there all right i love