today we're talking about teeth damaging
diets and we're making asparagus
sushi right here asparagus sushi I'm
excited about this right out of brain
saver
protocols what you'll see out there in
the world is everybody in the dental
chairs they're in the dentist offices
they're getting their teeth drilled
they're getting root canals cavities
filled they gum disease they're getting
that plaque ripped out right all that
plaque ripped out they're doing all that
too it's another thing
happening everybody's going in there and
they dread it they dread getting the
under the gum plaque ripped up it's
awful scrape scrape scrape scrape we're
going to numb you up here we'll do a
whole bunch of numbing agents scrape
scrape scrape scrape scrape that's a
painful process so many people are up
against that and then of course they get
root canals they get all kinds of
different things
see they have problems with their nerves
and their teeth they have pain that's
not even Dental caused but either way
people get a lot of root canals they
have a lot of problems with their Dentin
we're going to cover a little bit about
that all on its own we're also making a
sparga sushi but we're going into the
teeth big time and I'm proud to say I'm
going to say it right here every single
one of my teeth are mine they are not
implants every single one of
them that's key to know because people
are going to be probably wondering what
about his deep what about his deep it's
one thing the other thing right I don't
have one root canal not one root canal
important right there another thing too
aw doesn't have any gum disease on any
level not even the basic gum disease
that people have not one gum
disease and number three not one
organic cavity which is critical for
people to know how come how come aw
doesn't have all of that like what's
going on wonder wonder because I stay
away from teeth damaging diets it's one
thing too so we're going to talk about
also when you come into this world as a
child and you're severely Trace mineral
deficient and filled with a lot of heavy
metals because it's passed down from the
parents how teeth can become a problem
very early on with so many kids all the
way going into teenager and and young
adult and so forth how many teeth
problems so many people can have and
we're also going to cover how our teeth
just start to fall apart we don't see it
yet we don't know what's happening but
deep inside our teeth are starting to
fall apart we don't know and our acidic
diets are actually draining the calcium
from our teeth and then out of nowhere
they fall apart when they fall apart
they are time capsules that means you
want to start a new diet that's really
special and great and your teeth start
falling apart right away within the
first week or month or the first few
months your teeth were going to fall
apart anyway because it took years for
them to fall apart and this is Inc
incredible information we're covering
get ready for this one you may like what
you hear you may not like what you hear
and we're also going to be doing the
medical M cooking show today which is
cool too cuz I'm making some really
really badass Nory rolls the asparagus
ones I got
cauliflower as the rice I got my pan
ready so let's give a run now you guys I
don't know if you guys have the
ingredients at your house right now
maybe you do maybe you can make a Nori
roll that maybe you don't have
everything here but quick rundown we got
the cauliflower that's going to be the
cauliflower rice we got the
scallions onion scallions from my Garden
I'm I'm actually proud of those those
are really good they're sharp though
they got an edge to them they really
they got the garlic ginger right there
hot cayenne peppers for my garden we're
going to use that in some of the dipping
sauce we got the radishes I love the
radishes whoa that one almost got away
from me and we have the asparagus which
is lightly steamed asparagus is lightly
steamed it's not steamed to death but
yet it's actually a little softer I like
it that way for rolling up so it doesn't
tear apart the Nory sheet the Nory roll
right that's there I got my limes you
might not be able to see in the bowl
right here and of course I have my
oranges as well so I got those as well
so I'm excited I might even have
something else that I'm using here I got
some honey over here whole bunch of
other stuff so let's get into some teeth
talk and then we're going to do some
cooking we're going to make the
asparagus sushi
roll right here and I want to show you
that one more time if you guys are okay
with that are you guys okay with that
there here we go it's out of brainsaver
protocols okay am I allowed to show my
book am I allowed to show my book is
that
okay someone's like he just shows his
book he just wants to show his book uh
okay life saving books yes I do I would
like to show the book is that if that's
okay do I get permission let's go we got
a lot to talk about I'm excited and I
know not you guys you guys are cool with
it I know you guys are cool with that
every now and then you'll get somebody
that does that all right let's roll into
it teeth destroying I like using that
word with this situation because it gets
that bad number one thing you got to
worry about right here probably one of
the number one things there's a bunch of
them what you see right here is vinegar
okay different vinegars I got the white
vinegar I got the vinegar that has a
darker color I don't care if it's apple
cider vinegar I don't care if it's
vinegar from planet Mars I don't care if
it's vinegar from planet Pluto I I don't
care if it's vinegar from somebody's own
backyard I don't care if it's red wine
balsamic I don't care what it is where
it comes from I don't care if a monkey
in a tree in Costa Rica made the vinegar
I don't care if someone pressed the
apples themselves in their basement
somewhere in the bush and made the
vinegar and I don't care if it's the
finest vinegar in Italy on a trip to
Europe I always feel better when I go to
Europe I'm always feeling better when I
go there how come everybody in Europe
though are sick sick sick sick and
they're eating the food too reason why I
must be feeling better when I go to
Europe is because it's a vacation I'm
not so stressed out and I'm happy to get
out of the states for a little while and
I could go on my little tour and I could
be yeah exactly anyway we're going to
cover that another day that's a big
topic the point is I don't care if the
vinegar comes from Grease it comes from
Italy I don't care what kind it's going
to slowly destroy your teeth I can say
it over and over and over again until
I'm blue in the face like blue in the
face because people don't realize is
vinegar not just wears away the enamel
so you can stick a straw in something
and drink it thinking it's not going to
hit the enamel but that's not the
problem the vinegar goes in deep and
causes a Calcium deficiency meaning it
draws calcium every time you use vinegar
anywhere anyhow you're pulling calcium
from your teeth
yes and over time this gets worse and
worse meaning the effects happen each
year you don't even know it you might
not be aware of it and then and the
dentist doesn't even see it too doesn't
even see deep down in the tooth deep
down in the Dentin what's happening cuz
that's important right there so let's go
and let's talk about that a little bit
down into the Dentin of the
tooth it starts there
that's where it starts in the Dentin
critical to know you do the vinegar and
then the vinegar eats away the inside
out not just from the outside the inside
out probably one of the most important
things to learn if you're trying to
protect your teeth now I don't have root
canals I don't have teeth problems I
don't have gum disease and I have all my
original teeth I don't have in plants
and I've never gotten veneers I don't go
and get professional whitenings okay I'm
not a supermodel supermodels get
professional whitenings like once a
month I get it that's what they do
they're getting veneers they're getting
dental work left and right they're
getting implants they're getting
whitenings I understand that's what
people do and people in the public eye
do that too I don't do anything for my
teeth to be in the public eye I just
want to make that clear to anybody
that's here here I protect my Dentin and
protect my teeth by not
doing one of the things that people do
every single day every salsa they have
every condiment every relish every
pickled this pickled that every little
thing that has vinegar in it from
mayonnaise to you name it they're doing
vinegar every single day you might be
one of the people that I don't want any
restrictions I can't have restriction I
want to eat what I want forget medical
meat restrictions I'm going to have all
the vinegar I want oh my teeth are
falling apart 2 years later 3 years
later my teeth are falling apart during
that medical medium but I don't want to
let go of my vinegars no way I'm going
to make sure it's in all my condiments
and all my Salsas and all my dishes and
all my salads and people pay the price
so vinegar is one thing right there so
let's go a little deeper into it how
does it work the minute that vinegar
touches your mouth inside goes right
inside
there's a call for calcium your body
goes into freakout mode it's like
calcium where are you calcium where are
you instantly because it's acetic acid
send me the red wine vinegar the Apple
Ceta vinegar whatever kind you want the
minute it goes into your mouth your body
screaming an alarm Bell that alarm Bell
is calcium calcium the vinegar is acetic
acid it's going to create it's going to
create a problem it's going to burn the
body internally I'm not talking about
outside use there's there's uses for
vinegar on the outside of the body
periodically I'm talking about
internally so there's a call for calcium
it's kind of like when a fire starts in
a building and the fire department's
called and the fire department comes out
and they're freaking out and they're
bringing out their hoses and they're
trying to save lives and they're trying
to die out the fire what's happening is
your body is freaking out the minute
that acetic acid that vinegar enters
into your
mouth your body's calling for the fire
hose it's calling for the calcium fire
hose is what it's calling
for and that calcium fire hose is your
calcium storage bins so any kind of
calcium you got in your bloodstream
instantly gone instantly gone so what
happens with people don't
realize and this is an important thing
to know right off right off the start
here okay we have calcium floating
around the
bloodstream we have calcium that's
circulating around the bloodstream just
from the things you eat on a daily basis
cuz a little bit of calcium in almost
everything if you're a meat eater
there's a little touch of calcium in the
meat chicken eater there a little touch
of calcium in the chicken it's not much
but it's there if you eat a vegetable
there some calcium in there if you eat
an orange lots of calcium there's
calcium in the foods you're eating that
calcium is floating around your
bloodstream you might be somebody that
takes a calcium supplement maybe you got
some of that floating around your
bloodstream that's not exactly the same
but the point is is we have calcium from
the foods we eat that are floating
around our bloodstream and guess what
happens the minute you drop in that
acetic acid right off the running that
calcium is used up fast it's used up
that hour that hour I'm going to take my
apple cider vinegar shots because I
heard on Tik Tock it's a great thing to
do let me go keep doing it there and
then you're losing all of your calcium
that's in your bloodstream in that
moment and not only do you lose the
calcium that's in the bloodstream in
that moment but you start losing calcium
out of the bones and teeth you guys in
that
moment not next
year in that moment you're losing
calcium out of your bones and
teeth calcium is there to neutralize the
AC IC acid it doesn't do a great
job but the calcium's there to
neutralize the acetic acid so your bones
and teeth don't fall apart too quick but
they still fall apart over time let's go
into drum
roll we
got
chocolate we
caffeine
caffeina we got
chocolate Okay caffeine that's a big one
that hurts the teeth too teeth
destroying diets well I'm on this great
diet it's really good it's this keto
diet it's really cool it's a keto diet
it's got some it's got a little bit of
fruit and some lots of vegetables in
there it's good yeah know I have my
cacao I do have my cow I really like it
and that's good there I do have my
chocolate that's in my diet you know you
got to have balance you got to have
moderation and
balance but your teeth are going to
suffer they just are I'm not trying to
just be like you guys look I want to
make your lives miserable today I want
to tell you about caffeine and chocolate
cuz you guys are most most everybody's
on it I'm sure some of you guys aren't
right but I just think it's this if you
know what causes teeth problems and you
learn and you still do it I don't know
what to say just when the teeth are
falling apart and you're getting more
root canals and you're getting more
teeth work and more cavities filled and
your gums are getting that plaque
underneath the
teeth just
know some of the causes to begin with
okay so a lot of people think
chocolate's healthy chocolate's good for
you because we're taught that we're high
on chocolate we're high in the caffeine
life's hard we need that rush we need
that coffee we need that CA c in there
coffee is so acidic it's another teeth
destroyer from the inside out so when it
comes down to coffee it's a little
different than acetic acid coffee
happens to be extremely acidic what it
does is it kills those those um adrenal
glands it kills your stomach glands it
starts to actually cause problems
deficits in those glands your adrenal
glands and your stomach glands both
those believe it or not do help and
protect your teeth over time but what we
do is we drink coffee every single day
not only is the cdic nature of coffee
really harsh on enamel do you ever hear
about coffee stains right coffee stains
coffee stains are different than if you
eat a whole thing of
blueberries blueberries that's a pigment
that's anthocyan in that gets into the
teeth sometimes you're eating a hole
you're eating all these blueberries
right blueberries blueberries
blueberries that's different than coffee
stains coffee stains coffee stains what
you'll notice today in today's world is
a lot different than back in the 80s in
the 70s and '90s where everybody's teeth
were just
yellow just yellow you see people on
talk shows in the 1980s their teeth were
all
yellow even they they're using white
strips everybody had white strips in
their mouth everybody in the
professional you know public figure
Arena all had white stripss their mouth
every single day they did they were
living on White Strips on their teeth
but their teeth were all yellow you see
a
concert even like you see a you you see
a theater or concert program and you see
people in the front in the 1980s and you
see them all their teeth are just
doesn't matter what age they were 25
years old 28 years old 32 years old
their teeth were just all
yellow right so we're in a place where
there's so many cosmetic approaches es
on teeth between veneers and whitening
strategies that people have and getting
you know implants and so forth and
Replacements and everything else so all
of that is kind of like putting that old
Decor of what happened years ago and
yester year with
teeth okay but if you go back and you
see some old footage and you're just
like everybody's smiling laughing you go
back to an old Oscars back in the 1979
and you see footage of like the Oscars
in 79
1985 all the celebrities her teeth are
all
yellow that's what it was like back then
right before what we have now out
there but it doesn't change what's
happening inside of the teeth it doesn't
change what's happening inside the
Denton it does not change what's
happening inside the
enamel so right now we're in the world
just like the world of the past we're in
the teeth destroying world the only
difference is we're probably doing even
more vinegar cuz we're doing more apple
cider vinegar probably doing more
caffeine than we ever did 20 30 40 years
ago and decaf coffee is in the same
league it just has a little less
caffeine a little less caffeine and
guess what the crazy things most decaf
drinkers maybe not you but most decaf
drinkers drink more of
it they drink more of it they supersede
someone else who has a little bit higher
caffeine in a cup of coffee a decaf
Drinker would be like I'm going to drink
four
today because I can because it's less
caffeine so they drink four cups of
coffee when someone else is drinking one
to two cups a day with the higher amount
person drinks four or five of the
decaffinated is like surpassing the
person with the not decaffinated right
caffeinated right so here we go people
drink matcha they drink tea they drink
soda they drink energy drinks they they
drink all those things too getting all
the caffeine with that but
decaf still is a problem very important
to know I want to go into like root
canals a little bit too in this episode
I'm going to cook for us in a little bit
if you guys just got here we're doing
asparagus Sushi is what we're doing I'm
excited about this Claudia Draper yep my
teeth were all yellow and same with
everyone else I knew that was the world
of yester year
so Amanda says that's amazing my dad is
losing his teeth they're just falling
apart it's like a time capsule is what
it is it's time capsule a time capsule
that just starts to ring the bell it's
kind of like on the ranch everybody's
working out there right everybody gets
hungry it's lunchtime ding ding ding
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding time to eat lunch ding ding ding
ding
the alarm goes off and what happens over
time the alarm goes off and the teeth
just start falling apart different areas
of the mouth too sometimes it's a
certain area of the mouth versus
another and sometimes it's everywhere in
the mouth starts you just falling apart
like
crazy
everywhere important to know so let's go
into bacteria a little bit so that's the
next thing we want to do
it's okay
bacteria you have to have bacteria to
have a
cavity you have to have
bacteria to have gum
disease you got to have
bacteria to have you guessed it root
canals well infected abscess
Roots
bacteria and at leads us to the next
place how does bacteria somehow get down
in there deep when there isn't cavities
and then where when there are cavities
and so forth but how do we get bacteria
down there deep in the roots because of
our immune system our immune system is
struggling we got zinc deficiencies
Galore zinc deficiencies are rampant all
around the world everywhere and that's a
problem all on its
own our immune systems are
compromised therefore we get in trouble
with teeth problems the more viruses we
have in our
life the more
bacteria the weaker the immune
system autoimmune so forth neurological
problems usually people with multiple
sceris suffer with their teeth the most
usually not every exact person there
reasons why there's different situations
versus how many heavy metals somebody
has how many toxic heavy metals and so
forth and different toxins with
viruses but the point is compromised
immune system leads to the bacteria
frenzy in the
mouth that's why the medical medium
information which I proudly
follow which at my age I have all my
teeth and no
problems which no implants no veneers no
root canals you name
it
right the goal is like when I take care
of myself the best I can because
honestly I'm not perfect at taking care
of myself at
all but I try my best in the sense where
I work myself to the Bone I burn the
candle at four ends I drive myself into
the ground I wouldn't recommend that for
anybody it's a bad
habit s and I started from the beginning
so so here's the thing okay when we get
a compromised immune system and our
immune system gets weakened we get more
teeth problems because we have an immune
system that's struggling it's trying to
fight and battle different things like
viruses and bacteria a lot of people
have multiple varieties of strep and
they have viruses like hhv6 and shingles
and Epstein bar even if they just have
an Epstein bar that's causing problems
their immune system cannot keep a tight
watch on the teeth and the gum so the
immune system cannot keep a really close
tight watch on the gums your immune
cells want to capture viruses and
bacteria on the gum line inside the gums
and behind the teeth in the
jaw our immune system wants to capture
Invaders pathogens viruses bacteria but
our immune systems are usually dealing
with other problems
other things that we're actually having
inside our body our immune systems
dealing with a lot of different viruses
and
bacteria people who have simplex one
Simplex 2 different varieties of epine
bar cyega virus is a pain in the butt
and a lot of shingles viruses these are
the autoimmune plague that's the
autoimmune plague aroni is all those
different bugs and
pathogens and so our immune system is
really busy on trying to protect us with
all that and at the same time our immune
system can't go and then take care of
the teeth and gums it can't go and take
care of everything here it just can't
our immune system wants to help it wants
to take care of things but it just can't
cover every single tooth in every part
of your gum there's no way it can only
get some of it at different times some
of it at different times so taking care
of our immune system is critical
learning why we're sick is critical it
protects our teeth and then if you got
somebody who's compromised and they're
chronically sick you guys they're also
doing chocolate they got the caffeine
cranking in their system chocolate wears
away your calcium reserves chocolate's
another thing that breaks down your
calcium
reserves it breaks down your immune
system I can't tell you how many time
over how many times over the years
helping out people all these decades did
I see when someone went on a chocolate
bin they broke out a week later with a
Simplex cold sore fever blister
chocolate binge fever blister if they
didn't have herpy simplex one chocolate
binge Simplex 2 if if that's what they
had
PS in the genitals area right if they
didn't have that chocolate binge okay so
chocolate binge and
then a a flare for Epstein bar chocolate
binge and then a new bout of mono
chocolate
binge and then an abscess in the tooth
jaw starts to
hurt chocolate
binge and then catching an STD
easily when they probably wouldn't have
really caught it cuz their immune system
would have pulverized Gara would have
pulverized the clap would have
pulverized it there means system didn't
pulverize
it so now they got
chlamidia they got chlamydia and their
immune system can't keep up with the
chlamydia they just contracted in a
relationship because their immune
systems bombarded by chocolate binge and
stuff like that and other
things the point is is that our immune
system can only do so much when we tip
the scale and death by a Thousand Cuts
and we push things over The Edge it's
not our fault it's nobody's fault it's a
hard World hard
life but there's a real reason why
people's teeth just start falling apart
over time we have a lot of compromises
our immune system is actually looking
out for so let's go into root canals a
touch
vegans are in the
dentist but so are animal protein people
if I hear one more
time that a vegan is going to be in the
dentist chair more that vegans need
dental work
more the next live we do I'm GNA ask
Samantha the the
dietician to come on and talk about that
topic the next time we're live I'm going
to have Samantha come on you guys know
you guys just met Samantha recently
she's going to come on and talk about
that like vegans and
dentist chairs and stuff like
that you know why people go vegan and go
plant-based because they got sick
outside of a handful of hippies that are
trying to protect animals which I
believe
in I believe in
immensely
outside of a few people that don't want
to actually drink C's milk because of
you know they're worried about the abuse
on the cow don't eat meat cuz they don't
want to kill the cow cuz cow has a soul
we know that right and this isn't a
vegan Channel propaganda or animal
protein Channel propaganda I'm trying to
say something really important here
outside of a few vegans that decided to
go vegan because of a certain
belief outside of that vegans go vegan
because something's wrong with their
health and they get sick that's what
happens plant-based people go
plant-based because they get
sick
fact and
Truth vegans go vegan plantbased people
go macrobiotic people went macrobiotic
years ago because they got
sick pescatarians went pescatarian
because they got
sick what it means is if vegans are more
deficient and end up in a dentist chair
they were sick to be they were sick
animal protein
eaters doesn't mean animal animal
protein caused them to be sick they were
sick Pro animal protein eaters and this
is this is a Nuance it doesn't mean the
animal protein caused them to be sick
it's not what I'm trying to say I'm
saying they were already sick and they
were already sick animal protein eaters
they were already sick Animal product
eaters and they became vegan
vegetarian macrobiotic pescatarian
eating a few fish whatever it
is they became these things because
something was wrong something was wrong
unless it's some like hippie dude that's
like no killing animals is wrong I will
not I will eat soy and everything else
I'm going to be vegan unless it's
somebody like that everybody's going to
a different diet like that because
they're not
well and the bottom line is everybody's
in the dental chair everybody's at the
dentist office everybody's getting
drilled everybody has a problem with
their teeth at one time or another one
way or another and the roots of the
teeth problems or mineral deficiencies
that I'm talking about like the Calcium
deficiency from it being leaked from our
bones and
teeth along with coming into this world
with immune system issues and
deficiencies Along With viral issues to
like pathogens and so forth along with
toxic heavy metals Mercury is like the
teeth Destroyer I'm not talking about
just Mercury amalgams I'm talking about
Mercury in our body in our bloodstream
or Mercury in our organs and not even in
our bloodstream Mercury and our organs
which is a medical medium piece of
information all on its
own Mercury actually in organs
undetected that's medical medium
originally and then Mercury in our bones
which is which is medical medium to
information I have to say that because
you be like oh I heard that before it
comes from mm info so you know where the
source is but the bottom line is you
guys I'm trying to say
something something that's really really
important is that there are so many
different angles we can do to protect
your teeth down from the basic First
Fundamental options right down to going
as far as we want to protect our teeth
and the first thing I would tell anybody
right off the running hey a w I want to
I want to keep my teeth I want I don't
want teeth problems every minute I want
my my teeth would be okay boom vinegar
gone boom chocolate boom gone
woo just gone coffee Bing
gone that's just a few things right off
the running then I would go even deeper
than
that deeper than that eggs boom gone
because the eggs are going to feed all
the viruses in your body and that's
going to compromise your immune system
and when that compromises your immune
system who's going to be watching over
your teeth and that's another thing oh
and its own I was talking about before
who is going to be watching over your
teeth when your body your immune system
is watching over
pathogens pathogens that are feeding off
of eggs and dairy products and
gluten next thing IID tell people is get
rid of the
gluten not because the person's
sensitive or not to gluten that's not
what it would be no you want teeth
problems to be gone someday or you want
them slowed down and you want them
halted you also get rid rid of gluten
too cuz gluten is going to feed bacteria
guess what that bacteria that sits in
there eating away your root in your
teeth feeds off of
gluten so there's your root right there
you see it you guys see your root we're
going to do we're going to do a
procedure right here hi I'm I'm the
dentist here uh I'm filling in for your
dentist yeah I'm here I'm a
yeah I'm only here for a day say take a
seat I'm going to cut this root right
out here for
you anyway the point is is those roots
right there that people get bacteria in
and around love to feed off of gluten
love to feed off of gluten these are
just some of the really powerful tidbits
to actually show you guys a lot of
people get
staining with their
enamel it's not just their enamel
wearing down but they get stained right
like I said 20 30 40 years ago
everybody's teeth were yellow just
yellow college kids their teeth were
yellow high school kids their teeth were
yellow it's rare you ever ever ever will
know college student with yellow teeth
anymore I'm sure there's some but it's
rare they'll go to their dentist they'll
do whatever it takes to make
sure right they'll use whatever
procedures they possibly can that did
not exist before back in the 80s and
90s but yeah everybody's teeth get
stained as well from all their different
habits and then smoking that's another I
got to tell you something interesting
right
so what are the top three things that
cause dental
problems like you'll hear out there
there was a dentist out there pretty
recently it was just like well tearing
open envelopes with your
teeth tearing open EV envelopes the
dentist didn't say about calcium
depletion because of vinegar the dentist
didn't say anything about minerals Trace
mineral
deficiencies zinc deficiencies the
dentist didn't say anything about
pathogens and viruses the dentist is
like tearing open envelopes with your
teeth so doing that that's like tearing
open envelopes that's a really good one
right there it's like it's like um I am
a dentist the top the top three the top
five things you should avoid with your
teeth one is try not to tear open open
the envelopes you're going to ruin your
teeth the second one is don't pop open B
bottles with your teeth try not to pop
open lids and Bottles your teeth I swear
to God I swear to God that's the advice
out there try not to break open bottles
with your teeth yeah cuz that's
something I do every day you guys break
open bottles at your teeth bottle caps
all day long is that what you guys do
you do that every day do you tear open
envelopes every day with your teeth how
many of you guys tear envelopes open I'm
sure somebody does but it's like the top
reasons that's not good for your teeth
all
right it's obviously not good for you to
pop open a bottle cap off a a beer
bottle with your teeth or a soda pop
bottle and it's not really smart to
actually open up a can a bear
can a bear can with your teeth and try
to rip it open
and it's not smart to tear open
envelopes or anything else with your
teeth it's a duh it's a duh but what
about the real reasons why people's
teeth are falling
out if I hear another time out there
that it's because of being vegan and
your teeth fall apart because you're
vegan that is so grossly
mistaken not only are vegans in the
dental chairs the dentist office so is
every single animal protein eater that's
a major
ignorance that is a major cross theboard
ignorance to actually think that
plant-based people or a vegan ends up in
a dental chair more than a meat eater
probably the dumbest thing I've heard
out there it's ignorance
pure it's sad but it's said constantly
out there over and over and over again
everybody everybody is getting their
teeth drilled and if they haven't
already they're going to because even if
someone seems indestructible they're
exercising they look like they're in
great shape they got it they're young
their teeth look good they're getting
they're going to their dentist I got all
my original teeth I'm 22 years old I'm
exercising I'm doing good uh it's all
going to fall apart later even if it
takes to their 39 years old and it just
starts to fall apart and crumble all
then fraction of the people on the
planet are vegan by the way or
plant-based a fraction it's a grain of
rice to a silo of rice a grain of rice
to a silo of rice meaning the grain of
rice is the vegan and The Silo of rice
are the Animal product
eaters and the reason why they're vegan
to begin with is because they have
symptoms and conditions in most cases
except for that random person that's
like you know what they're chopping down
the
rainforest they're doing all kinds of
stuff and I want to be vegan Jasmine
over there on YouTube says my teeth are
falling apart and I'm only 23 I had
cavities on almost all of my teeth by
the time I was 20 I got them all done
but now they're back
again I've seen this happen a lot over
the years with a lot of young people we
come into the world with a little bit
higher elevations of mercury into toxic
heavy metals I mean ask your dentist
what's right for you ask him what you
know he thinks but what I've said about
younger Generations having teeth
problems there's either immune system
issues where they're battling some
lowgrade pathogenic infections that
happens a lot they have an elevated
toxic heavy metal Reserve inside organs
that happens a lot too and they're Trace
mineral
deficient and they're extremely acidic
or
it didn't take well like the vinegar and
all the different things that they've
been actually eating in their foods from
meals out from eating out from when they
were like 5 6 7even years old of the
family and 10 years old and 15 years old
and you know and so forth and it was
just you know restaurant food's a big
one right there for actually taking
people out you can be somebody that's
plant-based and you're in the finest
plantbased restaurant you're in Europe
and you found this wicked bitching cool
plant-based restaurant and you're in
there and you're having vinegar and
everything else another thing is
fluoride treatments it is by far one of
the teeth destroyers of all is fluoride
treatments something that people don't
realize right is when they get a
fluoride treatment in the past it causes
damage in the future so a lot of
children get their fluoride treatments
and that fluoride treatment when you're
8 years old 9 years old 10 years old
means you're going to have teeth
problems when you're 20 25 30 and so
forth forth so fluoride treatments is a
big deal that's another one that eats
away at the enamel and also affects the
teeth from the inside out is
fluoride going to start cooking in a
minute you guys we're covering some
teeth stuff on its own healing single
over there in IG says I have a broken
tooth my dentist wants to pull and
replace with an implant I wonder if it's
worth it since tooth the tooth is in the
back
so I mean it look it all depends on what
your dentist wants to do if I ever had a
broken tooth in the
back you know I would I would avoid the
implant I would avoid it and try to seek
out every option possible also would
seek out a see a few different dentists
about the same topic that's what I would
do I'd go to this dentist I'd go to that
dentist I'd say okay what do you think
do I need to just do is there another
route I can do is it possible to fill it
is the tooth cracked all the way
through a root canal won't work a crown
won't be sufficient do I just need an
implant or I just pull the tooth these
are all questions that you have to kind
of obviously go along with with your
your
dentist or do you want to just pull the
tooth and let it heal up and you're
missing a tooth because you don't want
to implant so many things you know
there's so many options Divine Light
says Anthony what does Spirit say is it
okay to not go do anything anything to
cavities should we always go get them
fixed or is it fine to let them be the
only thing
is if you're battling pathogens your
immune system's compromised you got
bacteria in the mouth that's lit it's
lit right and that bacteria is working
on your teeth okay and you're taking
care of yourself and you're trying to
fix other problems it's hard sometimes
to get the
teeth up to par fast enough so you got
to keep an eye on the cavities that's
what I would do to keep an eye on them
if they start they start doing more they
start getting away from us then that's
another story so you might want to keep
on it that way but if it doesn't look
like it's getting away from us that's
another story I mean I have friends that
they have cavities and stuff and they
don't do anything with them because
you're not getting away from them but
there's different ways of handling it as
you're building up your immune system as
you're cleaning things out as you're
avoiding all the bad stuff and the
vinegars and everything else you're
building up your calcium reserves in
your teeth you're doing all that
cavities start going away for a lot of
people what I've noticed medical mem
information I've seen over the years so
many people get rid of cavities your
cavities just healed right up in their
mouths I have friends where they did mm
really good like you know there's people
that do mm there's people that do mm
there people that do a little bit of mm
fly on the wall you know like fly on the
wall and you're like whoa why is that
person doing this whoa why is that
person doing Zite that'll really mess
them up why is that person doing that
why is the person doing dite clay that's
not going to be good for them why is
that person doing Pearl powder that's
going to really rip their intestinal
track apart so it's like you're seeing
all the things they're doing why is that
person doing sodium bicarbonate why is
that person taking so much like crappy
powders that have all these agents in
them like you see all these things and
why is that person eating this why are
they eating that and then you know you
know you know as all that's happening in
there and they having all these problems
problems are going to develop and
everything but then there's people who
do who and they'll do a little bit of mm
they'll do some celery juice to do a
little of this maybe do the heavy metal
detox once in a while but they don't
really do mm a lot they don't do a lot
of mm their teeth start falling apart
later and the easiest claim is like it's
got to be mm that did it it's got to be
that celery juice meanwhile what they
were doing and what they had going on
was like whoa that's not mm oh that's
not mm you walk into their house and you
go through their cupboards and you're
like that's not mm that's not mm that's
that's got natural flavors no way that
stuff is terrible for the gut that
stuff's bad for your immune system it's
just you wouldn't believe what you would
see in people's
houses and then someone who's doing
really good solid mm and they're working
hard man they freaking cavities healing
so many
people a lot of people are not eating
enough greens and mm is about getting
the spinach soup in you that 28 day
cleanse spinach soup one of those
incredible spinach soups medical medium
not eating enough greens not a lot of
people stay low fat enough they're
eating so much fats bacteria is
proliferating let's go into that real
quick that's a good one
okay all right stomach and ol liver
right here in my
hand right A lot of people are eating so
much fat they're blowing out their
livers high fat diets every single day
they can't stay away from the fat they
can't even back it down a little bit
even if they're like intermittent
fasting or something like that which
isn't medical medium even if they're
intermittent fasting and by the end of
the day they eat one meal they blow it
out usually with a lot of fat so many
people cheese butter eggs meat chicken
too much avocado too much too much nuts
too much seeds too much though too much
chocolate too many oils and they're just
blowing too much oil and they're blowing
out their liver and their their stomach
right and when they're when they're
dealing with that what happens is their
immune system can't keep track of the
bacteria
the bacteria starts to get out of
control and when that bacteria starts
getting out of control we get gum
problems we get you know abscesses we
get teeth problems we get all kinds of
issues with
cavities you can't control the bacteria
in your mouth that's sitting on a cavity
or creating a cavity should I
say when we're dumping in so much fat in
our diet so there's a lot of people that
do medical medium to some degree but
they still pound the fats because they
go somewhere else and they hear fats are
so good for you you should be on lots of
fats and now they're on lots of fats but
they still like medical medium stuff and
then there's people that are just like
they're just they're dabbling in medical
medium but their teeth just start over
the years falling apart but they love
the medical medium stuff they might like
what I do and they're just like my teeth
aw and it's like dude you've been
killing it high fat for months and years
you had like one loow fat
week you've had like you're not doing
leafy greens you're not doing the
spinach soups you're not staying really
strong on the celery and you're not
doing any of the supplemental protocols
with the right stuff and yeah of course
something might go wrong in tip because
you're bringing all this you're still
eating chocolate you're still doing your
Apple CER vinegar and you're still doing
whatever it's just really really
difficult not judging anybody at all I'm
happy you're here and if you even drink
a sip of celery juice God bless you and
be here that's great if you want to
watch me dance around and make a meal
I'm here and I can do it I could be your
monkey it's not a problem and if you're
just doing one little thing I'm happy
Ivon says for the past three and a half
years my teeth are more luminous with
medical Med protocols which happens when
you're
solid with you know JS says dentists
always talk about how strong my teeth
are boom I know it's thanks to celery
juice lemon water lemon water is
incredible for the teeth in all the
fruits and veggies thank God for mm info
this is a lime right
here but
lemons and limes lemons are amazing for
the teeth when you hear dentists or
anybody say it's a lemon water don't do
lemon water who and
what is that why everybody has teeth
problems it's lemons because you know
I'm scratching my head here and I'm like
nobody eats lemons how much lemon is in
their diet
that's insane people have been in
dentist chairs for centuries is it all
the
lemon the last I knew is that Sailors on
the ocean for a year had scurvy and
their teeth rotted out of their heads
because they didn't have one lemon on
the
boat one lemon on the ship on a
year-long journey a 6mon journey out
there in the ocean over out there in the
seas and their teeth just Rott it
the last I've learned scurvy rotting
teeth from no
lemon I mean when you really add it up
and you think about it you're just like
what the heck lemon tree sends Roots
deep into the Earth deep into the Earth
grabbing onto alkaline minerals like
calcium lemon tree goes deep into the
Earth and starts to draw out
all those alkaline incredible minerals
like
calcium and yeah gets into the lemon you
squeeze that lemon water lemon doesn't
erode enamel if that's the case I
wouldn't have a tooth in my freaking
Mouth left there wouldn't be a tooth in
my
mouth I wouldn't have a tooth left I
have all my teeth my teeth no root
canals no nothing I have good teeth
right all the lemons I used to eat
lemons straight I can't really eat them
straight anymore you guys have to be
honest I drink lemon water and I put
lemon on everything but I I used to eat
the lemons I used to bite into them I
used to rub my teeth and gums into the
lemon would open the lemon and just like
just literally like like a animal I
would just like go into the lemon I did
that for years why do I have teeth they
should be gone by all means jenier here
says I always get an A+ at the dentist
they say it's like cleaning baby
teeth
amazing gum recession be careful not to
brush your gums off your
skull let's go into that real
quick I have to make I have to make a
five course meal for you guys in a
minute okay I got the pan getting hot
right now let's keep it away from the
ice cream I got the food processor there
I'm making cauliflower rice okay be you
you can brush your
[Music]
teeth okay you can brush your
gums
okay hold on here hold
on can brush your teeth and brush your
gums
okay was upside
down right
but you don't want
to
brush your gums right out of your
head that's a medical medium tip don't
be afraid to brush don't be afraid to
brush your gums but I see people out
there that are brushing the crap out of
their gums you're like like brushing
their gums and I'm like dude don't brush
your gums out of your skull it's very
important to know okay but yes get them
get in there good and brush your gums
good definitely don't be afraid to this
isn't fear about brushing your teeth or
gums it's not it I know the trolls would
be like fear fear fear medical medium
fear but it's not that it's you just
don't but I've seen people go freaking
nuts and and really go really crazy
right you don't have to do that cussy
it's says my teeth my teeth are starting
my teeth started covering with black
stain what can cause that so black stain
on some people's
teeth okay so a lot of things to keep in
mind okay um if no one did anything
cosmetic to their teeth in today in 2000
and whatever we are
now if no one did anything you would see
black black teeth Brown
teeth dark yellow teeth you would just
see the
craziest colors of teeth like if if a
choir was singing you would see like
brown Teeth did you ever see that like
old like 1970 Choir in the 1970s in a
video there's all different ages in the
choir and it's like brown
teeth you see all kinds of different
colors but a lot of people their teeth
will stay in a certain color it'll start
getting you know like a little darker
stains some people get lighter stains
they'll get different
stains there's nothing wrong going to
your
dentist and getting you know getting you
know maybe get your teeth a little you
know buffered out or something if
they're really
stained you don't want to also sit there
with things in your mouth that will
stain like you don't want to sit there
stain chocolate stains the freck out of
people's teeth chocolate does you see
that right
there chocolate does so much
staining I don't do anything for my
teeth I don't use
whiteners I don't get like cosmetic
dentist stuff done I'm I'm not like out
there doing
it I like leafy greens that's incredible
for
teeth I don't like really too many
toothpastes out there in the market but
you got to use what you got to use
nothing's
perfect
anyway all right let's let's let's let's
get let's get going I got a whole meal
to make you I got Nory rolls to make you
I got to have I have to have it down
today cuz I got like a lot here and a
lot going on let's get on to it now
let's chop an onion real quick here so
I'm going to do an onion I'm going to
saute in this pan I'm going to give it a
quick
chop if you guys don't mind my my eyes
might
tear is that a sign of something
bad just wondering okay so I'm going to
saut these onions I'm chopping them up
small for this not using any big pieces
in here I'm making cauliflower rice if
you want to know
okay and I'm going to
put some garlic in there
too okay there we
go let's go in the
pan nice and sizzly hot look at
that you guys I'll do like a part two
just not like right the second but
there's there's more to talk about with
the teeth but this is going to be like a
4our live
all right let's chop up these
onions and we'll get some closeups
eventually listen to my Teeth podcast
medical meem podcast at Apple podcast
right okay let's get some onions on
here
okay onions on the pan guys are okay
with
that okay let's get some garlic on the
pan Karen says I've been traumatized by
Dentistry as many have with much of
alpath so as much as you've had been
traumatized with Al apathic medicine
let's get some garlic on the board you
guys okay with this all right oh
remember this
remember okay if you ever crushed garlic
sharp blade going out see see the sharp
blade it's going out never crush garlic
with the sharp blade going in I have to
remind you guys because it happens all
the time out there you do it this way
the the knife naturally flips up like
this when you're doing it that way and
you're going to go like this you ready I
got garlic under here you're going to go
like
this boom
ah bad you got to have it go out very
important beatric
says that some people get problems with
their teeth with the medical medum diet
and others have great teeth could it be
due to the quality of the teeth when
they were formed while lying in the
mother's
womb well first of all you don't know
what they're actually doing a lot of
people do medical Medium say they do
medical medium and they really weren't
doing a lot of medical medium they were
doing teeth destroy in their diet they
had a lot of teeth destroyers in their
diet they had a lot of mineral
deficiency problems because of what
they're eating and doing they had a lot
you know a lot of other problems going
on that we covered in this whole episode
keep that in mind so it's it's hard to
say because I've heard people say
they've done medical medium it's caused
teeth problems and I know for a fact
through
evidence that they weren't doing medical
media breaks my heart
they were dabbling in medical
medium they were dabbling in medical
medium I'm not judging anybody for
dabbling in medical
medium I'm happy to have dabblers here I
want dabblers here just try not to blame
the wrong thing because you're a dabbler
please if you
in and it depends on the past what they
were doing what they were eating teeth
are like time capsules I just actually I
was telling you guys they're time
capsules is what they're are keep in
mind that's very important to
know okay
teeth tell a story a story of the
past coffee green tea energy drink
drinks chocolate vinegar eggs dairy
products teeth tell a story of the past
and then you come and you do medical
medium but you have the baggage of the
past and your teeth for the last 20
years were're already becoming weakened
internally inside out yes and also in
the womb too some people come into this
world very deficient high in mercury and
the teeth have problems automatically
okay so what I'm doing here is I have
sauteed onions if you want to take a
look sauteed garlic in the pan let's
keep that going a little bit more and
we're going to make some cauliflower
rice now crooked teeth have to do real
crooked teeth have to do with toxic
heavy metals too coming
into the world with because they'll say
it's jeans crooked teeth are jeans jeans
jeans they say well the crooked teeth
this person has is similar to the
crooked teeth their family member had
and so forth and it's like really what's
happening it's similar to the Mercury
the family member has all the way down
the line it's Mercury Mercury Mercury
that's in their body and it's passed on
from generation to generation and then
you get the crooked teeth because of all
that mercury let's saut these onions
nice and good let's get some cauliflower
in here
now wild blueberry dream says I used to
drink lots of alcohol batter for the
teeth smoke lots of sigs bad for the
teeth lots of eggs and dairy did not
help my teeth oops it happens it's not
your fault at
all I'm
serious let's be
clear not your
fault life is hard we do things because
life is hard so I got a cauliflower
right here I'm going to use the little
pairing
knife if you don't mind guys I'll show
you this right here really quick if you
want to get a
closeup okay so I'm just cutting them
like this you guys probably know that
right you guys know how to do this you
don't have to do it this way this is the
way I did it like growing up and now you
know all the way till now I just like to
cut these
out and what I don't like to do is
really cut this part of the fuet because
if you do that
you get um you get like all this stuff
everywhere I mean you get the
cauliflower everywhere is what you get
everywhere looks like white snow so I'm
just cutting some of this
up but you don't want it so big and
hunky you want it to really get you know
good in the in the um processor all
right so this
is this is getting real hot in that pan
we're going to get some cauliflower rice
in here shortly bear with me please
hi my name is Anthony William we're
going to talk about teeth
today this is a grainfree sushi roll are
you okay with that just curious It's a
grainfree sushi roll now on IG you're
not going to see my food processor right
now I can bring it over really
quick cuz I'll do anything for you I
will
how about that tick Tok you guys
there Pan's burning a little cuz I put
only one onion on there but that's what
it's okay that's possible let's get this
how small do you want your
cauliflower your cauliflower rice how
small do you want it that's good I don't
want it um puree I don't want it pureed
I feel good about that right there let's
get some of this
on I got garlic in the pan with the
onion all right this is coming together
really quick pop this back in boom let's
get these in I'm going to do a decent
amount of cauliflower
here medical medium is not just
plant-based it also teaches people how
to use animal protein properly medical
medium that's why some of the vegan
people in the world in in the health
meaning
competitors whatever you want to call
them they don't like medical medium
information because it's not so
dogmatic of like has to be vegan only
vegan vegan
vegan you could be here as an animal
protein
person okay keep in mind you don't want
you don't want cauliflower puree
which I almost created but I didn't I
caught it in
time let's get some more of this here
are you guys following me we're going to
make some
rice you don't want it too hunky either
keep that in
mind someone said I look
stressed look like stressed freaking
multitasking I'm trying to give you guys
a freaking lecture on
teeth I got I'm mean I'm live right now
I got like I got [__] everywhere I got
like props everywhere I got stuff
everywhere I'm putting the human body
right here on on the table here right
the anatomy I'm trying to get enough
rice going I look
stressed I
do I'll try to deliver with a happy face
so it doesn't matter if I have a hundred
things going at the same time doesn't
matter if we're live right
now that doesn't matter
um yeah I should just be
happy all right let's get this in here
I'm making a decent amount of
this I look
stressed almost only nearly killed
myself doing the brain saver books so
people can have their lives
saved W realize what went into that I
know some of you guys do that so I lost
my first teeth 23 years old now I'm 45
and I do not have many teeth because so
sick but healing now with your
information I so like to know if it
would be bad for me to get a bridge
prothesis I'm glad you're working on
your teeth now your teeth health your
dumb Health you're doing mm
stuff it's important because you want to
stop the leak that's something that you
talk about yet because I'm busy making
you guys food too you want to stop the
leak the leak is what's been happening
all these years you want to reverse
that is what you want to do you want to
reverse that
leak you want to plug the leak so that
your teeth and gums aren't getting
diseased aren't falling apart you want
to plug that
leak
boom and that's what you're doing when
you're taking care of yourself all right
let's cook this rice up let's get
marinating we need a marinade I'm not
stressed I only have two marinades to
make all right only I'm stepping on
cauliflower fettes on the floor right
now
okay I want to put this one here cuz it
looks good I like it cauliflower is
great so people know that's what I'm
cooking diing sauce that's what we're
doing next let's get to it orange
is Boom okay we want a half a cup of
squeezed orange juice I'm going to grab
these Smaller oranges right here because
I think they're juicier oh yeah that's a
juicy orange right there you guys I
really need Samantha The dietitian who
was on recently on the medical medium Jo
I need her to explain things to you guys
um I'm hoping we can have her on again
because she was really a informative
dietician she talked about a lot of
things and
um we want her back here so I am going
to ask her to come back if you guys are
okay with that
um I'm doing some orange juice really
quick right here you you guys see we're
making a not a dressing a dipping sauce
oh oh ho let's just get this mixed up I
don't want the
cauliflower cooked on one like one part
too much more than another part I Want
It All
equal there we go looking great okay I
have a lot of Merk this is on IG I have
a lot of mercury amalgam fillings
amalgam fillings they are in very bad
shape but I still haven't started to
heal can't handle dentist visit
completely understand is removing them a
priority in order to get them to stop
decaying look I always tell people I've
said it over and over again I think it's
in the books
too is um if one breaks you got a crack
tooth it's falling out falling apart
that's the one I would get done in book
one medical medum book one I talk about
this I don't think it's good
from what Spirit of compassion has
taught me to get them all done at once
if you're going to ever get them all
done getting six done eight done at once
not good you want to do just a couple at
a time maybe one at a time um per Dental
visit it's less burden on your immune
system I tell friends they could leave
them alone unless they're causing a
problem in sense where they're um
they're broken the tooth is cracked and
needs to be cared
for it's great to be on here you guys
today Wendy says removing the Mercury
fillings was my biggest
mistake it's really hard for a lot of
people all right so this rice is coming
along great and I'm making the um the
dip and I want to make a decent amount
of it to be honest so I'm going to
squeeze one more orange in there if you
guys are okay don't get them all done
removed at once it can be a
disaster if you get them all removed at
once that that that's really hard on the
body that's a lot of mercury being
released at
once
okay that is g gorgeous that orange
juice right there amazing look at that
huh okay let's just get this rice this
rice is coming along so great too can
you see this you guys over there on
Instagram Tik Tok can you see this rice
cauliflower rice making it straight from
scratch
nice you don't mind can I just do a
little
sample hopefully you guys are okay okay
with this
okay it can still it can still take some
more a little more
time all
right I'm going to put some finely
chopped red pepper this cayen for my
garden we're making asparagus Sushi By
the
way asparagus
sushi
brains saer protocols book okay let's
get some H see this we'll get a little
um closeup on this
too let's see if we can I'm going to
just chop up this red pepper I want you
to see this Cayenne right here if you
guys can grow
Cayenne if that's a really great hot
pepper to grow the cayenne pepper really
great now you don't have to chop it too
fine in here but I'm going to go a
little bit there we go watch this I'm
just going to slide this on if you can
see this back here let's see where are
here we go now that's that's trying to
follow the cameras
there okay got the hot pepper in
there now let's go let's do some garlic
quick clove of garlic really quick here
it
is
nice oh let's catch the rice one more
time here you don't want to over steam
one side of this pan you want to mix mix
it in get it evenly distributed amongst
the
pan we're going to do a little bit of
garlic one
clove
boom one clove just bear with me for a
second
[Applause]
[Music]
okay let's get that
in this is an incredible dipping sauce
right
here let's go with a little bit of
finely grated Ginger look if you don't
have fresh
ginger if you don't have fresh
ginger that's okay use the Ginger Spice
if you need
to it's okay that's your kitchen you
have the Ginger Spice I'm using some
fresh ginger really quick here we
go okay you see that nice piece of
Ginger right there let's just get this
going I'm going to taste this as if this
is
okay coming along
nice so
good so yeah Samantha's going to come on
again and she's going to talk about
protein she seems to know a lot more
than
me
so I hope you guys respect
her Susan says on IG my mom was in her
early 70s with dementia we had a bunch
of dental work done on her her line was
significant after
that just get this here there we go in
it goes I'm going to bring this
over
nice so good so good get some lime juice
in
there you guys
I was with a friend and they were eating
we were eating together with some family
and some
friends and they did it they did it you
know what they did I did
this I said this is so good
aw and they did this so
good okay Colleen says I've seen medical
medium folks remineralize your teeth and
regenerate the enamel back yes it's
true and so have
I I truly have Lea s says just healed my
gum infection with medical medium
protocol and swishing with uh sere and
silver W it really
works um can I reverse loss of enamel a
lot of people can when they do the right
stuff but remember you you guys it's the
death by a th000 Cuts it's chipping away
at the stone keep that in mind what are
you doing that's actually harming your
teeth knowing this learning this that's
the key to getting enamel
back okay all right let's get a little
lime juice in there and we're
good wow that's
insane that's really
good let's mix that
up
okay this rice is getting closer we have
one more to
make oh I forgot the raw
honey
aha
boom yep and this is an option this is
optional little bit of doul flakes are
are optional for
this you guys seriously though I have a
lot of fun cooking with you guys
seriously it it's a lot of fun for
real it's it's a good good fun it's a
fun
fun it really is just mixing this look
at that right there Terry Johnson says
on Facebook I have enough crowns to rule
several small countries and kingdoms may
I add premedical medium postmed medium
no work needed and the stains are
lifting not white but lighter that's
medical medium stuff that's medical
medium
stuff your mouth to God's
ears all right let's get another one
down real quick while this is
okay okay guys what's good about this is
you want to refrigerate this one so I'm
going to do that really
quick all
right let's get that in the
refrigerator I'm back marinate I'm
making now marinated Ginger I'm going to
take oranges
I'm going to marinate Ginger this this
is going to be really good right
here all right let's do this again with
a little bit more orange this rice is
cooking keep an eye on it don't turn it
into mush this is rice you're making
don't turn it into you can turn rice
into mush in a heartbeat you really
can okay look at
that
nice that hot pepper and that the onions
steaming in the pan with this asparagus
sushi I'm making sushi
rolls so
good look at that orange that's a really
good orange right there
nice you
guys but seriously with teeth
problems you'll see everything blamed on
the wrong thing with teeth like lemon
water lemon's bad you'll see that out
there like people would just say the
wrong things for teeth but they just
don't realize it they don't
know and the whole vegan thing like if
you're vegan and that's why your teeth
are bad that's really rude and wrong I
mean if it was real fine if it was
actually accurate
fine I will say this one diet that will
destroy teeth turn them into that
terrible time capsule
problem it's the carnivore diet where
it's not even the healthier meat eating
diets where you're getting enough fruit
and vegetables and everything and
carnivore diets are changing right I
predicted that I predicted it would
change because you can't survive that
way only eating meat on its own by
itself you gets so deficient and glucose
deficient no sugar to the brain it gets
so bad and and so yeah that's a real hit
on teeth right there intermittent
fasting can be a hit on teeth too
because it's you know done wrong you're
not doing enough alkaline leafy greens
so intermittent
fasting that one right there can
definitely hit teeth really
hard okay let's get a little honey in
here and we're going to marinate some
ginger okay let's slice up some ginger
pieces for this I'm going to move this
over and I'm going to get another piece
of Ginger and the rice is almost
done
nice you guys with me on this can you I
can't wait to try these cannot
wait okay let's slice these pieces of
Ginger slice them
thin don't slice them thick these are
thin slices you want to marinade in that
orange so I'm kind of doing thin slices
carefully last thing I want to do is cut
my finger in front of all you guys that
would not be
fun let me put the Bowl here you see
that there we go I'll cut back here just
get these Ginger pieces nice and
sliced look at that nice and sliced in
I threw a thick one in there I'm going
to do another piece of Ginger why
not okay check the rice one more
time almost
there almost
there
okay peeling back some this
Ginger okay we're going to do these thin
slices that are longer
slices just like this might not be able
to see them behind there but we'll we'll
just get it going there we go
nice okay look how thin these are take a
look you you guys see popping them in
like this and then here's a thick piece
there you go marinating these rice is
just about
done all right put this
aside
wo when you're up against a lot
already your body may not prioritize
your teeth you're up against pathogens
low-grade viral infections strep
bacteria staff in your system a lot of
people got CF in their system a lot of
people got unproductive fungus yeast
mold in their system right mainly the
pathogens like the viruses and stuff
really keep the immune system
busy so bacteria and viruses tend to
keep everybody busy and then add the
toxic heavy metals and the chemicals and
add the coffee and the caffeine and add
the vinegar and all the other different
things including a lot of the stuff
that's in in the health realm that
doesn't doesn't actually help you it
hurts you and maybe you're in a bad
stressful situation you're under a lot
you're under a lot of stress you have an
emotional um emotional challenge that's
really hard on you losses struggles and
it's draining minerals from you quickly
and your adrenaline is rushing so I want
to hit that one last
time right there fight or flight bad for
the teeth
fight or flight flight or fight is bad
for the teeth adrenaline surges because
you're under something that has happened
like someone texted you something that's
awful maybe maybe someone misunderstood
you maybe you're triggered maybe you're
going through a really hard time maybe
you're struggling it's adrenaline right
maybe you're just somebody that's into
adrenaline Sports you're physically
capable of doing it and you're doing
you're like an adrenaline junkie
and so and you're somebody like that too
so but adrenals what they do is when
we're up against stuff and we're using
them a lot they pump and they pump and
they pump and what happens these little
adrenal glands are pumping and
pumping and they're releasing adrenaline
and adrenaline is corrosive and
adrenaline needs to be calmed down by
minerals in the
body but we just it depletes our
minerals instead it just gives us
mineral deficiencies and then we get get
in trouble that's another thing too you
add all of these
up all right let's get the filling going
let's get things
going I have to thinly slice some
radishes really
quick
okay Den gay says a w bro you got so
much energy that's a testament to
Medical mean protocols in itself I do
enjoy your your live webcasts thank you
very much I really appreciate that I do
truly so what I'm going to do is slice
these really thin because I'm going to
place them in the Nori really thin so
they don't break the Nori
sheets so if you can see really quick
and I think our rice
is is just about there I'm going to give
it a couple more
minutes okay slicing these radishes
really thin you guys this is going to be
fun when we fill these Nory sheets it's
going to be insane it's going to be sick
seriously
okay there's
one I still got more to go I got some
fixings to
go I I I fell asleep on you guys if you
have trouble with the screen freezing or
sound go to YouTube rumble or medical
medium.com on medical medium.com we are
actually airing this episode live right
now I think we have a whole bunch of
people watching it from medical
medium.com right now so we're spread out
you know we got a lot going on we're on
Tik Tok right now we're at Rumble right
now live there we go let's do one more
and then we'll get the Cucumber done and
we're
good so we're actually airing in a few
different places
few different
channels I'm going to shut this
off because this is
actually at its best that's cauliflower
rice these are really nice and
thin I wouldn't say paper I would say
close to it
though
okay
the thing is is Dental when you get
dental work done cosmetically it wears
out and you got to redo it again it's
like you get veneers then you got to get
the veneers again it just wears
out and so do fillings fillings wear out
over time they crack they break they got
to get redone and what happens is most
of the time when they get redone if they
were deep fillings deep ones then the
dentist is going to say hey you need a
root canal now that's a that's what the
dentists will do they'll be like you
need a root canal now and people run
into that a
lot okay radishes I want to put it in
this
bowl there we go and I want to move in
cucumber really quick knock this
out the rice is
done all right I'm peeling the skin back
on this I know I told you guys the last
time I did the Nory rolls the reason why
this is not a garden cucumber this skin
will have this is an organic cucumber
but the skin will have a treatment on it
and kind of keep that in
mind organic produce and conventional
produce not all conventional produce but
conventional produce will will be
treated so this skin right here will
have anything from MSG in it nicotine in
it so what you'll see
and not to mention if somebody's
fingernails are got all kinds of crud
under there like crazy
DNA all kinds of different junk and
garbage and feces and everything else
and their fingernails and they're at the
supermarket and they're grabbing the
cucumbers and they Le they put it back
and what happens is their fingernails
went jammed into the Cucumber I kind of
want to get the skin off a little bit I
don't need
to be eating somebody else's like FEC
particles it's not something that I
would like to
do just like the feal matter implant
thing feal implant matter I don't like
that either I would never never allow
that would never do that modality where
they put somebody else's feces up you
know in your colon through your anus oh
my God I would never do that there's no
way someone's putting somebody else's
[__] up my ass it's not happening it's
not happening and I see that getting
popular like are you insane they don't
catch the viruses and that stuff they're
not looking for all the viruses in
different different pathogens and
material that'ss in that stuff it's
crazy so what I'm going to do is I'm
going to cut this cucumber a certain way
so it's
not there we
go I'm going to cut it like this too
there we go I don't want them real big
and hunky keep that in
mind I want these nice
watch this right I want it like
this let me just get this right there we
go thank you Anthony just had a tooth
breaking some days ago it's one of my
four dead teeth thank you so much
forever okay making these nice and even
because I don't want them tearing up
these nor rolls normally I wouldn't be
this careful but
but I'm having having some people over
and what's going to happen is I want
these to really like have a look to them
I want them to
be you know presentable I mean honestly
if I was making this for myself right
now just for myself I would just throw
this whole piece of cucumber in that
that roll possibly with that rice and
some other stuff I would probably
wouldn't be doing it this way but this
is okay this is great I like the Pres
presentation that this is going to
exhibit you guys if you could hit the
like button I know that I never asked
for it I see on YouTube it's just every
single day every it's like Please
Subscribe and hit hit the Subscribe
button and hit the like button give me a
thumbs up or whatever I see that every
day everybody's doing it's like I never
want to ask the medical medum community
for
anything cuz you guys are on mattress
Island you don't feel feel good you guys
are struggling you guys are fighting for
your health you're rising out of the
ashes last thing you need to do is to be
like worried about hitting a like button
or
subscribing all right we got that done
we got that we got that now we're just
going to cut these scallions back a
little bit look at these scallions from
my garden take a look at that look at
that is that insane or
what it's really really amazing I'm
going to cut this one this is very long
one so you'll see half of it being cut
here we
go just made
these nice ones right there look pretty
cool right all right pop them here do
another let's get this bottom
piece lost that knife we're going to use
this knife
now got to be careful in the kitchen
we're
live all
right there we go
we'll do
another we take off that tip all right
Wendy says or Rook Canal's necessary
Unfortunately they are to keep a tooth
for a lot of people Unfortunately they
are they're
necessary if it gets that
bad okay there we go all
right so
if your
um if what happens is if that cavity
went too deep or you just have bacteria
that somehow got deep into the root your
body's immune system did not like
capture it it not grab it it didn't
destroy it and you got bacteria that got
in that root somehow and around that
root or you had a cavity done
okay there's a better better look at the
root right and you had a cavity done and
yet some bacteria still stayed in there
it went too deep the cavity might have
been too deep either way a lot of people
are getting a cavity a lot of people
don't know they're going to get a root
canal until they're in the dentist chair
and the their cavity is being drilled
and then the dentist goes too far and
goes into the pulp of the tooth right
into the nerve way too deep and then
they're like whoa you're going to need a
rot canal in order to keep that tooth
it's necessary to get a rot canal it's
necessary to do that sometimes they'll
do a crown sometimes they won't it all
depends on the dentist or what's
happening or how much how much of your
tooth is left but a lot of times
bacteria inflames those that
nerve and yeah root canals are are
necessary
unfortunately you know in alternative
movement it's like don't get a root
canal don't get a root canal don't get a
root canal okay then what are you going
to do you're going to lose your tooth
like what are we going to do like the
tooth's
gone
got another
knife like you know we get in trouble
like that and then there's Teeth Let's
talk about I didn't know I was actually
going to be able to talk so much about
teeth while we're doing this but it's
fun that way I like that let's get a
couple more of
these this is actually
fun I don't know about you guys but I'm
having a good time let's just get the
scallions the scallions done and we can
make these rolls and we're going to make
these rolls good
look at that see how I'm doing that
these are long long scallions from the
garden and I can I can make so many out
of these look I just made one right
there see I'm going to add that to there
right and then I'm going to take this
and I'm going to cut this in half so
we're not doing a huge
scallion in in the Nori roll look I cut
it in half and watch this you guys boom
look at this perfect sizes let's do
another
one clenching I talk about in the
medical medium books
right shingles
TMJ pain trigeminal nerve pain how about
that all of it and then and then the
tension and then the teeth grinding it's
not just strep it's not just strep or
and and bacteria that's in around
people's teeth it's not just cavity
bacteria it's not any of that it's viral
so what happens with people is when
they're clenching their jaw and they're
grind Bing their
teeth that right there that's from the
nerves the cranial nerves like the
trigeminal nerve being inflamed so when
it's even mildly inflamed we get tension
and we actually clench and when people
have the fever blister the Simplex
herpes one simplex virus you don't even
have to have the blister on your lip you
don't have to have it and you'll still
be
clenching so a lot of and shingles
that's another one shingles in
somebody's system can do a lot of
clenching wondering Wishin says thank
you for saying root canals are okay I
had four before medical medium
information now I don't feel so bad
don't feel bad at all don't feel bad at
all we try not to get root canals by
taking care of our teeth in all the ways
we can that's medical medum information
but if you have to get a root canal in
the past or something happens and you
need one it's it's not it's it's not
your fault it happens all right you guys
I'm
ready let's go and let's make these I
actually think we're ready voila Nory
sheet I need to tell you something about
this Nory
sheet if you take Nory sheets these are
toasted if you take Nory sheets straight
out of the
package you have to moisten them if you
want to make a roll up because they'll
just explode they'll explode and fall
apart so you have to moisten them dampen
them I don't have to with these cuz I
had the I had the package open for a
long time and moisture just got in there
and that's what's really cool too people
do get unnecessary root canals I just
want to say they do when there's viral
issues a virus inflaming like shingles
or herpes simplex 1 inflaming the
trigeminal nerves and they're feeling
jaw pain they're feeling gum pain like
they're gum a lot of people have burning
gums from the shingles virus even a
little bit of Epstein bar they'll have
burning
gums they'll have jaw pain they'll be
hurting over here really bad by their
MERS the dentist does that
Panorama takes digitals says
everything's looking pretty good but if
you keep on having pain over here if
that hurts ma'am if that hurts right
here we're going to have to do a root
canal maybe that will fix it a lot of
people get unnecessary root canals they
don't work they get the root canal and
they're still in pain because it was
viral inflammation I see dentist talking
about that now but guess what that was
published first with medical medium
material and medical medium
information and now they're using that
my most unfavorite thing ever is MM info
out there origin it from the books and
from my lectures over the years and then
taken used the wrong way and then at the
same time they say that medical medium
knows nothing out there it hurts people
bad because they can't get back to the
source and learn the information so they
can heal all
right I got a nor sheet right here I
don't have to moist inate I might take a
little bit of the orange juice at the
end to seal
it okay I'm not going to use a sushi mat
I don't need one I don't like using
those I think they make it more
difficult I think they're even harder on
beginners so that's that's something
that's important to to
know all right let's get some rice in
here let's
roll we got some cauliflower
rice piping hot too it's piping
hot guys see see this it's up to you on
how much you want to use how much you
don't want to
use
okay all
right I'm going to move this over so it
actually
helps okay there we are we have that
let's go one asparagus this is the
asparagus sushi roll you can do two
asparagus
Spears you can do one I'm going to try
one to start with right there I'm also
going to put one of these cucumber
slices in
here I don't care if this cucumber slice
is kind of long right there I'm going to
put one of these you can also cut these
in half a couple of these let me see do
this all
right there we
go okay we got that let's put some
scallions in
here here we
are let's put some SC I
in guys is it focusing at all let's see
what we got let's move some of this
stuff there we go all right I'm going to
put some scallion in here you have some
cucumber in there you got an asparagus
in there as well let's put little radish
slices in here too nice and
thin so they don't destroy the
roll there we go how do you like that
that that's coming together really good
what am I missing is it anything I think
we're good let's roll
up as I said I don't like the sushi
mats here we
go okay I'm going to put a little touch
of this orange juice on the edge like
that that one's done let's cut
it now you want to give yourself
somewhat of an end here so you can
really have something to grab on to you
want to saw you want to saw with your
knife it's important see see I'm sawing
right
there if you don't do the sawing
action
okay use a straight blade don't use a
saw blade of any
kind all right let's get this on the
tray and make sure you cut these really
good take a good look right here closeup
do we have
a there we
are I'll give you guys a little rundown
on this I'm going to use these for the
ends there you go got a closeup there
and I want to give you guys on IG a
closeup and you guys on Tik Tok a
closeup right
there and
YouTube and
Facebook okay let's keep them
coming let's cruise though let's get
these like a lot done I'm hungry I'm
getting really
hungry Simon Says on YouTube that's the
point we have the choice but can't make
the past disappear today like white like
with teeth but with me thank you thank
recognized immediately the quality of
healing with mm thank you so much I hope
I said that way I need to say that there
that was a very nice comment thank you
so
much and the community the medical M
Community really
appreciates your
support all right let's go let's get a
little scallion in
here you guys I'm going to put two
scallions just like like that in there
okay I'm going to stick
cucumber see yeah I'm going to
do one there one
there okay I'm going to put this
beautiful asparagus spear in here like
that these asparagus Spears are just big
enough if they get any skinnier they get
any smaller you want to use two I would
let's get some radish pieces in here too
look at this radishes have to be sliced
thin I know I said that before this is
like so fun there you go let's roll it
up are we missing something do you guys
know I don't think we're missing
something I think we have it let's get a
little bit of this orange juice on the
edge there and now we're ready to cut
give yourself a little bit of an
edge do a sawing action all right there
we
go seriously though a lot of
people they're doing things that are
hurting their teeth every single day
they're out there're doing stuff that's
hurting their teeth they don't know it
they don't know it it's really
sad now if I had look if I had a bunch
of
implants if I had a bunch of implants if
I had three or four root
canals I shouldn't be I honestly I most
likely shouldn't be giving you any
advice on this I
mean
because I've had a chance since I was
younger to take care of my teeth through
S so's information with this knowledge
to stay away from things and to be
cautious but um but when I talk to like
podcast doctors or you know a lot of the
guys that are out there in the health
realm a lot of the doctors your teeth
are just they're just they're a terrible
shape their teeth
and I mean they have so much teeth work
done it it's crazy how much and I'm not
judging them but they sit there and they
actually try to say they know everything
about everything they try to say they
know everything about autoimmune they
say the body attacks itself that's why
people have autoimmune they say all
these things right talk about genes and
all kinds of stuff and they talk about
like you know these different keto diets
and intermittent fasting diets and their
teeth are just all like mangled up and
they've been in the the realm for a
little while enough and they're like
afraid of lemon water they're afraid of
all kinds of things they just don't know
I'm going to put a cucumber in here
asparagus and let's get some more slices
of of these right
here I'm going to just cut a couple of
these there we
go radishes in
here radishes are really good for you by
the way don't be afraid of radishes
bring them in when you can um I
um I want people to know radishes are
really a great
food for so many reasons I can cover
sometime but I'm going to put this end
right up here let's get these done this
is going to come out
great remember saw or you're going to
squish it out there you
go Sushi board
down let's get the over here I crushed
that one right there all right you guys
it's coming
together I want to ask how many of you
guys are using vinegars at all how many
of you guys used vinegars in the past
that's what I wanted to ask
you how many of
you do apple cider vinegar that's a
question I wanted too like are any of
you guys doing apple cider vinegar did
you stop using it are you still using it
don't get me wrong it's the best vinegar
there is out of all the
vinegars
apple cider vinegar I don't want
confusion I'm not trying to contradict
myself I'm just saying it is the best
vinegar out of all of them especially if
it has the
mother but it's just as damaging there's
no difference it does a lot of damage in
the body in different ways put a couple
of these in here like that let's get
another asparagus in the middle let's
get a
cucumber that let's get some of
these wait till you taste this with
dipping sauces
so
good let's roll that baby
up it's a little it's a little tricky
that one there we go okay another one
slice it
up there we
go how many of you guys are doing apple
cider
vinegar
all
right these up
here how's it look you guys coming along
I'm making a really nice setup here take
a
look that's what we're
doing I want it to look
good and I'm not done
yet we still have some more to
do
I think one of the most confusing Parts
about teeth no matter what is because
they're time capsules they're like a
ticking Time Bomb what happens is
because they're like that ticking Time
Bomb people don't realize when they fall
apart like what's happening in their
life in that moment they'll be like wait
a minute I'm taking care of myself I'm
eating better I'm doing good things and
then why are my teeth acting like
this and they just don't know that
that's because of the past that's
because they're like little you know
little ticking
grenades in somebody's in somebody's
mouth where they just start falling
apart from Gears of all these different
things we
covered I don't want anybody feeling bad
about a root canal getting a root canal
in the
past I completely understand when people
have to get R canals
um
all
right another thing too is finding a
dentist that you trust and you're happy
with that's something I want to kind of
cover while we're doing this I I tend to
actually not talk about that too much
because there's so many other different
things to talk about but finding a
dentist you're comfortable with there's
a lot of people that they feel really
uncomfortable with with their
dentist they don't trust their
dentist but yet they have to go to
them sometimes it takes shopping around
to a few different
dentists don't be afraid of a
conventional D dentist you can say yay
or nay you can be the one that says hey
I don't want to do that but I want to do
this to Don't Be Afraid like PE there's
some people they're just afraid of
conventional
dentists they go to a holistic dentist
that's fine there's some good holistic
dentist out there but there's some bad
ones there's some good um conventional
dentists out there and there's some bad
ones you might find a conventional
dentist that's amazing really good
drills like no other handles your mouth
with care but yet they don't really know
anything about holistic but yet they do
the job they're doing that you hire them
for they do it right and you you can go
to a holistic dentist that has
everything to all the bells and wh
whistles they do the ozone they do the
ozone therapy they do this they do that
all the bells and whistle they tell you
to stay away from lemon it's going to
dissolve your teeth whatever which is
wrong but they'll do all these bells and
whistles they have all the equipment
there and and but yet they're not really
good as a driller they're not good when
they when they're working on your mouth
they're not changing out gloves when you
ask them to change out
gloves you want a dentist that you can
feel free to say look change your gloves
if you can I saw you touch this this and
this
yeah
and it's a way and to learn about how to
be careful at the dentist office read
the brainsaver books where's the brains
saer book right here but how to take
care like what to like look out for at
the dental office make sure you check
out the Brain saer book right
there all right we got asparagus in
there we got that beautiful um scallion
we got the cucumber in there once again
we're going to throw some of these in
here take it a little longer cuz we're
covering a lot of
information yeah nice but you better
believe I'm going to eat one of these
you better believe it let's roll this
up let's got this one up
now
okay there we go it's coming
together just about there putting these
guys on the
edge you guys can see now here we
go
and we're going to make some Wasabi in a
little bit
too okay dud a balancing act over here
whoa If This falls and goes down and
that whole tray goes
down that would be really
terrible I would be so
embarrassed so embarrassed I would be so
embarrassed I'd be like blushing I'd be
blushing kind of
embarrassed I really would I'd be like
oh
man failed you
guys failed you guys
okay all
right Courtney says learn so much today
amazing thank you for being here
seriously okay what are we missing
cucumber let's get a cucumber in here
let's get even another cucumber in here
some Nori on my hand let's roll whoa
that one that one's actually got some
meat to its bones right there look at
that one you guys all right let's do an
end when you do these
noris now what I like to do is roll like
four of them and cut like four of them
in a
row so I'm going to R um roll up two and
show you guys
okay getting there let's move these pack
them
in fit them in here like a puzzle okay
all right two more and then let's knock
this
out two more and then it's out the
door going I put that there for now okay
right
now listen if you're a rice
fanatic yeah if you're a rice
fanatic you can use rice if that's what
you want to do the mm doesn't really you
know we don't the mm Spirit of
compassion and I don't really do a lot
of rice
stuff for people who are chronically
sick but if that's what you're doing you
know that's what you're doing
but the
Millet the Millet is definitely one you
can do which is really really good but
if you had to do Rice you can do Rice
you can do
it
okay if it's something that you really
wanted to do and that's something you do
then you use rice all right another
thing I want to talk about is about
medical meme information is about
ammonia coming up out of your gut rising
up up and eating away at your gums also
destroying your teeth ammonia is
another problem that's all about the
liver and the HCL being really bad off
with people Hydrochloric acid's really
low because they burned out their their
stomach lands from all the coffee and
all the chocolate and the the vinegar
the acetic acid and they burned out
their stomach glands it's the last one
you
guys
and what happened was their food's
rotting in their gut it's rotting
they're getting gut rot right food gut
rot and then all this ammonia is Ghostly
and it's traveling through their
intestinal tract into their bones
everything and into the bones means into
your teeth and when that ammonia is
constantly percolating up all night as
you sleep you lay flat when you're
sleeping and it just seeps seeps right
into your
mouth that's a big deal all on its own
really big deal all
right and I'm going to put the last
pieces of this on here this is my last
roll up I think we have room for the
dipping sauce and everything we will see
there we go let's roll this
up that's what we're talking about I got
two right here now check this out now
usually I do this with four but I'm
doing it with two you ready so I'm doing
it I'm I'm actually cutting these
like that see two at a time I usually
cut four I cut five at a time too look
at this showof right show off look at
that for those who cannot eat the Millet
Sushi because they are avoiding grains
this is an amazing option an amazing
recipe to use cauliflower
rice okay let's see what kind of room we
have
okay
okay there we go I'm going to get it
clean
for you guys with
me going to get this ginger in
here okay I'm saving that that's a
little that's a some extra
they see me rolling Dr Fawn
MD an amazing
doctor amazing
doctor all right you guys I'm doing just
a little
bit of playing around with this I'm
looking for presentation are you guys
okay with this I want to
exhibit a
different kind of look
here I know you guys can do a better job
than this and I know that like don't
think I don't know that cuz I actually
do I actually know you guys can do a
better
job
okay let's get the dipping sauce right
here
and we still have the Wasabi to
do oh wait we got dipping sauce too
let's get it out of the
fridge
okay
yep so we're going to strain this
one you don't have to you can leave it
all like
that let's
see we're going to strain strain the
ginger huh everything everything else is
going to
strain all
right I think we're going to go
different route
[Music]
here
okay get this for the wasab I got to
make some Wasabi you
guys
okay all
right all right
guys
someone was banging at the door and
banging at the door and we had to
actually take a little break for a
second to find out what was going on and
it was a delivery but they wouldn't stop
hanging at the door I am back you guys
all right all right get some more of
these little bowls out real quick so
what I'm going to do is take out this
Ginger
here like
that
nice and that's why we're live that's
what's incredible all
right this is coming out
great this is here like this if we want
it all back on here
and this is
here
there we go going to try our best and
let's get some Wasabi on here too you
guys look if you have some extras you
can pop them right on top if you really
want
to there we
go last but not least little bit of
Wasabi this is the stuff that gets
me I actually think it's kind of funny
someone was banging on the
door okay
woo already I can feel the hit on that
Wasabi that's going to be like crazy I'm
going to put a little bit of water in
here there you go going to mix that
up this is like playing with fire this
Wasabi you want to be careful it'll give
you like a brain freeze like worst than
ice cream can give you like a brain
freeze
I'm going to add a little bit more water
in here just give me a
second I wish I could have you guys
over you know and just like just make
this massive amount like I can I can
just like stay up day and night and make
these rolls for a whole bunch of
people all right there we go we got the
Wasabi put it right in the middle
just like
that
wo
okay I'm going to lift this
up there you go right there in the
camera and I'll show I'll give you guys
a viewing
too all right that's it right there I'm
going to spin it a little
bit dang you see the Wasabi in the
center you see the two different dipping
sauces well the ginger is one then you
got the dipping
sauce okay that's marinated Ginger it's
been soaking in the orange and the honey
I'm just spinning this around a little
bit okay I want to give you guys a
closeup to
ig boom closeup to Tik Tock you guys and
if you don't mind I'm going to have
some I'm going to drop it right
here try not to like spill it or
anything I got some chopsticks I found a
new way to use
chopsticks I hope you guys are okay but
here's my new way so what I'm going to
do is I'm going to
actually are you guys okay with this
this is my new way going to hold on here
bear with me
here
here's this is this is my my new way of
doing the Chopsticks right just bear
with me a little bit
I'm going to dip it in the
sauce then try to get a little bit of
the Wasabi on
it good thing I got all my teeth and
they're good the medical mean of
information all
right all that was
good um
woo and it wasn't Bryce no Bryce wasn't
knocking on the door I wish Bryce was
knocking on the door Cynthia says where
can I find a recipe medical medium
brains saver protocols I'm going to have
another one if you guys don't
mind right that's where the recipe is
you don't have the Brain book all right
let's get another one okay all right so
I'm going to take this one right here
and I'm going to dip in the sauce you
guys don't mind right
look but
I found a new way of using these okay so
what I'm going to do is I'm going to put
some wasab oh this is going to be insane
I'm put a little Wasabi on that that's a
lot of Wasabi oh no that's going to be
crazy you guys see this right here how
much Wasabi's on there okay and what you
do
is right all right you get your Ginger
piece right that's you want to do I'm
going to get this Ginger piece right
here okay
now I'm going to put this Ginger piece
right on here
okay all
right get
ready I put a lot of Wasabi on
there here it
goes woo oh my God it really clears
things out I like get to your head all
right and then last but not least I
found this other way of doing this
which is I do it this way I'll take it
like this you
guys and I'll dip it in the sauce like
this and then I'll try to get it up to
my
mouth just got to bear with me right
here I think I can get this one hold
on lost
it
Dar lost
jeez Dar
it ah
all right you guys seriously that was
one that bit the dust which didn't need
to bite the dust that was terrible cuz I
was fooling around I'm going to get a
little bit of that
Wasabi a little bit of that right there
this is incredible you got to do it this
way that's the only way to do it don't
do it the way I just did
it whatever you
do F we watch this live talk about the
teeth and everything about
it of what happens please rewatch us
live if you you get a chance and don't
do it that way do it the right way do it
the right way get you know do it the
right way please whatever you do okay
right it's so
good so
good okay you guys know that I care I'm
going to try to do a live pretty soon
because I need Samantha to come on to
teach everybody on
Instagram how smart of a dietitian she
is she knows a
lot um Samantha The dietitian I hope you
guys are okay when she does come on
please treat her with respect if you
can the medical medium bulletin went out
today with everything that's been
happening all the latest stuff
everything latest content latest
recipes get on the medical medium
newsletter make sure you sign up to
telegram because I leave these messages
sometimes like one o'clock in the
morning 3 o'clock in the morning 11
o'clock at night I leave these messages
Pride and Prejudice messages and other
messages please sign up or I don't know
sign up or subscribe or whatever to my
Telegram and check out Tik Tok and
please get on my Tik Tok Channel again
because that would be amazing I had
almost a million followers on the last
one before they poofed it in The Ether
forever and now I'm back down to trying
to get people there because I want to do
exclusive content for people to see and
like and comment on this video please
let people know that you like the recipe
if it tastes good cuz it does taste
good and um subscribe to Medical Med and
podcast at Apple podcast because I'm
going to have some health podcasts
eventually a whole ton of them so
anyway mat your
service at your service this please know
I
care I really do I kid around I joke
around cuz I want to you know I want
people to keep a sense of humor
especially if you're sick and you're un
mattress Island I want people to be able
to have a light heart the best they can
even when they're struggling somehow
okay and know that I care I truly do and
you guys know Aurora's morning says I
hope you'll do more funny videos on Tik
Tok those were so fun remember the
caffeine one I did you know remember
that with the
song Why do you make things so
[Music]
complicated right okay remember that one
okay
guys love you
much remember the milk cheese and butter
one on Tik Tok that was funny
all right you guys love you