live on tick tock and gonna make my
lunch and dinner or whatever we call it
because it's time to eat
so i'm excited about that i'm gonna make
some cool stuff i might make a kale
salad
so that's what i'm gonna do um and
so medical medium right here gonna
answer some questions i'm live
as we speak i hope you guys come on got
some lemon balm tea right here
i'd like to help answer a few questions
but i'm going to go on tick-tock a
little later and answer questions
thoroughly
um for sure
don o'brien said hi how do you feel
about the rife machine well
the rife machine was around everybody
was still sick
i remember 35 years you know being in
this
in this all these years and it would be
like okay we got another
guessing game another guessing game
another guessing game
the rife machine was around everybody
was sick
everybody still had the chronic fatigue
syndrome and they had the rife machine
still had the chronic fatigue syndrome
unless they knew how to do the right
tools like
really clean up their diet just right
know what viruses to go after
truly know what they're doing and know
what supplements to take
to go anti-viral to go anti-bacterial
to get the metals out too and then
they would make improvements rife
machine or no rife machine
but back in the rife machine days it was
like okay rice machine what next
everybody still stays sick what next you
know that's what it was like
and it the only difference you might get
out of the rice machine now
is someone's actually maybe taking on a
couple of medical medium tools out there
because that's what i've seen i've seen
people say well the rife machine works
for me
and then you look at what they're doing
what else are you doing and they're like
oh i'm doing some celery juice or
i'm doing some spirulina or
i'm making sure there's no gluten and
dairy in here or um
and you'll find out then as you gather
it up there's a lot of little medical
medium tools all
spur interspersed in there and
and then if they're in the in the mood
that they think the right machine might
be open then they'll just
just call it the rife machine but i mean
years ago though it's like everybody
with the right machine nobody got better
that's how it was um good to be here
right here
uh jamie woodall says tick tock question
mark yeah
tick tock today live answering questions
thoroughly on tick tock gonna make
dinner to
uh medical medium dinner i noticed you
guys i mean i'm
i noticed you guys are talking about it
lately as far as what i've been eating
you've been asking me for years what
does he eat
what is he gonna eat today like does he
walk the talk
does he eat what's in his books does he
what does he do and so i'm gonna be
making
food you guys have been noticing i made
the roll-ups so i made
one day i made the roll-ups another day
i made the roll-ups another day i made a
salad
um another day i forgot what i made i'm
making kale today kale salad and some
other stuff today too
and i might even juice some celery juice
you know what's funny you guys have seen
comments lately where
um because the new videos that i'm doing
on tik tok
like the cheese butter bread that video
there
and like the egg video on tik tok
so people are i'm getting all these you
know new people that
that haven't paid attention to medical
medium information they heard about
medical medium but they really haven't
paid attention to it or anything and
then they're like
leaving comments saying hey you should
write a book medical medium
you got some cool information you should
actually write a book
and it's funny because six new york
times best-selling books
later number one new york times
best-selling author
um millions of books around the world
that have already reversed illness and
disease in people
um and the and the in the uh results are
in it's proven
and it's the funniest thing ever when
you hear that when you hear that in the
comments section all the time
medical medium you should write a book
it's really it's it's actually funny
um tracy phillips says i was wondering
about the ozone therapy as well
um back years ago
ozone therapy was still something that
was going down back then
but it was all experimental still is you
know that's how it is it's like well
what do you do with ozone therapy do you
breathe it in
and that's what happened in the original
days back years ago
people were breathing it in so they
would actually do ozone therapy and
breathe it in and it wasn't a good thing
that way not that
way so um so i'm not a big fan of ozone
therapy i'm not saying it's bad right
now just i wouldn't
i wouldn't use it as an inhalant i
wouldn't use it as a
a breath tech you know a breath
technique therapy where you're breathing
it in
on that level i wouldn't do it but i
mean i just wouldn't recommend that i'm
saying if your doctor wants to do that
and then and that's what you want to do
just do what you're going to do but i
wouldn't recommend that
but ozone therapy i'm not against it in
some dentistry
i'm not against it and some other
reasons too because the reason why i'm
i'm not against it so much with small
applications of it but
when you're sensitive it's a little edgy
and all the people that i've known and
all the doctors i've talked to over the
years that have
have wanted my help to troubleshoot
there are people
um a lot of sensitive people severe
chronic fatigue syndrome neurological
problems and ozone therapy was
too harsh so you got to apply it just
right
has to be in small settings or small
increments
small amounts for certain applications i
think i'll do a
medical medium podcast apple podcast
episode about it so you know just to air
it all out
because there's a lot to cover right
there tiffany says what time on
tick-tock
well right from here i'm going to
instagram live for probably like 10
minutes
and then from there i'm going right to
tick tock live
so that's something to keep your
notifications on make sure they're set
so that you get notified
and then so you're you know so you can
be there so just look out
um or constantly check too
because you know constantly be like is
he on is he on and check it out
so you can catch it um so yeah
so important to know
so i just saw a question about tinctures
and teas
would you explain the potency difference
between
teas and tinctures you can get a lot
more
extracted from a tincture you can take
it in higher dosages if you need to
therapeutic wise
like four dropper folds of a lemon balm
four times a day
versus tea it's a little harder to
extract it's not as strong
you gotta do a lot of it there's a
difference but i love the tea
but you know so what i do is i like
recommending the vimergy lemon balm and
so if i had it on me right here i'd show
you you guys probably know the vimer
gv's and victor i-m-e-r-g-y that's the
lemon balm
so you know you use the that's what i
would do it's like someone's got anxiety
i would do like four
five dropper fulls of that three four
times a day
personally that's what i would recommend
a family member or a friend
and you know i talk about that also when
cleanse the heel if you want to take a
look and cleanse the heel
but but uh the t it's harder to do that
i have the lemon balm tea here but still
it's a great thing
have you know keep it in there the whole
bit
michelle l the mo the most truth gets
the most haters
yes so true and boy
does medical medium get a lot of hate
and guess what still standing
still standing all right discrimination
lots of discrimination for hearing a
voice lots of discrimination
for getting people better over these
years lots of discrimination for
putting out six new york times
best-selling books with no pr
and marketing what you're gonna hear out
there all the time is
he's got new marketers now that's why
he's doing these tick tock
good marketing team good pr and
marketing that's funny because
i never had pr marketing it's only been
done by me
and me alone as far as i decide what i'm
gonna do i decide how i'm gonna do it i
don't have any big pr marketing or
a marketing firm breathing down my neck
i don't hire a company
never did isn't that crazy just could
you imagine if i did could you imagine
if i put millions of dollars
into like these people do out there into
like a big big
marketing firm can you imagine what
medical medium information would be
there
it would and look what it's doing now
organically millions of books around the
world
it's grassroots look organically healed
so many people
without marketing in pr and should i
shortcut stuff and do the cheat game
should i cheat and not have the
integrity and hire the big pr marketing
firms
and just have them pay their way through
so that something gets seen should i go
the cheap way
no i go to the organic grassroots way so
that's just the way i do it katie alder
katie adler said the haters were wild
laugh out loud oh yeah
it's been like that for months and
months been like that for years
especially the last six
eight months deanna d.a
yeah haha you should write a book yeah
funny
isn't that funny you guys i have a video
coming out i got a video tick tock video
coming out soon i think it's going to
come out tomorrow
and you're going to be i think you're
going to laugh at it i think it's going
to be pretty funny maybe you won't find
it funny at all
but i worked on it i worked on it last
night i worked on it last night hard
um so yeah you guys it's pretty funny
how it works
so
been talking all day by the way i've
been talking all day since
early this morning
and anyway on tick tock i'm going to
make myself some dinner
that's what i'm going to do angelic
marketers i just saw a comment where i
got angelic
marketers vicki b if you had marketing
anthony you wouldn't be doing lives in
your kitchen
you see you know marketing firms have
tried to bang down my door
and said how dare you do it alone you're
not allowed to do that
you better hire one of us you know
marketing companies
they they don't like knowing i got
somewhere without them
and they would probably never let me do
it in my own kitchen they would probably
never let me sit here in my kitchen
talking crap
oh it's funny it's funny it's just that
i mean look look i've always had people
with chronic illness i've always had
their back and it's about
just being real you know not saying
you're being real not that stuff because
the marketing companies tell their
their uh clients to say be real and say
this and that and whatnot right and
that's what they do
too it's crazy it's crazy i mean people
pay them like
two million dollars a month i mean stuff
like that out there just to get
their books seen these you know fancy
doctors and some not all of them but
it's just crazy how it works
christy may what do i do with constant
cold sores
terrible i don't want to go on valtrex
but i have no choice
i feel i do lysine eat fruit greens all
day potato sweet potatoes
and even lettuce spinach nothing bad
question mark um so you're doing that
you're not doing the nutritional yeast
right that can easily stimulate a cold
sore
you're not doing the apple cider vinegar
right just making sure you're not doing
chocolate right
this did you do chocolate two weeks ago
did you do chocolate three weeks ago did
you have cacao
that that will cause simplex to just
bust out that'll just cause it busting
out i'm not saying you're doing any of
that
i'm just asking to make sure in case
there's something you have done
and and you haven't caught it and then
have you tried the simplex protocol in
here you can take to your
practitioner your family doctor whatever
it is and but have you seen that so and
cleanse the heel
um simplex protocol so
check that out maybe give that a try and
that's what i would recommend a family
member a friend you can always talk to
your doctor about it
but and so so even though you're eating
really clean no chocolate right because
chocolate is the
chocolate is the the herpes instigator
simplex is epstein bars
it's it's a trigger it's a trigger it is
the
it's a trigger i mean a little bit of
chocolate once in a blue moon fine or
whatever in a recipe once and
a while but people do a lot of chocolate
so yeah just be careful on those kinds
of things
um
marissa anderson thanks for being here
just received my life-changing foods
book
love it and love you you're a human
angel from above
hey that's that's a beyond a compliment
that should be beyond a nice compliment
thank you so much
um by the way there's a subtitle
question too please have subtitles i
enjoy reading your books unfortunately i
can't hear you
there are subtitles here on facebook and
youtube
and tick tock i'm pretty sure
let's see and i'm honored you're here
truly
yes i'm really proud of all of you by
the way for all you're doing
bletchley says what causes your hair or
scalp to hurt
um a lot of neurotoxins cause that
that's one thing that occurs so any kind
of neurotoxins can cause that
any kind of low-grade viral infection
shingles is a big one for that for
hair and scalp to hurt or not hair but
scalp
yeah and well yeah i mean hair too to
the scalp area
so that can easily do that when you have
low grade viral infections so
i mean what i would do if my scalp was
hurting like that
i would be for sure making sure there's
no milk cheese butter eggs making sure
there's no apple cider vinegar or
vinegar
making sure that's out of your
out of your diet making sure there's no
nutritional yeast
making sure there's no corn or soy just
just try to eliminate those first no
pork and i know that's a lot i
i know that's a lot but i would do that
just to move the needle get the celery
juice in see if it starts breaking down
any low grade viral stuff
and and talk to your doctor i mean you
know and say hey look medical medium
has helped a lot of doctors and he tells
doctors about the fact that low-grade
vital stuff hurts the scalp because
those are
nerves and any kind of nerves means
neurotoxins you could talk to a
practitioner about that
they might the light bulb might hit over
their head and they might then help and
support you to what you're doing
um tiana says anthony please talk about
ears ringing
i talk about that and cleanse the heel
look i'm not trying to push a book on
you just go to the library get it for
free if you want everything's free
um you can get it on amazon sure and
it's on sale there
like a wicket sale which is cool for
this book but the ringing in the ears is
the information's in there tinnitus the
whole bid it's a low-grade viral
infection
and labyrinth of the inner ear and it
gets inflamed and it starts to swell and
that tinnitus can go
just crazy it could go they could you
could get popping fluttering
buzzing humming you could get ringing
you could sound like church bells i mean
you could sound like
sirens like sirens all of it in
in the years and it could get brutal and
it gets worse at the end of the day or
gets worse at night
you know you should do medical meeting
podcast at apple podcast
catch the neurological symptoms episode
don't miss it if any of you guys haven't
heard the 17 episodes please go and
listen
five meditations you can't i mean really
it's the information is so
packed the medical meme podcast at apple
podcast um
alicia diane says wish netflix would do
a documentary following your journey
they've asked me for years that's what i
want to talk to you guys about too
sometimes i'm glad you brought the
question up
i've been asked to do tv shows for years
and all the networks they've always
knocked on my door they want to do the
medical medium series the tv series but
i always felt that it wasn't going to be
it wasn't going to be enough about the
person it was going to be just me my
story my gift
and yeah i guess if he got a really big
ego that's really a fun thing to do you
know and
i'm not saying i don't have an ego right
everybody's got something in them
that sparked and says hey wait a minute
hey wait a minute but
um but i just don't want it to be about
me and that's what happened i remember
over 10 years ago even a little over 10
years ago i asked to do tv shows meaning
my own tv series my networks and i know
anybody else would have many other
people would have just jumped on it
and i get asked to this day for netflix
and other doc
docu-series documentaries tv shows
all of it so constantly get asked and
i turn it down and what do i do i mess
around on tick-tock
i don't want to say i turn all those
things down and yeah those things would
give me credibility
they would give me credibility i
realized that you know big production
company behind you
big you know hey let's protect him and
put him on one of the channels one of
the cable big cable networks
his own series and it would give you
credibility because then probably nobody
would mess with you you probably
wouldn't be tried to be messed with or
tried to be canceled all the time or try
to be discriminated against you'd have
like you'd have a big production company
over your
over umbrellaing you you know and i
guess it would give you some credibility
but you know what i do instead
i take my beatings take my lashings and
i hop on tick tock
and do videos but create the best stocky
series style
medical medium podcast to have on
podcast packed with information
then you know because it's it's really
is and i put out
and i put out the books um
it's funny michelle says yeah they're
trying to steal your stuff
of course of course michelle mclellan
says
well done on your tick tock thanks for
answering this live chat
i love your book fair play from this
irish girl
well thanks for everything you know um
yeah i mean um monica says i like your
humor greatly
monica i'm honored um look i got a
tick-tock
episode coming out i think it's going to
come out tomorrow
uh i hope you think it's funny you know
you never know maybe
maybe it might i might not come out
tomorrow i'm not sure when
it's a video actually let's see leah
renee says any ideas for stomach
paralysis gastroparesis anything like
that
you know it depends if you're still
eating if you're not on a feeding tube
if you're on feeding tubes you know
there's other techniques and stuff but
if you're actually eating
and you're not on a feeding tube or
anything you know i personally like for
gastroparesis the
different mono eating cleanses here um
celery juice is also important too
i talk about that the monowing cleanses
are great
um the heavy metal detox smoothie
getting heavy metals out can really help
so there's a mono eating chapter you can
talk to your doctor about it
um i help doctors about that all the
time with the astroparesis
jeanette says hey jeanette glad you're
here your info is truth and it shines on
its own
thank you it does even though all that
muck out there tries to squash it down
marc o'neal love your sense of humor
thanks mark thanks brother thanks for
being on here man
i appreciate it mark catherine king and
them lives
and then lives are a sacred place that
means the world to me
that means the world to me so that's
incredible really does
seriously um sheena says where do i
begin on the medical medium book list
let's start with cleanse the heal
and then work your way work your way
through the other books lorraine l says
no you actually are
real hey lorraine
lorraine's on you're in the uk right is
the uk or you just or you're i know
you're overseas
you're not in the u.s every time i read
your comments on youtube
um and facebook and stuff i think you're
you're
you're um i don't know if it's scotland
i don't know where it is but it's
somewhere out there
and i'm probably wrong about that from
what i remember susan janet
listen to his podcast on anxiety thank
you it's really a powerful podcast
episode you guys got to hear it
evelyn dixon my daughter has lipomas how
to correct it
first thing about lipomas to understand
my poems eat
they're hungry they have these little
tentacles coming off of them blood
vessels
so if you got a lipoma say you gotta you
gotta a lipoma
and it's there fatty tumor it's a fatty
growth it's got these
little blood vessels and these blood
vessels they
draw up food they draw food to keep the
lipoma growing right keep it alive and
what happens is if you're eating eggs
it's just going to feed the life home if
you're eating cheese and milk and butter
it's going to feed the lipoma
gluten feeds the life home so when
you're eating that food it goes into the
lipoma
so get those foods out for sure to start
with that's one thing you want to do
truly nathan haynes nathan glad to be
here glad to be here with you man
love your work legend hey legend that's
cool
keep the light shining thank you hey
that's that's cool you know when i was a
child it's like
huh never thought someone would call me
a legend someday
um fabi says
anthony i was wondering if you could
talk about or do an episode for pregnant
women
or women and they would like to get
pregnant is very important instead of
taking prenatal vitamins yes
i'm gonna do a pregnancy episode i have
to get these
podcast episodes done i did 17 of them
and i and i haven't even scratched the
surface meanwhile
it's they're packed with information so
much to do denise says we love you
honored that that that you care you care
about the purpose you care about what
we're
trying to do spirit compassion and i get
the information out
regardless of of adversity
constantly i mean if you guys knew the
crap
medical medium has been through hmm all
for
what right didn't do anything besides
trying to
reverse illness and sickness make sure
people get their lives back which is the
most important thing
get people off of mattress island and
couch island
but you know because that's critical
it's critical to do that
critical you guys anybody who just got
on here i'm going on tick tock i'm going
to be making dinner i just got to go to
ig first but then you know and then go
to
to tick tock to make dinner and answer
questions thoroughly
debra can you please say more about
osteoporosis yeah
osteoporosis really bad cases of it
including you know
stenosis that come with it including
um including other things too
just um ankylosing spondylitis including
all these different things that occur
um osteoporosis being like really
popular that's being like
one that so many people have a lot of
times people lose their calcium from
years of vinegar from years of caffeine
from years of acidosis that's a big
piece of it so they lose their calcium
so when you do vinegars
your calcium just sucks right out of
your bones and teeth all of it
so keep that in mind no vinegars keep
that in mind no caffeine
and then leafy greens leafy greens are
critical so like spinach like medical
medium spinach soups and
the medical medium healing broth every
day if you want hey trisha maurice here
just saw that comment come up
incredible so glad you're here oranges
are important citrus is critical for
osteoporosis like oranges
grapefruits lemons those are so
important for osteoporosis you guys
so important it's a big deal um
because that's where the calcium is the
calcium is there you know broccoli is
important too but
but really the citrus is a big deal
because calcium is deep in the earth and
the citrus trees the
roots go deep into the earth and they
grow in places that are high in calcium
it's really important um
really important um yeah so going to
tick-tock just so you guys know but i'm
not going to
quite yet almost there i just got to go
and make a quick stop at ig
let everybody know i'm going to tic toc
going to make kale salad the whole bit
um jennifer sprindley says yes please do
a pregnancy one okay we'll get a medical
mean podcast pregnancy one
in the works um wyla green said we'd
love to do podcast on you
and your life i want to do that while i
do but you know i i worry and
everybody's gonna say hey he's making
about him he's making it about him
um so i'm going to be answering
questions thoroughly on tik tok like
really thoroughly answering questions on
tick tocks i'm letting you know
that's what i'm going to be doing
thoroughly asking questions it's really
like
an educational session too you got get
your pens out kind of thing it's pretty
intense
and i'm going to be making dinner and
making food kale salad how cool is that
maybe some other stuff potatoes gonna
have some potatoes today i can't wait
uh elena says how much salt do you think
is okay daily
um make sure you don't do too much uh
depending on if you're feeling sick and
you got problems with anything like that
i would stick to celery juice spinach
soups keep the salt away
use lemon on everything have some
tomatoes in your food
and that's the kind of salt intake
that's natural that's really incredible
for you
and i would keep back on the salt but if
you're somebody that really loves salt
try to do a little bit then if you don't
feel so bad you're not struggling
susie king i have tick tock but can't
find you huh
okay tick tock dot com forward slash at
medical medium
tick tock dot com forward slash at
medical medium link is in the
description
try that hopefully that gets you there
because i want to have you there
anyway guys i am going to ig
and we're going to do a couple minutes
on there and
let's go is trisha marie going to be
there because let's just sit down she
goes from there and then she goes to ig
anyway you guys i'll see you if you
come over