[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and it's
decades ahead of what's out there now
and that that just reminded me about
something you guys that you know back
when back a few decades ago and just
even even not even a few decades ago
let's just go two decades ago the
internet wasn't in it you know it wasn't
in that stage it was in obviously if
there was even an internet at that time
and you know when someone was sick when
someone was sick and they had symptoms
they had like fatigue or they couldn't
function well or they had a weak
sensitive central nervous system or they
had vertigo balance issues being dizzy
um anything of that sort they weren't
well for some reason sinus infections
chronically chronic UTI mystery symptoms
aches and pains neuralgia you know
tingles and numbness the list goes on
migraines all unexplainable all mystery
when someone had all that there was
really no support system it didn't exist
if you walked into a
drugstore you couldn't get eation this
is hysterical you know I purposely
walked into a drugstore a long time ago
and this is decades ago I walked into
the drugstore to look at the vitamins
see if they had vitamins in the
drugstore and they had at the time you
know two major company vitamins you
probably know who they are right I'm not
going to mention any names and they're
just sitting on the shelf there and I
went to the pharmacist I said do you
guys have any eonia and they laughed at
at me they laughed at me literally
laughed me out of the
pharmacy okay I'm just telling you right
now and okay sure this is 25 30 years
ago but I'm telling you right now laugh
me out of the pharmacy think about that
for a minute okay and that wasn't just
there it was it was Nationwide like that
so what does that tell you just that
alone so when you were sick back then
with anything and some of you many of
you probably experienced it were are you
kidding I mean that's the whole point if
you were sick back then with
anything good luck good luck now you
would think things are actually better
now we have the internet thank God we
have all these different things thank
God okay and and you know we have
communication you think things would be
better now now you had all these fancy
books out we got experts everywhere but
chronic illness is
quadrupling forget quadruple it's it's
way past that it's way past it it's it's
by 10 it's by 15 times past it tripling
doubling doubling times five it that's
where chronic illness is going and
everybody's got a symptom you may know
people you may know family members you
you may know friends you may know loved
ones you may know anybody that's got a
problem that's got something and here's
the problem the problem is there's the
misinformation that's out there both
conventionally and alternatively it's
riddled in there everywhere so the iCal
medium radio show we're clearing that up
that's the whole point you stay with me
for the ride we're going to clear up
each each show we're going to just just
move forward all together we're going to
work together on this because I've said
it before in some of the last shows I
need your help too to get the
information out there so you can help
and spread that and spread it to your
family and help people and help a friend
or a stranger that you run into because
it's incredible when that occurs because
you offer assistance just by accident
also just by just just being it just
starts to happen and the world starts to
change but back then forget it you get
chronic fatigue syndrome you're just
you're you're just stupid that's all
you're just stupid if it's something
that can't be tested for and measured
you're just you're just stupid that's
how bad it was it's still that bad in
other ways we're still in these weird
places now a lot of misinformation a lot
of trouble we're still we're still the
reason why is because we're dealing with
Antiquities we're dealing with antique
tests antique information even with a
Best Equipment the best functional
equipment but you know the best
alternative you name it we're still in
the Dark Ages so we have to clear this
up because you don't have 10 years I
don't have 10 years we don't have 20
years I don't have 30 years to wait for
answers life is precious and it has to
be cleared up now and that's what we're
doing okay so today's show we're talking
about grains The Good the Bad and the
Ugly are grains good for you are they
bad for you are they good for you are
they bad for you am I driving you crazy
yet or we going to have to all right
hang in there okay I'm going to just I'm
just going to relax I'm going to Calment
down we're going to have to get our seat
bels on for sure okay for this one cuz
grains is a big topic and I don't mean
greens I'm not saying greens okay I'm
saying grains all right we're going to
talk about these grains it's really
important um so I'm excited so let's
let's talk about this hey you know and
and look remember there's an LA event
coming up Los Angeles there's an event
coming up I'm really excited for it
because since I was young when Spirit
was talking to me and still does of
course and I hear Spirit perfectly clear
and I diagnose my grandmother of lung
cancer after that you know after that
and growing up a little bit I asked
Spirit what more can I do what more can
I do for everyone I saw the suffering
Spirit was telling me everything that
was wrong with everybody I remember
being at this convention with my parents
and I was 8 years old and I was at this
convention and you know and I was it was
really crowded and anyone who knows me
or knows anything about me knows that I
go blind when I'm around too many people
that's why at the events I practically
fall off the stage it's it's actually
kind of humorous and embarrassing at the
same time because the more readings I do
it's it's why I have an assistant come
with me everywhere it's why I have to go
on the plane with my assistant because
150 passengers on the plane I'm going to
get readings for every last one of them
there's no break there's no relaxing
there's no going on a cruise and one
medium said to me oh that that's that's
I I could I can't shut it off either
that's not true because I see everybody
going on cruises I see everybody having
fun everybody taking vacations trust me
everybody can shut it down enough I
can't shut it down and so the
information's going to come nonstop it's
always been like like this I'm going to
know if someone's got a brain tumor on
the plane I'm going to know if somebody
walking by's got diabetes I'm going to
know if someone's got this and what
happens though is because of that I'm
forced to scan and I'm forced to hear
spirit and I start going blind so I go
almost permanently like mostly blind
depending on the situation and how many
people so at the events it gets kind of
funny so I asked so what happened when I
was younger I asked people you know I
mean I asked Spirit sorry about this I
asked Spirit what can I do what else can
I do and I remember being at a
convention with my family and it was
crowded it was mobbed and I was getting
the readings Non-Stop Non-Stop and I
came across this one person who was
really suffering just suffering really
bad had some terrible things going on
when I mean terrible means you know when
I looked inside the body I saw
everything wrong that was imaginable and
I was like how is this person even
standing and I said to Spirit what can I
do and spirit says let's do the light
blast let's do the light technique I'll
send down spirit said to me I'll send
down light on the crown of the person's
head full throttle
you just work with me on it and let's do
it we sent the light down on the person
and then I started doing it to everybody
that's around me everybody at the
convention sending the light down
practicing and from there on out there
on out I learn that technique starting
with you know round 8 years old really
perfecting it and I do it at the events
I don't care what it takes I don't care
if it exhaust me I don't care if you
have to scrape me off the floor at the
end of the event and just in literally
like you know piling pile me into a
hotel room it's just it's got to get
done I got to do everything I can so I'm
really looking for it look if you're
there it's great we'll ignite the
healing process people have already done
it and been there know what it does for
them they felt it there's all kinds of
testimonials everybody knows about it so
join us if you can also check out the
lifechanging foods book check that out
um finally thank God it's done it's you
know it's it's pretty much ready meaning
ready ready for takeoff make sure you
lock down a copy get into that webinar
that we're doing we're we're offering
all these different things and uh make
sure you you lock down you know a whole
thing I did just recently I talked about
raw honey having over 200,000
phytochemicals that stop disease and
protect us in the 21st century and it's
all from Spirit knowing this information
it's in the book it's in the
life-changing Foods book just lock down
a copy you'll when you get this book you
won't be mad at me you won't be upset at
me I promise you you actually won't you
won't be upset at me you know when you
get you know when you go out and buy a
book every now and then you buy a book
and you're like oh okay wait a minute
all right I've heard this before no I
promise you you haven't heard this
before and it's lifechanging so you know
so check that out um so yeah look let's
talk about grains are you guys worried
about grains at all I mean you know on
any level have you been told that it's
really bad for you to eat grains are you
you know uh are you on a ketogenic diet
are you on a grain-free diet are you
scared to death about
carbohydrates you know what is it going
on are you afraid of fruit um you know
all these questions you they come to
mind because I hear people all the time
people ask me Anthony are grains good
for us are they good for us they bad for
us they good for us and I hear this all
the time I hear it all day long I mean I
hear it from everybody and there are are
answers to this question there are but
first we have to explore some
misunderstandings we have to explore
some misunder understandings are you
guys open for that are we going to do
that I'm just going to sip a little bit
of this tea right
here it's a grainfree
tea
um all right so here's the deal we have
to understand something about autoimmune
we have to we have to visit the
autoimmune topic I know I drive you guys
crazy sometimes with it but it's one of
the greatest mistakes of all time it's
the greatest mistake next to
nuclear nuclear weapons that are out
there sitting in bunkers okay this is
this is the next greatest mistake of all
history and of all time on the planet
and it's the confusion of autoimmune
where conventional and alternative
doctors and
practitioners believe that autoimmune is
the body attacking itself this could
never be more wrong than ever before
this happened due to the fact that
modern medicine doesn't know what's
wrong with someone and what's causing
their lupus symptoms their Celiac
problem their their um colitis problem
with their intestinal tract their
Hashimoto thyroiditis and and Medicine
Medical Research Medical Science doesn't
know what causes it so guess who takes
the blame you your body takes the blame
100% that's the easiest way out the
greatest way out for medical denial it's
the greatest way so you feel like crap
you feel like your body's attacking
itself you feel like your body's
betraying you you like the way that
feels I don't I don't like the way that
feels I had someone tell me someone tell
me who just you know believes in
alternative medicine you know enough and
believes in you know conventional
medicine but very this person's very
like you know um what is it black and
white in many ways or whatever which is
totally cool I'm not saying that's bad
and and this person's just like you know
no no medical science medical research
understands they know what autoimmune is
and I'm like no they don't they don't
know what it is it's not the body
attacking itself and they're like well
well of course it is and I'm like no of
course it's not of course it's not what
happens is with hosoo thyroiditis your
thyroid gets inflamed because there's a
pathogen called Epstein bar which I
brought to the attention to the world
years ago and I'm bringing attention to
the world now and and we can fact check
it we could backdate it I brought that
to the world and you're hearing it here
at the show and you're going to hear it
now all the time out there in other
books coming out you name it AB bar
causes hasim modus thyroiditis all stems
from me with the information brought
from Spirit I'm boasting on that but
it's a fact so you know that any new any
new people logging into this show today
knows that it comes from here and it's
important to know so I want you to stay
tuned for further shows so you get
information that's moving people forward
information that's Advanced and so it's
what what happens is autoimmune is just
the body producing anti Auto antibodies
and antibodies to attack the virus not
the body not the physical body not the
physical organs they're not being
attacked at all in fact your body is
working handin hand to get rid of a
pathogen that's inflaming you so hear me
out a pathogen virus like Hashimoto
thyroid itis it's a virus inflaming the
thyroid the virus is inflaming the
thyroid not the body the body's not
inflaming the the thyroid it's a virus
it's Epstein bar same thing with all
these other different autoimmune things
rheumatoid arthritis is a virus
inflaming the joints and the body is
trying to stop it and inflammation is
created by the pathogen inflaming the
joints and if you don't look if you want
to know more about this you you get the
medical medium book to be with and then
you know I talk about even more in
life-changing foods but what happens
here is that this confusion is one of
the worst of all time it really is I
could go into a lot of other ones too
but this one's one of the worst because
it breaks down your immune system and
messes you up messes you up because if
you think your body's attacking itself
you don't stand a chance you don't stand
a chance it's like like that's saying a
snowball's chance in hell or whatever it
is whatever it is you're not going to
stand a
chance so you have to rewire that right
now bam it's rewired I'm telling you so
it's important to know your body doesn't
attack itself and I'm not talking about
it on a spiritual way I'm talking on a
physical way I'm talking about science
that's not discovered that way that's
how I'm talking about it right here okay
and so the bottom line is is we have to
you have to adopt that you have to make
that a belief system you're going to
have to make that part of a factual
belief system because what happens is
autoimmune is really now wrapped up with
the grain thing grains you guys know
what I'm talking about you do right it's
all about grains causing autoimmune
grains causing inflammation that's not
accurate either that's not accurate at
all so wheat causing inflammation that's
not accurate at all I don't care if it's
the best newest autoimmune book that hit
the Shelf just recently or coming up or
whatever it is if it doesn't realize it
in that book or whoever's writing that
or doing whatever or talking on some
podcast if they don't realize it's the
wheat feeding a
pathogen such as a virus or bacteria and
that virus and bacteria eats the wheat
and then eliminates a
toxin or the virus and the pathogen eat
the wheat and grow stronger and cause
more damage that's the truth if no one
has that in their their books yet which
they don't we look out for that stuff
cuz we want everybody moving forward we
want people to know the truth then you
know what you're dealing with something
that's already an antique you may as
well just I said this before and I'm
saying it again may as well just go
antique antiquing on the weekend and
come home with a l lamp an old lamp
you're better off so this is really
important this is important to know this
and and I'm I'm not saying oh ho ho this
is because Anthony's got all the answers
no this is just how it works what
happens is there's people out there that
are 70 years old that feel fine they
don't have Celiac they don't have
anything going on they don't have you
know all they just don't have nothing
going on I know people like that I was
just talking to a friend who's uh whose
you know parent is 96 now and nothing
going on nothing to complain about at
all guess what she eats she eats Bagels
wheat
Bagels from from Dunkin Donuts she eats
wheat Bagels from Dunkin Donuts she puts
cream cheese on it too cream cheese on
her wheat bagel she's not having
autoimmune wait a minute if it's an
inflammatory food how come she's not
inflamed I want to know I want to know
okay so you see what I'm trying to say
and it goes on and on and on and on
that's no joke I know lots of people
that could eat what they want they could
have pizza it's no big deal they could
have pizza wheat and cheese lots of
Wheat and they're not getting inflamed I
know because I do scans I don't see any
inflammation and they're not complaining
of One symptom no aches and pains
they're not complaining of you know this
and that they're not complaining of
fibromyalgia they're not complaining of
anything because they're lacking one
thing they're lacking the pathogen that
feeds off of something that's what
they're lacking do you see how it works
you guys I mean seriously you guys are
on board with me I need to know you're
on board I need to know that you're
you're with me here because this is how
it works I mean do you know somebody
that's feeling good and they could eat
they could eat a chocolate cake just
filled with wheat and just throw some
lard in there too throw throw also MSG
in there too whatever you know throw
anything you want in there that fondant
that's on chocolate cake just filled
with God knows what weak gluten it's
100% weak gluten or whatever it is with
sugar pasted in it so you know and um
and that's how that's what I'm talking
about and it's like uh you know and so
here's the deal the deal is it's not the
wheat I'm not saying the wheat's good
and I'm going to cover that I'm going to
cover that and talk about what grains to
avoid what grains you know if you do
like you can have some I'm going to talk
about that so don't get me wrong I'm not
the pro weak guy I'm not the pro weat
guy I don't want anybody eating wheat
I'm just telling you it's not what
causes the inflammation those books are
outdated I want them updated that's why
I'm complaining I want them updated
that's what I want the reason why is
because like I said before we got the
internet now but there's still the wrong
information out there we got communities
but they're dealing with the wrong
information and people are still sick
staying sick and getting sicker and
sicker and sicker and like I said at one
show it's an epidemic but it's an epic
demic it's an epidemic and that's what
we're dealing with all all around you
guys that's what we're dealing with you
know you know you see it so so here's
the deal let's let's talk about grains
for a little bit let's go back down into
history a little bit too which is kind
of funny back in
the80s the the deal was sprouted wheat
if you were eating sprouted wheat H you
were you were eating you were eating
healthy so it wasn't it was just
sprouted wheat was the deal you go into
the health food store and yeah you can
pull a loaf of sprouted wheat out off
the off out of the freezer or maybe even
freshly made you can you know get a loaf
of sprouted wheat and that was a big
deal that was a big deal it was in the
70s and 80s that was a big deal it was
that sprouted wheat
bread and um and you know now you go
into the store and there's just
gluten-free this gluten-free that that
you got everything this everything rice
you got you know different things you
got Millet bread um you know the whole
bit and you know it's a different you
got quinoa pasta whatever you know and
then you got corn you got all this corn
stuff as well and we're going to talk
about that too because corn is corn is a
grain as well corn is a grain as well so
you know people think it's a vegetable
um so we're going to we got to fix that
you know I heard somebody tell me
recently no Corn's a vegetable I'm like
no no no Corn's a grain and they're like
no it can't be I don't no I promise you
it's a grain and so that's you know
that's another thing to talk about we're
going to but back then all you had was
that sprouted wheat bread now we got
better options we got better grains too
you know singled out if you want to you
know get yourself some like organic
Millet you want to get yourself some
quinoa so we got different grains and
everything but back to the autoimmune
thing the great maake autoimmune just
back to that so if we eat something that
feeds a condition you know a pathogen
that's in us we get
inflammation I've been telling people
for years you eat eggs you're going to
get more Hashimoto because the obsin bar
and the thyroid that causes hasim Hashi
sorry Hashimoto thyroiditis the Epstein
bar in the thyroid that feeds off of
eggs so it eats the eggs and then it you
know and then it grows nodul you grow
nodules in your thyroid it creates cyst
in your thyroid it can create thyroid
cancer the Epstein bar can even create
thyroid cancer I'm the one who brought
the fact that thyroid cancer is caused
by Epstein bar um that's that
information Spirit and I brought to town
too and and also breast cancer is caused
by Epstein bar as well and guess what
now they're starting to finally bring it
out medical research and medical science
is talking about it for the first time
in history um um I've been talking about
Epstein bar um creating breast cancer
for over 30 years so anyway the bottom
line is is that you know these pathogens
they feed off of the eggs they feed off
of the wheat when it comes down to the
grains it feeds off the
corn that's what happens there so these
grains certain grains can feed a
pathogen and that's why it's all these
diet gluten-free diet books they're like
oh the autoimmune diet oh this
autoimmune you know no
actually it's really should be kind of
redone and refixed because the stuff is
outdated it's a pathogen feeding off of
the wheat this is why someone can eat
cupcakes every morning you know for like
50 years and not have a problem I've
seen this over and over again but times
are changing times are changing and
there's less people pathogen free
there's less people free of of viruses
less people free of bacteria you guys
and the less people there are that means
we're you know we're we're seeing
dinosaurs now people were you know
dinosaurs where you know they're they're
the last of the the breed that can eat
what they want and not have a problem
and then there's some rare young you
know young ones that are rare and they
can do it too right now but it's
becoming less and less and less because
we got people filled with more radiation
more toxic heavy metals plot lots of
pathogens you know utilizing it all and
then utilizing the Grain and this is why
grain doesn't
work so what grains are good what grains
are bad first of all if you're dealing
with any condition or any symptom you
want to keep wheat out chances are the
wheat's feeding something and when it's
feeding something that something is
creating a problem whatever that could
be when it's strep
related so that strep strepa cacus
feeding off of grain causing more sinus
problems more sinus congestion it's
strep Aus that causes all the UTI by the
way it's it's not yeast it's strep yeast
is just always around when you have a
bacteria that's causing the real problem
so when you think you have a yeast
infection it's a UTI it's actually a
strepa cacus infection with yeast being
present and they look for the yeast they
don't look for the strepa cacus just so
you know it's rare they even bother to
look for it so you get told you got a
yeast
infection and um and then when you get
you know if you get a UTI that gets so
bad where it gets to the kidneys and
there's bleeding then they finally say
oh yeah it's bacteria let's do lots of
antibiotics you know they just forget
the yeast tag they just don't use the
yeast tag anymore but it's always been
strepa cacus that's how it's always with
always has been with UT so when you're
dealing with grains like wheat you could
be feeding a condition can be feeding
strep it could be feeding you
coli you could be feeding um some SE
diff that's in your system that's been
sitting around slightly dormant for
years and years and years you could be
feeding um the viruses all the different
viruses there are if you're dealing with
a retrovirus you know like HIV you're
dealing with a retrovirus you don't want
to feed it grains so that's another
thing
too if you're dealing with stealth
viruses you don't want to feed them
grains um if you're dealing with the flu
you don't want to have a grain well a
grain like wheat you don't want to like
a grain like
corn so those are two that you really
don't want to
use um and and we want to be careful we
want to be careful so these SE are some
of the things to think about of how it
works um and and let's go into a couple
different things while we have time
about grains I don't want to leave you
guys hanging without covering like info
about them are there good
grains yes there are um quinoa is a good
grain um people are convinced it's not a
grain I think
psychologically it was a really good
twist but it's a grain just so you you
know people are convinced it's not a
grain people are convinced it's just a
seed that's incorrect I'm going to tell
you that right now it's a grain but the
technique of calling it a seed has upped
its value tremendously by taking it out
of the grain world it's a bril it was
brilliant it was absolutely brilliant
because it it really did Elevate Quin
elevated out of it it said no you're the
Jesus Christ of of the grains you're not
a grain and it elevated it up but it's a
grain sorry about that it is so so the
deal is is quinoa is a good one now if
you're you know into like um if you're
into like uh no car and autoimmune is
caused by grains you're you're not going
to be offered quinoa most
likely um but it's actually okay now if
you're somebody you're dealing with a
lot of different symptoms and a lot of
different varieties of symptoms you've
been diagnosed with multiple sclerosis
it could be anything Hashimoto could be
anything lupus um and you know
Scleroderma to um you know anything
sarcoidosis to um you know spino litis
whatever it is that you're dealing with
all these different things ecomori to
different problems ra um chronic fatigue
then it's a good idea to keep even the
good grains out even the good grains out
but your heart set on it your heart set
on on it you really want the grain then
you want to be thinking about quinoa
it's one of the best ones if you um if
you know if you're not dealing with a
lot but you enjoy grains you can go with
quinoa let's talk about another one too
uh Millet Millet is a good one now the
problem is with grains now too is that
they're changing a little bit there's a
lot of GMO grains on the market they're
moving in that kind of ruined it in so
many ways like wheat's changed wheat's
been hybridized so many times that's one
way that that's kind of gotten it a
little messed up um the old days it was
hybridized and and hybridization is not
a bad thing but when it comes down to
when its grains it's not helpful at all
and um so Millet is something that's a
good grain too you can get Millet bread
but Millet bread usually comes with all
this other stuff so you're better off
just cooking up Millet on its own Millet
by itself is really nutritious it's a
gluten-free grain quinoa is gluten-free
and it's a really these are two
nutritious grains so it I learned this
too you know it's food is really
expensive really expensive I mean it it
it takes a whole paycheck to shop
nowadays um you're buying fruit you're
buying vegetables people don't buy a lot
of fruit really anyway you know so which
has to change in the world we got to get
people eating more fruit for their
longevity but you know people buy
vegetables people buy you know proteins
people you know and it's expensive and
it adds up really fast you know and I
have people that are on budgets I know
people that are on budgets they go go
look I only can have I only have $50
this week and what do I do you know only
have $25 this week what do I do and if I
think they're not so bad off with
different conditions and pathogens and
everything else if I think they're not
so bad off with all of that I'll say
look why don't you get some Millet why
don't you get some Miller it's really
cheap really inexpensive you can cook a
huge pot of it it's not going to feed
your
pathogens because you know Epstein bar
really doesn't feed off of millet it
really doesn't you know there's
pathogens that won't feed off of it it's
not the it's not great for anybody to be
on lots of grain or grain if they have a
lot of conditions because something
could potentially feed off of it but
Millet is one of those foods that
doesn't really do that so much so I'll
say to somebody who's only got $25 a
week uh which I totally get I totally
understand and it's like here you know
get a pot of millet cook that pot of
millet once a day and in the end that
pot of millet is going to cost you you
know every time you have a bowl of M
it's going to be 10 cents 15 cents I
don't know what it is something like
that and that's one option and the same
thing with with quinoa you can get
quinoa it Cooks up it's light and fluffy
you can get away with it um oatmeal
that's one right there oatmeal
gluten-free oatmeal why do we say that
cuz it's always process in factories
with gluten it's always processed in
factories with gluten and wheat and
everything else so you want to make sure
it's gluten-free so there's not gluten
if you're worried about gluten but
oatmeal still cut of Oats that works for
some people but listen listen understand
this some people they just don't do good
with grains but some people don't do
good with meat some people don't do good
with chicken some people don't do good
with you know fruit they say some people
don't do good with vegetables at all
some people can't eat a salad salad um I
have people who can't eat a salad but
they can eat oatmeal I have people that
can eat you seriously I got people that
all they could do is you know eat
chicken and they can't eat one
vegetable um you know I got people that
you know can only eat fruit it's the
only thing that feels good in their
stomach and they can't eat you know a
vegetable I got people that can only eat
fruit and can't eat meat I got people
that only you know can eat meat and and
like one vegetable so it's it's you know
it's it's kind of like that you got to
see where you're at but
oatmeal won't necessarily feed a bad
pathogen so if you need to use it or can
use it you can if you can you can um
Millet won't necessarily feed a pathogen
if you need it you can use it I like
Millet better uh than oatmeal I like
quinoa better than oatmeal and like I
said affordability it's pretty cool
definitely don't do Sprout at wheat it's
not it's a waste of your time it's a
sprout at wheat it's totally a waste of
your time um and stay away from wheat
completely if you're dealing with any
symptom or condition and if you don't
even have a symptom or condition I still
just don't even like wheat um cuz the
potential is there the potential is
there for something the potential is
there let's talk about rice arsenic are
no arsenic is arsenic in rice okay this
is this is going to blow your mind
is there arsenic and rice no there isn't
there isn't yeah do you have Stones
ready cuz you're going to have to Stone
me to death over here because there I'm
I'm going to get a lot of people angry
okay this was a
misconception there is arsenic in one
variety of stripped white rice okay one
variety of stripped white rice out there
there's some arsenic in there due to the
pesticides but those arsenic pesticides
are on
everything everything they on everything
and that's where it came from I mean
that's where where it's happening it's
everywhere it's copper and Arsenic and
it's on conventional stuff I mean if
you're really really in a financial
problem and you can't eat one thing
organic then we yes we do conventional
fruits and vegetables without a doubt
but the Arsenic is on
every it's in every pesticide it's
ladled everywhere it's it's on
everything so you get organic
rice and you pick organic brown rice the
safest and the best is organic short
grain brown rice organic short grain
brown rice okay that's the safest
there's no arsenic on it there's no
arsenic in it it's not it's not there
because arsenic comes from those heavy
laden pesticides sides especially in
other countries where they're still
using DDT everything else that's where
that arsenic is I'm just telling you
right now this was another Mass
confusion don't be afraid of rice um
rice is gluten-free can totally do rice
if you really like it um absolutely had
someone tell me hey look you know I ate
rice all these years I heard it's bad
for you now I heard it causes autoimmune
no rice doesn't cause autoimmune rice if
you eat a lot of it it could
potentially instigate a pathogen but if
you're feeling healthy enough you're
feeling stable enough you don't have a
lot of symptoms you don't have a lot of
conditions you don't have a lot of money
you want to have a pot of brown rice you
have a pot of brown rice if you really
want have it with
vegetables you see how it works it's not
about what Anthony's belief system is
like does Anthony you know believe in
this and this only or does Anthony
believe in that sounds silly but it's
not about that it's about what's right
it's about what works about what's
really wrong with someone's Health it's
about the right information if you
logged on to this show you're going to
get the right information you're going
to get why autoimmune is called called
Auto autoimmune and how the blame was
put on us you're going to get why you
know we're told their body's attacking
itself you're going to get why we get
sick you're going to get what's really
causing the sicknesses oh it's not the
grain you're also going to get a guy
that says which is me don't eat the
grain don't eat wheat don't eat corn
they'll feed the pathogens so it's not
like I'm sitting here saying oh you can
eat all the grain you want oh forget
autoimmune that's not what I'm talking
about you guys are listening so if you
just logged on to the show go back to
the beginning and you're going to have
to hear the beginning of the show
so how can grains work better for us if
we're going to eat them if you're going
to choose to eat them I mean me
personally I like eating some fruit
because I want the longevity I want the
antioxidants I want the
phytochemicals um I want the asparagus I
want the spinach I want the papaya you
know I like those because of what they
offer I talked about the raw honey I
like the raw honey I know I get the
vegans so upset I understand I get the
plant-based people so upset with the
honey but we're going to do a show and
I'm going to talk about how honey really
is vegan by the way so this a whole
another misconception I have to help
everybody out with it's so important to
know this the vegans need to know this
that honey is okay to eat now I really
got everybody mad but here's the deal
here's the deal um it's all about
phytochemicals what has the most
medicine what can help and heal our
diseases and our conditions what can
protect us from cancer is why I did
lifechanging Foods book if you haven't
ordered a copy yet just don't forget
because it's it's my greatest prayers
and wishes that people actually have
that information and I want people to
heal and then you could help other
people heal and other people heal and
that's what it's about so you know it's
about this fight of chemicals it's about
the antioxidants it's about all of that
information it's not about what I like
what I don't like and so that's very
important it's not what about a belief
system I subscribe to it's about just
making sure you guys get what you need
celery works great with with uh grains
it works incredible you can you can cook
celery steam it chop it up have it in a
grain dish if you want you can have it
raw chopped up raw and put in a quinoa
dish celery is amazing you can for that
it's incredible for that really healing
really profoundly powerful when you put
it with a grain meaning that what celery
does is celery makes the grain work it
makes the grain um
eliminate its potential of
phytochemicals because grains have
medicine in them too so what happens is
when you have celery with with quinoa if
if you have celery with a little brown
rice if that's something you want if you
have that the celery the mineral salts
in the celery the the rare mineral salts
that are are not measured by science and
research turn the grain into something
that's what happens it Cates the grain
it Cates what is good the phytochemical
in the grain could have that with quinoa
you can have celery with any grain you
choose cucumbers chop up cucumbers have
that with a quinoa dish have that with a
millet dish have that with a rice dish
incredible cucumbers help as well they
help balance the acidity of grains cuz
grains are really acidic they're really
acidic so they help so you know the
Cucumber helps balance that acidity with
the grain
spinach spinach is incredible it
actually helps the body break down
digest and use the amino acids correctly
from the grains
one of the things is Arginine you know
that's one of the amino acids
everybody's worried about when it comes
down to grains carnitine is the amino
acid we have to worry about carnitine
don't take carnitine supplements if you
have a condition it'll blow it up it'll
blow that condition out of the water for
you in a bad way so don't you know
carnitine that's the one that's
Troublesome it ignites viruses it
ignites everything Under the Sun arine
is like a
firecracker to carnitine which is like a
bomb okay I'm just telling you right now
so you know um spinach helps knock down
Arginine uh actually celery does too
both those knock down Arginine levels if
there if a grain has any of that in
there um lettuce lettuce is really work
good with grains rice can go in lettuce
um lettuce wraps you can take Roma leaf
lettuce we could put rice in there and
um this is if your you're you dig grains
you know like I did have a few people
tell me look I love grains ate them my
whole life the whole world's against
them what do I do I'm like look as long
as you're feeling this and feeling that
and guidelines and everything else that
I'm talking about on the show then fine
um Water Crest it's a great one with
grains
arugula that's a good one mhm
sipping a little water here arugula
that's a great one arugula is like a a
tonic for the
stomach arugula helps with hydrochloric
acid as well those rare seven the seven
hydrochloric acid blend and arugula
helps stimulate that and create a little
bit more hydrochloric acid a little a
lot different than celery celer you know
basically helps build the strength of
your hydrochloric acid helps build the
strength the
sorry arugula tongue Tiding me there
arugula does more than that in a
different way it takes the the
hydrochloric acid that you have and it
strengthens it celery produces it get it
actually allows a production of
hydrochloric acid helps you know build
that hydrochloric acid up levels of it
up aruga you know amplifies it in a
different way that was a little
confusing but that's what ites does it
they both work together and it's
something to have in your diet one way
or another but it works great with
grains Sprouts micro grains help
neutralize the acidity in grains because
they're so alkaline that's another thing
right there parsley amazing with grains
it's incredible actually very helpful
cilantro cilantro is wonderful with
grains if you're stuck with that one
variety of white rice from that one
country that's still using d te with
tons of arsenic on it and you're stuck
with that one you know just bottom of
the barrel rice because you got nothing
else to eat and I totally understand
that then cilantro you eat cilantro with
that that type of rice you eat cilantro
with that variety of rice that can be
really
helpful um and then let's see we'll see
what else we got cooking here Tomatoes
it's incredible with a grain can under
estimated at all that's another great
one so don't be afraid of tomatoes and
you might say hey night shades I can't
eat tomatoes no no no you don't want
pizza with tomato sauce that's how
you're going to have aches and pains
because the the the uh crust the wheat
crust is going to feed some kind of
pathogen the cheese is going to feed
some kind of pathogen that's what's
going to give you a problem when it
comes down to you know aches and pains
and ra and all these other issues that
night shades caused no it's not the
Tomato on the pizza so it's it's the
pizza so remember that so Tomatoes
really helpful for grains fresh tomatoes
tomato salads tomato cucumber salads
with some quinoa in it can't go wrong
onions they work great with grains I'm
not talking about Flavor I mean sure
probably flavors it good but I'm talking
about synergistically bio identically it
connects to
the grain um scallions and chives they
work great with Millet TEF they work
great with TEF that's another one they
work great with amaranth you can use
amaranth and TEF they're very good
grains um you can definitely get into
those if you need to Ginger it's
incredible too it's an incredible um
tonic for the stomach which helps you
utilize the grain more turmeric um
turmeric does something interesting it
enhances enhances the good amino acids
and Grains it enhances them pulls them
out enhances them actually puts them as
a star puts them up on a
pedestal
Rosemary I think I put that one in
because it tastes so good with a grain
Rosemary Rosemary does more than that
Rose Rosemary stimulates um digestion
strengthens digestion it's like a
digestion Aid and when you have that
with a grain they really work together
good avocado goes great with grain
because instead of using butter instead
of using butter instead of using you
know um cheese or some other type of fat
um you can instead of using bad oil like
canola oil you can use avocado with your
Millet avocado with some rice avocado
Azure
butter and garlic Garlic's a great one
because garlic the phytochemicals and
garlic actually bind to the grain they
become one so as they go down through
your intestinal track they become Bug
Killers garlic sticks to the Grain and
it kills bugs as it goes down through
your intestinal tract so anybody's
worried about a worm that's a great way
of
deworming so these are some of the
options that we have so here's the deal
here's the deal if you're somebody that
is afraid of eating fruit but you only
eat grain try to switch it off try to
move the grain out of your diet and eat
more fruit there's no question um if
you're somebody afraid of a lot of
vegetables but you eat a lot of grain
try to move the grain out and start
bringing in more
vegetables um if you're someone that
likes a lot of fish keep the grains
really low it don't want a lot of grains
while you're doing a lot of fish you
don't want too you know like a lot of
people do fish and rice I would say
quinoa is the safest grain with fish so
if you like wild salmon and you want to
do a grain or you're over somebody's
house house that's what they're making
whatever it is you know I mean or you're
at a restaurant and you want to ask for
something like that you can do like
salmon and some kinoa but try not to do
salmon and some a basket of bread at the
restaurant too you know wheat bread try
not to do wheat and salmon try not to
have a salmon
sandwich and um and same thing with rice
try not do salmon and rice you try to do
say salmon and quinoa or just salmon and
vegetables or you know another fish that
you like if you're a big meat eater keep
the grains to literally a little bit of
quinoa and maybe a little bit of of
millet once in a while if you're doing a
lot of meat meat doesn't go great with
grains at all we've known this forever
and I say we because I've seen that
circulate among the um alternative
communities and I agree with it since
the beginning of its conception that the
body has a hard time digesting digesting
heavy amounts of protein while digesting
a starch at the the same time if you're
a big grass-fed beef eater keep your
grains minimum you can do more fruit you
can do lots of vegetables you can do
more fruit you can do a few nuts and
seeds but keep your grains down lower if
you're doing animal protein once a day
if you're a person who just likes to
have a little bit of chicken at night or
a little bit of turkey at night or
something like that and you're doing
animal protein once a day um don't do
don't do grains more than once a day if
you're grain eater if you really like
grains so that's the kind of the you
know a little bit of a systematic plan
for you guys if you're really you know
doing that um if you're raw vegan um
just just stay away from grains all
together um if you're dealing with a lot
of illnesses or conditions stay away
from grains altogether you know if
you're feeling pretty good and and
you're living your life and you want
some Keen watch it'd be all right so
it's kind of like that you got to play
it by ear see where you are but but
there's no skull and crossbones in front
of quinoa Millet steel cut oats even
buckwheat you know it's not buckwheat's
not my favorite but you know meaning
like I'm not that fond of it for a lot
of health reasons but even buckwheat
rice you know te amaranth there's no
skull and crossbones in front of it okay
they don't create autoimmune all right
so that's how it works corn and wheat
definitely feed bugs
that mistaken the world as the body
attacking
itself okay when really it's the bug
attacking the body by getting fueled up
with wheat and corn so I'm trying to
clarify that 100% so understand that
that's important to know but there's
still skull and crossbones in front of
grains and um so if you need to
incorporate them like I said some people
they can't afford food and you can buy a
big sack of millet and you can cook it
each day and you could feed your family
and you're feeding them healthy you
really are so you got to you know there
there's different ways of of doing
things so anyway I hope I covered like a
lot of grain stuff there's only a few
minutes left so let me just cover one
more thing mot toxins and mold and
fungus okay that's a whole thing about
grains so it's mot toxin that whole mot
toxin thing um it's not what people
think microt toxins are really not the
the the problem with the grain as far as
with the grain microt toxins are a
problem when we get triggered by
inhaling breathing in or eating or
living in mold like the dangerous molds
the black mold I did a mold show talking
about this and the MotoX sins are
actually poisons that are in the mold
that the mold produces and grain does
collect mold and we know it's been been
you know capable of collecting mold but
so does everything you can get the worst
microt toxins from meat collecting Mo
mold you can you know anything can
collect mold fish can collect mold meat
can collect mold anything can collect
mold so you have to understand that the
microt toxins are all around everywhere
with every food item we have on this
planet and that's just how it works so
you just don't want to eat moldy grains
is what I'm trying to say so when you
get quinoa you just make sure it's good
stuff high quality it won't have mold in
it so you're not going to get any MIT
microt toxins this is another huge
confusion out there in the alternative
movement about microt toxins and
everything else and but wheat and corn
feed viruses that create neurotoxins and
those are the ones that make us
neurologically sick not mot toxins I'm
not saying mot toxins are good cuz mold
isn't it does knock us down so that
Epstein bar can take over and other
things can take over so and we'll do
another mot toxin show too to really
clarify that as well so we know what's
going on look you guys um check out the
event I the event coming up I talked go
to medicalmedium.com check it out check
out life-changing Foods lock down a copy
I can't wait I'm so excited when you
guys open up that book because I got so
many surprises in there it's killing me
man it's like because the surprises in
there are serious like I'm serious when
you open this up uh you're going to be
like your mind's going to be blown I put
so many different things in there you're
going to see it and you're going to be
like he outdid himself it's really
spirit that outdid
himself and when you see it I think
you're going to be excited so I'm giddy
over it I'm excited I can't wait for you
to see that um it just it gets me up in
the morning when you guys are going to
open that book and you're going to be
you're going to be happy cuz it's for
you it's for you I love you so much I
care about you so much and listen it's
all about you healing
it's all about you getting better it's
all about you moving forward it's all
about that's what it's about Spirit gave
me this gift for you guys it's not for
me it's not for me okay it's not the
part that's for me is seeing you heal is
seeing you move forward is seeing you
live your life is seeing you you know
really get past your illnesses is seeing
your loved ones get past your illnesses
get benefits watching you guys drink
celery juice and heal watch you guys
move forward in your life like never
before getting rid of neurological
symptoms and and that's the part that's
for me okay but the gift is for you and
for me watching you heal and move
forward is just it's just it's it's food
for me and I love you for all the hard
work you're doing I believe in you I
stand behind you you didn't create your
illness I promise you that and it's not
your fault you're a good person never
think different never think you
manifested your illness or disease or
condition cuz you didn't you didn't at
all it's not your fault there are real
reasons I love you take one day at a
time I stand behind you bless you take
care