we're live right now facebook we're live
on youtube we're live on tick tock live
on clubhouse
we're here making spinach soup they
rob and steal any chance for you to heal
they take they take they take they take
and they don't give back
but we don't care we're brainwashed
we stay brainwashed and we let it happen
because we don't know any other way
and if we're not sick you can play that
game
you can be that robot you can be that
brainwashed person
i'm not sick yet i'm not sick yet i'm
not sick yet i can play in this
i can eat this i can do this i'm not
sick yet
if you're not so sick you can still play
in there
not so sick not so sick acne breakouts
once in a while a little bit of eczema
oh try to keto diet
treat keto diet i'm a robot not so sick
yet not so sick yet
not so bad not so bad and then when you
get sick
the games the health robbers
that's when they really get you because
there's no room to play anymore
there's no room to play i'm really sick
too sick oh let me do the whey protein
powder again
really sick let me do the next thing let
me do the fish oil capsules again
let me do the apple cider vinegar again
let me do the chocolate oh that's plant
medicine again
let me do the next thing let me do the
next thing and then
boom you're done and nobody cares
nobody cares because the thieves
don't care and they want to rob and
steal
any chance for you to heal even if they
don't even know that's what they're
doing
they're doing it and the industries
support them
and support them and support them right
chris good to see you chris
be open-hearted good to see you too good
to see you guys coming on
maria debbie good to see you going i'm
making spinach soup
we're talking about protecting you
lorena good to see you
protecting you should should you
be protected should you be protected or
should we not be protected because
that's the other thing too they've
brainwashed us
and taught us about using
false protection
false protection that's how it's done
okay i'm doing oil pulling now doing oil
pulling i'm going to protect my teeth
and gums protect my teeth and gums oil
pulling oil pulling
but nobody knows that the oil you're
using when you do the oil pulling it
coats your gums and it conceals and
seals
all of the bacteria in there and you
lose your gums faster
i'm protecting myself apple cider
vinegar protecting myself apple cider
vinegar
and then you lose your teeth later on
they all just start crumbling but you
won't know
you won't know when you're not sick and
you won't know when you're not so sick
and when you get
sick it just it all happens it all
happens then
that's how it works making spinach soup
one
powerful powerful healing tool
got the medical medium cleansing heal
book letting you guys give me this for
warning before we move on
just to get a little bit of a quick
forewarning okay mono eating cleanse
challenge is going to be coming up next
month
you might want to have the book it's
going to be a mind-blowing challenge
it's going to be really fun tremendous
amount of information
so we can heal heal together can't wait
you guys
amazon.com 51 off that's where it is
you can find it there all right and
get it at the library if you can get it
at the library wildly green good to see
you
good to see you lots to talk about
because
shouldn't we be in the business
of protecting the chronically ill
because i'm scratching my head i'm
scratching my head
good to see you guys on tick-tock
because we're not in the business
of protecting the chronic leo we're not
the industries aren't
alternative health industries not
they're
also the thieves the robbers of health
yeah you may not think so you may not
think so you
you left a conventional diet you left
the standard american diet
you got some high blood pressure got
some high cholesterol maybe you got a
skin condition maybe something happened
where you
you left the conventional world of
health and then you
joined in in the alternative you found a
good guy found a good
you know gal in the industry you're
getting help from a practitioner they
got you off of bad food
they got you off of that i mean they may
not have known it was bad food
without medical medium doing 35 years of
getting it out there and out there
but they took the office some bad food
right
you're exercising more you're on your
keto diet
which isn't keto because there's no such
thing as a keto diet anymore
there's no such thing you can't go into
ketosis you can't because they let
sugar into the keto diet so they call it
keto no one realizes that all is just a
clean animal protein diet is all it is
or a plant-based diet they call keto but
all it is just
lots of fat in your plant-based diet but
there's also sugar everywhere nuts have
sugar in it
avocado has sugar in it you can't go
into ketosis your body can't go into
ketosis when you eat an avocado because
an avocado is part sugar
part sugar you can only go to keto you
can only go to ketosis
the body going literally into ketosis
michelle miller are going to
smoking mountain paradise you can only
only go into ketosis
if no sugar is in there no sugar
anywhere right no sugar
and guess what when you go into when you
go into ketosis and you're on a no
carb no sugar diet whatsoever no fruit
no nothing
you go downhill fast
boom because guess what i watched people
die
years and years ago that try to put
themselves in ketosis
stupidest thing on the planet you know
why the keto diet is not the keto diet
anymore
if they call it a keto diet but it's not
the keto diet you can't go into ketosis
because there's sugar in it everywhere
they let you have a green apple can't go
into ketosis one green apple a day you
can't go into ketosis
you can't they can't you can't one
avocado a day you can't go into ketosis
it's impossible
because there's sugar and avocado right
see how it works ashley kevin good to
see you
so we live in this false world of health
the information isn't just
misinformation anymore that's a medical
medium term by the way
medical medium didn't create the word
misinformation that was long before my
time
but medical medium put misinformation
the word in every single thing saying
look that's misinformation out there you
guys that's misinformation now
now people are saying misinformation out
there but it's gone beyond that
it's not it's beyond this information
now okay
it's beyond it is that a place where
it's just
screwed up it's just totally screwed up
so yeah i'm gonna go on the keto diet
really what you're doing is you're
getting rid of fast foods getting rid of
greasy foods getting rid of processed
foods you're starting to exercise more
you're taking a bunch of garbage
supplements maybe you'll get one thing
in there and you get it in your system
and then you think you found the holy
grail which you just found all you found
was your future pea cup at the doctor's
office
that's what you found because you're
going to get sick down the road
because they rob and steal any chance
for you to heal
sarah dylan also i healed chest
tightness with medical medium
amazing that you're doing a cleanse
monolingual cleanse is going to be fun
good to see you guys on tick-tock
uh yeah there's no one that offers
free life saving information about how
to heal chronic illness out there on
tick tock
all right you guys i'm gonna make a
spinach soup
we got we we we got stuff to do hello
from germany hello back
glad to have you here on tick tock so
yeah
um sarah dillon thank you for that
comment much light and love good to see
you
so isn't it about making sure someone
has your back
or or am i wrong okay
because here's your fish oil supplement
you're going to get alzheimer's faster
that's not having your back
it's not the practitioner's fault of the
doctor's fault here's your whey protein
powder that's going to get you
sick because the bugs in you that got
you sick
are going to feed off that whey protein
powder here's your l-carnitine
but you don't know it no one knows it
really unless they heard it here it's
the only place you could have
l-carnitine
feeds pathogens rapidly so when you take
out carnitine
products you're gonna feed your bugs
and let you know basically land up real
sick
okay and classified research and science
raised all the bugs that we have now
and then it took doctors to to find them
by accident did you guys know that
did you guys know that did you know
epsilon bar
did you know epstein-barr virus the
cause of hashimoto's thyroiditis
the cause of fibromyalgia the cause of
rheumatoid arthritis the cause of
neurological
lyme the cause
half the cause of eczema and psoriasis
the cause of chronic fatigue syndrome
cause of mystery brain inflammation for
most
cases usually my epstein-barr virus did
you know the epstein-barr
virus right was discovered in the 60s
1960s right like dr epstein dr barr
okay and did you know
those guys that was the public medical
research and science
those were public medical research and
science virologists
they weren't the classified
medical research and science virologists
the ones
that already knew about epstein-barr
before 1920
before 1920.
chris you seem fine to me we know this
information because of anthony
honor honored you're here cindy lou good
to see you darcy lee good to see you
so the classified medical research and
science
that the publicly known is not privy to
you know the classified that put out
that plague
right the classified that's out there it
puts out every single
plague every single all the viruses
they already put out f steam bar virus
they already sent it out
they already sent it out before 1920
and then it sat around that virus got
people sick it spread it spread the
epstein-barr spread it mutated more
varieties came out of it more varieties
came
out of it
and then what happened was
dr barr and dr epstein were in their lab
in their
public public virologists
they discovered it they didn't discover
it they found what was already thrown
out there by classified medical research
and science
you know it's like just like security
secrecy secrecy
it's good information it is because i'll
tell you why
because all this time alternative
medicine
didn't know anything didn't know
anything
didn't know nothing it's try this snake
oil see if you can get better
try this snake oil and see if you can
get better try this and see if you get
better
oh okay lyme disease well lyme disease
in 1970s early 1970s let's just
antibiotic you guys to death no one's
protecting anybody
so we got a wave of people that lost
their lives from lyme disease not
because of lyme disease not because of
the real reason of lyme disease which
i've seen more virus they lost their
lives because
they were antibiotic to death by
the publicly known research in science
and meanwhile the epstein-barr that's
behind
neurological limes was put out there by
the
classified medical research and science
you guys get the gist of how it works
out there
i mean this is unbelievable information
i mean
boom it all comes together
so we're making spinach soup we're
covering different things so who's
protecting you guys i want to know
who's protecting you guys is it the
collagen industry
they protecting you guys because i'm
scratching my head on that one
is it that because medical research and
science
okay both alternative and conventional
they don't know why anybody's sick but i
love how billions of dollars go into the
stupidest crap like the collagen
right so is that protecting you the
collagen powder
it can't it's not you can't eat collagen
and create collagen that's original
medical meme information guess what
now there's a couple of products out
there where they take like a little bit
of this and a little bit of that a
little bit of nettle or a little bit of
something else they put it together and
they say
and now they say medical medium
information supplement companies
and they say oh yeah you can't you can't
create
collagen you have to build it you need
the building blocks you need plant food
building blocks that's original mm info
once again taken so there's two kinds of
thieves out there
there's the industry that's a thief they
steal your health
they steal it they steal it and they rob
it that's what they do you don't believe
me
fine fine am i pissing you off five five
you don't want to watch this fine i
don't say right
because oh no he doesn't know what he's
talking about i go to my practitioner i
got my practitioner i get all the things
i need i'm feeling better because i'm
keeping out the bad food um exercising a
little more
you know there's a lot of people they
just they haven't been there they
haven't been
sick enough to actually know that
they've been duped they've been duped
renee says also confusing is my blood
work
showed reactivated but my pcr test is
completely negative
i'm now at a loss i just spent over five
thousand dollars to find out why
i was running a temperature every
afternoon
feeling awful and sweating through my
clothes at night
it's been a year marginally better
but i still have this mystery illness my
doctor is clueless renee that's how it
works out there
that's how it works take the book to
your doctor
okay take the book to your doctor
ask your doctor if it's okay to do
things in here
and get it fixed get it fixed
the whole reason why these books are
here reactivated epsilon bar is medical
medium information
doctors never took they never tested for
reactivated epstein-barr
until medical medium books were
published so it is
mm info if your doctor's even checking
are testing for reactivated epstein-barr
it's mm info
and reactivated epsom bar is not even
easy to even find
because there's over 60 varieties of
epstein-barr and that's the whole thing
people don't have the answers they don't
have the information
the medical system doesn't and you learn
that when you're really sick
there's a way to heal it's a way to heal
okay and
now they didn't even know epsilon bar
has anything to do with anybody being
sick they thought it gave you tiredness
and malaise when you had mono and that
was it
gone forever and
and then they they thought epsilon bar
only was one virus
medical medium put out that there's over
60 varieties of epstein-barr
right you guys now guess what science
research
publicly known science and research is
now saying there's two varieties of
epstein-barr
two varieties of epsom bar important you
know
medical medium is always on track
it has a record of it it's the only
published information that said there's
more than one epstein-barr virus
nowhere else in the world has it existed
i taught this for years and i've
published it too
now i've seen now science research is
saying there's two varieties
did they yet learn about the other 58
varieties
because there's over 60 varieties so
it's already been published first
important enough
if you're new here that's a major deal
that's a major major amazing thing you
mean to tell me he knew there's more
than one variety of episode bar the
science of research is talking about it
years later
and then neurological fatigue fatigue
that's a that's in medical medium term
neurological fatigue
no one knew that it's neurological the
fatigue
just thought you're tired and then they
thought it's your adrenals only
then they thought you're crazy but
nobody knew it's from the brain becoming
inflamed
it's neurological fatigue your nerves
being inflamed
by the epstein-barr virus
so who's looking out for everybody
because it's a wasteland of answers
and now podcast doctors are stealing it
so that's what they're doing now
so you got two kinds of thieves out
there you've got the thieves
the industries that want to steal your
health and take literally rob and steal
your health and steal any chance you can
heal and the alternative movement will
join in give you all the collagen
all the whey protein powder i'm just
naming a few things and they'll join in
and just show you just lose you lose
and then there's the other thieves
podcast doctors that take medical medium
information
abuse it don't cite where it comes from
and pretend they know what they're
talking about because they're desperate
for something new
right another thief and that thief
doesn't help anybody either
so who's got your back i want to know i
want to know
who's got your back so let's make some
spinach soup right here
good to see you guys
once i grew up at 40 i started looking
out for myself with your information on
tick tock
amazing what section is the nerve
god's good on tick tock what section is
the nerves
nerve i mean it's all neurological in
here so much neurological information
just look up
disease your symptom your condition or
autoimmune
whatever whatever you need to do just
there's the symptoms are in there
they're all through there all the nerds
digest this chest tightness tingles and
numbness
you steal medical medium information and
try to discredit me at the same time
that's what they do now i don't care
about
the you know like the discrediting like
my feelings don't get hurt i'm like oh
my feelings are hurt now
my feelings are hurt that's not it it's
just that when you can't find your way
to the real information to where it all
comes from
it hurts that's what hurts because it
keeps people from healing
that's the painful thorn that's in my
side that i have to carry i have to
carry
a knife in my back a knife in my side i
have to carry that every day
it's knowing they're going to steal
little bits and pieces
make it look like out there in
alternative medicine and conventional
medicine that they have some answer or
have you on the right
track and then you end up like people
i've seen
where they never never get to the real
source to know
how to heal and
that's the part that kills me because
it's so
unfair it's like long paul kovet being
epstein barr
that's medical medium information
stolen by the podcast doctors
low grade viral is medical medium
information
the terminal of great viral all of it
lorena good to see you and
but why am i talking about this
because if you're not careful
they'll take you down they'll take you
down
the fish oilia fish oil
corella chlorella gorilla
uh what's the next one uh whatever
whey protein powder diatomaceous earth
particles
sodium bicarbonate coffee enemas
uh what's in that and it goes on and on
neem oil mct oil
uh no fruit not allowed to do fruit
chocolate's good for you now
[Music]
coffee's good for you now oh high fat
fat fat fat give me more fat give me
more fat lots of fat
give me fat much tea green tea give me
more
and it goes on and on and that's just a
few things
give me dear antler i'll take that give
me colostrum i'll take that now
where's what just keep it coming keep it
coming
and all that's finding dandy
bone bone broth give me the bone broth
give me the apple cider vinegar what
wine's good for me i can have a glass
on the weekends or every night oh let me
have it's just it's endless
endless and you know what
we have this mechanism inside of us
because we've been brainwashed that
doesn't mind
self destroying ourselves
literally you can you can i told you
guys last time
right adele says coffee and chocolate
was so hard for me to stop
but feel so much better now guess what
what if someone
is really sick and they're stuck on that
coffee and chocolate right
to really sick i mean it'll kill them if
they're really sick
see they got neurological symptoms like
bad ones and someone's like here have
this bar of chocolate
you can end someone's life
if they're bad enough if they're low
enough
a cup of coffee so for someone who has a
really
neural bad neurological problem and
they're half bedridden and they're on
mattress island you give them a cup of
coffee
you might give them a seizure in their
bed
but if you're not that sick you'll just
feel crappy and not know it and you walk
around jacked up
jacked up jacked up and feel crappy and
not know it and you get rid of it and
you'll be like whoa i feel so much
better
just imagine someone who's really sick
arthur king i feel great after stopping
coffee
incredible incredible yeah
it's amazing so i'm gonna make some uh
spinach soup in a second you guys it's a
powerful healing tool
and make no mistake the spinach soup
is a healing tool really is
really powerful so who's looking out for
everybody that's kind of the thing
it's like you know what i think about it
and i woke up this morning i'm like
who's looking out for anybody
everybody looks like they're looking out
for everybody smoking mirrors are really
good
it all seems fine and dandy but
everybody's duped
and they're all tricked and i can't stop
them from pulling the pin out of the
grenade i told you guys last time i was
on here on youtube
on facebook right i could just be like
no
no run jump literally on top of them
and try to stop them from pulling the
pin out and they'll pull it out anyway
and be like what
they'll do it anyway people are like
they're set
to destroy themselves because the system
brainwashed them the system has
conditioned them you're conditioned
you're conditioned
and then here's the other thing now
we're up against
something i never saw before the
internet doctor
not all of them but the internet doctor
the internet doctor wants people sick
i never thought i would say it all these
years i'm like
it's the industries it's the industries
you guys they want you sick
not the doctors the doctors have all
this compassion in the world
the doctors go into the business with
compassion
they want you better they go into it
with an open heart
even if they don't know why you're sick
and what to do for you the doctors come
into
it they come into it with a good heart
freaking wrong i'm wrong
when do i say that i'm wrong boom i've
been proven wrong
been proven wrong i used to say this all
the time
you guys have heard it a million times
the doctor's hearts are in it they
become a doctor because they want you
better
they don't know better of what they're
doing or what they offer they don't have
the answers medical school's not
teaching them
but you have to give the doctors the
benefit of the doubt because the doctor
is a good person and wants you better
i'm wrong boom wrong
because there's a new doctor out there
and it's the internet doctor
and they suck they suck
because they want people sick they
they're paid to keep people sick
they want people chronically ill they
stamp them out of medical schools left
and right
and they don't go to work they just get
on the internet
and they're the young doctor that's
coming out now it's this young line of
doctors
that are stamped on a medical school
they don't want the job really and they
don't want to work because the minute
they worked a day in their life
they came out of medical school and they
started working in a practice for two
seconds they realized
it was just too hard everybody's sick
nobody knows why
and they just whoa they're so entitled
they back up and then they get
a job as an internet doctor and then
they literally try to stop the
chronically ill from
chronically ill from healing yeah
they're selfie doctors
chris it's a new doctor that came out
and you know what happens you put out
your healing story
and then you get a whole bunch of
doctors going on there saying you didn't
heal you didn't heal
there's no signs of research to show
back up that you got rid of your
condition
you're not you're you weren't sick you
were lying you were lying
you were faking it you were faking it
and they're doctors
it's weird they're like naturopaths the
chiropractors
they're like functional doctors they're
mds and it's this new internet doctor
and they don't care if you die
they don't care if you live they don't
care they're just like no where's the
study where's the study try this mct oil
where's the study you should be on a
high fat diet
where's the study you should be on this
you should be there and they just want
you dead
and it's the new internet doctor i've
been proven wrong
proven wrong i screwed up i screwed up
because for decades i've been saying
every doctor that goes and becomes a
doctor they got their heart in it and
they got compassion
and they want you better they just don't
know the answers you can't blame them
they're all good people because their
hearts in it they came into it this way
i was wrong i was wrong
you guys need to know the traps out
there because the traps are just getting
bigger and uglier and bigger and uglier
and then next thing you know everybody's
peer pressure you need to do something
that could hurt you too
therese rock hi ew how much spinach
is too much to eat studies say it has
folates that can damage kidneys
studies are wrong studies don't know why
you're sick
studies don't know why anybody sick
studies don't know why a baby has eczema
studies don't know why someone has
fatigue studies don't know why anything
studies don't know anything besides
telling you caffeine is good for you so
what does that tell you
because you know caffeine is bad for you
then why are studies telling you it's
good
so what does that mean studies are also
paid for
studies are also traps studies are also
created and paid for to stop you from
eating spinach
studies are there to stop you from
taking care of yourself because once
again we're back to that
we're back to paid for corrupt finger
thumb on the scale science and research
study
crap is what we're at and then your dog
waiting for a bone
and then your dog waiting for a bow and
that's it
you'll be a dog waiting for a bone is
what you'll do
because in the end those studies those
studies ain't gonna save you
in the end then they're not gonna save
you
the studies they're not gonna save you
because you'll be a dog waiting for a
bone it's like that's what's gonna
happen
it's like okay is the next study coming
out i've been sick for a long time i got
hashimoto's
i got hashimoto's thyroiditis okay i'm
on my thyroid medication
but yet my thyroid problem's there
forever so what do i do wait a minute
okay uh i got xmas fries this is the
next study coming
we're next steady coming waiting for a
dog waiting for a bone waiting for a
bone
where's my bone oh wait a minute there's
the bone you guys you guys there's the
bone
we might actually have a study we might
have a study here's the study ready
ready ready oh my god they say coffee is
actually good for you
were you did you guys read that coffee
is good for you now they did a study on
coffee
oh yeah yeah okay next study let's wait
wait for a bone
for bone fibromyalgia we got
neurological lyme i know somebody who
died from lyme disease
one of our dogs did all our doggies do
all our doggies get sick here it is the
next day in the next day
here it is spinach is bad for you when
you eat too much of it
it can hurt your kidneys okay okay
where's the next study
where's the next day there's no studies
showing that all the high fat diets are
slowly killing people
no studies showing that the high fat
diet and
and protein diets are killing kidneys
that's what kills kidneys
it's a high protein diet you guys we
gotta wait for one more study
here it comes ready um your study
omega-3s and chicken eggs
are really good for us and it can help
our memory
omega-3s and chicken eggs can help our
memory okay
okay here we go there we go oh another
dog guy oh no
no okay when was the other dog we're
still left we got some dogs left
we do oh no ten years go by let's get
another study going
let's go it's terrible
and and that's what happens because
we're just dogs
waiting for a bone and that's what we
are and people don't realize it
they just don't get it they don't get it
and it's really really sad it is
because you won't eat the spinach
all you need is one one warning flare
where is it one warning flare
where's that warning flare
here it is it's a study you spinach
might hurt your kidneys
there's a flare all you need is one
warning flare
and in the back of your mind that
brainwashing is going to take over
and you're like spinach i don't really
want spinach um
let me have another piece of chicken
though
so in every single study says
inconclusive except for the caffeine
studies
studies caffeine industry they don't
even want the word inconclusive there
they just want to be like no you drink
that stuff
you drink that stuff you better eat that
stuff
you better drink that stuff and you
better shut up drink it eat it and shut
up and don't complain
you you get high on that caffeine and
then we need you high
to to keep on keeping the shareholders
happy tic toc the handle good to see you
danielle i love eggs on tick tick-tock
look it's like i'm not trying to put
fear in you that eggs are going to hurt
you but if you got
a sickness of any kind a symptom a
condition and something you don't want
eggs are just going to keep it around
they're gonna keep it around forever
is all that's gonna happen yeah
yeah we we all love eggs
but classified medical research and
science
took your egg and they cut open the tops
they cut open the tops you guys back
before
1920 they cut open the tops the
classified medical research and signs
cut open the tops
and then they found out they can grow
bugs inside those eggs because there's
undeveloped
proteins in eggs pathogens feed off of
undeveloped proteins and eggs and so
they've ruined our eggs you don't stand
a chance if you're really
sick if you're on eggs because if you're
really sick you've got some bugs going
on you've got the epstein bars maybe the
simplexes that have gone a little too
far
maybe the sediment virus maybe the hhv
hb6
hhv 7 hhv-8 you got all these dip
shingles
streptococcus all these different bugs
they'll feed off of these because when
you eat them
you eat them you eat the egg you don't
want eggs on your spinach soup
or your spinach salad sarah dillon
it's this info he has a podcast about
oxalates from a long time ago thank you
thank you let's make some soup
you know what's bad for your kidneys you
know to kill your kidneys
chicken you got a kidney disease you got
a kidney susceptibility you got a kidney
problem
chicken will send you downhill
with kidney disease where's the study
for that
where's the study for that how do you
heal kidneys
leafy greens help to heal kidneys and
spinach is a leafy green
chicken that will kill a kidney
will kill a kidney i've heard stories of
people getting kidney transplant brand
new kidney transplant
they killed the kidney real early from
just
eating chicken in the hospital trying to
recover the brand new kidney was like oh
my god i'm in shock the body's in shock
and you're dumping that in me right now
i'm not anti-animal protein
eating you guys if you guys like that
i'm not anti-vegan plant-based
i'm just saying i'm about knowing
the truth and the right information and
the rules because
if no one's got your back out there even
though everybody's pretending to have
your back
or think they have your back then why is
there so many mistakes made
every minute i hear about it all the
time
and i heard about it all the time
anybody who got a hold of me for help
throughout the years
it'd be like so i'd be like so what are
they offering you what are they doing
like well i'm on this i'm on that i'm on
this i'm like oh my god
oh my god oh my god exactly
doesn't matter if you're the best of the
best it's like oh my god oh my god
so anyway i'm gonna make uh cucumber
noodles i'm also gonna
you guys can see this i got the food
processor right here
let me bring it over a little bit so you
guys can see it better
okay let me do that so
let's do this we'll do uh some spinach
soup i'm gonna pop some spinach in here
in the food processor i'm gonna make
this a little thicker than normal
i like spinach i always do i like
spinach soups to be thicker
it's like colitis they cut your colon
out
because they don't know why you're sick
you're going to bathroom you're filling
the toilet up with blood
you're in agony i don't know why
they give you steroids and more steroids
the hopes to stop it
hopes to stop it right emergency
medicine right
they're giving you steroids to try to
stop the bleeding and bleeding
and then it just isn't working
and then you're getting 22 inches of
your colon cut out
you're getting 12 inches of your colon
cut out because
or you get your whole entire colon cut
out
because they don't know why you got the
colitis
but you can learn the truth of what
causes colitis in the books
you can learn the truth the medical
medium books and then you know the truth
of what causes colitis this is a prime
example
but how many colons have they cut out i
can't tell you how many people knocked
on my door
in the last 35 years right
with already their colon removed and i
just was brokenhearted because it didn't
have to go that way
so sad so sad
so i published the books so people
couldn't just see me one on
one and and you know and then what about
everybody else
charlie says does excess spinach intake
cause stones
no no there's no study that can show
that
there's no research in science that has
a scope that goes in your body
to say watch that spinach it's starting
to create a stone
are you kidding that doesn't even exist
and who's eating that much spinach
i didn't know everybody's eating so much
spinach because i just spent 35 years
trying to get people to eat spinach and
no one eats spinach what they have three
leaves in a salad and a mixed
medley salad green what everybody was
eating icebergs
iceberg lettuce for decades no one ate
any spinach
there's millions of people with kidney
stones no one's eating spinach
i talked to people now who are in the
health movement and be like yeah i gotta
eat more spinach i'm like well how much
spinach have you had
how much spinach you have like i gotta
eat more spinach i don't know i don't
know when i had spinach left i go but
aren't you
plant-based dude aren't you plant-based
yeah i'm plant-based
but i don't know i had some spinach i
guess in a mixed green
salad i got when i was out at a
restaurant with a friend i'm like are
you kidding me
who's even eating spinach
what a handful of spinach in a juice or
a smoothie are you kidding
a couple of handfuls of spinach in a
juice or a smoothie with someone
no one was even eating spinach years ago
what spinach in a can 50 years ago
someone's canned spinach sitting on a
shelf in their house from 1968
a a can of spinach
in a lead a lead steel can
people hardly eat spinach now i could
talk to people
keto people keto doctors they get a hold
of me be like you know i thought my keto
was working i've been teaching about
ketoko first of all dude
dr dude you ain't even kido he's like
what
what do you mean i'm not keto that's
impossible i'm keto i'm like you are you
eat avocados like yeah every day i go
you're not keto
you can't go into ketosis just sugar and
avocado
i hear it all the time doctors go what
the heck in there go you're right
yeah you can only go into ketosis if you
got no carbohydrate whatsoever on any
level has to be completely eliminated
for the body to go into ketosis
but it's like who even eats spinach
unbelievable like science or research
thinks that
knows does it first of all you guys find
that funny i just want to ask you this
right here
if science research doesn't know what
causes any of your autoimmune conditions
whatsoever
in any of your symptoms and conditions
right
except when you get heart disease and
they still don't know the cause
but when scientific research still
doesn't know why anybody's sick and they
don't know why your children have eczema
now because guess what there's
commercials on television with kids with
eczema it's like what you know what that
means right
millions of kids have eczema millions
science and research doesn't know this
then how do they know spinach is going
to give you a kidney stone i've never
seen anything so stupid in my life
never seen anything so stupid in my life
you guys if you're on youtube give the
video a thumbs up i never asked for it
but i'd appreciate thumbs ups thumbs ups
subscribe
if you want to subscribe so let's just
blend up a little bit of spinach
i'm doing it kind of i'll do a little
bit of time just kind of giving it
i love doing it in a food processor
love it love it
food processors are fun you know i like
them better than blenders in so many
ways
katina i love your rants
you say it like it is my husband had
kidney stones
when we ate meat and iceberg lettuce
now 20 years later no kidney stones and
we eat lots and lots of spinach so proud
of you katina
so proud of you the thing is
i see that some people complain about my
rants or they call you like if you call
it a rant right
some people complain it's to get to the
point get to the point i'm going what do
you mean there's a lesson in all these
rants there's a lesson lorraine l will
tell you
she's always leaving comments saying no
he he's giving you a lesson
in his rant you know california poppy
will say it he's giving you
in each sentence he's giving you a
lesson it's valuable information
do you want just the do you want just
the three to five minute blurb on
youtube where you get a
a youtube doctor hi i'm dr john's
whatever
if you add mct oil to your diet
you will see improvements the study
shows it
if you add fish oil to your diet you
will improve in your memory
if you if you start a keto diet you can
actually lower your sugar
and your blood pressure in a matter of
possible a year
depending on this if you you know it's
great you're done
three minutes you're like okay i just
took those tidbits in and guess what
you're gonna be nowhere with that
it's not even real information terry
um balance does not exist here we are
sick
it's the other thing too it's like
everybody thinks balance i still see it
now
i still see it now out there it's crazy
you guys it's like
you know i see people out there now
health so-called health expert
influencers
they're talking about how yeah you just
intuitively here's my fridge you guys
here's here's hey everybody or they'll
just like hey guys
that's it right we're youtubes everybody
says hey guys hey guys
i'm just going to give you a tour of my
fridge today and i'm going to show you
what i do
in my lifestyle and how i eat because i
know you guys are going to be interested
in my fridge
here it is let me show you what's in my
fridge here so you'll see here that i do
like this and hey my boyfriend has some
cold
some cold brew coffee going here and we
drink that once in a while that's so
cool and
hey um you know i i find it's balanced
and being intuitive
here's all my condiments uh i even know
there's vinegar in every single one of
those condiments
but yeah it's all about balance and kind
of intuitive eating
oh wait here's my guacamole right here i
got my guacamole here you guys take a
look
oh down here i really like these these
are these coconut wraps in here
yeah they're so great it's like a keto
thing that's great and you just go on
and on and on
and then wait here's a chocolate drawer
in the house but you guys i do have a
chocolate drawer
here it is this is where we have all our
chocolate bars and our chocolate and
everything
check this out because i'm you know i'm
a youtube influencer to show you my
chocolate bar
yeah when you get sick
you're gonna be hurting and ain't no
one's gonna be like
they're just being like um aren't you
off processed foods yeah i'm off
processed foods
i don't know why i'm so scared so sick
and i got the heart helps i don't feel
good
it's like well you're having your plant
medicine chocolate yeah i eat my
chocolate every day
and everybody says it's good for me
balance isn't going to get rid of your
real problems real problems that science
and research aren't even identifying
classified science research knows
everybody's suffering from pathogens
publicly known medical research science
which everybody's privy to that
they don't know why everybody's sick
unless they learn from mm info and
they're starting to
they're stealing it right heavy metals
people don't know that's
really what's doing it either and
poisons and toxins and
balance doesn't work for that right
there
what you'll find in my so-called rants
are protection measures
protection statements for you
lessons of protection
in the real world of sickness
and they'll just tell you you got
candida candida is not the problem
can't eat is not the problem you die
without candida did you guys know that
check this out
just just give me one second right right
did you know that the last thing you
ever want to do is kill off your candida
did you know candida is a beneficial
absorption fungus
it's there to help you transfer some
nutrients
it's one of the only beneficial fung
beneficial microorganism based
fungus so the one and only that allows
you to get some nutrients it's one of
the big ones there that actually helps
to transfer nutrients right
in your intestinal tract to your
bloodstream
and we just spent 30 plus 40 years 40
years
of practitioners trying to kill and
destroy your candida i can't tell you
how many lives were destroyed because of
that
and they're still doing it today still
doing it
still to this day i still hear a story
my doctor thinks i got candy and i'm
like jesus christ
are you serious we're back to that again
candida candida was only was only came
about
because nobody knew why anybody was sick
in 1980 and they still don't i talk
about this medical medium box right
in medical medium book one check that
book out it's a new edition
right this is 51 off you guys mono
eating cleanse
i'm doing in july make sure you have a
copy whether you get it from the library
or get it from amazon.com us 51 percent
off
if you don't have it just take the
plunge take the plunge
all right so i'm grinding up some
spinach or blending it up in the food
processor now i'm going to start putting
some other things in here
i might put a little bit more spinach in
here really like this two cups
four cups of spinach is really it's
really best
i mean i don't know how much i have in
here right now this is a healing
tool such a great thing for people
before i came to medical media my
naturopath kept blaming candida
even though i knew i never had yeast
problems on tick tock
yeah i believe it believe it
all right so i got enough spinach in
here for my spinning soup
now i'm gonna start popping in some
other stuff i just pulsed it
let me put some tomatoes in here right
another piece of misinformation tomatoes
are bad
nightshade nightshade where does it end
where does it end
where does it stop it doesn't i'll tell
you what i'll tell you what
there's nothing in my power that can
correct the big screw-ups in the medical
industry in the alternative health
industry there's nothing i could do
i can i can help you if you find your
way to this information so you know that
it's okay to eat a tomato so you know
that a potato is actually a healing food
i can do my best to make sure you know
this elizabeth good to see you
you need to start doing your spinach
soup you're laughing
i can do my best but the amount the
amount of misinformation
now out there and then the the fake
internet doctor that's out there now
that just wants people's lives destroyed
and never thought i'd say it in my life
and never thought i'd say
that there's a crap ton of planted
manufactured industrialized
doctors that are on the internet
purposely trying to derail people by the
thousands and thousands in hopes to get
them sicker i never
thought there'd be cold-hearted doctors
but guess what we have a new age and a
new wave of doctors
it's the internet doctor they are the
worst i'm not talking about internet
doctor that works their butt off
in their practice and then hops on the
internet and does their thing and does
their own
media platforms talk about one gear
specifically
to just be a jerk
so i have to spend a lot of time telling
you guys about all the traps if i don't
i know where it's going back years ago i
spent a little bit of time during doing
it right i was always mentioning it here
and there and everybody was like get to
the point
but if i don't if i don't safeguard you
guys a little bit if i don't
have my eye on the ball if i don't look
out for you guys
i don't know what i'm gonna i don't even
know what to say
yeah so all right i'm going to blend
this up a little bit
i'm going to put some cilantro in here
so
that's going in the spinach soup you
guys let's put a clove of garlic in here
so april says i haven't got a food
processor can i make it another way
blender
blender absolutely the blender's a great
way to make it seriously
i mean i like the food processor for it
but just the blender
blender is great this is a clove of
garlic right here
right here
yep clove of garlic reading comments you
guys both on tik tok and facebook
youtube
my body bloats swells badly with
potatoes so
i always want people to be their own
detective lin i'm glad you're here
um be their own protective right so
if i had bloating and swelling right
i'd ask myself do i ever bloat on
anything else
so i went through my life with no bloat
nothing bloats me i'm going through life
i'm going through life i would ask
myself this
nothing bloats me i wasn't bloated last
week when i didn't eat a potato
i wasn't bloated last month when i
didn't eat a potato i wasn't bloated two
days ago
i'm not bloated now i'd ask myself or am
i bloated two weeks ago did i blow up
from some other food did i bloat for
something i eat did i blow and what you
might find out is you're bloating no
matter what periodically because you
have a bloat problem
right and then you might have potato
the wrong way was it steamed did it have
oil on it did it have fat on it
was it in bacon grease what was the pit
was it
was it fried did it have cheese on it
did have sour cream on it did have
butter on it did it butter in it
i'd make sure that's all set right there
and then i'd be like did i have it
steamed like medical medium says
and maybe with some greens or steamed
steamed on a mono level
mono eating cleanse level by the way you
guys like i said mono eating cleanse
challenge in july you want to be there
i'm just letting you know
have that book so these are the things i
would actually ask myself
or weren't you just perfectly fine never
bloated ever all's good and then you ate
a potato and you blowed it and like well
that potato bloated me
so kind of keep all that in mind did you
do the potato the right way are you
bloating anyway did you bloat the day
after
some other bad food but then you had a
potato a day after and thought the
potato was doing it
when really you had a slice of vegan
pizza a week ago and you're still
bloated from that all these things are
important enough
manny palmer the mono eating takes me
out of a bloating flair it does
you can mono eat potatoes and get out of
a bloating flare absolutely
and and moderating cleanses all in here
next month you guys i gotta let you know
i'm not trying to
not trying to be a pain but i'm letting
you know early because then no one sees
it and other people see it
another time whatever read it and get
prepared read the monolining cleanses
and get prepared we're going to do
moderating cleanse in july
cleanse a heal it's on sale 51 off 16.
it's just incredible takes more money to
print that book
i got the tomatoes in here i got the
spinach ground up a little bit i got the
cilantro let's throw a couple celery
sticks in this
right let's do that
get some celery in there right all right
you guys
squeeze some orange in there now let's
go
i gotta spend a substantial amount of
time having your back
anybody who comes on i see it once in a
while that says i can't watch him for
more than two minutes because he doesn't
get to any points why am i i'm making
the soup
but the points i'm getting are how do we
protect you
you might think you're fine and dandy
you'll be sick someday
everybody gets sick everybody gets sick
my grandmother is 89 years old and she
can do what she wants and she's not sick
but she will get sick and she will pass
away at one point
that's just the facts of life and what
did she get sick with when she passed
away
did she get the flu and she didn't have
enough zinc in her system and she passed
away at 92
and 89 90. what's going to take out
grandma
and that's the whole thing it's all
about hey no matter what we have to know
this information
so a lot of people say at 20 years old
at 18 years old
marissa aw makes a million points in
those
two minutes i'm honored i'm honored
truly honored so i'm squeezing orange in
here
this is a juicy orange i'm surprised
actually it's extra juicy
and i get it a lot of this information
is over a lot of heads you guys but you
guys are really brilliant you guys are
smart
but let me tell you something every now
and again you get somebody on there and
they're just like you know
i don't like him i don't like the way he
looks he's ugly
he's ranting and it's like dude you you
miss the whole plane
you have to be seasoned and understand
this information you have to be seasoned
and help
out there to understand you guys are
seasoned you guys are seasoned
yeah okay we got
orange in there so i'm gonna make the
soup let's do that
before i make the soup though let's get
the cucumber noodles ready how about
that
that might be a smarter thing to do
mv doom he isn't telling you what you
want
he's telling you what you need
truly honored so i'm making cucumber
noodles i got this little
julienner right is that what we call it
you guys let's get these noodles going
so i'm making noodles right so these are
cucumber noodles spinach super cucumber
noodles is so good
it's so good
so let's do that let's make some noodles
and then we're going to blend up that
soup
you know what people want to hear by the
way you guys they want to hear
you know what they want to hear they
want to hear a two-minute
tip they want to hear a five-minute tip
a lot of people want to hear
and it's sad
if you eat right you don't get sick
easily and avoid food that causes
internal body inflammation
it's not the reality of it it's not
so you're telling plant-based people
that are on a keto plant-based diet
they're so called eating right and
balanced in their plant-based but they
get sick or they lose all their teeth or
something starts out their teeth are
falling apart or they get sick
they get hives you're telling me that
their plant-based diet that was like
healthy avocados every day and all that
that every single doctor would say
they're eating right on
you mean to tell me that well then why
they get sick it happens every day
plant-based people go screaming and
running from the plant-based diet into
back to the animal protein diet they
start eating eggs out of nowhere
it's not about just eating i know people
that are eating terrible
but they're not sick they're terrible
because they don't have a pathogen they
don't have the virus they don't have
epstein-barr they don't have that okay
they're not dealing with that they don't
have three epstein bars in a shingles
virus
they don't have they don't have toxic
heavy metals
they may not be high in mercury where
the virus is eating all the mercury
they're not you know and that's the
whole thing because that's what i mean
you could be on the best keto diet
best animal protein diet best
plant-based diet that's everything and
you still get your butt sick
and you end up sick and now you don't
know what to do and you're seeing all
the different doctors and they got you
on gut health products they're telling
you about your
microflora they're trying to convince
you to do go back on this go back on
that
they're doing sodium bicarbonate they're
telling you to do fish oil again mct oil
they're telling you to do all these
different things
and the next new thing comes out they go
make sure you do that make sure you do
the pine needle tea which actually is a
terrible tea
terrible thing to do and it doesn't do
what everybody says so next thing you
know they're just telling you
all these things and we're back to that
again
mm info is about the true cause and how
to heal
and we're doing a healing tool right now
you do your spinach soup every single
day
you got a chance to heal you take out
some of those troublemakers
medical mean information talks about you
got a chance to heal
you throw away your apple cider vinegar
you be careful on your chocolate
consumption you got a chance to heal
these are just some things
okay so we're making some spinach soup
see what bowl do i want to use you guys
i want oh that's a nice bowl right here
that's a very nice bowl
this is raw spinach is what this is
so i'm putting some noodles in here get
a
another cucumber
this is raw spinach you don't want
cooked spinach yes you can cook spinach
but you want the spinach raw that's
where you get the most out of
spinach and if you can't eat a lot of
spinach
try the spinach soup you can get a lot
of spinach in you that way even if you
have a small bowl of it
how about that how about them apples huh
how about them apples
so we got some nice cucumber noodles
here this is so
great
right the spinach soup is rich in
electrolytes mineral salts that's how we
heal
that's how we get better that's one
option right there that's one way
okay one way to heal
get the old brain out
need electrolytes you need electrolytes
you need the mineral salts
and the brain needs to trace mineral
salts the brain needs the electrolytes
this is a way to give give your brain a
part of what it needs
that's one part of what it needs right
spinach soup the medical medium healing
tulle spinach soup
is also antiviral antibacterial
antiviral antibacterial
so all right we're going to blend this
out
that's half a brain just giving this a
you get a little spinach soup
what i like to do is i like to just some
of the spinach off the sides and
love the smell of the spinach soup when
it has a clove of barbecue here
it's really incredible
if you're sensitive to garlic does it
feel so strong
take it out take the garlic out
it gets sensitive do less garlic do a
little tiny bit
but if you're less sensitive do less
tiny bit a little bit
[Music]
okay we got the spinach soup it looks so
good
right here it is cheryl
that i'm afraid would give me loose
stools
just do a little at a time acclimate how
about that acclimate
so i'm gonna pour some spinach soup
right here it's nice and thick you see
that's the way i like my spinach soup
you can have it thinner some people they
just really like it thinner
than like a soup soup i like kind of
like a spinach pesto
kind of so it's over the noodles i just
put it over the noodles you see that you
guys
right
it's amazing you can use a spoon
you can use a fork right
what i like to do is use a fork a little
bit cause i got the noodles in here so
take a look you guys
so i got this beautiful spinach soup
right here now
what i'm gonna do okay and there it is
right what i'm gonna do
i don't want you guys to do this right
but i'm gonna put a little bit of a hot
pepper chopped up
since this is my dinner so i'm gonna
i'm gonna chop up a little bit of this
red hot chili pepper
a little bit of that red hot chili
pepper right there can you see that you
guys
i'm gonna pop that right on top
loose stools aren't always a bad thing a
loose stool
these foods are cleansing
okay so keep that in mind cleansing
loose stools aren't always a bad thing
now i'm thinking would i like a loose
stool
or would i like a compacted hard
constipated stool stuck
somewhere in a pocket in the colon where
i'm
struggling to get that baby out and i'm
straining
and sweating and having an anxiety
attack
because i can't get that stool out
and it's putting pressure in my gut and
making me feel swollen and bloated
i think i'd rather have the loose stool
that's what i like that doesn't look
delicious susan blonda
right l good to see you over there on
tick tock
so this is the spinach soup it's creamy
it's the the noodles in here it's like a
pasta dish without the pasta look at
that
right yes it's so good too it's insanely
good have you guys tried it
such a good good good good good soup
just so you know you guys mono eating
cleanse challenge coming up
in july make sure you have okay
the handbook because you have to think
about that
so i thought about it i'm like so i got
people they'll tell me why don't you do
for the first time ever you
charge for this big cleanse you have
people sign up and you have people come
on
you charge a thousand dollars a person
or fifteen hundred dollars a person to
come in for the mono eating cleanse
and then you get everybody in and you
take it to a private platform
and have everybody buy a ticket or
something like that and they have to
have the book as a reference i'm like
you know what
i get it some people do that out there
that's what people will do right
i don't want to do that have the
handbook get live get at the library for
free if you don't want to buy it 51
off have the handbook
do the mono eating cleanse with me in
july
make sure you have the book in your hand
okay
and you won't have to pay two thousand
dollars three thousand dollars thirty
five hundred dollars twelve hundred
dollars
okay and we'll do it for free margaret
valentine good to see you
i get it though we wanna self-destruct
we're taught we're trained we're
conditioned
we are we're taught and trained and
conditioned that's what we are
okay and
you know it's it's you got to remember
medical medium information also does
something where
it prevents you from getting sicker
there's so many people
that would have gotten so sick they
picked up some new bugs they picked up
some new pathogens along the way
they picked up more toxic heavy metals
if they weren't doing their celery juice
or some medical medium information
they'd be going downhill but there's
tools in medical medium information to
get you out
out of trouble so you can take it to
that finish line and every little piece
counts and like i said on the last
youtube apple cider vinegar
will make it so you can't make the
finish line it just you won't make the
finish line you won't be
able to go as far as you need to go with
your healing process do you know what
happened
when we did the apple cider vinegar talk
last time guys do you know what happened
a tick tock do you guys know what
happened right
what happened was all of a sudden an
army
an army of paid apple cider vinegar
advocates dr fahn good to see you an
army of them alexandra sophia good to
see you an
army of paid for advocates for apple
cider vinegar
came slamming on all the medical medium
platforms
i had i had to delete them man they were
just like
so they were just like you're evil going
against apple cider vinegar
you need to die you're evil how dare you
go after apple cider vinegar
it was like they're all it was like
thousands of admin paid for by the apple
cider vinegar corporations
to like go and attack medical medium
just because i'm literally trying to
keep people's teeth in their mouth
so you know because this stuff will just
ruin your teeth and your stomach glands
and just tone and just ruin your bones
over time
and it's like it's it's i mean it's
unbelievable they were just they were
just coming on in droves
literally doctors were coming on that
were paid internet doctors to just
fend for apple cider vinegar and they
were like
no apple cider vinegar does this for you
apple cider vinegar balances your
pleasure apple cider vinegar does this
apple cider vinegar that
oh my god it was unbelievable
and and meanwhile acv
yeah acv topical is fine
topically it's fine but acv will stop
you from take getting to the finish line
forget it you ain't going to the fish
line you're not you got that stuff in
your system you're not
meanwhile meanwhile all these internet
doctors
they're not real doctors these internet
doctors they all got like veneers they
got teeth missing they got
implants they got dentures in they got
bridges in they got root canals left and
right
right but see nobody cares about the
chronic leo i've noticed they don't they
don't care
just they don't care they want the
chronically ill to be sheeple they want
them to be sheeple and paddle
they want to be sheeple and paddle and
that's what they want
they want the chronic wheel to be
sheeple and paddle
right so sheeple and paddle it's like
we'll listen to you okay i better go and
buy the apple cider vinegar
okay we'll listen to you all right i
better go buy that fish oil okay
don't eat spinach that's right um um
yeah that's right uh salicylates oh wait
what's in salicylate it's a lectins okay
i can't eat this anymore don't eat a
ripe
banana don't eat a banana and it's
endless it's endless
we're told to be sheep we're taught to
be sheep
soup's amazing you guys and
so if there's anything to take away from
today
today show you guys all right is look
out for the pitfalls look out for the
traps
okay and be your own detective too
it's another thing all on its own i want
you guys to be able to heal and make it
to the
finish line to get where you need to go
because they'll rob your health
immoral to this story the power points
to this
talk however you want to see it view it
the takeaways
from this live is
they'll rob and steal your health away
and they won't claim any responsibility
in the end
it's just a dark industry all of it now
yep one love says my friend lost some of
her teeth
from that oh my god and it has and has
bone density tests
yeah the vinegar and here's the thing
you guys
you open your fridge and maybe not your
fridge but you open your fridge
and the vinegar products the vinegars
and everything every salsa every hot
sauce
barbecue sauce hot sauce salsa dressings
uh salad dressings you know all the
vinaigrettes ketchups mustards
what else what else mayonnaise
mayonnaise ketchup
mustards all the condiments you can
muster up
pickles whatever it is right horseradish
whatever it is
all your condiments the whole bit all
the vinegar is in every last one
all the salsas everything vinegar
vinegar vinegar you go into a restaurant
there's vinegar in every one of your
dishes no matter what whether you like
it or not
it's in there it's like it's vinegar
everything courtney ma
yep it's in salsa it's in 99
of all salsas vinegars and everything
and so in in it's there you're doing so
much vinegar
so much vinegar and so what happens is
that here you are you're getting a
little older and then boom osteopedia
comes your teeth starts this
teeth start to fall apart disintegrate
disintegrate
yeah and that's what happens right there
medical medium community is about not
just answers
true causes right what tools to heal
right keeping alcohol out of your
supplements you guys
now you'll see less alcohol and
supplements out there than ever before
because of mm info because talking about
how the
alcohol and the supplements are bad you
don't want alcohol in your tinctures
you don't want alcohol in your tinctures
okay if you're somebody that's worried
about you did a lot of vinegar so what
i've noticed a lot of people are saying
this what i noticed is a lot of people
are saying that
what can i do to help like what can i do
to help and i tell people that look if
you've got teeth loss
if you've got bone loss anything like
that
nettle leaf is really a good thing right
there so nettle leaf's a great one
so i tell people about that that's the
vimergina leaf i'm not sponsored but
that's the one i give
family and friends that say hey i've had
a lot i've been watching your vinegar
stuff
and i've had so much vinegar over the
years i have teeth problems i got other
stuff like that
and i'm like well you make sure you're
doing some metal leaf that can actually
at least
help reinforce uh that's the vimerginato
leaf it's no alcohol in it it's the real
thing
these victor i am ergy dot com
i want to make sure people have options
at least something that's helpful
because i know people just down the
calcium they'll think that will fix it
but you need other things it's not
that's not how it works lemons is
another one so like lemon water
medical medium 16 to 32 ounces of lemon
water every single morning can help with
the calcium
and spinach soup so that's another
reason why we're doing the spinach soup
is great too you guys
okay so anyway i'm going to ig
hopefully we'll have some fun on on
instagram live that's what we're gonna
do
i hope you guys come over because it's
not it's never the same show
as we do here as we do spirit of
compassion than i do
on ig it's a different show anyway guys
i'll see you there pretty soon
okay give me a few minutes i hope you
guys hang around
and we'll do ig i'm going to turn tick
tock back on at the same time you guys
clubhouse will turn you guys on back too
and uh i'll see you guys ashley's
natural nook
the new vimergy subs use flax glycerin
it tastes like
alcohol but i called them and they
assured me it's
it's flax glycerin yeah it's far from
alcohol there's no alcohol in there
um flax glycerin is actually incredible
it's actually incredible
so yeah that's advanced that's how
advanced the company is
i think they're the first company that
used flax
uh glycerin because it's actually it's
actually the it's so
it's so amazing for a stabilizer so
amazing
amazing and giving me all the other
companies are just using the worst
corn glycerin and they're using uh
they're using uh
you know all this other junk and garbage
it's it's unbelievable
how much stuff they use and you look at
they use alcohol and they use
killers and you use all this stuff
that's why i love emerging
exactly what you just said there is why
i love energy right there
incredible because they don't use citric
acid beverages use citric acid all the
other companies you citric acid they use
corn glycerin they use all this crazy
stuff
fillers and by-products and stuff and my
god alcohol
that's what they use and vimersy's the
purest i've seen out there yet to this
date
it's what i recommend friends and family
okay you guys
remember the challenge is going to be
coming up
next month keep that in mind i love you
guys i'm heading over to ig
turning on tick tock again and clubhouse
love you guys