hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who is 10 or 20 30 years to
wait for answers to their illnesses life
is precious this is the only Health show
out there today where the information
here doesn't come from any interest
groups medical funding with strings
attached botched research research with
the thumb put on the scale to make
things turn out the way they need to be
spun research spun information lobbyist
internal Kickbacks persuaded belief
systems because when we fall into a
belief system it can't be broken so no
matter what happens it's where someone
forges ahead forges ahead and they don't
open their minds for something else
private panels of influencers and health
field payoffs and trendy traps you don't
think that stuff's out there in
alternative medicine it's saturated it's
something that spirit and I have had to
deal with for years and years and years
it's nobody's fault it's nobody's fault
and meaning in the sense that people you
know they pick up information you find
on the internet and you find in other
places whatever and and you know you
think this information is what is going
on out there and then it gets trendy or
catchy and all these things happen but
what happens is that
information has been tampered with along
the way all along the way starting from
the very beginning and it just gets more
tampered more tampered one way or
another all the health information I
share here comes from a pure untampered
with Advanced Clean Source a higher
source the spirit of compassion there's
nothing more healing than compassion
there's nothing more healing you know
someone said to me the other day look I
hear you got kind of like like a new
opening in the show where you talk about
where the information comes from and
everything else why are you doing that
and I said because some people who are
new come on to the show meaning they
they they log on to the show and they
just think it's the same old stuff they
don't even give it they don't even like
really listen to it they think it's
maybe the same old stuff that's going
around now that every expert knows or or
that experts you know created or experts
know or something or science has to
offer or whatever and then experts and
they and they think it's that oh wait a
minute and they don't realize they don't
realize that the information here has
been different all along going all the
way back to our first show and it's
always been like that including in the
books and it's important to know it's
not something that should just be you
know and I was telling this person it's
not something that should just be
ignored because someone has to be aware
of what's going on conventional medicine
we all know a conventional medicine and
chronic illness has so many problems I
mean so many problems it's
unbelievable and we know that that but
alternative medicine has so many
problems too with with chronic illness
it's unbelievable and it's not the
doctors you I have I I know so many
doctors amazing people without them we
can't live it's like that song Can't
Live living without you or whatever that
it's like you can't live without them
because um there's so many life-saving
things that are out there now and
life-saving techniques and and
life-saving Equipment being invented yes
by science but chronic
illness is a whole another place it's
for some reason it's not it's not
separated properly like for some reason
there's serious medical Denial in
conventional medicine and you know I
mean even in summon alternative medicine
thank God alternative medicine became
more open to that that's the whole point
yeah I got to tell you something if you
go back in time just a little bit I hate
giving everybody like this like history
stuff but I can't help it it's
interesting if you go back excuse me if
you go back a little bit in time maybe
the
80s and and you wouldn't believe how
separated alternative and conventional
was I can't even tell you look maybe
some of you already know that out there
maybe the younger people coming on
listening logging on to the show they
don't know this they they they they
think that it's always been kind of
functionally put together where you go
to your functional doctor you go to a
clinic that has alternative and
conventional and they're both working
side by side that didn't
exist um alternative medicine was the
enemy the enemy to Conventional medicine
the hatred was
unbelievable it was a war it was a war
it's no joke conventional
doctors they I mean literally would
dispel the slightest remedy you walk
into a drugstore Pharmacy you wouldn't
find real vitamins there you wouldn't
find eona golden seal you wouldn't find
anything there it didn't exist and if
you ask the pharmacist about and say hey
I heard golden seal is really helpful
for something if you did that where's
the golden seal they look at you like
you had 10 heads on and you know so the
deal is here that the things you know
times have changed but what turned
alternative medicine into something was
that millions of people with chronic
illness chronic
illness with no answers were so fed up
so fed up with going to their doctor
being told they're insane being told
they're lazy be being told there's
something wrong I mean with them
emotionally mentally and that their
symptoms were in their head and you know
it was a really hard time and still is
now today I talk about some of that that
I've never talked about actually before
in the other books in the thyroid book
and so
conventional medicine was this place
where when it came down to Chronic
mystery illness forget it forget it and
so you know hey the door was open it was
open right at the beginning of the 80s
right there late' 70s early ' 80s it's
when alternative medicine was actually
when people were filing in women mostly
were filing into offices naturopaths the
first naturopath in California the very
first and other naturopaths that came
after that and you know on the east
coast and you couldn't find a naturopath
in the in the uh middle of the country
in the middle of the country you
couldn't find you just couldn't find
them you couldn't find a herbalist in
the middle of the country I mean good
luck in that time time period it's
really a hard time that was happening
and you know so what happened was people
were filing in and the only answer
really alternative medicine had back in
1980 for anybody with any mystery
symptom is it's it's your it's candida
it's candida it's candida that's all it
was candida Candida candid God bless
them I mean they were wrong but God
bless them you know because it gave
something it gave an answer to some
degree to what to to anything to
anything to knowing to knowing that
there's something else going on there's
something else going on that they're not
crazy that all these women are not
insane that they actually have some
symptoms and something's wrong and you
just can't be throwing antibiotics at
them 24/7 and steroids because that's
it's still all we have today and
conventional medicine to deal with
something that's critical or something
that's you know coming you know out a
little bit out of control whatever it is
just antibiotics and steroids oh
immunosuppressive drugs which is kind of
you know almost many of them are in the
steroid category or whatever but it's
just it's a combination it's like
biologics or Amun suppressives or now
you know steroids and any biotics that's
all we got and so women were getting
answers it was
candida and you know and yeah that's the
candida that was the whole candida craze
that started that's it took quite a
while to catch on finally and get to the
'90s and then finally get to then
everybody was getting diagnosed the
candida left and right now you know it's
sibo sibo that's the craze it's sibo
it's sibo hey leaky gut leaky gut leaky
gut that's a crazy which leaky gut's a
whole big confusion we talked about that
already in one of the shows I'll do more
about that that's information is still
off on that still off on sio we talked
about that in the sibo show and candida
especially candida because just just as
a reminder we can't live without candida
we're not saying we can't live without
doctors we can't live without candida
you die if you have no candida we die
we're we're gone we're gone we don't
live I mean we'll just
literally we won't be living like you
and I'm serious about that you have
first of all you can't get rid of all
your candid it's impossible no matter
how many cleanses and everything else
you do thank God thank God CU if you did
get rid of all your candida You' die
okay because that's that's what keeps us
alive that's a neutral fungus that does
all kinds of Miracles for us internally
and when it grows out of control that's
because something it's actually helping
you it's cleaning up a mess another
problem so that's a whole thing and you
won't find that information anywhere and
if you do it's because I I put that out
there and that's what I mean and it's
not about me being smart it's about the
information coming from that clean
Source spirit and and that's that's you
know that's what it's about and and the
deal is is that you know people were
pouring in being told that they had
candida and the conventional doctors
were like they were like that's in
that's insane conventional doctors were
like you know whatever this craze is but
women were being hurt heard and it was
so important you know we talk about all
these different things women's rights
and all these different ways but in
chronic illness oh my God it's been
terrifying
terrifying and so it's better now but
the problem is now that every single
person who has a symptom and who gets
sick gets diagnosed with Lyme disease
whether they like it or not and that's a
tragedy all all on its own absolute
tragedy and you can't it's hard to argue
it's hard to argue and even if even if
the information I talk about is 100%
right on to what's really going on it's
impossible to battle it out there it's
almost impossible because it's just it's
it's so ingrained it's been bred into
our psyche through our pets to begin
with with Lyme disease and then and then
through us it's been
unbelievable of what's going on so every
single I I'll tell you I'll give you a
prediction right now 10 more years 15
more years everybody's going to have
Lyme disease that has a symptom or not
just going to the doctor and getting
some blood tests because there's there's
something totally 100% corrupted in the
system of medicine today alternatively
that's allowing for these Lyme disease
diagnoses to get out of control to this
degree if you just logged on and you
don't understand like meaning you're
you're like what's he talking about
what's he saying you know get book one
and read the lime chapter to begin with
just so you can get familiar with what's
really
happening and and I'm talking about this
because it starts like I said the
conventional here's okay here's the deal
so conventional and alternative medicine
they were separated they were separated
far apart they came together there's
some good things there's some bad things
there's some good bad and ugly about
that okay some good things are is thank
God we're all working together some bad
things are it's really brought in
exactly the Lyme disease craz now like
that was
conventional that was conventional
believe it or not even though you don't
think it was because conventional
doctors would ignore lime they would
ignore it no it was conventional it was
and it was conventionally founded and
conventional doctors didn't accept it so
it it made a confusion where wait a
minute maybe alternative medicine is is
responding to to Lyme disease more than
ever before so that's where and then but
really what happened was it was
conventionally founded
and then it was and then the
conventional you know doctors actually
the the medical system ignored it that
was a game that was a game that was a
game to rope everybody in to get the
confusion twisted and swirling out there
so that conventional alternative would
finally come together in the end to
where we are now and there's going to be
the Lyme disease craze like you've never
seen before in history ever in history
just 10 more years you won't believe
what you're going to see and how off it
really is unless we do something about
it and get real answers and do things
the way we need to do it but
conventional and alternative medicine
came together now you can get it in one
package and there's good things about
that really incredible things about it
because alternative medicine offers so
many great things incredible things and
um and the support and it has The
Compassion there's more compassion in it
you know nowadays than even there was
before and in and and it and it forces
the conventional model to have more
compassion than ever did before so
there's some beautiful wonderful things
that have occurred from having them join
together you know great things and then
you there's been more more opportunities
for both sides to to you know glean from
each other as well and that's been some
of the good things there's there's also
other bad things too but why why am I
kind of talking about the history a
little bit and where we're at now cuz
when it comes down to lupus which we're
going to get to that is one massive
confusion that's one massive confusion
and the reason why I'm even talking
about lime is because every single
person with lupus will be diagnosed with
lime even though they don't really have
it I'm just for warning just forewarning
you if you're a practitioner listening
to I'm just just just giving you the you
know the
411 that's just everybody with lupus is
going to be going to a lime doctor filed
into the lime trap every single one
eventually and there's there's going to
be something strange happening coming in
the next 10 years lupus diagnoses are
going to be
less they're going to be less even
though there's more people with symptoms
mystery symptoms that would have been
identified as lupus
originally but there's going to be less
diagnosis multiple
sclerosis um patients people with MS
symptoms are going to be getting more
symptoms meaning more and more people
getting new found symptoms and of of Ms
but they're going to be diagnosed less
with Ms do you see because they're all
going to be funneled to the lime machine
the lime machine a trillion doll coming
up business the lime lime machine and um
and every every time you see a tick
you're just going to you're just you're
going to lose your breath
you you know and that's what's going to
happen and and the reason why I'm
talking about this is because we're
talking about lupus but it's lupus is
going to be outdated the diagnosis
itself is going to be outdated even
people who have been carrying that
diagnosis for 10 years already 15 years
they're going to be forced forced to
believe they have something else
even though lupus in itself is confusion
to begin with the diagnoses everything
about it's a mystery doctors don't even
know what really is lupus is it even
something at all even with all that it's
going to be less less and less of a
diagnosis and people who have already
had long-standing long-term lupus
identified in their medical records
they're going to be going to doctors and
doctors can be a look I just did a lime
test on you you got lime now maybe
that's what this has been the whole
whole time it's been lime this whole
time it no one talks about this no one
talks about the truth about anything
about this even you can alter medicine
listen to podcast or just no one's going
to any of this it's it's it it it blows
me away and maybe because they don't
have spirit and I got to remember that I
always have to remember that you know
Spirit even reminds me once in a while
and even even my family reminds me and
like remember you know you're just you
can't get all wound up because they they
don't have Spirit talking to them
telling them this so you can't get that
charged up you can't get charged up of
why everything's so slow and coming and
why it always gets twisted and turns and
goes in different in the wrong
directions out there in alternative Inc
conventional medicine
and and then somebody else will say well
you know that's crazy look what science
has to offer absolutely and I love it
I'm huge I'm a big science fan I'm a
science fan because I love Spirit
debunking it constantly it's fun that's
one of the reasons why I'm a fan the
other reason why is because a lot of
science is really gr but even the
mechanical stuff that's created by the
technology that's created by science
still there's problems everywhere look
at the hernia
mesh I mean look at the I mean it's just
one blunder after another and these are
things that have been weighed and
measured science is about weighing and
measuring you guys it's about weighing
and measuring that's what science is you
can't weit you can't measure it then
it's just a theory which if there's the
right funding in the right place then
that theory will take off and be
something they'll make that theory and
turn that theory into something because
it'll be funded and when people put
money in oh you don't want to piss them
off you don't want to piss off those
people who put big money into things so
you got to put your thumb on the scale
and make that theory into something oh
yeah no it did come out this okay let's
do it this this did come out this way
worry about the consequences later and
so so but but science is about weighing
and measuring it's about facts facts
that have been weighed and measured
perfectly and so there's things that we
create in science technology and and
physical things just they don't work out
you got they just don't they were weight
and measured they should have worked it
but they didn't even that has holes in
it why am I talking about all this again
because when it comes down to lupus it's
so so confusing and and it's a hard deal
it's a hard deal the way lupus came
about the way it was discovered the way
you know the way people like okay you
got rash you got fever we don't know
what it is you got lupus whether tests
show anything or they don't lupus has
been a tough one so I'm letting you know
it can't be weigh or measured lupus
can't be weigh or
measured it can't be weight or
measured even lime disease can't be
weight and measured it can't why do you
think people get a borderline listen if
you have a pathogen if you have say a
bacteria that's causing Lyme disease
it's either you have it or you're not or
you don't
so the best Labs the best newest labs in
the country say oh it's borderline it it
could be there it might not be there no
no if you have a
pathogen it's there or it's
not that's one of the greatest mistakes
they're going to change that cuz that's
a that's a
flaw that that is showing something's
wrong with the whole lime testing to
begin with and that's going to change
watch I guarantee you doctors won't be
getting tests coming back borderline
anymore because that's a massive mess up
all on its own that's happening they're
going to fix that they're going to fix
that because they know that that was
they shouldn't be saying that and you
know the thing is you know so weight and
measured lupus can't be weight and
measured chronic illness can't be weight
and
measured it can't be it can't be and so
this is this is where chronic
illness has to be separated and
respected it has to be respected and
separated from all the nonsense it
really does and it has to be it it
really something has to change and
that's what the shows about and uh and
the the decades and decades that put
into uh helping people and everything
else around it you know check out the
Instagram medical medium Instagram
because it's just it's so inspiring it
just constantly inspires me everybody
telling their stories of what they go
through what what's happening what
meaning their healing process what
they've been through and how they're
healing I it's it's incredible to watch
somebody reminded me recently a mom and
their child and and she said on
Instagram she said you know the all
storms pass everything changes and
nothing stays the same really helped her
to get through a hard time and in in
spirit you know Spirit gave me that a
long time ago all storms pass everything
Chang ches and nothing stays the same I
want to just talk about it for one
minute a couple minutes what does that
mean what is that about first of all
storms meaning whether it's a Health
crisis whether something's happening in
your family whether something's going on
whether you got stress whether it's
Financial terrible financial problems
whatever it is whatever is going on in
your life it's a
storm if you're sick it's a
storm and there's something to
understand that Spirit taught me doesn't
matter if the storm going on for 5 years
minutes 5 months 10 years it doesn't
matter how
long everything changes and nothing
stays the same it will change it will
pass this is something that can bring
you peace no matter what's happening in
your life it's brought me peace if I've
ever come across a storm because storms
don't Define us you have to know that
they don't Define who we are the storm
is not you
the storm is not
you that's what I'm saying the storm is
not you even if you're sick because
guess what if you're sick it's not your
fault it's not your fault you're sick
you didn't create it's not because
you're faulty it's not because you have
bad genes it's not because you're a bad
person that's that's not why you're
struggling with some kind of illness
something happened something happened
that medical science and research hasn't
figured out that's what I'm saying it
can't be weighted measured in chronic
illness that's not your
fault did anybody um listen to the uh
autoimmune autoimmune webinar I just did
I talked a little bit about that in the
webinar there's some webinars coming up
and you got to catch them you got to
catch them there's a few more
webinars um so all storms pass whether
we're going through hard times
hardships and whatever that is doesn't
matter what it is somebody's trying to
you know throw judgment on you so
whatever they're trying to do someone's
bullying you whatever is happening
everything changes and nothing stays the
same and you always have to remember
that and that storm isn't you it's not
you so if you're having a problem with a
a
coworker or or colleague or you can't
find work or whatever it is that's not
what defines you
it's not if you're sick it's not either
and and when we're sick we're always
it's always blamed on you it's always
blamed on you blamed on us we're sick
that's St you you you're obvious not
doing something right you're obviously
not doing something or you just got bad
genes if there's no answers you know or
you're just you know or it's autoimmune
your body's attacking itself oh my God
if I hear that one more time out there
and so so when we have these storms and
we have mystery
lupus it's not what defines you okay
it's not who you are something's
happening we're going to talk about it
and we've we've already probably talked
about it I know we talked about in book
one a little bit where lupus comes from
I'm sure some of you are like oh yeah I
know where it is I know what it is where
it is in the book and the whole bit but
this is important to just understand
though about how it works it can't be
waiter measured it's a
storm and it's not you it's not your
fault that's just like that with
anything going on anyway the person that
reminded me if you go to Instagram and
you you you search through and
everything like that the mom that
reminded me about all storms pass um
things got better for her
child got better for her child and and
better for her and they're moving
they're moving past the storm like never
before and so it's just something to
think about it's something to think
about so um so let's talk about lupus
that's what it's about we're trying you
know I'm giving you this whole the
reason why this whole monologue is
happening right at the beginning this
really long monologue which you know
whatever is happening is because I'm
trying to prepare you because these are
the things going on especially with
someone with lupus is they get filed
into lime the lime trap like I talked
about earlier there there's going to be
less lupus diagnoses because everybody's
just going to put everybody into lime no
matter what it is and we can just we
could talk about all kinds of of of
different autoimmune and illnesses and
everything else so all right so lupus
the whole bit let just let's run down
some of the symptoms of
Lupus fatigue right chronic fatigue
depending on how serious somebody's
lupus is could be uh mild fatigue on
andof fatigue sometimes chronic joint
pain could have fevers no fevers could
be fevers for some people no fevers for
others um uh joint pain joint swelling
swelling
edema so edema which means swelling
ankles mysterious you know chronic
illness is all mysterious swelling
ankles swelling knees um fluid retention
the whole bit um some of you probably
like hey I got joint pain do I have
Lupus that's how ridiculous it is
because meaning not the pain not your
symptom not what's going on there you
totally validated that's not the problem
but if you went to a lupus specialist
yeah you'd probably get you know thrown
into a lupus category it's possible but
eventually like I said that's going to
be outdated everybody's going into lime
and don't get scared you don't have lime
um swelling hair
loss so that's another thing too that
occurs hair loss Rod's phenomenon right
Rod's phenomenon rod syndrome some
people say in the whole bit that's the
discoloration of the uh hands or the
feet that whole thing uh rashes all over
the body that could be lupus um give
take um so these are some of the
symptoms these are some of the symptoms
let's cover these symptoms for a minute
let's talk about him for a little
bit um fatigue chronic fatigue that's
Epstein bar that's Epstein bar because
with with lupus you can get the white
count could be off it could be up it
could be down red red bullet cells down
that could happen or they could be
stabled and go down low platelets can
occur you could you may not have low
platelets May not have red blood cell
problems with lopus but you have white
blood cell issues it's all Epstein bar
right there it's all viral infection
viral infection to this day why aren't
the best medical doctors saying you have
a viral infection when you go to the
doctor you have these symptoms that's
what's supposed to be happening I'll
tell you why it's not because something
is just messed up in the system and it's
been messed up in the system and it's
not the doctor's fault it's not the
awesome amazing doctor's fault who's
dedicated their life to helping sick
people it's not their fault but there's
something terribly messed up in the
system it's legit seriously messed up
I'm serious for a long time now and
still going and not
stopping you walk into the doctor's
office and you got
fatigue and you got um
swelling you got a viral infection
you know I mean of course they can do
all the weighing and measuring they can
do some tests they can look for some
weird thing that happened you know what
happens too some people if they have a
cancer they never knew about sitting
inside of
them that will be blamed on
everything when it has nothing to do
with the whole thing they're going
through like nothing to do with the
symptoms they're going through at all
nothing to do with their fatigue at all
but if they find something cancer oh
this is this is it right here it's all
this it's another mistake made
constantly so um you know this this is
this is how it works so joint pain
fevers that are chronic up and down I
mean you walk into a doctor's office it
should be instant you got a viral
infection it's like what happened with
Lyme disease back in um uh 70 whatever
73 or whatever it was and I'm going to
tell you now I'm going to tell you right
now that right in the early '70s when
people filed in the doctors knew it was
viral they knew Lyme disease was viral
they knew the symptoms that everybody
was getting were 100% viral but there
was a massive problem the problem was
back in the 70s there weren't even
antivirals to make money off of so there
wasn't antivirals to make money off of
viral mean we we got to throw our hands
in the air and there's nothing to treat
you there's no way to help you and
that's just the bottom line because an
antibiotic was not used at all back in
the early 70s and when they noticed that
they when they used it for somebody that
walked in that had these these these
crazy symptoms that were viral they knew
that if they used it and they they did
use it they got sicker which happens to
90% of the lime patients of today now
remember this if you're one of the 10%
it's that had some antibiotics and swear
by them you know amazing but 90% think
about 90 people out of a 100 people 90
out of a 100 gets sicker from the
antibiotic meaning their condition
worsens they're worse off to where they
started with their lime 90 out of 100
just think about that line up a 100
people 90 of them are going to become
more worse
off sure 10 may not or eight out of that
10 may not but 90 are is a problem is a
massive problem and that's that's that's
what you have to understand and and so
back in the early '70s when they filed
in with with the first symptoms on in in
Connecticut and just so you know
everywhere globally was happening at the
same time globally at the same time it
wasn't just Connecticut it was
everywhere at the same time I talk about
this in in in book one with the lime
chapter so I don't want to go too deep
into it all you can you can totally just
get it from there but the bottom line is
when they filed in they knew it was
viral a viral
infection amazing smart Physicians
you know dedicated to helping people
knew somehow some way that this was
viral and and and that's incredible
that's incredible but medicine it wasn't
good for for big Pharma it wasn't good
for the medical world because there's no
way to treat it and make money off of it
there's no way to treat it no way to
make money off of it so it was a
disaster it was a finan it was a it was
it wasn't a financial
gaining illness there were people filing
in but there's no way to financially
gain so that's where the bacterial thing
had to come later I know people you know
that are that know that they're really
hung up on Lime right now they're
probably just swearing at me and maybe
even turning off the radio and uh just
keep it on try to keep it on and hang in
there and so when it what was bacterial
deemed you were able to treat it and
then and then the antibiotics became a
massive a massive financial gain
and we've suffered 30 I mean I've seen
people 30 20 years ago whatever you name
it even longer that if if their lives
have been ruined and they put in
wheelchairs because of the antibiotics
but the point is is
that anybody coming in they knew it was
viral now the same thing should be
happening now with any lupus stuff
instead of the trend heading to they
come in well I know you had lupus I know
you've been diagnosed with lupus 4 years
ago go ma'am I know that but we need to
do a lime panel we got to send you to a
lime Specialist or do a lime panel and
you probably had that this whole time
instead of it going there it should be
like this is viral The Chronic fatigue
the joint pain the on andof fevers the
white blood cells being totally up and
down which wherever where they want to
go which lympocytes nutrifil basophils
monocytes whatever it
is um all this involved should be like
hey this is viral that's what should be
happening but it's not it's not it's not
it's not it's a disaster and there
nothing's getting fixed out there did I
sound negative
today sound negative today what have
happened did I wake up on the wrong side
of the bed so
what all right here's the deal so um
when you know with lupus and lupus
symptoms those are viral symptoms the
first thing we have to understand why is
that important because in order to get
better you have to know what's going on
in order to get better you have to have
you need a truth you need to know what's
happening what's going
on and it it's critical to know that
rashes all over the body the lupus
people with lupus have rashes those
rashes that's viral those are viral
rashes that was
101 that was um one 101 back in the
early 1970s with Physicians rashes that
H that are like you you know someone
with lupus is 101 a viral
infection chronic viral
infection where did we go wrong so the
early the Early
doctors that you know took in early lime
people the very first ones in early 7s
they were brilliant
brilliant but they got stifled that they
were told to shut up
they were told to shut up that's right
they were told to shut up don't be
telling everybody what they really don't
be telling the truth cuz we we need to
make money off this and that's where it
went wrong it's the start anyway and
then we were trained trained otherwise
so now we're trained with lupus the
body's attacking itself it's autoimmune
you walk in you get a lupus diagnosis oh
it's your fault your body's attacking
itself how's that you see what it mean
it's just it's just it's mindblowing
yeah this stuff keeps me up at night you
know I wake up and I'm like thinking
about it like how do we change this what
do we do and spirit's like we're going
to put the books out and we're going to
get people to learn we just have to I'm
like okay all right and you know here's
the deal so with
lupus the body is not attacking itself
bottom line so you're told the body's
attacking itself it's not attacking
itself it's not there's a virus there's
a viral infection there's a virus
attacking the body it's important to
know that because your immune system
will line up to that your immune system
will line up to the thinking to actually
The Knowing to your cells in the body
that there's an Invader that needs to be
kicked out of your body and that's what
you're going to start doing kicking the
crap out of it out of your body what's
the Invader with lupus 100% Epstein bar
Epstein bar 100% related it is what it
is when someone walks into a doctor's
office and they got the chronic fatigue
and they got the unexplainable Jo joint
pain and unexplainable everything else
that goes along with it they should be
like the doctor should be like we're
doing Epstein bar panel and we're also
not going to we're not going to stand
for whatever that panel says because the
Epstein bar panel is is still not a
strong it's still not a strong test
because there's so much confusion with
it but it's Epstein bar is what it is if
it shows like what happens is you'll get
the Epstein bar test and be like well
you had Epstein bar you had it at one
time in your life but it's not what's
causing the lupus symptoms now that's
not true what happens is Epstein bar has
different stages you get it first it
goes away but it doesn't go away it goes
away and it still causes problems it
still causes problems to organs it still
causes symptoms it causes toxins which
are
neurotoxins which identify to a lot of
the chronic pain chronic nerve pain
because of neurotoxins you don't need a
blood test saying that it's present in
the moment because it's not in the
bloodstream the virus the Epstein bar is
not sitting in the bloodstream it's in
tissue it's in the liver it's in places
in the body it's in the spleen they
can't test for that that's what I mean
science and research just can't even get
up to the point of what to do for
testing for viruses properly but lupus
is the Epstein bar sits inside the liver
releases a lot of dermatoxin which
becomes the
rashes the rashes these they're dermat
toxic
rashes it's a toxin the liver gets
sluggish every lupus person has a
sluggish liver the liver gets real
sluggish the Epstein bar sits inside the
liver it releases the poison the poison
gets surface to the skin because it
can't find its way out of the body easy
because the liver is really sluggish and
the lymphatic systems swelling with a
lot of people with lupus so the toxins
have nowhere to go they surface to the
skin and you get the rashes they can be
shapes and size es all kinds they can be
butterfly they can be not butterfly they
can be everything blotches blotches here
everywhere and that's why everybody's so
confused and they're staying confused
and then the doctors who just you know
like because lime is getting so popular
it's like just no wait it's been lime
all this time and then Lupus patients
get bombarded with a ton of antibiotics
which a lot of lime doctors have learned
over the last 30 years they practice
that it was a mistake so they're doing
way less of that thank God and they're
using cat's claw and they're using other
things but they don't realize those
practitioners don't realize the reason
why cat's Claw is working is because
cats claw kills Epstein
bar it kills
viruses that are creating lime symptoms
and they're like oh okay well now we're
on to something we're doing less
antibiotics and sometimes no antibiotics
at all and we're using vitamin C and IV
infusions and we're using cats claw and
we're getting results thank God Spirit
was able to give those results 30 years
ago to all the lime people that came to
me and I've had to recover hundreds and
hundreds and hundreds of lime patients
over the last three decades because
Spirit gave me the advanced information
I'm giving you today then when it was
really
prehistoric back then really
prehistoric I love it when someone comes
to me and be like yeah you know this new
lime doctor is great doesn't use
antibiotics he's just starting to use
vitamin C IV and he's just starting to
use some cats claws like great I was
doing that 30 years ago cuz the spirit
helping my people live their life and
get better then so they can have a life
now and you know so the good news is
it's shifting am I being sarcastic I
think so it's shifting it's shifting and
that's the good
news but with lupus yes those rashes
they're all dermato toxins coming from a
virus that's releasing the poison after
consum consuming poison in the liver and
in the body including foods that we're
not supposed to be eating whatever that
might be dairy products cheese milk
butter eggs ghee whatever it's just
anything like that can feed viruses
really bad and so that's something there
canola oil can feed viruses really bad
we got to be careful and stay away from
that we got to be cautious on the animal
proteins I'm not anti-animal protein I
say it again I say it in the different
groups I've always said look it's about
lowering your animal protein it's you if
you're a big animal protein person you
can keep it but you got to lower it you
can't be doing eggs and bacon for
breakfast in the morning it's not going
to get you better I don't care what
anybody says whatever belief system is
out there cuz it's not about a belief
system here it's about what's wrong with
you
internally that's another problem I have
every now and then somebody to be like
look I think you're anti- you're anti
the high protein animal diet out there
no that's not it I'm anti whatever is
going to happen that shouldn't be
happening inside the body that we can
change by doing something different so
something gets better in the body I
don't know if I'm anti whatever that
meant but you know what I
mean and and so if you're big on animal
protein you've been diagnosed with lupus
that's got to you got to cut that back
I'm just saying because I'll tell you
why the animal fat in the animal protein
is hard on the liver and with lupus you
always have a liver problem there's
always a liver issue that's why the
inflammation tests even come out like
they do when they come out the Ana
anti-nuclear antibody test comes out in
a lot of new lupus people because it's
just gear it's showing inflammation C
reactive protein showing
inflammation and these are showing
something that inflammation stemming
from the liver that's from having a
viral infection deep in the liver
longterm like every single lime person
has as well and that can release a lot
of rashing and sometimes it just
releases depending on what variety of
Epstein bar you have and what strain you
have sometimes it just releases the
neurotoxin causing the joint pain and
not the rashes it all depends the fever
is because you have the virus there
too that's that's happening as well
organs getting inflamed isn't your body
attacking the organ and that's what
happens with medicine today they're
putting lupus in the autoimmune category
your body's attacking itself your the
problem your body's the
problem and um and so that's that's
where you fall into the category there
too eventually lime will just be thrown
in autoimmune as well later on I maybe
it already did so far and I didn't I
didn't you know I didn't get told about
that I don't check about I don't check
on what's happening out there too often
I get Advanced information from Spirit
that's always forward past it so I never
I never really you know I never because
I you know there's something sometimes
you get you know how if you if you look
into things that are so cockeyed and
they're so they're so they're so
backwards that you you you almost get
like what is it you start losing brain
cells and that's what happens out there
so um so I don't know if they've deemed
Lyme disease in the autoimmune you know
category yet or whatever I'm sure
they're probably heading there but
damaged organs everything around that
you know um inflamed organs kidneys
kidney problems with lupus that's that's
a viral inflammation inflammation that
because a virus is creating the
inflammation not your body antibodies
produced by your body are trying to go
after the virus they're not inflaming
you they're trying to go after the virus
they're trying to work on it now you
need to know that you're viral so that
your body works for you even more and
you need to know you can stomp it out
and you can kick it out and you can beat
it down and you could win this and you
can heal I've seen it I've helped people
go through it for years and years and
years
and have helped them get past it cuz
when you know the truth and you know
what's wrong you can heal you can you
have a better chance of healing versus
completely not knowing and and and be
and just falling in the whole chronic
illness pattern that's out there in the
world where there's just so much
confusion so getting the inflammation
down got it back down on the animal
protein when it comes down to lupus so
your kidneys so your liver can actually
heal the amount of bile your liver has
to produce to break down animal fat is
unbelievable you can't even imagine how
much bile salt is needed how much bile
is needed in general and and and to to
try to break down and disperse that fat
that's in a piece of lean meat I'm not
anti-meat not anti-animal products you
just have to minimize it this the same
thing with vegans same thing with vegans
vegans just this this is example someone
also said wait a minute you're
anti-vegan someone said that to me the
other day I said no it depends on what's
going on inside the body if you're
eating too many nuts and seeds like
putting tablespoons of nut Butters by
the way there's all kinds of high fat
diets out there that we're going to have
to do a whole show just on that I know
I'm going to get Flack I know that
that's a trend that's taken over I know
people are going to be pissed at me but
it doesn't matter it's about you you got
to remember something that's the whole
point it's about watching your back it's
about you that's that that's the whole
point you know so if I got to take flak
because there's a trend going on so what
it's about getting you the right
information okay that's the whole point
so if you're doing tablespoons of nut
Butters and coconut oil and blending
that up in the morning it's hard on the
liver you got to keep your fats down
lower those fats when it comes down to
lupus break them down 50% if you're
vegan break it down 50% 50% less fats
do an avocado that day okay do a handful
of nuts the rest should be apples and
other Foods it you shouldn't you
shouldn't be doing all the fats the
heavy fats the same thing with the uh
high protein diet doing lots of animal
protein plus you're doing coconut oil
all the stuff you just hard on the liver
but with lupus that is not a good thing
it's not a good
thing so that's something to understand
it's something to always kind of get in
your psyche um Epstein bar protocol for
Lupus now lupus people are really
sensitive just like so many other people
lime people everything exactly they're
really sensitive so you start slow you
get the right kind of B12 oh I've been
on B12 I've been on B2 the the the the
adino silab ball and meth meththa Bolam
in adino silab balum in combination if
you go to my website you can find a
directory I don't sell the supplements
you just but there's a directory to get
you to the right
ones and you get the right kind of B12
you get the right kind of zinc cuz zinc
is critical
for it's an anti-inflammatory because it
shuts down the Epstein bar virus that's
something to think about you want to get
a little that go to your practitioner
talk to your practitioner about it cat's
claw it's an amazing one I mean it's
it's like God's Gift God's gift to us
for for battling viral issues you can
even do a little bit on and off some
golden seal little bit of golden seal on
and off here and there talk to your
practitioner too lysine it's amazing for
Lupus take a little bit each day you
start small if you need to vitamin C is
a miracle for Lupus that's a miracle for
Lupus as well okay so vitamin C that's
another one lemon bomb yeah these are
the Staples these are the basics the
reason why is because there's a lot of
people that are viral a lot of people
that have viruses low grade and high
grade low grade or or B in their system
and so all this is important foods you
know what to avoid avoid the dairy avoid
the eggs eggs are just the worst for any
chronic illness the worst and I feel bad
because you know there just farm raised
chickens and pasture raised and they're
pecking and they're eating grass seeds
and they're all happy and beautiful eggs
and the yolk is so gorgeous you open it
up you got that deep yolk color and it's
like it's like this amazing beautiful
food right I get it but the problem is
the viruses of today feed off of eggs no
matter where what how when so you just
got to take an egg break take an egg
break all right you get better maybe you
can have it a couple of eggs again maybe
you could have the neighbors chicken
eggs again okay look so um but stay away
from the foods that are you know that
you got to stay away from foods to bring
in don't be afraid of fruit bring in a
little bit of fruit try some different
fruits you know stay consistent on
apples get the wild blueberries in there
celery juice that's an amazing weapon
powerful weapon extraordinarily um
healing weapon when it comes down to the
liver when it comes down to cleaning out
toxins out of the body when it comes
down to um helping out edema lymphodema
all the different symptoms so celery is
good fennel you can juice fennel the
bulbs of fennel if you can find some of
those the bulbs of fennel you can juice
those juicing not easy I totally
understand so if you can just if you can
just do some more green salads and chop
up more cucumbers for your salads put a
little avocado in there trade it out
instead of turkey that that that that
day and then you know have your turkey
for dinner or something whatever but you
know try to bring your fats down your
animal fats down bring just a little bit
maybe a little bit of avocado in try to
switch it up change the diet get the
diet cleaner I know the 28-day cleanse
in the first book um got a lot of people
with lupus better because they got a lot
of people with Epstein bar better it was
an
antiviral um diet the 28-day cleans was
an antiviral diet and um and that's
something you can maybe play with maybe
do two days of it just two days of it
one day of it could could be helpful
most importantly know this is not your
fault you're didn't created you can heal
viruses don't like you knowing the truth
the minute you know the truth you start
getting better things start changing
your body you wouldn't believe what your
body does when you know what's going on
inside and it's not just this random
label with no identification of what
really is
happening it's it you wouldn't believe
what the body does it it takes over it
takes over and it starts to run the show
better than ever before and it starts
going after the viral matter it starts
going after the viral cells and you
start building yourself back
up start building yourself back up you
keep a lie heart you didn't create your
lupus lupus isn't your fault it's not it
at all never was never will be it's a
storm that will pass I've seen it pass
with hundreds and hundreds it's not your
storm it's a storm that's dragging you
in that's pulling you in but it doesn't
Define you it's a storm that will pass
it's not your fault you didn't create
the storm everything changes and nothing
stays the same even if you've had loopus
for 10 years you've lost the early 20s
of your life I know a lot of people
they're like a lot of women they're like
you know what you know all my friends
they were able to do what they needed to
do they finished College they went to
grad school they you know did whatever
they needed to do um they you know and
and I couldn't because I had lupus I
couldn't because I had lupus I've been
really slowed down you're going to pick
it up on the backside you're going to
pick it up on the end on the flip side
you're going to get it in your later
years meaning you're going to get rid of
lupus and you're going to get the good
times are going to roll okay and you're
going to get a your life you're going to
have your life in a in a place that
makes you happier and happier things are
going to good things are coming you
always have to know that when you're
sick doesn't matter if you're just been
sick for 20 years 15 years 10 years it's
going to pass we're going to you chip
away little bit at a time going to chip
away at the stone a little bit at a time
okay check out um the Epstein bar in
book one the Epstein bar chapter look at
some of the supplements there listen to
the Epstein bar show too cuz that's what
lupus is the reason why I'm not giving
you a lot of fruits and vegetables and a
lot of different supplements right now
is because it's the Epstein bar you can
EAS just you you go to the Epstein bar
show look at the book
and the thyroid book coming out I talk
about Epstein bar and some other things
information I've never released or
talked about on this show or put in any
book and it's more than that I talk
about 88 different conditions and
illnesses and symptoms and and
information about the thyroid and the
inner workings of the thyroid that no
one's ever heard or known about not even
the leading experts in thyroid so make
sure you look into that um
and it's also helpful for Lupus cuz I I
wrote something in lupus in there too so
anyway keep a l heart we take one day at
a time when I was given this gift when I
was younger you know it wasn't for me I
remember people would tell me when I was
younger oh my God you're special you got
this gift no no this gift is it's not
about me it's about you getting the
right information it's about you healing
it's about you knowing what to do keep a
lighe heart have some comp passion for
yourself you're a good person you didn't
do anything wrong I love you dearly
everybody take
care