Elderberry seven times more potent than
anything out there it's really important
because this right here is revolutionary
it's an Elderberry product it's in my
hand right now respiratory right hint
hint hint was happening out there
respiratory immune system really
important for people right now but seven
times more potent this stuff I can't
wait to show you this elderberry I can't
wait to show you this thing so I'm
actually really excited about this okay
just came out vimergy.com you guys know
I endorse these guys fully endorse these
guys because this is the kind of reason
why right here this is it it's like
seven times more potent than what
anybody's using out there think about
that right now like all right that's a
big deal so I can't wait to show you
this right here okay but you guys know I
don't own viy I know the conspiracies
are out there I don't own them I don't
own any stocks I don't own any shares
I'm I don't have a percentage of the
company I'm not an owner of the company
I fully endorse these guys though and I
work with them because this doesn't
exist out there that's why very
important have you done the Elderberry
thing and you've gone and got an
Elderberry syrup out there or some kind
of Elderberry thing right and you're
using it they add water to those they
add traces of alcohol plus water plus
everything else this has raw organic
honey in the Elderberry product think
about that right there raw organic honey
in the Elderberry product I'm holding in
my hand right now it's called soothe
wise but seriously when you think about
that there's raw organic honey in this
not garbage sugar garbage beet beet um
dehydrated beet sugar all these other
things that are in the other ones like
because companies won't do this they
won't do with them did right here and
I'm blown off my seat when I had this in
my hand right here I was just like oh my
God I can't believe it finally an
Elderberry product finally an Elderberry
product that's mindblowing okay so I
just want to show you right here okay
it's really consistent really thick okay
and I'll even pour a little bit more in
there really thick really consistent all
right I'm just pouring that in there I
don't know if you can see see that seven
times more potent the concentration is
so so potent so that's the difference
right there over anything so when it
comes down to immune system immune
Health immune anything and respiratory
okay you're looking at something right
there that's critical all right so I'm
just going to put a little bit right
here in this right off of here okay so
I'm just showing you right here if you
guys can see
this nothing out there
touches this right there I'm sure you
know competitors are going to be all
jealous and freaking out because of this
product and they're going to try to
create something and say oh yeah ours is
good too you know that's going to happen
but it's never going to touch this and
what what happens with vimer G's they're
so revolutionary with what they do it's
insane I mean seriously but this is an
entirely different
Elderberry than what's out there in the
world right now and that's what we need
it's things like this that change the
world of Health it's stuff like this
that changes the world of Health okay is
when it comes down to immune system you
need every Fighting Chance if somebody
has a symptom out there okay somebody
has a symptom anybody that you know
comes to me old friend or something
they're like I got the symptom and I'm
like ooh so sorry about your immune
system like what are you talking about
the the the doctor said nothing about my
immune system nobody said anything about
my immune system if you have a SI
symptom if you have a condition it's an
immune system problem already just right
from the start and that's what people
don't understand his immune system has
everything to do with your symptoms and
your conditions and what you're
struggling with on that level physically
if you break your leg and it doesn't
heal as fast as the other guy there's a
good chance there's a reason if you
break your arm it doesn't heal as fast
as the other guy there's a reason even
breaks even bone breaks and things like
that immune system assists with that
immune system comes to the rescue it's a
big part of how we stay healthy and heal
faster immune cells so if you're immune
deficient if your immune cells are
actually on the lower scale if your bone
marrow is not producing like it needs to
produce or your immune cells are being
eaten up and eaten up because of all the
Predators that enter into our body
that's something to know because that's
what the bug world is really so the bug
world they're Predators that's what the
bug world is they get into the lymphatic
system they get into all kinds of
different areas of the body they enter
in through the mouth they enter in
through the eyes in the ears in the nose
they enter in that way through the lungs
we breathe those predators in right they
enter through bodily fluids like sharing
bodily fluids or running into a bodily
fluid thing with somebody else whatever
it is we get these bugs they go in us
some are stealth some are more just
flash in the pan aggressive with a big
bang that's what bugs are like right but
they Predators is what they are and
they're there to actually beat somebody
down they want to invade and if they're
stealth viruses stealth bugs and
different stealth kind of like pathogens
they like to nest and they nest and they
live and they stay in organs because our
immune system is
struggling that's how it works because
our immune system is struggling people
get the cold sores they get the herpes
simplex one they get the herpes simplex
right and they get the breakouts
periodically and stuff immune systems
always challenged they come out shingles
whether it's non- rashing or some other
form and they're actually struggling or
they're dealing with some kind of
fatigue but don't know why and they got
the cyto megal virus they got the
upsteam bar they got the hhv6 H h37 they
have no idea all the different bugs that
are out there right some are stealth
some are flash in the pan Big Bang bugs
that's what they are right like bugs
that are going around and everything
like that like the flues and so forth
and all that but we need to feed our
immune cells right they're hungry like
we're hungry so keep that in mind so
here's the thing I want to talk about
Hunger for a minute right when we're
hungry why are we really hungry what is
calling for a hunger okay well our body
systems become hungry right our brain
becomes hungry our neurons become hungry
right our body system becomes hungry
it's not just like us it's not just us
emotionally or consciously or
subconsciously we're hungry or the fact
that we need fuel right we need fuel for
everyday maintenance and everything
there's more than that there's deep
seated hunger that rages inside of a lot
of people because that appetite isn't
just for our stomach it isn't just for
us it's for us what that means is for
every cell in the body immune cells take
fuel that we consume and we eat and
you're looking at something right here
that's the vimergy right the vimergy
Elderberry product in my hand right here
seven times s more potent than anyone
that's out there and I am excited to
even say that because I can't even
believe I'm holding that kind of product
in my hand it's the kind of things that
I dream about like I know that you guys
you know you you probably know somebody
that dreams about something different or
maybe you dream about something
different people want to dream about
being on in paradise and Island and
soaking up the Sun and holding a coconut
in one hand and a mango in the other
hand that's an incredible dream it is
but what I do is I dream about what's
going to come out to help people like
really make a difference and help people
and turn their lives around what's going
to come out next right so my dreams
they're kind of different they're not
about being on a tropical island sure I
could just you know what I could hang
everything up and just hit a tropical
island for a few years and I could sit
there with with exactly cracking open
coconuts that would be great and maybe I
would take my my phone and do some
selfies or something like that right
that would be fun but that's not my
dream
my dream is something like this an
Elderberry concoction an Elderberry
Elixir that is seven times more potent
than anything out there and that right
there means everything to me because I
know what that can do for people how
crazy is that so somebody said over
there and I gee what is this good for
and need the name please right soothe
Wise It's called soothe wise right what
is it it's s o o t e wise sooth wise
vimergy V is and Victor i m m is and
Mary E RG y vimergy.com that's where you
get it go to vimergy.com to find this
thing you'll be blown away when you see
it I'm so pumped up it's it's
unbelievable I didn't even need to take
celery force today this did it for me
just having this and I actually had a
bunch of it already so you get it you
can purchase it at vimergy.com V is inv
Victor i m is in Mary E RG y guys I want
to talk about the immun system I want to
talk about how powerful and how
incredible this product is and what's
going on here and what's in my hands
right here and the difference there's a
difference this is incredible no fillers
no garbage no beet sugar you guys you
see you see sugar in those Elderberry
syrups out there and stuff you see cane
sugar yeah how was that cane raised what
what what kind of contaminants that are
in that cane it's not even just that
they mix cane with other things sugars
aren't just pure sugar anymore so when
they put cane in there's a small tiny
percentage of another type of sugar put
in there and people don't even realize
it so they could put cane sugar on a
product but it but cane with something
else right VY won't do that it won't go
near that this is raw organic honey in
this Elderberry Elixir seven times more
potent than anything else out there that
is insane right there okay so I want
everybody to know what's happening okay
so when we have problems we have immune
system problems that's what happening
and right now there's a massive meltdown
on this planet Earth it's immune
functions lowering you know they say
things like this now right medical
medium information called the shot first
that life expectancy is dropping I said
this for years I published this before
science published their thing okay so
science finally came out with it and
said life expectancy is dropping it's
dropping why is it dropping it's not
supposed to be dropping it's supposed to
be advancing it's supposed to be getting
better and better and longer that's how
it's supposed to go but it's dropping
more people eating organic food more
people you know doing what intermittent
fasting more people you know eating
better somewhere I'm not saying
intermittent fasting is a good thing you
know about medical me information I'm
just saying more people are trying to
take care of themselves and they're
eating more fruits and vegetables and
all all this other stuff they're staying
away from processed food but this is
what's happening though life expectancy
is dropping dropping dropping because
there's an immune deficiency an immune
system problem on planet Earth right now
and that's what's happening and there's
stuff being dumped out of the sky every
single day you guys know about that
right dump stuff being dumped out of the
sky everybody's breathing it in it's
going on the skin lowers the immune
system that's just one thing all on its
own and they're releasing pathogens
right now and they're releasing
pathogens all the time periodically but
the pathogen spill is happening and when
they spill pathogens out there they want
people to get them and get sick but
people don't know how to protect
themselves immune system wise that's why
I love this being like soothe wise okay
it's smart this is powerful for the
immune system and
respiratory respiratory
right there and that's the thing it's
okay it's like yeah yeah I picked up an
Elderberry you know syrupy thing I
picked up Elderberry well it's supposed
to be good for the immune system
supposed to be good for Respiratory um
but is it but is it really but when you
go seven times more potent with the
highest quality Elderberry unlike other
places they can get bottomed here okay
here's what it is you want to start a
supplement company go ahead start a
supplement company and what you're going
to do is you're going to buy the lower
tiers they're going to going to say it's
quality but you're going to buy the
lower tier the reason why you're going
to buy the lower tier is because of cost
and so forth right that's one thing they
tell you to buy the lower tier and then
you buy the lower tier and you package
it up and you go here's my Elderberry
product and you put it out there right
they don't do that they buy the top tier
Elderberry the one that people don't buy
so the industries don't buy you know
supplement companies don't buy they
actually use that one the one where it's
like no no that's the Premier High
quality and it's just too much it's too
much for cost it's you know whatever and
then the supplement companies they
ignore that one and they buy that bulk
bulk crap Elderberry and they put that
into their their syrups right that's how
it works vimergy doesn't do that they
get the top tier and that's why I
endorse these guys like I do that's why
I work with these guys because I don't
see that anywhere you guys I've tried
I've tried to make friends with so many
supplement companies throughout the
years tried to make friends and then I
talk to their CEOs I talk to the owners
of their companies right out there and I
say look why don't you guys do this just
like no way sorry aw it's not going to
happen I like you in all aw you're
really cool guy you know and you do you
do great work and great things out there
but we're not going to do that as a
company I ran into that every day out
there and then vimer said no no no no no
no we're not going to do it that way
we're going to do the best of the best
of the best of the best and that right
there says everything and when it comes
down to immune system people go they get
glass some people just get glassed right
they're just like immune system whatever
oh yeah that's why people don't feel
good okay they have symptoms conditions
because their immune system is shot it's
either shot struggling illing or just
weakened or deficient any of those and
all of those above people walk around
with these immune systems that are
struggling right so it is important end
very important especially the stealth
stuff that's spilled out there all the
time especially other stuff that's
spilled out there all the time that the
that they put out there okay that they
actually engineer so that's the
Elderberry right there I want people to
know about it it's called sooth wise
check it out at diy.com the is and
Victor i m is the mar ergy.com so you
know it's there it is
unbelievable stuff seven times more
potent you can't go wrong raw organic
honey in there so rapy over there on
YouTube love this stuff and it tastes
great it actually does taste great
that's incredible and there's a little
bit of lemon juice in there too little
touch of that as well I'm pouring it
right into here there it is you guys I
don't know if you can see that but it's
so incredible it's just so incredible
I'm going to have to consume that
because it's out of the bottle I'm
actually dumping it all out lra 144 over
there on YouTube says energy supplements
really make a huge difference in my
health they really do for so many people
I know it's incredible so that's an
Elderberry right their respiratory
immune system because immune cells need
to be fed and when you're using an
Elderberry product like this and
Elderberry Elixir like this you're
feeding immune cells you got to think
about it that way because that's what's
going on you're feeding those immune
cells and that's critical and people
they walk around sick they walk around
miserable right they're not well they
have so many different symptoms those
are immune system issues all to begin
with starting from the beginning when
they picked up an EBV when they picked
up a cyto when they picked up anything
like that a strep when they picked up
anything like that they run into people
they got sinusitis they got
conjunctivitis they got sty they got UTI
bladder infections kidney infection
they got P they got all kinds of
different things guys with PR prostate
issues all of that stuff out there and
it's like strap strap strap strap strap
strap strap strap strap strap strap and
it's like immune system is really going
on there it's like how come your immune
system is not beating down that strep
how come your immune system is not
pushing that back and holding that back
what's happening with your immune system
how come it's not doing its job is it
weak is it underfed is it not getting
what it needs is something wrong with it
what is going on with your immune system
what is happening and that's that people
just don't realize that's what's going
on Barbara cold and flu season shortly
it's coming it's coming cold and flu
season it is and there's bugs out there
okay they're dumping them out there you
know hey look you know they're getting
out there yes and that's what I mean
that's why the is important
so anybody anybody I know who knocks on
my door and says hey W what youve been
doing like a friend or a doctor friend
or somebody or a family member and
they're like what are you doing what's
happening you know and I'm like immune
system is what I'm working on right now
is I'm trying to get information out
there for the immune system I want
people to know I want them to be armed
armed and ready it's an important year
for that because there's going to be
some tricky Dicky stuff happening out
there and they're put they spilling
stuff out there it's going to be
floating around it's going to happen all
winter long be ready have what you need
very important tools right here okay so
if you look I got a few things out here
right now this is I'm talking about V
you guys I got a um Anatomy over here U
right on my cutting board okay I want to
talk about the immune system a little
bit too so bear with me we'll get into
that I want to talk about the liver
immune systems right there liver immune
system pancreas immune system I want to
talk about immune system in the gut too
and and all of that and how people were
like immune systems all in the gut
there's immune system in your gut for
sure but there's more immune system all
around your lymphatic system around your
torso around your gut I want to go into
that as well and then your bones
producing immune cells how important
that is your spleen if you still have
one if you still have one how many
people do I run across don't have a
spleen anymore it blew up it blew up
either from something like you know a
reaction because it got injured or it
blew up because just spontaneously on
its own because of a viral infection
they didn't know about because they just
don't know nobody knows that that's what
swells up those spleens like Epstein bar
and all that people walk around with
spleen issues immune system problems
because of their spleen being really
problematic really inflam
that's something all on its own and the
stuff they dump out there and put out
there for people to breathe in and take
in and ingest and everything knocks
things down in the in the body I want to
go into that as well so let me just show
you a couple more things and anybody who
just got on here I don't own vimergy I
want to make that clear okay I just I I
support them I endorse them I work with
them on that because of the products but
I don't have any stocks or shares don't
own the company don't have a percentage
of it I want to make that clear it's
important to me because I I don't want
people to think otherwise it's just a
fact I personally trust these guys
because these guys do it right I've
become close friends with these guys
over the years because they don't care
about the out there and they
just want to do it right they don't want
to play the games that other supplement
companies play I can't tell you the the
doors that I've knocked on the people
I've talked to in other supplement
Brands supplement Brands you may even
use every day and I talk to the heads of
those companies the owners or the CEOs
and it's the same old crap every time
they won't change their standard of crap
they won't Elevate they won't take it to
the next level and vimergy does that is
everything to me right there lupus
freeze celery 333 which one supplement
should we pack when traveling and what
about the radiation does it affect our
supplements in the
airplane so another let me talk about
airplane radiation for for one which is
really important okay unless your
supplements are actually opened on the
airplane and Spilled Out everywhere if
you took your supplements on the
airplanes this is important and you
dumped it all in a glass that was
exposed in the open you're going to have
particles radiation particles enter into
that supplement of course if that's how
you're doing it where if you take all
your bottles and you expose it all is
what I'm saying then you got the
particles radiation in the sky most L is
Fallout from World War II mostly not
it's it's also other things too like
what chobble or you know or
Fukushima right so Fukushima is a big
one right there so a lot of what
happened with Fukushima was that when
that all blew up when that reactor
melted down okay it released so much
radiation particles okay into the
atmosphere when that thing blew up
that those radiation particles they're
floating around everywhere they're in
the atmosphere floating around World War
II right heroshima right the big bomb
that is still up in our our skies
floating around the atmosphere the upper
atmosphere too really like concentrated
up there it comes down all the time we
get radiation exposure every single day
you don't get radiation exposure because
the sun technically is giving you
radiation exposure because you'll hear
that that right there is just something
that's really interesting too that I
hear all the time it's like oh the sun's
giving you radiation exposure it's like
really what it is is when you're laying
out in the sun and your clothes are off
because you're wearing you know your
swim trunks or your your bikini or
something your swimsuit when you're
doing that it's exposure from particles
it's particles landing on us every
single day radiation exposure we get
every single day that's how it works
because of of Chernobyl and Fukushima
and the big bomb and then nuclear
experiments nuclear nuclear testing in
the middle of the country on fed lands
right because did you know that there's
this many people in the just in the us
alone right compared to the vast amount
of land in the US that's uninhabited is
that insane they're like oh no there's
too much too many people population is
out of control there's way too many
people on the plane really yeah yeah 8
billion is way too many pushing on 9
billion going to be way too many we
population's out of control it's taking
up too much space really because this
much of the US is just taken up that
much small tiny little pockets right the
rest of it is tons and tons and tons and
tons and thousands and thousands and
thousands hundred thousands of Acres
that are not being used that are owned
right by the gov or owned by like the
feds or they're like they're owned by by
right
the Industries or they're owned by
something and they're all just out there
not nothing happening and that's where
you got all the area 51 crap going on
that's where all the chemtrail planes
are landing they're landing on strips no
one sees right you don't see the
chemtrail planes landing at the
airport at JFK You Don't See You Don't
See LAX you don't see airplanes coming
in all day long in LAX and they're all
the you know chemtrail planes you don't
see that and Only One Pilot gets out no
passengers get out you don't see that
where do they go they land in the middle
of the US they land in places nobody
sees that all that land that's
uninhabited all that that's how it's
done that's how it works very few people
are really in this country compared to
how much space and land there is which
is a whole another talk a whole another
whole another thing that I want to get
into sometime because it's interesting
as heck how it works and and so let's go
back to radiation a little bit so
radiation exposure in the planes is
mostly not all of it but mostly from
particle exposure and that particle
exposure is because of the the radiation
the atmosphere that's floating around
from Fukushima so forth from the bomb
World War II from from right Chernobyl
from experiments that are happening in
the in in places people are not living
and so forth out there right on on land
out there that's being tested sitting
there testing all kinds of different
things so that's where that exposure
comes from okay so you don't have to
worry about supplementation on that
level or anything like that and when it
comes down to like things you know um
let's see J over there on YouTube what
about airport scanners good question
there like first of all like I I get the
pat Downs just letting you know that's
one thing right I'll get a pat down so
when I go through the airport that's
what I do all right remember this one
time I was waiting for a pat down for 45
minutes okay so was standing there in my
socks and in those 45 minutes every now
and then someone be like Aw what are you
doing there they'd be going through the
scanner they'd be getting into the
scanner and be
like they come out of it right and in
those 45 minutes this one time there's
like a family I was like oh my God it's
medical medium right and I was standing
there in my socks right the whole bit
and they're like oh my God oh my God and
the other people it happened like over
and over on and off but the point is
that I was like and I'd be like hey hey
why are you going in the scanner why are
you going into the scanner you know like
are you going in the scanner like yeah
of course we're going in the scanner
boop boop boop they go in the scanner
it's like I'm getting a pat down for a
reason so I don't go into that scanner
but it's just you know I've talked about
that over the years for sure but the
bottom line is what about the scanner
you mean the scanner where you put the
luggage in and you got your your 2 oz
supplement and stuff like that and you
they go through the luggage that the SC
it's worth still taking even with that
even with that exposure it's worth
taking so I'll put the 2 O bottles you
know or I'll put my supplements in 2 OZ
containers I'll put those in the bag
McCaron I'll have it go through that
that you know radiation detector scanner
right where they where they take that
the images of your your luggage that I
talk about in the books and and I'll do
that and I'll be like okay there's
definitely going to be a small amount
but it's not going to touch what this is
going to do for me on my you know on my
travels on my trip it's not going to
touch what it can do for me it's not
going to touch what the zinc can do for
me it's not going to touch what the
golden seal can do for me it's not going
to touch that I'm just letting you know
so don't panic there okay so very
important to know right there so yeah
all right so when traveling these are
some of the top supplements I would take
with me I'm going to take with me matter
of fact okay so one is propolis right
there it's a must for me I love it I
know what it has the power to do I know
how good it is I know the quality of
this any propolis that I take that isn't
this one I just scream poison that's
what I scream it's like poison you taste
the alcohol I don't care if it says
alcohol you taste the alcohol you taste
that garbage you know it's burnt yep
burnt you guys know how I showed you
that before this propolis is not burnt
it is there's nothing like that out
there is the propolis pure the coratin
in it alone is a reason to actually take
it okay the coratin in this alone is
good reason to take it I'm just saying
I'm not saying go out and take hortin
because that's not going to it's not
going to help dead coratin in a bottle
in capsules does not help that's I'm
going to tell you right now coratin
that's alive active coratin that's in
the propolis pure makes the difference
that is another story right there the
active living corsin polyol in the
propis pure is another level Next Level
so that's right there um
I take these daily for my immune system
but I take them for also for protection
of bugs going around so it's about
protection I like that I like feeling
that I'm being very smart about stuff
which is important so on on the
Elderberry I just want to talk about
this one last one last moment
here there's nothing out there that's
seven times more potent like this this
is game Cher bottom line experience it
if you if you can get a chance and get a
bottle in your hand it is unbelievable
when you taste this and you use it
you're going to be like you could and
then if you ever did a taste test thing
like that's what I did I did earlier
it's like I got some some of the top
leading brands of elderbury top leading
Brands okay and I put it side by side
and tasted it and it was like oh
couldn't never ever take anything like
that that's the difference right there
respiratory important for the
respiratory system right there the lungs
very important so I want to talk about
the immune system with the lungs and
everything else Mar over there at
YouTube I always travel with propolis
and I am happy I drank it directly from
the bottle I drink it directly from the
bottle I do when I came to LA in June
this propus helped me so good I did not
pick anything up from the airport and I
usually do okay okay so that's what I do
too I don't use the dropper I take the
dropper off put a little of whatever the
dropper in my mouth like that and I
actually just do that I take a a little
Swig off the propolis bottle that's how
I take it doesn't mean you you should do
that but that's what I do
um say suus aw can you please show us
the continuity test again I love the
continuity test I love it
love it so okay there's a couple of
different continuity tests that so has
taught me throughout the years okay so I
have what I do is is I hold it in my
hand okay and and
then okay I touch my head and you that's
just one right but this is one I've been
doing a lot and I might have shown you
this one before right you guys but you
hold it in your hand and you touch your
head okay that's what you do and when
you get a chance to do that that's
that's that's a continuity test that I
do and you can feel the difference if
you take another
Elderberry right product that's out
there and you do that you'll see the
difference okay from something that's
pure and not congested with bad alcohols
bad cane sugars okay bad water because
that's what they do they mix bad water
with into the Elderberry syrups that's
what they do they mix bad water in this
Elderberry product there's no water
they're not adding water and that's
important to know it's a continuity test
you can put your hand right on your head
and you can feel it what you're feeling
is right you're feeling the energy
you'll feel the difference when you
actually hold on to anything that's
vimergy so when you do that and you do
this you'll feel it it's it's it's a
clear feeling it's not painful it's not
congestive it's not like impeded and you
can feel that with other products when
you put your hand on top of your head
like this okay and you hold the product
you can feel the imped in the product
it's really it's incredible that's just
a that was in a nutshell real
quick if we drink our supplements from
the bottle does it leave bacteria stepen
I never worry about that I don't you can
if you're concerned about that do the
dropper that's why the dropper there for
all kinds of reasons right but I'm not
worried um when I drink it from the
bottle I'm not worried about bacteria
first of all I'm not worried about
bacteria trying to survive in that right
there I if it's your bottle only then
well here's the thing if you're sharing
it that's another story if you're like
hey dude you need a swig of this and
some some guy on the street takes this
thanks you know what I mean hands it
back to you yeah I'm worried about
bacteria yeah I'm worried about bacteria
right there but if it's just you and
you're doing it another story okay or
you picked up a bug you picked up a flu
family member didn't and then you're
swigging it and you're saying to you
know family member to use it no that's
another story too okay but if it's you
and you're a bug I'm not worried no I'm
not and that's what they do
continuity look the continuity test
explanate so seeing the comments fly up
right now so I'm trying to catch a
couple while I'm talking right here
um so listen so there's a couple things
you can do with the continuity test okay
so I want to I want to run by a couple
more you know aspects of it right
so Puris pure is active right like like
it's got the six Active polyphenols like
the cortin right there's nothing like it
in the propolis world nothing like it
okay and that's an energy from like a
living be product like this there's an
energy in there right continuity test is
something that the bottle I just threw
that bottle and caught it okay
continuity test okay is when you put
your hand on your head okay and that
continuity the connection from your head
to your hand where the bottle is all
right and what you're doing instead of
your arm being out instead of your arm
and hand being out here okay you're
connecting it back right here to the
neurons to your Consciousness
subconscious to your soul you're
connecting it right there you're holding
the product in your hand like this and
that energy is running up your arm it's
running up your arm like that and what
you're doing is you're making the
continuity happen between your head and
the product in your hand is what you're
doing versus holding the product in your
hand like this okay now you're going to
make that continuity happen and you're
going to actually off boom and there it
is okay and you'll feel it and you'll
know you'll know right there when you're
actually holding these what's going on
there I'm going to do more in depth on
that too we'll do one where it's just on
that because there's a lot going on
there why do I always get sick when I'm
traveling are you putting stuff in your
mouth are you are you doing um are you
doing like an alcohol wipe on your hands
when you're traveling are you grabbing
all the door knobs are you grabbing you
know all are you hitting all the plane
button seats and then you're not you're
not like you can touch anything you want
but you just you don't all of a sudden
start eating eating
with your hands if you you could touch
anything you want you want to touch this
door handle you want to touch this you
want to pull this tray down in front of
you on the plane if there's a tray does
it matter if somebody puked on that tray
you know like a month ago and there's
still little remes all over it your
residue you you're using your hands
everywhere right you're touching
everything great nothing wrong with that
but then all of a sudden your finger's
in your
eye you're not thinking maybe you're
watching a movie on the
plane yeah you're watching a movie on
the plane and your finger's now in your
eye your finger's in your ear your
finger's in your mouth that's why that
is why the big reason probably the
number one reason why people actually
get things traveling because it's
different when you're in a house and
you're touching everything in your house
or your apartment or something it's
different but when you're out there and
you're grabbing everything and you're
touching everything it's another story
cuz you're putting it in your mouth
you're putting it in your your eyes
everybody rubs their eyes they rub their
eyes um thought garden over there and IG
says any tips for not getting sick when
traveling this is the big one right here
it's all about your hands because that's
what I do I if I'm not
traveling and I have to go somewhere and
do
something right and I got to open up
doors or whatever it is out there or I
have to go somewhere or I got to shake
somebody's hand right and got Shake
somebody's hand okay I'm not going to
take my hand and then just do this thing
where I put my fingers on my tongue to
try to get some moisture on my fingers
so I can move some papers around oh yeah
hold on I got some papers I'm Shuffling
through right here okay sure all right
yep yep hold on hold on all right yep
just lick in my hand right here like
that licking my fingers okay there we go
nice to meet you there yep nice to meet
you too okay great let me just stick my
finger on my on my tongue and so I can
do these papers right here here's a
paper for you here's a paper for you oh
nice to meet shoe too yep oh oh oh I
need some grip on these papers let me
just got my tongue there perfect here
you go here you go sick with the flu
now the other thing is is are you giving
your immune system enough support so if
you do lick your finger if you do lick
your finger after it was touching the
bathroom door in the bathroom sink it's
another thing too you're traveling
you're in the you're in the airport
bathroom right and I talk about this
flush the toilet before you do your
thing if you're going to do an
elimination in that toilet flush the
toilet that's what I do I I flush it I
go in there and I'm like well before I
do an elimination right here in this
toilet ball right here I'm going to make
sure I get a clean flush going on so I
might even lift up my leg and and hit
the handle if I don't have a handy on me
right there if I don't have any kind of
Handy wipes on me or anything like that
or I don't have a paper towel on me or
something like I carry like a paper
towel or something in my shirt pocket so
I can take the paper towel out and if I
got a flush toil at the airport I'll use
the paper towel like that right I'm not
going to touch the handle on the toilet
I know there's a lot of toilets now that
they're just it's automatic it just
happens right but I'm just saying it's
okay let's talk about the sink same
thing with the sink and other things too
there's a lot of them that aren't
automatic but the point is I'm not going
to just touch the toilet bowl handle and
be like okay all right yeah what's going
on here H let me think here got my
finger in my mouth H thinking hard who I
just give myself like five different
bugs so you got to just be really
careful like rubbing the eyes the whole
bit you get tired I mean I've traveled
with people and they've touched
everything everything under the sun
practically that they shouldn't be
touching out there while traveling and
then I'm watching they're like they're
falling asleep or something you know
they're whatever like we're we're in a
waiting room somewhere we're in some
chairs at the airport in the lounge and
they're falling asleep and they're
rubbing their eyes really hard you know
after they just touched everything I see
this all the time out there it just
happens all right so there are things
you can do to prevent getting sick and
protecting your immune system that's one
of them and now there's a whole look
there's a whole thought out there that
the more you get exposure to the
stronger you get that's not necessarily
true no it's not it's not how it works
right you you want to if you get exposed
you get exposed if you catch a flu you
catch a flu if you get sick with
something you get sick with something
yeah and you address it you take care of
it you do the right things for yourself
you keep your immune system strong you
do like you know the shock therapies
whatever it is that you got to do but
keep in mind though like keeping from
Catching things by having these you know
these the this information of not
rubbing your eyes your ears picking your
nose putting your hands in your mouth
when traveling and so forth you know not
sanitizing your hands once in a while or
giving them a wash keep that in mind
that is important to do so you're not
catching everything under the Sun out
there so um so 4 oz bottles vmer has 4
oz bottles out there you guys I'm just
going grab one right here and
um they got they got 4 o bottles out
there so the refills which is really Co
cool so they're refill 8 O bottles is
what I mean that's what they have out
there I forgot to always tell you um
which is incredible so 4 oz bottles
that's what these are so keep that in
mind which is incredible these are big
bottles all in their own there's the 8 O
refill but there's the 4 o bottles so
it's not 1 o bottles so that's another
thing somebody will be like cost-wise
it's like oh yeah I just I just paid
$112 for a 1 o bottle or $20 for a 1o
bottle and meanwhile 4 o bottles it's
different it's a whole different story
you know that's what's incredible and
then you got your 8 O bottles that's
your 8 O bottle refill bottles and you
save money with the refill bottles keep
that in mind you do save money in fact
the B12 refill makes it less expensive
than competitors out there people don't
realize that in the 8 O refill bottle so
I just wanted to show you that right
there all right let's talk about the
immune system a little and I'm going to
cover a few more things right here I'm
also going to make let me make
a right there that's the propolis right
there so I got some propolis in there
let make a little bit of a swig that's
what I call it little bit of a swig here
so I'm going to actually add some
propolis in there this is what I did
right here I'm going to show you right
now okay there's a golden seal right
there never ever ever never
underestimate golden seal uh-uh never
underestimate golden seal there's some
golden seal right there it's not burnt
okay potent but not burnt there's a big
difference right there just so you know
and what you see out there with all the
tinctures is they're burnt you'll see
the color but yet the potency is here
which is incredible but they're not
burnt all right so um I got a 8 O refill
right there of the B12 liquid B12 which
is incredible so per milliliter it's
actually less expensive you got the 8 O
than so many of the brands out there
it's incredible it's a massive bottle
I'm holding in my hand this is an 8 O
bottle I'm holding right here the refill
bottle which is incredible and saves you
money too so all right that's total
immune this is what I do propolis goes
in there total immune goes in there
golden seal goes in there okay boom just
pop that in there
okay Dr fun other brands of golden seal
really taste crappy because they're
burnt and there's additives that are not
listed in the ingredient list that's why
big difference I'm going to pop little
bit of zinc in here extra zinc it's a
little touch of zinc in the total immune
but I'm going to put a little bit of
extra zinc over there too so yeah yeah
Victoria rising from the ashes the vimer
golden seal tastes so much better and is
so much lighter colored than the
previous medical medium preferred Brands
before vimergy started making gold seal
I just want to explain that there's a
reason why the brands that are previous
Brands and the brands out there they
burn it it makes it darker but doesn't
mean it's stronger do you understand
that it okay and it doesn't mean also
that other Brands out there that barely
put any in and it's really light doesn't
mean that's stronger either okay but
there's not and the quality is not there
like the golden seal from vimer it's a
whole another story quality is not there
like that and yeah it does tastes good
and it tastes like golden seal though
don't let me don't let me um dress that
up too great golden seals tastes God
awful tried them all out there this one
tastes like golden seal
but it tastes better which is incredible
so you got the total immune got the
golden seal got the
propolis I got the Elderberry I can put
that in there
too crazy that kind of concentration
seven times more potent on the
Elderberry that is incredible I'm going
to add a little water if you don't mind
little bit of water I got a glass of
water here I'm going to just kind of add
that there
amazing okay wondering wishing says
vimergy golden seal shock therapy takes
away my awful period pain with 20 within
20 minutes only thing that takes the
pain we love it yeah no I love golden
seal shock therapy I love it I'm just
mixing these up right here you see this
for a second here you guys doing a
little mix up real quick here we go that
little spoon that's so nice
there I'm going to take this
down Victoria rising from the ashes the
vmer brand is definitely stronger
definitely I can tell the quality
difference with vimergy it has really
moved the needle with my health it makes
every difference it makes all the
difference it does you know if there was
a product company out there that would
touch what these guys do I would be
supporting it and endorsing it full
throttle and I would be sitting here
dancing in front of you guys trying to
tell you how great it is but it doesn't
exist
it doesn't exist when someday one does I
will be holding it in front of you guys
if I can see how they do it and what
they do and know for a fact that it is
that kind of like quality that kind of
level then I will show you another
company I will show you another company
here it's not a problem that's not I
want to do that I want options for
people in the world I want people to
have the things they need and right now
nothing touches this so anyway I'm going
to send this
down
woo people cut
Corners supplement company industry
World cuts Corners supplement companies
cut Corners they don't care they don't
care they want a ch- ching ch- ching ch-
ching on the chronical ill they don't
care they cut Corners because it looks
the same ain't the same B looks the same
but ain't the same okay another thing
right here
Boom the micro C if you guys experienced
micro C you know there's nothing that
touches micro C ain't nothing that
touches micro C out there I don't care
that ascorbic acid crap that burns holes
in people's stomachs you know that whole
stuff uh that all that stuff oh my God
and then the lipids mixing all the fat
lipids with the vitamin C that ascorbic
acid out
there terrible terrible terrible but the
micro nothing touches the micro SE I'm
just telling you guys right now and for
the skin and stuff I mean that's another
talk and another Another
Story and Another uh loving life
bartender give me another I forgot to
say it what the heck is wrong with me
how can I actually forget that can I add
some water in here jeez spart tender
give me another give me some more total
immune here please
boom boom nice can we not spill it can
we not
get can we not get a little
bit let's get a little bit better at
this okay how about that golden
seal
nice making one more here incredible and
I'm going to get a little bit of this
incred inredible incredible
Elderberry right there you guys the
Elderberry in there you see that nice
okay and I'm going to mix it up real
quick like this this little
spoon nice I yeah I'm just being kind of
a little
bit just trying to be
quick right here making a little bit of
mess but that's the deal all right get
ready I'm going to send one more down
that's right
woo bartender give me another aw's Barn
Grill it's talk about the immune
system okay so when you send like the
vimergy stuff
down you instantly do you guys get that
where you smile a little bit like you
actually it's like a smile that takes
over like do you feel that because when
I take that there's a frequency there's
there's a there's an energy to it I
swear to God it's like Supernatural
stuff going on with that because when
you're talking about a b product like
propolis with that living cortin and the
living polyphenols and that active like
living energy right and you're talking
about an Elderberry product that
actually has raw like raw honey organic
honey in there and you talk about a
golden seal that hasn't been burned and
you talk about a time you guys you guys
know that like total immune so look if
you're just somebody that's like where
do I start where do I start
okay ask your doctors what's right for
you ask your healthc care provider
what's right for you of course but what
I tell people if it's just you're
starting somewhere get the total immune
get the propolis pure get the golden
seal right at least get that right start
with that get the Elderberry right now
because of the Season we're going into
the Elderberry because of the Season
we're going into and you take these
right here that's an incredible start
all on its own okay you're looking at
golden seal yes exactly you're looking
at the time and the Mullen lung lung
lung respiratory respiratory respiratory
right and the zinc in there then you're
talking about the prois pure oral health
oral health so many people with oral
everybody's like clove oil clove oil
everybody's like yeah yeah you got a
problem in your mouth clove oil clove
oil clove oil uh propolis propolis
propolis that's what you put in your
mouth with oral health problems right
there mhm you put prop propolis in there
now like clove oil clove oil got a
toothache clove oil my gum got a little
absess clove oil got a little sore in my
mouth clove oil now that's a joke
compared to propolis pure that is an
absolute joke compared to propolis pure
same thing like oil pulling oral health
oil pulling propolis for oral health
that's another level there's another
level right like the fast food
restaurants I've said this over and over
again okay all right it's like years ago
I said this right you got McDonald's
right yeah remember I said this before
then you got Burger King Burger King
flame broils right they took things like
to another level they flame broiled and
then you got like Arby's they offer more
lettuce on their burgers then you got
then you it keeps on going up right then
you got what you got Taco Bell they're
putting all these different vegetables
now in their rollups then you got and it
keeps on going then you got Olive Garden
they got big salad bars then it keeps on
whatever it is keeps on going up right
and it goes up it goes up then it goes
up from there then it goes up from there
then it goes up to no processed foods
then it goes up to this level then that
level next you know no Troublemaker
foods you can keep like the medical me
information and you can go up higher and
higher and higher and higher and you can
get up here is what you can do you can
start from down here and you can get to
up
here and that's what's happening when
you actually use the right stuff you're
going from there to up
here so immune system we'll get into it
a little bit immune cells are
hungry
desperate immune cells can be desperate
okay sometimes there's people they're so
beaten down they don't feel good they
have so many symptoms they have that
despera livity they have that like that
feeling in that that that look they have
been through hell right they've been
beaten down and their immune system
shows through like their immune system
is showing through it's showing through
their skin it's showing through their
eyes it's showing through their tongue
it's showing right and and their immune
cells are desperate for fuel so they can
strike a
balance so they can strike a balance so
what happens with our immune system is
our immune system is trying to
constantly balance out the bad the
immune system is gobbling down garbage
and junk
immune cells are gobbling up radiation
particles immune cells eat radiation
particles that's how it works so keep
that in mind if you got a particle of
radiation and it somehow gets into you
someway somehow your immune cells come
by and they gobble it up that's the
whole point if something goes into your
lung that's toxic and not good like
chemrail stuff is dropping out and
you're and it's in your lung you're
breathing it in you're immune cells in
your lung are actually trying to gobble
that up before it even gets deep into
your bloodstream into your brain so you
got immune cells that are like going
into your lungs at the base of the lungs
right there little
pockets and they're actually all around
there around the lymphatic system and so
forth all around the lungs and they're
there to gobble up any kind of radiation
particles and so forth chemtrail
particles coming down your immune cells
are trying to gobble up all of that that
gets into your lungs right there okay
the flu goes down into your lungs you
breathe it in boom that's right your
immune cells are trying to get every
single little flu viral particle right
cell flu viral cell your immune system
is working hard but then your immune
cells get hungry how weak are they do
they have zinc in them are your immune
cells low on zinc is that happening or
your immune cells low on something thing
what is not feeding your immune cells
now we got to get what we can through
foods but this world has changed man I
run to people and I I respect that
because I believe you can heal so much
with Foods right but there's that one
person that that they need support
Beyond food because they're not doing
the foods right or enough of the foods
think about it it's hard right hard to
eat the way you need to eat it's hard to
take care of yourself a lot of different
ways a lot of people they struggle with
that and the stress and then they'll
emotionally eat then they'll eat
whatever some comfort Foods where
emotionally they can push to their Max
and their brain is about to explode so
they end up eating something that's like
a vice or something that's H right
something that's in front of them they
gobble
down it's hard to do everything through
food when you can't keep the foods
really good that's a whole problem all
on its own that's what I mean I believe
you can deal so much with foods but
people they have a hard time you guys
know you see it out there a hard time
with doing the foods so we need some
other things too and some people need
food and they need the
supplementation see Andre over there on
IG says and what about zinc oh yeah well
all right so here's what I love right
there's zinc in the total immune right
there so there is zinc in the total
immune there's
thyme Mullen
and zinc in the total immune okay not as
much as you're taking extra zinc like
what I'll do is I'll take extra zinc
I'll take
okay so what I'll do is take some zinc
right there you go put some zinc there
and I'll take a total
immune as
well do a total immune in there and I'll
take a golden seal and a propolis so I
just threw extra zinc in in
there right I'm going to do some golden
seal
right all right
so I added zinc to it because you zinc
deficiencies are rampant out there okay
so science is saying that men need to
have sex 21 times a month in order to
keep their prostate healthy so they
don't get prostate cancer so science
just came out with a study there really
was no study there when you look at
it scientist came out some that said men
have to have
sex 21 times a month every single month
or they're they're going to be risking
prostate
cancer okay well if a guy is having sex
21 times a month a guy most likely is
not being too
productive otherwise in their life or
work that's where for
sure pretty much that's a great way to
probably destroy a guy's adrenals over
time if it's 21 times a month without
fail not five times a month or 10 but 21
science says okay now if a man is having
sex 21 times a month they have no
zinc no zinc it is gone
gone gone like gone bye see you
later okay so if a man is having sex
five times a
month their zinc is
gone yep gone unless they're bringing
zinc in so what happens is science is
saying to protect the man from prostate
cancer they need to be having sex 21
times a month but when you think about
that that means they have no zinc
anymore guess what protects you right
your immune system protects you from all
kinds of problems like that but then you
you lose your immune system if a man's
doing that 21 times a
month because they're releasing all
their zinc they're releasing all of
their reserves because they're trying to
spread seed right that's what they're
doing they're trying to spread seed on
the planet so they're throwing all of
their phytochemical compounds immune
supporting nutrients and zinc and b12
and everything else goes out the door
it's gone but science says that's just
great because it'll stop you from
getting prostate cancer but this is the
kind of ridiculous crap you see every
day out there all the
time just like science now says even
though they have no study for it that if
you pair a tomato
with if you pair a tomato with
avocado you're going to get the
lycopenes much better and you're going
to Stave off cancer you're going to
saave something off because you're
eating your tomato with your avocado so
science now says whoa just don't have
like tomato have your tomato with
avocado first of all science was saying
back I don't know 20 years ago 15 years
ago that no one's allowed to eat a
tomato because it was going to kill you
because it was the nightshade family and
no one was even allowed to so science
was saying stay away from tomato
because they're going to hurt you and
give you arthritis because they're a
Nightshade you know member of the family
now science is saying if you pair a
tomato with avocado you can save off
cancer or anything else because it makes
the lopine so much stronger which is not
true when you put a lopine or a nutrient
with fat and you have it enter your
bloodstream it won't enter cells the
fats enter your bloodstream and they
inhibit new nutrients like lopine from
ever entering cells so easily so you
only get a fraction of that tomatoes
lopine because you actually have so much
fat in your system so science is wrong
again science is wrong wrong wrong wrong
wrong that's how it works there so
they're telling people you you get more
lopine that to actually save off cancer
protect you from cancer when you have it
with avocado but when you have it with
fat you don't get the lopine another
place science is wrong once again too
they're saying don't have berries and
antioxidants with your banan cuz your
bananas inhibited that's not true cuz
they don't have a study to show that's
actually accurate or anything exists but
there's always been an attack on bananas
because bananas actually help people
from guess what diabetes and
pre-diabetes and everything else and
they've been trying to keep people off
of bananas to make sure people go on
lots of medications like metformin and
so forth it's just crazy how it
works I talk about infertility of not
just women but infertility also of about
men too and how that works and I've
talked about that for years you know so
in life-changing Foods book you'll see
that I talk about infertility with men
and everything else in there CU I saw
somebody ask about
that
yeah so the bottom line is you'll see a
lot of silly things out there over and
over again another another really
ridiculous thing that's out there now if
you drink your tea too hot you're going
to get cancer that's the dumbest thing
thing they've ever said because they
said if you're scolding your esophagus
first of all in order to scold your
esophagus to that level you need to be
putting it down burning hot and you're
still not going to get cancer just
because you scold your you know you're
you're scolding your scalding your
esophagus whatever so it's crazy how it
works so I see this all the time the
different the different stuff they're
putting out there is nuts so back to
zinc zinc is critical because yeah
because science is actually trying to
push people to lose their zinc reserves
men and women in all all kinds of
different ways out there so zinc
deficiencies are really rampant because
we can't get enough zinc as it is so
another thing is people are saying don't
take zinc because zinc you know
minimizes your copper well we crushed
that in the past because that's not how
it works because copper is so so easy to
have in your system everybody is
overloaded with copper we have too much
copper so when you take copper
supplements you're pushing yourself into
copper poisoning when you take copper
based supplements so you'll see out
there people are like oh you're going to
get a copper deficiency if you take zinc
But the irony is no one's copper
deficient you can't be copper it's
impossible to be copper deficient we
have so much copper Copper at our
fingertips every minute avocados are
high in Copper everything is high in
copper copper is actually saturated in
the soils all organic farm soil has
copper in it all fruits and vegetables
herbs nuts seeds people eat all copper
in it right so copper is really high and
then people get sick from an in
inundation of copper both toxic coppers
and coppers that come from food so what
happens is they have this copper level
up to here it gets to the brain their
brain gets filled with copper and then
they can't talk right eventually they
start having problems with their memory
they start having all kinds of different
issues copper is one of the culprits to
why people are sick but yet zinc
deficiencies are one of the other
culprits to why people are sick zinc
deficiencies and then copper being
overloaded so when anybody's like oh I
want to take a little zinc cuz they
desperately need their immune system
desperately needs it they need it to
heal they want to take a little zinc and
then someone comes along and says oh
don't take zinc it's going to get give
you a copper problem it's like that's
insane all its own so I'm just covering
a couple of the myths that are out there
just a few things quick reminder if
you're signed up for the September 7th
meet and greet at
Aran and the a the and the Afterparty we
will be sending out a pre-order email
for the custom limited edition bottle at
airan so what's happening here is just
so you know if you don't know anything
about this yet okay Awan is making a
customized medical medium glass bottle
and it's going to have the hmds in that
glass bottle and they're putting it in
the refrigerator section made fresh
every single day so you don't have to
wait in line you literally can just grab
it and go it's an
inredible credible thing that's
happening right now I'm so excited it's
going to be in aan on the Shelf every
day if you want your custom bottle
though cuz you're only going to make a
certain amount of them and then they're
going to have the regular aan medical
medium bottle after that but it but this
customized medical medium bottle the
only way to get it really is to
pre-order it because it's just going to
get sold out right away pretty quick so
if you're coming to the meet and greet
event September 7th at airwan to meet me
I can't wait to see you guys I can't
wait to meet you guys I'm actually
really excited and there's going to be
the after party too so I'm letting you
know look out for the pre-order email is
what I'm trying to say so when you get
to that line at aan that you're getting
your bottles already you're actually
getting your customized you know um
collectable collectible bottle which is
incredible the medical meeting bottle so
you're getting it already so make sure
you look out for the pre-order email for
that hmds collectible bottle it's not
going to be the bottle by itself I still
somebody say something like no it's
going to be the bottle filled with
freshly made literally just probably an
hour before of the heavy metal detox
smoothie right in that bottle so I'm
excited about that you guys back to the
immune system protecting our immune
system is critical just want to let
everybody know our immune system is is
inside of our liver it's there every day
preventing people from getting hepatitis
C which is the low grade viral
infections you know hepatitis in general
in your immune systems in your liver
your immune systems in your pancreas
trying to prevent you from getting
pancreatic tumors pancreatic cysts so
your immune system is all around your
pancreas and in your pancreas your
immune system obviously your spleen
right you know that your immune system
is in your gut but not even a fraction
of what it is in your lymphatic system
throughout your body and in your
bloodstream so your immune system mostly
is in the bloodstream though to protect
you that's the whole point if your
immune system isn't in your bloodstream
then we would be in big trouble so our
bone marrows producing overdrive
everybody's immune cells to try to
battle everything out of the Sun from
stealth bugs to bugs that they're just
spilling at every day and Manufacturing
and putting out on us whatever it is
that we're up against okay your bone
marrows sitting there producing immune
cells every day to help you get strong I
talked about the blood draws right we
can go into that another day you know
what you have to look out for that but
either way your immune system is
floating around your bloodstream to
protect your brain and protect other
organs and protect your skin and
everything else and it's just there and
I like to feed my immune system hope you
guys like to feed your immune system so
I just wanted to tell you about that
Elderberry tonic the Elderberry Elixir
that Elderberry product which is mine
boggling right sooth Wise from vimergy
wait till you try it it's another level
it is incredible anyway you guys I got
to go and am I going to see you guys
though last second here am I going to
see you guys at airwan just want to know
if if you haven't registered yet
register it's a first of all it's a free
it's a free thing it's a free meet and
greet and Afterparty it turned into an
Afterparty because a lot of people were
signing up and I was like oh dear God a
lot of people were signing up so I was
like okay which is fine but I was like
okay after party after that so anyway
the point is if you haven't registered
register Medical .c so I know you're
coming so if you're coming but you
haven't registered you should register
so I know you're coming that's all just
want to say that all right you're
leaving already Erica incredible it's a
free event and free
Afterparty which is insane Le awesome
anyway all right guys love you and I'll
talk to you next time take care you guys
on Tik Tok guys on IG you guys on
YouTube
Rumble guys are the best but