reprehensive information about trace
minerals in this book you won't find
anywhere else I'm reading it a section
here about trace minerals versus toxic
heavy metals that sit inside our brain
to trace minerals in our brain connect
to our very soul
so trace minerals that are in our brain
tissue connect to the soul our soul
that's sitting inside of rain they hold
information within them that connects us
to the moon the stars
trace minerals they Harbor information
that connect us to the moon and stars
the atmosphere The Ether the heavens it
goes beyond textbook science it's beyond
numbers it goes straight to the soul
it's about everything people don't
realize that happens inside the brain
and what happens from above the
connection that occurs from the physical
to the metaphysical
it goes beyond textbook science it goes
beyond numbers
Beyond right or wrong are good or bad
trace minerals have both a physical
presence and a purpose and a
metaphysical presence and purpose that
information is incredible wait till you
read what's next to you guys I'm talking
about trace minerals and toxic heavy
metals but right now I'm talking about
detailed information about trace
minerals and how they connect our
physical brain to above
part of how that spiritual connection
occurs
so let's go into it a little bit
trace minerals have both a physical
presence and a purpose and a
metaphysical presence and a purpose and
along with macro minerals so I was
talking about trace minerals now I'm
talking about macro minerals trace
minerals were meant to be the only
metals inside our brain so check this
out the only metals that are supposed to
be inside your brain your friend's brain
your loved one's brain our brain is
supposed to be trace minerals because
those are soft metals that are supposed
to be inside our brain are those trace
minerals trace minerals were meant to be
the only metals inside our brain If
trace minerals had brains of their own
they would never think they'd be taking
up residence in our brains beside the
evil version of themselves good evil
trace minerals that are in our brain
good toxic industrialized heavy metals
residing inside our brain evil trace
minerals never would believe if they had
their own brain that they would be
taking up residence with evil
industrialized toxic heavy metals
so when a metal has been industrialized
like a toxic heavy metal mercury copper
lead aluminum arsenic goes on goes on
any benefit as a trace mineral is
completely destroyed for instance
industrial copper is different than the
trace mineral copper very important to
know if everybody's all into copper like
copper you need your copper you're
missing your copper and the whole bit
information in here clarifies all that
we get confused with copper we hear no
Copper's good we need lots of copper we
hear that all the time what really
happens is that when copper is
industrialized that is when it's turned
into a copper pot or copper pipe copper
vessel to drink your water out of copper
pot copper pipe or whatever it is it's
now deformed and people don't realize it
the copper is actually deformed any
opportunity for it to be beneficial
Trace mineral is now destroyed and
that's what people don't realize
whenever you industrialize copper now
it's the evil not the good but people
don't realize that professionals or
experts in health don't realize that the
residue of that copper pot or copper
pipe or copper water bottle or copper
kitchen tool or copper jewelry copper
jewelry everybody's wearing now is not
beneficial it cannot be used as an
active bioavailable Trace mineral inside
the body or brain anymore instead it's a
destructive dangerous metal because it's
been industrialized and denatured
the Earth is partly made of living trace
minerals and when they're kept in their
natural state they can be usable by the
body as long as they're in the right
amounts for the right purposes then
check this out
forging Metals though removes the
natural Earth's energy that exists in
them so when you forge the metal and you
want to make a nice piece of copper
jewelry out of copper you purchase that
was forged that was industrialized
that's toxic when a metal is
industrialized and forged it has lost
its memory an industrialized metal has
become toxic and destructive to our
bodies its natural Nature has been
disrupted and its active ability to
participate for the planet's benefit has
been lost so we're talking about good
versus evil good trace minerals that
reside inside our brain that keep us
thinking that keep us going that keep us
smart that keep us connected to above
right all of that we're talking about
the trace minerals versus evil Darkness
industrialized toxic heavy metals that
reside in our brain that have the dark
Forces attached to it that
industrialization
so I'm reading out a brain saver you
guys detailed information comprehensive
information let me just say this
when you get your brain saver books
prepared
to be mine blown
I am not kidding
be prepared and here's the other thing
be prepared
to become an expert and that's a whole
nother game the medical medium
information this is taking it to a level
no one's ever seen before wait till you
become an expert at Health in a way
that's just mind-blowing
toxic heavy metals are trace minerals
worst enemy and vice versa so check this
out
toxic heavy metals are the worst enemy
for trace minerals
Trace mineral Metals natural minerals
minerals that are inside our brain right
at the same time trace minerals the
worst enemy to toxic heavy metals one
way they're sacrificed is that toxic
heavy metals destroy the natural
energetic and physical abilities of
trace minerals so let's talk about this
your trace minerals become sacrificed
destroyed damaged by toxic heavy metals
toxic heavy metals hold a destructive
charge while trace minerals they're
polar opposite betrays minerals inside
your brain you guys are polar opposite
of toxic heavy metals they hold a
beneficial charge as neutralizers your
trace minerals that you get from
Everything Medical meme talks about from
celery juice and all the different
protocols and information and the brain
shot therapies that are in this book
here you wait till you see those what
happens is that's your neutralizer trace
minerals give up their existence and
essentially get eaten up by trying to
stop evil your trace minerals get eaten
up inside your brain because they're
trying to stop evil industrialize dark
heavy metals that's what's happening
inside our brains there's a battle going
on in our brain with good versus evil on
a physical level
not just metaphysical 2 out there right
the spiritual war that I've been talking
about for years the spiritual war
happening
as neutralizers trace minerals give up
their existence and essentially become
eaten up trying to fight and battle for
your life trying to protect you that's
what trace minerals do and they go up
against toxic heavy metals destructive
charge
here's another way trace minerals are
sacrifice because toxic heavy metals
make electricity in our brains run
hotter more Metals you got in your brain
the more the heat heats up the more the
emotional anguish and frustration and
depression and sadness and anxiety and
bipolar starts to amp up and the
depersonalization starts to amp up and
the heat happens inside the brain
the more trace minerals get eaten up
and the more mental health struggles
occur
yourself up from the mental struggles
the health struggles
that's what I recommend I recommend
becoming an expert learning how to
overcome the challenges we're faced
learning what's really happening inside
our brain how is anybody getting it
better when you really don't know what's
wrong instead we do hit and miss and
guessing games the information is in
here you guys 300 symptoms and
conditions detailed information on how
the brain works brain shot therapies
which is a new medical medium tool that
will blow your mind but that's just one
new medical medium tool that's in these
books seven heavy metal detox cleanses
and the list goes on and on not to
mention a hundred over a hundred recipes
for your brain to heal I'll see you next
time