doing a tick tock live today answering
questions
thoroughly that's number one okay
gonna be making my slash lunch slash
dinner
so i'm gonna be doing that i think i'm
gonna make maybe some roll-ups
and i might do something with potato i'm
still thinking about it so but you're
only going to be able to see it on tick
tock live
and um so it's coming up pretty soon but
you guys
and not because i don't love you guys
and want to be on here just
so you guys know 50 of the stuff i do on
here censored
uncensored if i say something a little
too far they just kick everybody off and
then the numbers go from like 1800 or
2700 down to 1800 down to 1400 and it's
1000. so that's why so i'm been going to
tic toc
and medical medium podcast at apple
podcast which is uncensored
yeah anyway good to see you guys i'm
happy
you're here jennifer mccall hey you're
edited
you're the best um and um
but i'll answer some questions of why
i'm on here so i will answer some
questions while i'm on here too
and uh but letting everybody know that
i'm gonna be on tick tock live
just you know shortly i'm going to go
from here to ig live and then boom
right on tick tock live the whole bit so
um
and there's the pamela living good
morgan says best food and supplements to
heal
pcos okay so um when it comes down to
pcos what people don't know
is that what what research and science
doesn't know it's so sad
and if something you might be someone
that's like oh don't say nothing bad
about research in science well that's
funny
because there's millions of people sick
and laying in their beds sick and going
to doctors and
fatigued and don't have answers and that
research and science hasn't saved them
it's it's really a sad
sad situation out there and we got to do
everything we can to get people better
we can't wait 50 years
in hopes that research does a test study
that determines
something about something so someone's
pcos can go away
like what uh you'll be 100 years old by
the time research in science actually
figures anything out about pcos
so anyway enough with like the sarcasm
and stuff but it's true it's true
it's true everything i said it's just so
anyway pcos it's a viral condition it's
epstein-barr virus epstein-barr virus
it's
it is from the mono and and pcos is a
result of that
the epstein-barr gets into the ovaries
that's the whole point
creates the fluid filled ovarian cysts
um
and it creates a disturbance hormonally
and and that's what that's what
epstein-barr can do
and a lot of women have epstein-barr in
different places in their body they'll
have it in their thyroids they'll have
pcos and their thyroid
in thyroiditis or hypothyroid and all
that um
best supplements are antiviral you want
to go anti-viral you guys the
supplements i use
uh personally i'll do a show on that
someday you know it's the vimergy stuff
and a couple of other things too that i
personally use but um
but um cleanse the heel is a place you
can find about pcos find out what the
cause is
a little bit more in depth what to do
dosages of supplements pcos is no joke
um people need to take that serious in
the industry
you know and and they don't understand
what it's like to have that unless
they're a woman that actually is
suffering from it or or
living with it or struggling with it and
and when you know when
people are in the industry and and the
industry is all
fine and no one's you know living in
their shoes then no one really cares
they just don't want to really discover
truly what's going on
pressing princess here hello love your
tick tock videos you're amazing pressing
prince i'm glad you're here today
awesome
uh so it's a good day when you're here
it's a good day because when i see you
come up
um are you going to do another music
video on tick tock
uh i'm gonna see you know one day at a
time one day at a time
uh i think i will be doing more but you
gotta go to tick-tock
to actually see them and i'm not gonna
be posting them
you guys i was just posting them this
week that's it so the tic toc videos i
was only posting them this week
you know the one uh the one that was
posted today and i'm
just posting them this week but i'm not
going to be posting the tick tock videos
on facebook
and not going to be posting them on ig
either
so that's just this week just letting
you know and the only way to see those
is to go there and
and see them um and but but
i'm going to be on these lives that i'm
going to be making my
lunch slash dinner i'm going to be
talking about how healing those foods
are
so i'm going to be making that i'm going
to be answering questions thoroughly
michelle
schuffer says you talk about coffee and
caffeine but not
organic decaf can i drink that well
decaffeinated coffee has caffeine
so it just has a little less so you got
to think about that so decaffeinated
coffee is just a little bit less
and so what that means is so if you have
a big cup of decaf
you're really having a half cup of
regular coffee
for caffeine wine so it's like so if
you're doing
a nice big mug of decaf coffee a nice
big mug
you're really doing a good old big cup
of coffee regular coffee caffeine wise
so it all depends if you want caffeine
out of your life
did you hear the caffeine episode
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
you guys
guys i did that podcast for you it's the
docu-series on podcasts
it's that apple podcast it's uncensored
there's 17 episodes
five meditations to heal the moon
meditation the brain meditation
freeze the bird meditation the fruit
picking meditation the star gazing
meditation
and then the potato episode and then the
apple cider vinegar episode the b12
episode
anxiety episode the neurological
symptoms episode
and brain block episode the list goes on
should really check it out
really check it out if you get a chance
adrenal issues okay rhonda says adrenal
issues dark circles
under the eyes well dark circles under
the eyes
here's what happens when your adrenals
get tired when your adrenals get tired
you get more dehydrated
that can kind of give you a little bit
of problems underneath the eyes
the other thing about underneath the
eyes is um
the liver so that's the liver so that's
what that is
so and when your liver stagnant and
sluggish
so and the other thing about dark
circles under eyes if you're tired like
me
i'll get you know i'll definitely get
some shadows under there
last night i slept three hours i've been
working full bore
some days i work 20 hours a day some
days i work 19 hours a day
i got five hours the other night three
hours last night
tomorrow i mean tonight i'm hoping to
get six if i'm lucky but i'm gonna be
working late
so just got too much to do right now so
it's but
you know so i might get a little shady
under the eyes
but but if you're getting the dark
circles in the eyes liver
that's the big one if you're rested
liver and adrenals too but mostly
liver that's the big one there because
when your blood gets toxic
the skin is really thin underneath your
eyes
really thin so when your blood gets
toxic
it shows through the thin skin
underneath your eyes that's how it works
talked about it in liver rescue by the
way you guys my book level rescue this
is cleanse the heel that's my
liver rescue um
but i'm doing a lot i'm doing more
tick-tock videos letting you know
so i'm doing a lot more tik-tok videos
i'm working on them
but i won't be re-posting those tick
tock videos
on ig and facebook so i won't be doing
that
that that's not going to be happening in
the future you guys might be noticing
that i'm i'm posting those tick tock
videos i'm going to be doing lots of
tick tock videos but i
i might not be posting them so much or
at all coming up so follow me on tick
tock so you could see them but
also most importantly follow me on tik
tok so you can get notifications for the
lives because i'm going to be answering
questions thoroughly i'm going to be
eating dinner lunch with you guys
and we're going to be shooting the sh
because
i'm actually not censored on there so
who knows what we're going to talk about
just letting you know get some lemon
balm tea right now
aaron stewart says how can i get rid of
chronic candida
fungus for 30 years on my feet um
so when it comes down to candida when it
comes down to fungus
of any kind and it's on your feet any
kind of fungus that's on your feet
you definitely definitely want to
address it with immune system you want
your immune system stronger
zinc deficiencies is why people get feet
fungus
at zinc deficiencies we walk around
through life with a zinc deficiency and
then we can catch anything
we can catch anything we can sit on a
public toilet seat pick up a variety of
strep
some antibiotic resistant straps
somebody else has
right off the toilet seat right off out
of the water someone
goes the bathroom and that's in that
toilet it's got strep all floating
around you they flush it it goes down
but the strap just clings to the side or
it's still in the water it comes back up
from the flush
then you go on that toilet you start
going the bathroom and it splashes and
that water splashes up
you know goes under your tush there and
boom you've got some streptococcus but
if you're
your zinc is good then your immune
system is going to be really
really strong and it's just going to
annihilate it hopefully before it could
get anywhere
say it goes with foot fungus it's like
if your zinc is low your immune system's
been down for years
and you're eating foods that feed that
feed
you know bad fungus i don't think that's
probably a candida but
but candida candida is not the kind of
fungus that's on feed i think
that's what they'll say but really
there's all these other types of fungus
that are on the feet
and they're not candida they're they're
a whole bunch of other ones
um so yeah yeah so much to talk about
you guys
can you speak on third nerve palsy and
the eyelid
shutting yeah the whole the whole palsy
thing the shingles virus is real you
know
any anybody i've ever known with any
kind of bell's palsy
anything like that where it it wasn't
there before
and you end up getting it where there's
a droop and all of a sudden there's like
a stroop
and you're like that or your eyes
drooping down like this and it's just
happening um and i've helped doctors for
years about this and
and and in fact medical medium
information is the only information
that put out there in the world that
bell's palsy shingles related and now
there's people that go into doctors
offices out there there's no science to
prove it there's no science research
that proves
bell's palsy is from shingles but
there's doctors all over the country in
the world now that are saying it's
shingles
because of medical mean information
without having some study it's just
really amazing how it works katie warren
hey katie you're here
you're here today um loving your tick
tocks
they're so great thank you thank you for
following tick tock
uh following me on there thanks for
being there i hope you're at the live
today
i think you're gonna be at the live
today because i could've sworn you're at
the live uh
the other day a couple days ago um
so yeah so so much good stuff you guys
to talk about so
anyway a couple of things these are big
things these aren't
silly things right these are big things
i'm talking about right here okay
really big things number one i put out
an
a podcast to recover and people's health
and change their lives
medically and podcast at apple podcast
it's not a coffee talk
where hey come on come on and we'll just
we'll shoot the breeze about some health
topics and
next what's the next guest bring on
another guest oh what are you doing
you're doing
uh you're doing fecal implants okay i've
got a specialist on there talking about
fecal implants okay that person's gone
next time next thing you've got another
person talking about something else and
that person's gone
that's not what this is and then nobody
gets better
nobody gets better you grab a tidbit you
might grab a little tip
nobody gets better this is the medical
medium podcast
17 episodes there's information packed
in there you just have to listen
and it's for free free free free free
free
everything's free free free yeah i'll be
on probably the side of a river
in a haystack in a hay bed with no shoes
on freezing and hypothermia
with no roof over my head because
everything's been free for six years now
meaning like as far as like anything i'm
doing on this kind of stuff
um debbie says i don't
drink coffee and i still have major hair
loss
please help um so what happens is did
you drink any coffee eat any chocolate
drink any much tea any black tea
throughout the years because the hair
loss comes later and it all falls out
and went with women
the the greatest joke ever played on
women which is the sickest joke by the
industry
sickest joke by the industry get them
addicted to caffeine
get them addicted to chocolate get them
addicted caffeine
throughout their life this way their
hair falls out later because it just
does because of it because the adrenals
lose their hormones
and then the hair follicles die and then
women lose their hair
now maybe you didn't have chocolate ever
in your life maybe you didn't have
caffeine ever your life
and you got some hair loss there well
then you're still losing the hormone and
the adrenal for other reasons and we got
to talk about that in sluggish liver
you know low-grade viral issues you're
not taking care of your adrenals you're
not eating enough throughout meaning
you're not eating enough snacks for
adrenals there's all kinds of reasons so
keep that in mind i talk all about that
and the information and
and maybe a bad event happened in your
life a divorce
a betrayal someone stabbed you in the
back and twisted the knife too hard
and which is terrible because that's
what happens out there maybe a couple of
emotional bullets hit you
because that happens every day out there
broken trust
dear lord broken trust betrayal
broken heart um everything and losses
that could that could also knock the
hair off your head years later
like three years later five years later
from a stressful event
you know i know i i have a friend who
had a big breakup
a big relationship breakup for her and
she was devastated
devastated it was three years ago and
her hair is just was just falling out
two years later after that
because your adrenals are running from
the emotional event all the time
and if you're someone who does caffeine
your adrenals are running during the
caffeine
and boom that hair is going to go for
women
it all it's it hinges on these things
sure a piece of chocolate it's harmless
i get it you know a cup of coffee is
harmless and espresso's harmless
sure but the hair falls out later and no
one wants to know no one no one cares or
no one
i don't know what it is it's the
weirdest thing but these things happen
anyway um but we gotta physically
support ourselves okay
and get it free at the library if you
want okay like i said everything's free
diana dia but you can get it on amazon
um dana's here so that's cool good to
see jennifer fry's here
today uh i recognize all the faces
um so yeah so
and uh lorraine um
she's here too so
so great you know great so great going
on so i want to say hi to lorraine
l glad she's here today amazing trisha
marie's here
trisha you're here and then you're on
instagram
and then i saw you on the tick tock live
we're live right now you guys we're live
right now michelle l
crazy you're here amazing that's crazy i
can't believe it because when every time
i see you here then i go okay
she's here she's really really smart
about medical medium information like a
lot of you guys are you know a lot of
you guys might not know the medical meme
information and you're here and you're
like oh i tried a little celery juice
and that's about it
but michelle really knows it lorraine
does too um so
leslie i drink coffee and have no hair
loss
yeah this is stupid you
it's really funny well here's how it
works okay
you can drink coffee for five years and
not have hair loss you can drink it for
two years
you can drink it for six years seven
years you could drink it a little longer
but it comes later and it comes later
for anybody and the timing doesn't
always have to be the same
i've seen 20 year olds drink it for a
couple of years and it all comes out
when they're 25 27
they're at these autoimmune doctors they
don't know what's wrong
alopecia is starting and you can drink
it for 10
15 years 18 years and keep your hair but
when you're now 65
it's all gonna fall out and then you're
wearing like a
a wig and so and then you're gonna be
laughing at me then maybe
and say oh he was so stupid but you know
remember me when the hair comes out down
the road
if you remember when you remember me
then then you can say wait a minute he
probably has
answers to to fix it so yeah i get it
um anyway much love and light
incredible all the praying hands
amazing stacy nesbitt struggling with
acne real
bad acne is really really annoying um
i've tried celery juice and it was
working
so it was working but now i feel like
i'm back to square one please
okay stacy look i'll give you a couple
of yeses and no's on stuff all right
but you might be like upset for a second
you might be like aw
i don't do that one food but you might
say oh aw i do do
that one food so let's just we'll play
that game for a couple seconds so
stacy um okay no nutritional yeast right
you're keeping that out there
away completely nutritional yeast will
bring that acne back on and off
it'll just acne be going good and going
good and your solar juice is trying to
stop
the acne but then a little nutritional
yeast and some little treat or some kind
of thing thrown on a food or a friend's
house and boom
the acne is going to come back that's
one are you doing any apple cider
vinegar and you might be yelling at me
right now behind the scenes here and be
like
aw i'm not doing those but you might be
so i'm just throwing this out
apple cider vinegar are you doing any of
that along the way
that's going to bring the acne back it
really is
it's good topically for acne i like
apple cider vinegar topically i talk
about that in the apple cider vinegar
show medical me and podcasts at apple
podcast
i talk about that then okay that that
mean there
so you've got to check out the episode
um
and i'm gonna do an acne stacey i'm
gonna do an acne episode
i really am i'm gonna do one and i'm
gonna do one as soon as i can
um and okay so stacy you're not doing
eggs right
because that's going to bring the acne
back too um
you're not doing eggs like at all right
now right not once a month
not once every two weeks because that's
going to bring the acne you do eggs
once a week gonna break butter cheese
milk any of that
are you away from butter cheese milk
gluten did you have gluten two weeks ago
the acne is going to come back did you
have chocolate chocolate's another one
so and if you eat a lot of grains
different kinds of grains the acne could
come back
these are just some of the things but
the celery juice is trying to battle
any of that too for one and then
can you do anything like can you help it
with any kind of protocol have you
looked into like
cleanse the heel have you looked into
any of the protocol back here
uh i'm just now i'm wondering do i even
have acme in here and
i'm pretty sure i do but i'm going to go
back here really quick and look
i got so many moving parts these days
you guys i can't
i mean to keep track of it all it's
almost
it's almost getting um
it's almost getting kind of funny okay
okay we're in the a's over
acne okay so talk about the true cause
and the supplements here too so in the
acne section
these are all the supplements and
dosages and stuff you can always try so
not only are you going to do the celery
juice but you can always try something
in here you could bring it to your
doctor whatever
um to talk to them about it but yeah so
those are the some of the things that
you got
to be cautious about but stacy stay just
keep the celery going
if you want you can up the celery juice
too a little bit i wish i had one on me
right now
fern morgan really good to see you glad
you're here i thank god for you anthony
um look i thank god for you because
you're taking care of yourself you're
doing things i'm currently in a moldy
apartment
any advice for moving into a new home
i want to heal from mold and don't know
how to clean my belongings
and what to take with me i'm vegan whoa
you're vegan
let's see that's incredible and i'm
using 32 ounces of celery juice
whoa that's that's that's a perfect
amount of celery juice really it is
that's so great
um you're doing the zinc you're doing
the lemon balm you're doing that well i
seen cats caught in spirulina fantastic
because you're keeping your immune
system strong
so the mold doesn't uh
break down your immune system that's
what you're doing so fern did you hear
my mold episode you probably heard that
um from medical media podcast at apple
podcast so what you're doing is
you're doing your celery juice which is
keeping your immune system strong
right it's also cleaning up any mold in
your system that could come in that's
incredible
you're doing your zinc to keep your
immune system strong so you don't react
to the mold
because that will help that'll help stop
you reacting to the mold
and um you're doing the lemon balm which
is really important for the nerves too
because mold can
start bothering things lysine cancer is
incredible so these are antivirals so
you're doing these antivirals to protect
your immune system so that mold
doesn't trigger something inside of you
so that's really smart fern i'm really
proud of you
i really am i really am so um
um so anyway you guys just want to
remind you we're going going to tick
tock in a little while a little later
i'm going to ig in a little bit then
we're going to tic tac but right now
we'll stay on here and we'll talk a
little bit for another one more minute
so fern um the belongings thing is
really the belonging things
is is tough what some of the things that
i've
some of the tricks that i've seen is you
put some stuff outside when the
weather's really nice
uh you can keep some of it in storage if
you have to until then but
the weather's nice you can put things
outside and i notice
that when they're outside you know in
the sun
in the fresh air sometimes it kind of
breaks it down and it starts to diminish
it diminish it diminish it it's one
little technique
it depends on how mouldy everything got
how moldy is it really is it so moldy
is it is it a is it is it a mold you
have tested
in the house and is it a really bad mold
out of all the molds
um or is it really the the usual that
everybody has kind of sprinkled about on
everything so all these things are
something to think about
i'm going to talk about mold more
eventually too so i could give you more
insight on that um carrie ford said
lemon balm and hashimoto's yeah of
course
limb bombs important for hashimoto's you
guys i'm going to
ig live now for just for a couple of
minutes i'll be on there and then going
to tick-tock live i'm going to make
myself lunch and dinner
i think i'm going to make some roll-ups
again i made some nori roll-ups
yesterday on the tik-tok lab
i did them with dolls and banana and
some other stuff i had scallions in
there
so i made that i don't know if you guys
missed it but i'm gonna do it again but
something different
and maybe something else too i think i'm
gonna make all right guys got my lemon
balm tea right now
i love you and hang in there bless your
heart truly
know that i got your back and pat
yourself on the back okay
you're you're a good person you didn't
do anything wrong it's not your fault
you're dealing with symptoms
i saw david witcher good to see you and
lorraine l okay you guys
bless your heart i'll see you