[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing
information and secrets about health
much of which is not found anywhere else
and decades ahead of what's out there
now so decades ahead of everything
science and research doesn't know what's
going on in chronic illness I'm just
going to say it plain and simple just so
you know I know that sounds strange but
if someone's sick and they're going to
doctor to doctor and they're going to
look through everything and they're
going everywhere in any place and
they're trying everything and they can't
get answers for their anxiety they can't
get answers for anything they can't get
answers for the depression cuz nobody
knows what's what's going on with
depression same thing with with anything
even basic hotus thyroiditis everything
aches and pains all kinds of different
neurological problems people get fatigue
and all that there's no real answers a
lot of theory the body's attacking
itself it's your genes so forth and so
on and so on so on this show clears up
everything for so much and for so many
people for a reason it's the source that
was given to me since Age
4 that allows me to have information
that's free information that's free from
everything
free from the whole thing this is the
only show anywhere that where the
information here doesn't come from
medical interest groups medical funding
with strings attached Bots research
lobbyist internal Kickbacks persuaded
belief systems private panel of
influencers and health field payoffs in
the system out there in
alternative and conventional medicine
and trendy traps we avoid trendy traps
so in alternative medicine so people
really get better so the belief systems
aren't all clog so everybody's not
clogged up with a belief system and they
get trapped and they're afraid of doing
so they're afraid of taking zinc cuz
they think it's going to deplete their
copper Meanwhile we're so depleted in
zinc it's the one thing to stop the
virus is causing people to get sick
everywhere sickness that's rampant
chronic illness is rising Fast and
Furious it's rising like never before
it's rising every day in the United
States alone chronic illnesses and
younger and younger and younger people
not to mention older people too are
getting sick fall falling ill with
symptoms of all kinds left and right
everywhere you go it's in Every Family
practically someone is sick with chronic
symptoms and illnesses over 250 million
Americans have problems right now it's
the only show where the information is
clean untampered with a Pure Source a
Pure Source uncontaminated that was
given as a gift to give to you guys
that's the whole point so if it's the
first time you know joining one of these
shows this you fasten your seat belts
for information you won't find anywhere
else and just know that you know my
heart is not only in it but my soul's in
it with you I got your back we're doing
it together let's get you better um try
to listen to some old shows too some of
the older shows you catch up on
everything and how things work at the
medical medium radio show today's show
is about lymphatic the lymphatic system
it's all about the lymphatic system and
you know this is this is an interesting
show because what do people know about
the lymphatic system what do we even
know I mean we know about mucus we know
they lymphatic system gets clogged we
know that our white blood cells that are
involved with the lymphatic system our
immune system is involved with the
lymphatic system we know we get lymph
nodes we know we get swollen glands we
know a lot of things out there but what
do we really know and what do we know is
causing it all what do we know the
lymphatic system is really doing what do
we know about any of it and that's what
we're exploring today we're going to air
it all out so that you become an expert
an expert at your lymphatic system an
expert at your health an expert at
getting better and
healthier and that's what we're doing
today so it's an important show it
really is so fasten your seat bels get
ready let's go for a ride let's do it
let's go for a ride get your herbal tea
get whatever you need chill out relax
we're going to just you know it's a
low-key show I'm not going to be I'm not
going to be you know throwing throwing
rocks and throwing darts and and you
know the whole bit I realize I realize
I'm a little tough on research and
science I'm a little tough on where we
stand but someone's got to stick up for
the doctors because that's what I'm
basically doing is sticking up for the
doctors because the doctors don't get
handed what they need they don't get
handed what they need in chronic illness
in chronic illness they just don't so
really what I'm doing is I'm fighting
for them I'm fighting for you I'm
fighting for them because doctors get
sick too practitioners get sick too
doctors healers get sick too they all
get sick with mystery illnesses no
matter if there's a diagnosis or a name
on it or anything like that they get
sick so let's get into the lymphatic
system that's it let's get into that the
lymphatic system so do you have a
lymphatic system yes you do of course
you do yep you you got one you better
believe it and it runs through
practically your entire body practically
your entire body it's it's it's almost
everywhere it's not every single spot
but it's darn close it I mean you got
your arms your arms your legs of
course um your abdomen all around your
colon all around your intestinal tract
around your stomach around your
pancreas okay around your
liver around your
thyroid your neck up around your brain
in certain areas
all in the lower part of the neck going
up jaw right in the back of your head in
the back of your head okay there's
lymphatic vessels in all kinds of places
these strings are literally practically
everywhere in our body what do they do
what are they even for well science of
research knows they know the immune
systems involved lymphocytes you know
lymphatic white blood cells they're
involved so that's known out there they
also know when you get a swollen gland
or a swollen node they want to poke it
they want to jab it they want to jab it
looking for cancerous cells they want to
jab it looking for things that's
something they do often when someone has
a node um in the old days and I don't
mean too far old I mean 20 years ago 20
years ago 20 years ago is nothing 20
years ago is nothing I know when you're
20 years old when you're only 20 years
of age or 19 years of age age or 21
years of age or 24 years of age 20 years
ago is a lifetime feels like a lifetime
that feels like ancient history but it's
nothing to people who get older so when
you're 40 20 years ago look that they
all of a sudden when you're 40 20 years
ago is really like oh that was it 20
years ago 15 20 years ago what they used
to do and 25 years ago what they used to
do is they used to try to remove them
they used to cut people open so if
you're child and you go to the doctor
and you got some swollen glands and they
kind of don't know what it is and they
don't know what's going on they do some
blood work your your rbcs your white
count look pretty good they say Hey you
know usually doctors are like we can try
to remove one and then we'll take a look
at it we'll try to remove it and take a
look at it or we'll just take it out
that was a bad that was a bad technique
and they still kind of offer it some
some people just kind offer it now it's
not a good thing but that's you know
that's kind of where we are instead of
realizing what's really going on now the
lymphatic the lymphatic system is
designed is designed to literally attack
and go after pathogens that's what it's
designed for it's one of its great
designs protecting you from viral
Invasion protecting you from bacterial
Invasion that's one whole Avenue the
lymphatic system is all rigged up for
another Avenue another another whole
thing that the lymphatic system does is
is it pushes out the
garbage so it gathers and pushes and
squeezes out the garbage a lot of toxins
different kinds of toxins a lot of
particles a lot of different what I call
troublemakers that get all into the to
the the the plumbing that get all into
the plumbing of the body and so this is
so the lymphatic system plays a big role
with with actually trapping trapping
what you know basically just look at
your house if your house is filled with
dust if it's filled with different
particles if it's filled with you know
termite spray if it's filled with all
kinds of different things ant spray if
it's filled with whatever you know
carpet cleaning
chemicals you know sheetrock dust
whatever your house is filled with you
know even mold whatever your house is
filled with the lymphatic system's job
is to actually do something about it see
that's what it's like so it's like when
your body gets filled with all that
stuff just like a house and your body
gets filled with all those different
things I just mentioned what happens is
something you know somebody has to do
something about it inside the body and
the lymphatic system is one of these
things but the lymphatic system is an
organ's best
friend and a specific organ at indeed is
its best friend can you guess what organ
that is which organ did you say the
pancreas nope you're wrong no pancreas
sorry to say that no if you said the
pancreas did you say the thyroid no no
and you know lymphatic system isn't the
thyroids best friend I mean it they're
good friends don't get me wrong and the
pancreas is good friends too um the
kidneys you say the kidneys whoa you
said the kidneys Y no that's wrong that
one's wrong too are we we're how about
the colon and intestinal tract that
seems like like the
lymphatic uh systems best friend doesn't
it the colon intestinal track come on
all the gut health people out there
would think it's its best friend maybe
we hit it on the nose right there did
you guess that one well that's wrong too
that's wrong too that one that's
terrible terrible that I'm doing this I
shouldn't be playing this game okay what
else is it the brain's best
friend yeah it's got to be the brain's
best friend huh of course of course
lymphatic system no it's not I won't
torture you any longer it's the liver's
best friend it is the liver it's the
liver's best friend the lymphatic system
because the liver is the filter the main
filter the big filter the big solid
filter for all that garbage I was
talking about all those different
troublemakers and poisons we get into
the ones we inherited like the DDT
pesticides herbicides fungicides the
fungicides we get when we go into a
store a department store or we order
online a new
shirt and the new shirt is saturated
with the fungicide because they're all
sprayed all new clothing except for like
special te organic cotton specialty
organic cotton clothing or something
from a you know like a specialty maker
or something like that they won't have
the fungicide on there but all close all
close now they're sprayed they're hos
down with the fungicide the fungicide
companies which are the pesticide
companies seem to have sold all
manufacturing Goods a bill of goods you
know that they've gotten in there they
it never used to be like that the
fungicide is one of the worst chemicals
for the body because it gets it really
gets into liver hampers it hurts it and
therefore what does it hurt what do all
these toxins hurt when the liver is
hurting the lymphatic system
it hurts the lymphatic system that's
what it does so we have all these
poisons everywhere it's dropping out of
the sky out of planes you name it I'm
I'm not just talking about planes with
jet fuel too that's a whole another
thing I'm talking about planes without
passengers on them specifically to drop
stuff out of them you can you can you
know you wouldn't believe what's going
on so all this stuff is coming out of
the sky we got stuff spewing out of cars
which isn't the worst thing in the world
compared to what we're up against all
the time
but we got poisons Galore everywhere we
got solvents we got you got gasoline at
the gas pumps see in the old days and
this is all important because we're
talking about toxins for a reason this
is all important and then we're going to
get into some other stuff in the old
days it was only the gas attendant that
got the gasoline on her or him it was
only the gas attendee or the gas
attendant which which you know the the
guy or the gal that pumped gas at the
gas patient pumping gas yourself years
ago was an anomaly it was it was it was
rare it was rare it was like the
Sasquatch sightings it's like the yeti
sightings it's rare to catch a yeting
Yeti sighting it's it's that you know so
it's like it's that kind of deal you're
at the gas pump now we're at the gas
pump in the old days it was just a gas
station people they lived their life in
gasoline they lived it every day and
that's what they did for a living and
there's still full serve in States and
there's full serve in different states
and there's full serve in different
places some gu some some states that
aren't full serve still offer it at some
places for like elderly people and stuff
like that so it's still out there but
it's it's it's honestly it's hard to
find unless you're in a state that does
full serve so the bottom line is the
exposure that gas station people would
get was just unbelievable they were
breathing it in all day long you got the
gas pumping into into the car you're
breathing in in all day long well now we
breathing in that never happened in
before our children are breathing it in
so our 16-year-old daughters are going
down to that they're pumping their own
gas that's because that's what we have
to do now so they're pumping their own
gas and they're literally being exposed
to gas fume something that never
happened in history never happened in
history before when gasoline in the oil
industry was created back in the early
1900s late 1800s and fuel was being
processed and the plants were being
built and all that was happening and
then we had engines running and then by
the 1905 the first cars or whatever I I
I don't have the year straight don't
quote me on those as the you know that
kind of stuff because I don't know what
year the first car I forgot but the
bottom line is you know and then the
cars 19 the 1900s early 1900s 1920s all
those years was Full Service gasoline
every decade 1930 1940 1950 1960 197 and
it went this it's changed now so our
16-year-old daughters are exposing
themselves to gasoline that's what's
happening now never happened before in
history I'm just telling you right now
our 16-year-old sons are actually
exposing themselves to gasoline and we
don't even think about it at all or
think anything about it whatsoever on
any level and of course our kids aren't
eating that good so that it's not like
they're eating they're drinking celery
juice it's not like it's not like we're
teaching our kids in the schools the
schools are teaching our kids how to eat
right no well that right now the schools
are saying stay high protein and low
carb that's what they're doing that's
not the answer either because when it
comes down to your liver and your
lymphatic system you need the right
antioxidants from Foods lots of fruits
and vegetables you need those
antioxidants to counter the amount of
poison
toxins that and and that are actually
getting into our bodies now than ever
before and going to the pizza place is
not going to cover it so so when our
kids are filling their gas tank and then
going to get a cheeseburger it's it's
all great and all and but it's not as
good as we need it to be is what I'm
saying so at a young age now we're
getting exposed to more toxins than ever
before we're inheriting toxins from our
family members going all the way back
from generation to generation from
Mercury going all the way back from DDT
during the old DDT days I talk about
this in life-changing foods you should
pick up life-changing Foods if you
haven't it's it's such like oh my God
it's one of my favorite books you know I
don't know which book is my favorite out
of the three books medical medium for
the first book and then life-changing
foods and thyroid healing I don't know
which one's my favorite I I keep on
going back and forth I'm like no this
one's my favorite no this one's my
favorite now this one's my favorite
anyway
anyway so we we're getting exposed to a
tremendous amount of toxins why is it
import important to talk about it today
because it's our lymphatic system it's
the very tool that's protecting us from
that and its best friend is the liver
and the liver's best friend is the
lymphatic system this is really
important to know so we're getting
Exposed on every level with every
chemical agent possible that's being
created at a factories every new new
chemical created every day and we're
getting exposed bottom line from our dry
cleaners all the way to perfumes and
colog that are highly toxic all the way
from plugin air fresheners by the way
the air freshener world that should be
banned and outlawed if the world worked
in the right way meaning in the way of
looking out for people with chronic
illness looking out for people with
disease looking out for people to even
healthy people getting anything the
freshener world would disappear the air
freshener world that would disappear
that's actually one of the worst of them
for the liver lymphatic system for our
bodies so we're exposed to this nonstop
nonstop and um and so what do we do
about it if we can't do anything about
what we're exposed to when we walk into
the mall or wherever we go people aren't
going to the malls that much anyway
these days but we still get exposed
everywhere else what the bottom line is
whatever we're exposed we can't do
anything about that in in a lot of ways
except what we can control in our own in
personal or own personal
environment you know you better believe
you won't see me ordering or going to
the store and grabbing those plug-in air
fresheners you better believe you won't
be seeing me do that and plug that in my
house and ruin it or plug that in my
apartment plug that into my car you
wouldn't believe that's not going to
happen so we can control those things
you can throw those out you can unplug
those and throw those out you can
control those things and there's a lot
of other things you can control too so
that helps we can still get exposed
outside of our environment and guess
what suffers our lymphatic system our
health over over all and everything else
if you got a chronic illness any
symptoms any conditions your lymphatic
system is working double time double
time up to that's what it's doing double
time and your immune system your we
counts your killer cells your white
blood cells all those your lymphocytes
all the different varieties of the
immune system monocytes basophils
neutrophils I don't know all of them I
all those lymphocytes all of them that
what happens is that they're working
double time they're working hard they're
working hard in and around the lymphatic
system the ones that are in the
lymphatic system work hard in there the
ones that are outside the body are
working hard in there they're all
working hard everything's working hard
for you not against you your immune
system never goes against you ever ever
ever ever never goes against you a
raging virus like a flu virus real bad
one yeah that goes against you you know
other viruses go against against you
bacteria goes against you other things
like that but the immune system doesn't
it doesn't and it doesn't attack the
body it never attacks the body I have a
chapter in thyroid healing read it again
the autoimmune mistake the great mistake
the autoimmune Theory weit just read
that it I'm it's it's it says it all it
says it all so so what do we do what do
we do we want to protect our immune
system we want to protect our lymphatic
system you know how we talk about immune
system oh immune support oh immune
support oh immune system support oh no
build up your immune system oh
strengthen your immune system you know
how we do that right it's really like
lymphatic system support that's what we
need to be saying build up the lymphatic
system strengthen the lymphatic system
over here and that's what we should be
saying too that's really what we should
be saying it's really what we are saying
without realizing
it yeah I know I know this stuff's heavy
I told you I told you this stuff is
pretty heavy it is so talk about viruses
let's talk about viruses the Epstein bar
virus responsible for mono it's it the
lymphatic vessels always are under
attack with the beine bar right from the
first bout of somebody's mono to later
on just having epine bar and and and
living with it everybody lives with it
we have it in our system and it's causes
everything it causes fibromyalgia it
causes multiple sclerosis it causes
rheumatoid arthritis it causes a
tremendous amount of neurological system
symptoms that get passed off as Lyme
disease it causes lupus it causes um uh
chronic fatigue syndrome all of the new
chronic fatigue syndrome labels they can
keep on stamping out a new one and a new
one and new one me and on you know to um
intolerance resist and everything they
can just keep on bringing new names to
try to keep keep everybody thinking
research and sence got somewhere with
with chronic fatigue syndrome but they
haven't yet unless they learn a it's the
Epstein bar virus and B the body's not
attacking itself and C it's not genetic
and then and then let's talk once they
got that down then then then they're
playing on a normal playing field or a
truthful playing field
so the just the Epstein bar virus alone
and what it does in the problems it's
causing within the body the lymphatic
system is literally Target number one
and they they go into battle your
lymphocytes in your lymphatic system
Epstein bar goes into the lymphatic
system and it it goes after it creates
these swollen lymph
nodes and the lymph nodes are trying to
destroy the epine bar that's where the
battle happens so much and so many
people and they get all the swollen
glands and a lot of kids with mono and
early mono symptoms they get the mumps
you know what the mumps is the mumps is
about of mono undiagnosed by the doctors
by research and science or medical
communities the MPS is Epstein bar
that's mono so when a kid gets the MPS
they when a child when a little girl or
a little boy gets the
MS that is Epstein bar that is aout of
mono that's what that is and that's the
you know and and that's what the
confusion is so when they give you you
know they give you that whole thing
about Ms it's not even correct it's not
even correct on any level it's not so Ms
that's what the whole Ms think that's
all lymphatic swelling that's a that
that virus is all the mono virus in that
lymphatic swelling right there that's
what that is and the lymphatic vessels
they're all wrapped up into that romatic
fever okay I mean that alone that's all
that's also epsteen bar um all of that
is and it's all involved with the with
the lymphatic system it's all inv
glandular fever that's mono glandular
fever they call it they call that in
different parts of the world glandular
fever and that's mono so I've seen bar
is the big one that the lymphatic system
is always up against and the lymphatic
system goes up against other viruses
viral situations without a
doubt but that
one Epstein bar and is is a big one for
all of that and so we get that when
we're younger the whole thing tonsilitis
tonsilitis is totally lymphatic it's
it's the tonsils that's what's that's
what what that's all what's around the
tonsils that's your lymphatic system
there it is tonsilitis is mono that's
Epstein bar tonsilitis they took a lot
of tonsils out of people and still do
without realizing that person has a bout
of mono
and the reason why they don't diagnose
it is because
misdiagnoses you know so a lot of
doctors don't know what they're looking
for don't know what they're looking at
happens all the time it's not their
fault that's one thing the other thing
is if you have a small bout of Epstein
bar or mono when you're young small bout
of mono when you're really
little when you get tonsilitis later a
little bit later on as a child it won't
register it the same way with your
immune system with the blood work the
finable blood work the the the the
faulty blood work system at the labs and
how we analyze blood you won't
understand the physician won't even
understand that this is a person's
second time having mono it's going to
look different in the blood work it's
going to be tonsilitis now and they
won't even have a clue at all at all
won't even have a clue and it's all
lymphatic system all around the
tonsils so these are just some examples
of how the lymphatic system works how
the tonsils work how your liver Works
how everything works all of it all of it
every last bit of it so and then there's
lymphodema lymphodema that can that
occur when lymphatic vessel swell
someone gets really viral and they get
viral inside the liver hhv6 undiscovered
nobody even knows you know they know
about hhv6 but they don't know that it
sits in the liver wreaking havoc all the
different shingles viruses that can sit
in the liver wreaking havoc hhv7
undiscovered 10 11 12 undiscovered 13
undiscovered 14 undiscovered 16
hhv6 and it goes on and it goes on so
and all these viruses the mutations
including different Epstein bars cyto
virus that's one too they all reside in
the liver and some Escape some Prosper
some turn into something some people
have less some people have more some
people only have the Epstein bar some
people have the
hhv6 some people have both the whole
thing is how it works and
then sometimes when we're immune system
is broken down we're not eating good
we're not taking care of ourselves we're
under a tremendous amount of stress we
have emotional hardships emotional
turmoil all these different things
losses all this stuff happens Financial
stress everything else and boom we're
getting chronic fatigue syndrome boom
we're getting lymphadema boom we're
getting Hashim modus
thyroiditis on our wedding day day yeah
seen that lots of times I've seen
weddings stress out a bride to such a
degree all the way to the point of
getting married and right after getting
married developing Hashimoto's
thyroiditis and running to 10 three four
five different doctors and and and
handing handing over getting handed over
Hashimoto
thyroiditis in fact on wedding days and
be right before wedding day right after
mostly right after because you know it's
's a high adrenaline thing going on and
the groom and the bride and and the
families and everything else there's
this High adrenaline thing going on and
every money is totally going
crazy and not for everybody but for a
lot of people and then boom Hashimoto's
diagnosis for a 28 29y old 25y old bride
32y old very common happens all the time
I saw it all the time for years when I
was helping out people and it happens
now our immune system gets run down from
stress from adrenaline or whatever it is
whether it's a good thing bad thing
however it is we get worn out and then
we get susceptible susceptible to so
many different things because our liers
harboring some viral material or we pick
up a new virus and our lymphatic system
can't do the job it needs to do because
it's rund down it's zinc
deficient zinc deficient a zinc
deficiency is like the lymphatic
system's worst nightmare
and the liver's worst nightmare the one
thing and I'm going to I said this
before I'm going to say it again the one
thing and I have this even I've even I
even put this in thyroid healing a
section about this okay in the myths
chapter if you go check out that chapter
and you'll see I think it's chapter 21
or something or 22 one of those
chapters um I think it is don't don't
quote me on that yeah yeah just I just
you know I've just basically finished
another book that going to be releasing
at the end of the year so My my brain is
scrambled on that I might be thinking
chapter 21 of my my my newest book
that's going to be coming out so anyway
the bottom line is zinc it's it's it's
the most precious thing for our body and
there's it's under attack by
misinformation that's just this is what
I talk about trendy traps you want to
know why I gave that little speech at
the beginning of the show trendy traps
okay because trendy trap per one is the
zinc fear zinc fear okay you you don't
have to OD on zinc by any means but
we're so deficient in it it's not even
in our food anymore our lymphatic system
is desperate for it a few tiny drops of
zinc every day can do miracles for
protecting you so that you don't end up
with Hashimoto thyroiditis on your
wedding day which I've seen so many
times if I only saw that once I would
never mention it I would never mention
that it's I would never go there if I
only saw that once I saw it dozens and
dozens of times over the years just
letting you know that's why I'm saying
it and I'll use other examples I'll I'll
switch to another example I've seen so
many times too and um well graduation
for college students you know you're
finishing up you're finishing up um
college and and you get the worst case
Amano you're finishing up college and
you get tonsilitis you finish up College
and and you get you know you get
something else you get severe chronic
fatigue you get hashimotos it's
happening now in all the kids the kids
at 22 23 years old young women
especially so I've seen that if I didn't
see that dozens and dozens dozens time I
wouldn't mention that either it'd be
this obscure one
time but anyway the bottom line is the
zinc could actually stop all that if you
have it on enough in you so you know I
always do for myself personally I always
take like one dropper full of zinc every
day one dropper full of zinc every day
of the right kind of zinc you can go to
the medical medium directory um on my
website find out which things are the
best but I do one droper full every day
and it you know it helps me and helps
protect me in my system I mean I talk to
Spirit about it all the time I want to
keep my lymphatic system strong my white
count strong I want because what does
the white blood count what does it
consist of is its most important mineral
out of all the minerals that it runs on
zinc and that's the main one that's the
main one so when we go zinc fear because
we think it's going to eliminate copper
we're so high in Copper food is so high
in Copper you eat one avocado you
wouldn't believe the amount of Trace
copper in one avocado there's no zinc in
anything there's no zinc it's gone it's
it's gone and partly because in the old
days when DDT was spread on the planet
in the old days and spread all through
the US and all over the planet and still
is in Parts DDT had a reaction in the
soil it canceled out zinc and DDT is
still in soils all organic farms even
have traces of it without without
because they're not testing for that
they don't even look for that it's it no
one there's not no one's testing for
that it's not but it's everywhere it's
the the world is dusted with it so you
can't you can't worry about you still
got to eat organic produce you ra better
eat organic produce than eating all the
time conventional produce unless it's
your only option um but the whole point
is it's dusted everywhere it's dusted in
all the fields that grass-fed cows are
raised on it still dusted they use it it
blows across continents they're using it
all all in other all in other countries
as if it was if if Z was safe and fine
and D
and what it does it blows everywhere it
lands on all the fields the cows are
grazing it lands on
everything and what does it do it has a
clashing effect it has a critical
interaction effect that nobody knows
about an interaction effect is it
literally destroys zinc so when it rains
and it rains those particles those fine
DDT particles and it rins them and
saturates them into the Earth everywhere
nothing's not free from it it's one of
those diabolical things that occurred on
the planet thank God it's it's at least
controlled here in the US and not
freshly used even though it's new
cousins in the pesticide world the nerv
asde world and funus side world are just
are rampant which are horrific enough
but thank God this isn't being used
fresh even though it's being used fresh
in other continents and blowing over but
it destroys zinc it destroys zinc in our
body it destroys zinc in the Earth and
we have DDT passed from our forefather
from our grandfather and grandmothers
you don't think you don't think that's
possible think again think
again yeah I don't you know look if it
if living in the dark and not knowing
these things makes you feel better and
that's what you have to do then I
respect that one one bit you I mean 100%
I expect it I mean you know I expect it
in a lot of people but I respect it
100% because you know I've I've had
people tell me I don't want to know I
don't want to know I don't know I don't
want to know what's going on out there
really I just want to be safe and just
not really think about it so try not to
tell me too much so I'm up all night
I've had people tell me that I
understand and I and I totally honor
that but the deal is we inherit the DDT
DDT is inside the liver it kills the
zinc Factory in our liver because our
liver resides and needs zinc it
functions on zinc it wants zinc it
manufactures even zinc when it can it
does it all the liver does it all so
what happens is is we have no zinc in
us it's really really really low if
non-existent for a lot of people so
taking a couple of tiny drops every now
and then could be a wonderful thing
protect your lymphatic system from
viruses so you don't end up with a case
of fibromyalgia which is a later stage
Epstein
bar but you know what science of
research thinks fibromyalgia is a case
of overactive nerves you know what the
alternative movement thinks fibromyalgia
is the body attacking
itself you know what geneticists think
fibromyalgia is
genetic God and here we are in this day
and age yep here we are would you
believe it it's
1905 it's 19 actually they knew more
about chronic illness probably in 1905 I
hate to say it they probably did so okay
so the bottom line is we wanted get some
zinc in there you can't worry about
about canceling out copper everything's
high in Copper the soil's high in Copper
oh dear lord everything is we also have
destructive copper like saturated in our
bodies we're high in Copper everybody
with eczema has copper high in Copper
everybody with the neurological
condition any neurological condition
whatsoever is high in Copper anyone with
one neurological symptom tingles and
numbness aches and pains dizziness
vertigo B you know balance problems
maners disease okay um anxiety uh from
crippling to mild depression from
crippling to mild the list goes on
eczema psoriasis skin disorders vitil
Vitiligo anything there's copper
involved all high in Copper all of that
eye problems ear problems um just all
high in Copper all of it sibo gut health
problems high in Copper
um Tremors ticks spasms it's because the
person's high in Copper all of it
anything neurological from adz migraines
trigeminal neuralgia high in Copper okay
whether you get a disease and you forgot
about you know and in the doctor doesn't
even talk about your symptoms they just
want to slap a lime tag on you or they
just want a lime disease tag on you or
they just want to slap an MS tag on you
whatever it is copper high in Copper
meaning it it it means you you still
it's I'm not saying copper is the
problem but you're high in Copper if you
got any of that and you know what you're
low in
zinc you're low in zinc why am I big on
zinc today in this show because the
lymphatic system needs it it needs it to
stay healthy do you need to take a lot
of it no have I taken a lot of it at
times yeah zinc shock therapy okay
that's something that Spirit created was
Zinc shock therapy zinc shock therapy is
incredible saved me on a trip saved me
on a trip years ago it's coming down
with a flu spirit said you're coming
down with a flu you're rundown you
haven't slept you're traveling you're on
planes left and right I spent more time
in the air than I did on the ground I
did on the ground for a little while in
my life oh I spent more time in the air
more time in the air I wasn't eating as
good as I could I didn't have it in
front of me so I was just scrapping for
for for scr was scaming for any anything
healthy I could find was run down no
sleep whatsoever I was also under
tremendous stress not just because
because spirit's talking to me 24/7 to
help others all the time I was under
tremendous amounts of stress I had some
deadlines I had some other things going
on I also was trying to help a couple of
family members I was do I was just
pushed to the Max and exposed way too
much to a lot of
germs I was visiting I was visiting the
hospital visiting some family members I
was I had people coughing on me left and
right I was exposed to everything and
was back up in the air again and what
happened with no sleep in me is coming
down with the flu and spirit said zinc
shock therapy right away and I had a
bottle of zinc on me couldn't believe it
I squirted four or five dropper fs and
because I'm not sensitive to zinc if
you're sensitive to zinc just like
you're sensitive you could be sensitive
to anything you start with a couple of
tiny drops you know just a couple of
honey drops that's all you need I did
four or five dropper Falls Bam Bam Bam
right in the throat I let it sit in the
throat spirit said let it sit in the
throat for 2 minutes I let it sit in the
throat for 2 minutes I had it sitting in
there my lymphatic system was sucking it
up like never before just absorbing it
like sucking it up like just bringing it
right in right into it getting all
through my lymphatic system the whole
bit you better believe it okay I woke up
the next morning it was gone spirit said
you did it you conquered it one shot
with zinc with zinc shock therapy
conquered everybody else around me
they're you know hop on the plank
everybody coffin everything and Bam Zing
shock therapy totally caught it in
time and you know and I had some zinc in
me already cuz you know I took it
randomly that's why I even had it on me
I took it once in a while I had it on me
cuz I knew about S I knew about
lymphatic system I knew about this from
Spirit and I wasn't in fear of it fear
of it eliminating my copper reserves
because there's always plenty of copper
reserves you eat one avocado you're just
building back your copper reserves in
one shot that's how much copper is in
avocado I mean it's good for you you eat
avocados it's good for you but that
that's how much is in there so all this
is important to know so let's just run
by some foods for the lymphatic system
help the liver too and the liver gets so
clogged up and it's so loaded with
poison and toxins so much debris and
it's saturated inside the liver and the
liver is just puffing it out back into
the bloodstream because it has no other
no other way of handling it it's so
overloaded stagnant sluggish livers high
fat diets no oxygen inside the blood
because you're on a trendy high-fat diet
or a standard American high-fat diet
you're on Either Ore you know and and
you're not eating enough fruits and
vegetables people should people should
switch
gears they should switch gears sometimes
to really help themselves bring in more
fruits and vegetables so what can we do
for the lymphatic system fruit is one of
the greatest weapons for the lymphatic
system I'll say it again I said it
before apples are incredible pears are
great peaches nectarines plums cherries
are really incredible for the lymphatic
system they're great melons watermelon
regular melon honeydew melon um you name
it those are all those are all great for
the lymphatic system okay so you know
that that alone green juice celery juice
is by far probably the greatest weapon
for the lymphatic system because the the
the Undiscovered cluster salts that
nobody knows about the the highly
mineralized cluster salts that are
undiscovered in the sense that they're
not studied no one's seen it no one
knows what's going on no one knows how
they work they strip off viruses the
cell membranes and destroy viruses they
kill the Epstein bar virus celery juice
people wonder why they're getting better
when they're drinking all their celery
juice thousands thousands and thousands
of people actually at this point
millions of people because of medical
medium meaning spirit and I of getting
the information about celery juice it's
it's it's unbelievable what's happening
the stores don't even have celery
anymore that's what's going on out there
and people are getting better and
they're wondering why their fibromyalgia
is getting better when they drink celery
juice because the celery juice is
stripping off the Epstein bar membrane
it's stripping off other viruses it's
knocking down
everything and not even just that too
bacteria like strap a cacus for for sibo
and all kinds of other things and H
pylori for Digestive problems and you
it's curing ulcers healing people it's
celery juice and what does it do it
heals the lymphatic system it's
incredible one the mineral salts bind on
the poisons in the liver and the
lymphatic system push it out they help
get rid of ly lymphadema you name it
it's amazing what celery juice can do
cucumber juice is another great one too
I like the heavy metal detox smoothie
it's incredible because it takes out
heavy metals and other poison out of the
liver it helps it gives you lots of
antioxidants wild blueberries wild
blueberries incredible for lymphatic
problems chaga mushroom I love the
vimergy chaga mushroom the vimergy
barleygrass juice powder I I use those
every day for my lymphatic system my
liver and I just you know I I take that
stuff every day Hawaiian spirulina
that's in the heavy metal detox smoothie
that's a great one right there all in
its own I like dandelion you know was in
the store and it's rare I'm in the store
it's rare I'm in theore store I mean you
guys probably know why because because
number one I'll be doing readings in the
aisle um people are going to be coming
up to me and being like you're Anthony
and I'll be like it happened the other
day it was like yeah I was in you know
the most popular uh the health food
stores you know the you know this health
food store that that's all over the
place those health food stores the
different chains and I was in there and
I like hey Anthony is this good for me
and that can you tell me what's wrong
with me can you do a read on me and so
next thing you know I'm sitting there
and I'm doing a read I'm like yeah all
right Spirit what's going on with this
person and I'm doing a read on this
person and another person comes over I'm
doing a read another person comes over
I'm during a read and all I was doing
was trying to get Dand lion greens and
you know what's hilarious know what
happened to me was I did four or five
readings right there in the produce
department aisle and spirit was telling
each person what they needed to eat out
of the pro protu section and guess what
I forgot my dandelion greens the whole
reason why I went there I end up just
walking dizzy and half blind out of
there because of I'm around too many
people I get the snow blind from doing
the readings but I want to be a human
being once in a while and I want to be
able to get out and I want to be able to
do things once in a while in a blue moon
I mean I got that right
right so but I ended up just like uh
blah blah blah just doing readings and
then after the reading Spirit was still
giving me information on people that
were just walking by me and it was a
little too much where I was like okay
and I grabbed I hurried up and I just
threw some apples in a bag and you know
I threw some celery in a bag and and
next thing you know what I left and as
I'm in the car spirit said where's your
dandelion greens I said thanks for
telling me
now I said you why didn't you remind me
in the store and spirit like Spirit was
like well and I go yeah because you were
doing readings over and over again so
you know so I I you I had to go back in
and get the Dany lion greens Dany lion
greens are amazing k o okay for
lymphatic system and liver I like it I
like kale don't be afraid of kale don't
think it's bad for your thyroid it's
actually incredible for your thyroid do
not be afraid some herbs like yellow
dock pick up some yellow dock don't you
know brew a ton of it that stuff is
bitter as heck just a little bit you can
do dandelion root tea yellow dock tea
make a little yellow dock tea a little
dandelion root to actually squeeze and
Purge your lymphatic system nettle Leaf
is great lemon balm is great too but for
the lymphatic system them too and and
the liver do a little Danny line little
yellow dock someone said to me oh hey
that information's out there we already
know is herbalist that you need Danny
line root for your liver duh and I said
did you know it 39 years ago when I was
a kid telling somebody that and there
wasn't anything around you couldn't find
an herbalist of your life dependent on
it never mind a store or or a internet
which didn't exist and they're like oh
sorry yeah sorry and I got proof I've
been recommending it since that age you
better believe it got people that know
about it I know about my family knows I
recommended it for my family when I was
7 years old yellow Dock and Danny line
root that's what you need and you you
know you use that too as teas that's a
great one nettle Leaf like I said
peppermint tea is a you know never
underestimate spearmint and peppermint
tea for your lymphatic system I love it
it's incredible olive leaf I love that
one for pathogens in the lymphatic
system it helps get the pathogens out of
the lymphatic system I love that one um
spinach secret weapon ma okay MH or mhe
I love that that's great for lymphatic
systems different lettu uses you can use
different lettu uses don't be afraid of
them you know I like butterleaf lettuce
the red leaf lettuce is great for
lymphatic systems specifically so if
you're thinking about you got some kind
of like your concerned about your
lymphatic system go in there and get
some red leaf lettuce and let do a salad
to made tomes incredible for your
lymphatic system I can't tell you enough
if you're afraid of tomato it it's it's
sad if you like a tomato and you're
afraid of it that's sad it is it's
probably due to trendy information like
Nightshade information that's wrong out
there misinformation I call it make sure
you get tomatoes for the liver Tomatoes
really help heal the liver they heal the
liver they heal the lymphatic system
when your lymphatic system is purging
and it's cleaning and getting less toxic
your can actually Purge and clean and
get free too it can lead you to less
illness and even help you hurry out of
chronic illness in so many ways that's
why the lymphatic system is so important
you guys like for really for real you
need to focus on that too sometimes
let's see what other herbs are really
good to lymphatic system I like Elder
flow tea it's an oddball it's a weird
one but let me tell you something it is
good hiss up you can get hiss up and
make you know you can get the hiss up
herb make a little hup tea that's not so
bad I like ginger and turmeric shots
that's a great one look if this is all
too much stuff all of it just try a
little bit of dandelion root tea it's
bitter it's harsh but try it berock root
I love go into the go into the produce
store and get berock root fresh berock
root and juice it run run one one trunk
of berock root one root of berock root
juice it and add it to a cucumber juice
or a celery juice you can try that I
always want you to do celery juice alone
make this another juice at a different
time of day but get a berock root juice
somehow in there do apple and berock
root actually apple and berock root
would be amazing for the liver and
lymphatic system apple and berock root
that juice so berock Roots incredible
for the liver but it's more incredible
for the lymphatic system that is really
where it's going to really help it's
amazing radishes listen if you're not a
radish person try to get into them
purple radishes red radishes when I see
purple radishes in the store I like Hub
two I hop too not because I'm trying to
run out of there as fast as I can so I
don't end up getting asked for reads or
anything getting asked for readings but
I hop too because I get so excited I'm
like oh my God oh my God and and I run
in there you know and it's it's pretty
funny it's pretty funny and so radishes
purple radishes red radishes you know
those are really good D donon radishes
those are incredible for the lymphatic
system they help Purge and push out
poisons out of the lymphatic system
really help you get going and to move
sickness and illness from you know out
of you and plus radishes read my
life-changing Foods book and read what
radishes do it's unbelievable what they
do what Spirit knows they do it's
incredible so that's another great one
and um and you can get a lot of you know
red bell pepper red ripe bell pepper I
love that one for the lymphatic system
and then if if you like cayenne pepper
or a little bit of hot pepper flakes you
know hey I like the cayenne pepper I do
I put it on things I like the cayanne
pepper you know if you're sensitive to
that and you don't like the heat don't
use it don't worry but a little bit if
you like it won't hurt at all like I
said the G Ginger turmeric shots or
ginger tea every day incredible for the
lymphatic system that's another option
and the list goes on for the lymphatic
system you can't go wrong I like melons
in the morning first thing
so here's what I do I'll do a melon in
the morning I'll do my celery juice a
little bit later on that's that's what I
do try not to eat a lot of melon first
thing in the morning because you know
you're just going to get filled up
you're going to have you're just going
to be filled up I mean I've eaten a
whole melon in the morning or two whole
melons in the morning you know and if
you got someplace to go you're going to
be peeing everywhere so you know just
because it's going to be cleansing you
but I like some melon or I'll do celery
juice first thing after lemon water so
let me just you let me back up I I like
doing my lemon water then I like doing
my celery juice and another thing then I
do the the melons too you can do it that
way depending on where you're going
lately I did I've been doing the melons
first thing but I know that my
schedule's changing so I'm doing them
later and so get the melons because the
melons really help also with the
lymphatic system don't be afraid of
those papaya that's a secret weapon
against the lymphatic system too helps
clean it up notice how I'm not saying
chicken fish um animal meat pork and
turkey
does nothing for the lymphatic system
I'm not saying you have to stop it I'm
saying if you're concerned about your
liver concerned about your lymphatic
system try to go on the 28 day cleanse
out of book one or the 90-day cleanse
out of thyroid healing or try to just
limit your M you know lower your animal
proteins a little bit so you can clear
out your lymphatic system and liver
because all the high fat from the
chicken and high fat from the chicken
breast the white chicken breast the all
high fat from the white pork the white
pork meat whatever the white meat the
pork all that fat from the turkey all
that fat from the grass-fed beef even
the lanest cuts of beef all that fat
burdens down the lymphatic system and
the liers take it and if you're vegan or
plant-based lower than nuts too many
nuts and seeds too many nut Butters and
too much coconut oil is going to get in
the way of the lymphatic system a little
bit is fine just lower that down a
little bit and bring up all the fruits
and bring up the vegetables bring up the
things I just said bring in the berock
rout te you name it we're running out of
time you guys are the greatest I have to
say and this is this was a fun show
rebounding could be really good for the
lymphatic system pulls and draws a lot
of poisons out of there but you got to
be hydrated you got to be hydrated so
that's what all this is about that's
what you know the the that's what all
the celery juice everything else and add
some water lemon water squeeze lemon
water every morning you know that really
helps hydration is really important so
the rebounding the rebounder that's
amazing jump up and down on it an
infrared sauna that's even a good thing
too it's really helpful for for the
lymphatic system so these are some other
things I stand behind you 100% And I
love you guys dearly one day at a time
God bless you thanks for being here I
can't thank you enough for just working
on your process your healing process bye
now take care bless your
heart