right there
greatest books of all time be the judge
yourself
because when you open these books up you
guys are going to be blown away so much
comprehensive detailed information that
you have to kind of like take a moment
and digest what you're receiving with
these books absolutely incredible so I
just want to thank you guys I'm really
excited I can't even believe it I can't
believe it I can't believe it the brain
saver books are here you guys
I'm gonna have to do the robot on this
brain say Sir here bring saber books are
here bring saver brand saber brain say
everybody's ever you guys I'm serious
okay let's just get into it let's get
into it by the way I just have to tell
you right now
brain saver challenge is gonna be at
noon eastern time today
nine o'clock Pacific
and you're only going to be able to view
that challenge and for 24 hours it's a
four day challenge did you find the link
or you like signed up to it and it's
free but but you can only see it for 24
hours all right
each video is up for 24 hours there's
four of them they're gonna be four of
them this brain saver challenge is
coming up wait till you see that because
I'm digging into the books all right
look
I don't even know where to start with
these because they're packed they're
loaded and what I mean the greatest
Health books of all time and cleanse to
heal has saved so many lives already
right
live a rescue has saved so many lives
medical medium book One new addition
saved so many lives already we already
know that but this is what
this is what's needed right now so let's
just go into it a little bit your pain
and suffering enlightened take a look at
that for a second your pain and
suffering enlightened right
just incredible information so what does
that mean
everyday brain and health maintenance
aches and pains addiction Addison's
disease ADHD age spots alcohol
withdrawal ALS Alzheimer's Amnesia
anemia aneurysms Ankylosing Spondylitis
anorexia anxiety anxiousness it goes on
and on I'm just scratching the surface
here okay phasia apraxia arrhythmia
arterial sclerosis arthritis atheroma
like it goes and goes and goes afib
auditory processing disorder autism
autoimmune disorders and diseases is it
avoidant restrictive food intake
disorder
Ayahuasca recovery
Ayahuasca recovery is in here so many
people are desperate for recovery from
that I'm not put Jade on anything I'm
just saying it's for the people that
that need it desperately if you're where
you are and you're happy and fine but
it's for the people that are now
screaming I need recovery from from it
anyway
so I'm just listening to the people all
right balance issues Bell's Palsy binge
eating disorders bipolar disorder
bloating blood clots blood draw problems
blurred vision body buzzing and humming
body euphoric you know brain abscesses
brain aging brain cancer brain fog brain
inflammation brain lesions you guys I
can't even scratch the surface to the
brain saver books this is brain saver
protocols which is incredible absolutely
insane
so if you're not hooked on to these yet
take a look and go to Amazon right to
Amazon or wherever you book stores or
whatever and just you know take a look
when you can right
so I'm just touching this breast implant
illness bulimia burning hot fueling with
no fever Burning Sensations in the mouth
Burning Sensations on the skin burnout
bursitis buzzing and ears caffeine
withdrawal calcifications in the brain
which so many people have by the way
canker sores carpal tunnel syndrome
Castleman disease celiac disease
cerebral atrophy cerebral hypoxia I'm
I'm just saying like that's how excited
I am that answers
are going to be getting to people
which is unbelievable brain shot therapy
cleanses in here the new brain shot
there'll be the medical medium tool
brain shot when you try the brain shots
you're just gonna be like what was that
what was that
my God I don't even know what to say I'm
just so excited about this right
so I'll just read a little bit more
about just some of the stuff in this
book chemical and food sensitivities
chest tightness chewing difficulties
chocolate and cacao withdrawal
no just saying you don't need people
that need that that are like desperate
for them because they go and they just
grow they eat the chocolate down again
and they know they shouldn't the other
another bar they're at the they're at
the grocery store they buy two more
chocolate bars and they need this
withdrawal chronic anger disorder
chronic fatigue immune dysfunction
chronic inflammatory female I mean you
name it now I know I'm just like I'm
stumbling over my words right now
because I'm so excited and I'm going
probably too quick
but I want you guys to know this is just
an epic moment in our history and I can
see that because I can have an opinion
because remember this came from above
it's all original unique it came from
above you guys know that if you know
medical medium information and I can
judge it myself
I have the right to judge it myself and
by far greatest information of all time
on the brain that will ever hit the
scene and for years to come and I'm
excited so let's talk a little bit more
about it right here chronic mystery
guilt coffee withdrawal cold flu and sea
cold hands and feet cold sensitivity see
you guys know what c means right like C
because you can't say that word on here
and then everything just gets crazy cold
sensitivity cold Source concussion
recovery side effects connective tissue
diseases that people have cranial nerve
atrophy
cranial nerve inflammation Crohn's
disease crooked jaw feeling
I mean who has that in any books
I mean I'm just asking myself that
question who has crooked jaw feeling
in any medical like any health book just
eat better books out there but they
don't talk about any of that Cushing's
disease
cystic fibrosis dark spots on the brain
how many people get MRIs they've got
this mystery dark spot in the brain dark
tongue discoloration right you guys if
you just got on here I'm talking about
the brain saver books
that are out this week lock onto one
when you can I'm reading just a little
bit like I I could sit here probably for
24 straight hours and not even scratch
the surface of just a section of this
book these books both these books
because it was one big one it had to be
cut in half
you guys know the story some of you
dementia depersonalization depression
let's keep on going okay dermatitis
devic's disease difficulty coping
that is incredible all in its own
dizziness drooping face dysautonomia
dyslexia dysphagia dysphoria Eating
Disorders
comprehensive detailed chapter on eating
disorders with mind-blowing Advanced
information about eating disorders that
will just blow your mind when you crack
into that chapter so I just want to tell
you right there a little bit ectopic
heartbeat ehlers-danlos syndrome
electric shock to the head feeling the
one thing about the brain saver books
they're so detailed so comprehensive and
they have so many symptoms and
conditions that their hat
chronically ill have to be just like it
has to be justified what they're going
through and the symptoms and the
understanding it's good to see you guys
I see you guys on Instagram with your
comments right now you have butterflies
um you know and
all of this matters when it comes down
to it these symptoms matter right and
electric shock to the head feeling so
many people have the electric shocks to
the head feeling that's a symptom that
the medical establishment's not even
talking about it's like what there's so
many people dealing with it right
Encephalitis encephalopathy energy
issues epilepsy
chapter in here an epilepsy okay and
seizures that is something that's really
important Epstein-Barr virus right
Epstein-Barr virus reactivated late
stage early stage and reactivated
I mean how cool excessive sweating
extreme fatigue
right
so and there's an OCD chapter that's
mined blowing in the brain saver books
an OCD chapter a bipolar chapter
Alzheimer's chapter even if you don't
have Alzheimer's and you're not worried
you want to read the chapter because it
blows your mind because you'll know the
cause of Alzheimer's in detail in detail
and um you got to check it out right
there's a section about epilepsy in here
that's the whole key excessive sweating
extreme fatigue eyeball unusual
movements so many people with
neurological problems have eyeball
problems so their eyeballs are moving in
different directions they're having a
difficult time with that right
so eye floaters I focused issues Facial
Pain fainting fatigue fever blisters
fibromyalgia flu fluttering in the ears
so many people get the fluttering focus
and concentration issues food poisoning
food sensitive I don't even know what to
say I'm not even scratching into the
symptoms and conditions but
what you'll like what you'll learn with
the brain saver books hands down
you will not find any of this anywhere
else
now 10 years from now 20 years from now
50 years from now unless it's poached
from here just like other stuff is
poached from the mm books right but
you're not going to find this
information about the brain the most
comprehensive brain information
ever
to hit the scene
and I'm just letting you know right now
it's really an exciting time so
you got the brain saver protocols book
right here Jim's pack you got the brain
saver book right here so I want to show
you guys and this is really a special
time in history when you feel the book
they're alive
there's a difference there's books that
are dead they're dead books dead
material dead words and then there's
books that are alive and you can feel
the energy you can feel the life to them
and you can feel that they're living
words and when you start reading about
the soul in these books and when you
start re there's even meditations in
these books that are just mind-blowing
right when you start reading and getting
into it you feel you can feel the energy
you can feel the living words and you
know when your heart as you're reading
this Advanced information from above
that this is life in here these are
alive not dead words on a page and not
dead books
so food sensitivities food poisoning
forgetfulness frozen shoulder gas pains
gastric spasms gastritis
gastroparesis mild
gastroparesis sphere
green tea matcha tea and black tea
withdrawal people are crying for that so
I want to make sure it's here for them
Guillain Beret gum pain gum pains and
spasms how many people have gum pain
they can't even get an answer for it
headaches hearing loss
I mean I could be here all day going
through this book but just let me let me
just let me go to uh medical medium
brain shot therapy which is an
incredible
resource
at everyone's fingertips pretty soon
once you hold the book in your hand the
brain shot therapy
I mean
if I was sick if I was sick and I knew
this existed
I would just be like
jumping on it jumping on it so brain
shot therapy is is in a whole thing on
its own there's a brain shot therapy
cleanse it's a new medical medium tool
powerful the brain shots you make them
yourself right with the ingredients that
are actually organized in this book from
above and they're for
quick acting relief but they hit you
right away and when they hit you you
just you feel it rush through your body
the brain shot therapies and it's just
and there's a brain shot there there's
seven brain shot therapy cleanses
there's seven heavy metal detox cleanses
which I'm going to go into in a little
bit too as well so I'm just going
through here these are the brain shots
right here brain shot shots are shifters
stabilizers okay so you got shifters you
got stabilizers
and you got exposures
so you have 10
brain shots for specific exposures
you've got 10 Brain shots
for stabilizers and you got 10 Brain
shots
for shifters so you have 30 all together
and then you got the brain shot therapy
cleanses out of those 30 brain shots and
when you Embark into this and you
customize it the way you want it through
the book and what it offers and you can
do those brain shots to shift and
stabilize so to stabilize the brain to
shift the brain it's a big deal
make sure you sign up to the brain saver
challenge
it's coming up it's coming up in a few
minutes okay and you'll see me make some
of the brain shots
it's going to be exciting so when you
sign up to the brain shot sorry the
brain saver challenge coming up
I'm going to be making some of the brain
shots on that challenge challenges four
day challenge four videos
it's for free sign up to it but you only
got 24 hours to watch them the link is
in the description and the link is in
the profile
I'm happy for you guys because when you
guys just use some of this stuff
you know the the amount of work that's
gone into this is a matter of sacrifice
that I've had
you know what's worth it what's worth it
is is connecting to you guys knowing
like getting ready for bed and I try to
rest and I'm like okay all right I'm
excited about everything excited about
everybody getting that information
having that like what's gonna happen I
ask myself when someone actually
experience experiences the stabilizers
experience is the shifters
I'm like it's going to be an entirely
entirely incredible awesome experience
it really is so I see you guys
commenting on you guys commenting on
Tick Tock I see you guys commenting on
Instagram I'm just trying to get the
information out as fast as I can I want
to answer some questions and we'll do a
lot of that in the future by the way but
I see you guys I see your I see your
some of your questions and I see some of
your comments I just want you to know
and over there too on Facebook on
YouTube I see your comments as well and
I really I'm honored you guys are here
truly am and are you guys where can we
sign up link is in this uh description
okay for the brain saver challenge don't
miss it why miss it it's four days it's
free sign up for it make sure you're
there okay and it's just incredible
um okay so brain shot therapy I'm in it
now and you've got the brain shot
therapy cleanse you got the exposure
shots
right I'm just guys just bear with me
there's so much information in here
and
another thing too I'm actually doing a
light infusion meditation on the fourth
day of the brain saver challenge
so I'm actually going to do with you
guys a light infusion meditation on the
fourth day of the brain saver challenge
today is the first day of the brain
saver challenge don't miss out sign up
it's free
it's gonna be incredible
I'm just going through some of the shots
that's a pathogen exposure shot right
there so a pathogen exposure shot that's
what happens like when people they get
into a new relationship and they might
have been just exposed or they they're
they're in a public place public
bathroom and they think they got exposed
right and you know the pathogen exposure
shot or you're around somebody with the
flu or
the flu or right you're around somebody
with either or and then that's a
pathogen okay here's one right here
there's a toxic fragrances shot
for people that it just got totally
bombarded with air fresheners perfumes
colognes fragrances perfumes all that
stuff chemicals in the grocery stores
cleaning chemicals anything like that
right
toxic fragrance exposure shot negative
energy exposure shot you're around
somebody and they've totally bummed you
out totally stressed you out brought you
down
I totally beat you down
and you go and you do this shot and boom
right
okay
mold exposure shot
so you got a mold exposure shot right
there
that's that's an incredible one all on
its own you guys if I was just I mean
okay
here's what's crazy about the brain
saver books
if there wasn't two books here packed
with volumes of information and all it
was was just one page in the brain saver
book and it was mold exposure shot it
would still be worth it
still be worth it
that's like that's how
incredibly packed and detailed the
information is in here you just signed
up amazing amazing when you guys try
these brain shot therapies there's
nothing like them and you will have an
experience of a lifetime
of a lifetime where do you get the books
go to Amazon that's a place to get it
right there go to Amazon if you're
overseas Book Depository there's other
places too bookstores barns whatever
link is in the description
if nothing else and all you did was the
mold exposure shot it would be worth it
yo
EMF and 5G exposure shot
I forgot that was even in there because
there's so much information in these
books
EMF
and 5G exposure shots
I wait till you try it
I I don't even know what to say I don't
even know what to say
oh traveling much anybody traveling much
right
radiation exposure shot
and when you try it you will be blown
away traveling much you soaking up all
that radiation but I talk in detail
about radiation and EMF in these books
too
you're getting Medical Imaging you guys
getting every anybody ever getting
Medical Imaging at all for CAT scans
MRIs whatever radiation exposed shot and
I was the first to say years ago 20
years ago that MRIs created radiation
and everybody said no MRIs don't I mean
it's magnetic Imaging is actually wrong
wrong wrong it creates radiation
they get radiation for memorize that's
the first to say that finally the info
got out took a long time and I had I had
a beat down from it lots of beat downs
but it does remember the early
information about the stuff and the
truth
and memory or you know Origins
incredible radiation exposure shot
traveling boom
and so so much toxic heavy metal
exposure shot if you think you got fresh
exposure to metal it's like fresh
you got the shot right there okay let's
keep on going it's endless
anybody spraying your Lawns you got a
neighbor spraying
apartment building being sprayed
anything being sprayed with pesticides
lawn chemicals fertilizers
pesticide herbicide and fungicide
exposure shot did you try on new clothes
have you tried on new clothes right new
clothes loaded with fungicides and air
fresheners that's what's happening now
when we buy new clothes you you
literally they come saturated in
chemicals and nanotechnology there's a
pesticide herbicide and fungicide
exposure shot in this book
it's just it's my numbing actually
right your neighbor spray I saw that
foreign
pharmaceutical exposure shot
interesting
sea Trails exposure shot
actual sea Trails exposure shot
looking up in the sky anybody
anybody looking up the sky
right
a shot is an actual drink
it's a drink
shifter shots let's head into some
shifter shots
obsessive thoughts who's ever had a
struggle with obsessive thoughts right
how many people have struggled with the
whole obsessive thought thing
boom obsessive thoughts shifter do you
know many people wish they pray to God
that there's an answer to break and
obsessive Obsession obsessive thoughts
like they're sitting there they're
laying on their mattress and they're
literally suffering because they can't
break the stream of thoughts it's
literally torturing them
obsessive thoughts shifter
I'll tell you right now if you threw
everything away you threw everything
away in these books through the whole
all the books away just that alone is
worth
just everything to someone
these are real for fast instant relief
while you work on the deeper causes and
that's the whole point the books are
packed with information to work on the
deeper causes to understand the deeper
causes but you've got instant relief
that's what's incredible mood shifter
Brett winter says these shots would be
on the aw Bar and Grill menu coming
right up
what would you like what would you like
ma'am
ma'am did you did you and your husband
have a good night's sleep here at aw Bar
and Grill upstairs in our hotel and our
incredible Suites
nerve shifter
Mr Ferguson's not feeling well today
what's going on he was on the toilet why
okay
nerve shifter
all right I gotta stop fooling around
you guys this is an epic this is an epic
moment energy shifter nerve shifter food
fear shifter Danny Jones says how do you
reprogram subconscious mind with a drink
oh my God wait till you try it because
so much of our thoughts are from our
physical brain
physical brain having needs our physical
brain having problems and so much of it
is that so yes you can shift it and
that's what's incredible
be the judge try it
craving shifter how many of you guys are
Cravings going through Cravings Cravings
anybody you're craving things can't
break the Cravings holidays are coming
by the way a great holiday gifts is the
brain saver books both the brain saver
books incredible for a holiday gift
but how many people during the holidays
are going to have the cravings
I can't tell you how many friends and
maybe like break out the craving shifter
break out the craving shifter boom knock
those Cravings back so you're not eating
you know 10 times the turkey stuffing
and the butter
10 times all the fried food and
everything else whatever you're gonna be
the Cravings people are stuck within the
holidays Cookies Cakes Donuts all of
that
right
pharmaceutical exposure shot I was
trying to tell you guys gotta read
between the lines anger shifter
right Lisa says do I need a g-stroke
check out check out the uh the
mm-900 mm 1500.
you want a juicer that saves money
anyway anger shifter right there
on sale
guilt and shame shifter
I mean seriously yeah if you're going to
be running out to get a juicer get you
know you guys know I work with Omega the
best juicers the mm-900 the mm-1500
they're on sale right now so if you're
going to go out and get a juicer get one
that actually is going to save you money
because the cost of food are up so you
want to squeeze the juice out of
everything so that you actually start
paying for the juice so like it pays for
itself people are actually saving money
because of that I know I have guilt and
shame shifter right there
Cold Light spring says I can't believe
you put out this uh Anthony
ego shifter you deal with anybody with
an ego right big ego got some big egos
out there right
right
if I feel my ego's getting out of
control I break out the ego shifter
everybody's got their ego going
everybody has an ego right if they you
know somebody you know the ego is just
totally out of control just get them the
ego shifter and guess what when you
knock back the ego shifter
yeah you feel it you feel it
I was getting too big for my britches
the other day because I was so proud of
these books so proud of everything so
proud of how many people are going to
heal around the world Spirit of
compassion says you need an ego shifter
right now I broke that baby out I took
it down it humbled me right down
right down
all right
okay
this next one
just get ready for this
you guys into your dreams are you into
dreams you getting nightmares you're
getting good dreams you want good dreams
you want to get rid of bad dreams you're
not dreaming at all dreams mean
something to you are you thinking Dreams
Are Spiritual whatever it is that's
going on whatever you believe in with
your dreams
make sure you try the dream shifter
before you go to bed
knock down the dream shifter
and you watch what happens in your sleep
and you watch what happens in your
dreams how do I know this because a I
tried it
when you actually knocked out the dream
shifter before you go to bed I'm just
saying right now look out
see
these are not big glasses of concoctions
or shots the reason why it's called
shots is because they're this big
they're shots this is the medical medium
tool the brain shot therapy and the
brain shot therapy cleanse when you
actually take this in and use it look
out these are the brain saver books
that's brain saver protocols that's
brain saver you guys it's two books go
to Amazon go to the bookstores whatever
all right
we're not done I I can't scratch what's
in this these two books I'm only just
talking about a little stuff
get ready for this
stabilizer shots
now what I love about the stabilizer
shots
and I'm going to be making one for you
guys during the brain saver challenge
coming right up sign up for the brain
saver challenge
it's four videos
it's got 24 hours to watch it
I'm doing one today
sign up links in the profile links in
the description right but here's the
stabilizer shots right here
nerve gut acid stabilizer so many people
have nerve gut acid problems they don't
even know it because research research
in science and even some functional
medicine doctors don't understand that
like the difference between the nerves
and the gut and the acids and how they
all work together
just try the nerve gut acid stabilizer
of course ask your doctor what's right
for you
grab the books take them to your doctor
and ask them what's right for you
okay
this one's dear to me right here because
I know what it's going to do for people
this one is trauma shock and loss
stabilizer
so so incredible
so incredibly exciting adrenal fight are
flight stabilizer that's a big one right
now
right
first of all the amount of cost that
goes into these books
they're huge books
it costs double to just print these
things this is like a love kind of thing
you just want to do it no matter what
these are two massive books right here
both of these are two massive books
okay
it's not a pamphlet
people are going out there spending
hundreds of thousands dollars on medical
help
thousands on alternative medicine over
the years and thousands on courses do
you know I can break up these books I
didn't even have to put these books out
you guys I could have broken them up and
charged for courses
I could have charged two thousand
dollars of course three thousand dollars
a course did you know the brain saver
challenge coming up today is free that
brain saver challenge should be priced
out is that's what everybody says to me
Anthony aw medical Medium you're just a
dumb ass because you're supposed to
price that stuff out if people want to
join the brain saver challenge let them
pay a thousand dollars a piece
and stop giving everything away
so when someone says
your book is forty dollars or your book
is whatever or thirty nine dollars or
whatever your book is you know 45 and
I'm like are you kidding me people spend
thousands upon thousands in alternative
medicine
they're buying gadgets they're buying
courses they're buying thousands in
courses are you kidding me
the answers are in these books I'm
giving it away
no
there's something out there called like
when people pay for stuff they actually
appreciate it right so when you give it
all for free they treat you like crap
and they don't appreciate it but I don't
believe the medical meaning Community
does that I believe the medical medium
Community doesn't take the information
and SOC and aw and medical mean for
granted I believe the medical medium
Community doesn't take the information
for granted they're smart enough to know
about the three thousand five thousand
dollar course courses they're smart
enough to know about the cost of being
sick and everything out there
and they're smart enough to know that it
costs to ship and print paper this big
and a book this large and beautiful
color paper the medical medium Community
is smart enough
they're smart enough to know that it's
for free and it shouldn't be on
it's for free it shouldn't be taken for
granted all this stuff and if something
costs a little bit to get a book that's
life-saving that sits on your shelf for
the next 30 Years
then the mm Community understands that
so when someone says well I don't want
to pay for that it's like what okay go
go then and go do if I was a fly on the
wall and saw what you paid for all the
courses you paid for that severe
compassion's telling me and all the
stuff you pay for out there and all the
things you buy and all the things that
you went through and here you've got the
answers right here
burnout stable Edge here's something
that's happening to people right now
around the world they're burnt out their
brain is burnt out
and you got the burnout stabilizer
medical mean books worth every pay thank
you Pearl worth any every penny betrayal
and broken here's one right here that's
dear to my heart right here I've been
betrayed have you guys been betrayed
before in your life have you been
stabbed in the back have you been
like let down has someone broke your
trust I'm just being honest I can't
pretend it didn't happen because then
that's insulting to the person oh don't
worry about it you aren't really
betrayed it's all in your head don't
worry you were just your trust wasn't
broken you're just too sensitive but
don't worry you weren't let down you're
just like you're just a wuss you're just
you know don't worry
no people were let down they're betrayed
broken broken up relationships all kinds
of stuff and this is the Betrayal and
broken trust stabilizer right here
if I had to print these books myself
okay
if I had a print and I didn't have the
publisher to help me get these books out
there in the world I mean it would just
be it would be impossible
it just
it would just be impossible
it's just these are just incredible
relationship breakup stabilizer here's
the thing if you had a breakup or
relationship breakup or something like
that years ago in your life like at one
time in your life
there's still those wounds that get
harbored down deep inside even when you
think they're not and you think you move
past this those wounds are still down in
there when it was a really bad breakup
when there was really a problem when
there was really a bad situation with
all of that
it still kind of sticks to us for life
right when we had a bad breakup a
divorce a breakup or or some time type
of problem with the relationship what
happens is that it sticks with us or if
we had one recently the relationship and
breakup stabilizer is incredible
right there
sleeping recharging stabilizer
speaking your truth stabilizer that's
powerful finding your purpose stabilizer
right there
finding your purpose stabilizer
that's an incredible 10. you guys
brain saver medical meme brain saver
challenge it's coming up
tap it in did you sign up for it
sign up for it so you can watch it it's
free
it's four days today's the first day
right here
it's really exciting
I'm just talking about the brain shot
therapy I'm not talking about the seven
heavy metal detox cleanses I'm not
talking about the comprehensive
metal information and how it works
inside the brain I'm not talking about
so many things that are in the books
both of them hoodie meditations
they're packed you guys
and back to symptoms and conditions loan
says you said at one point that it is
sad that after a few Generations
everything is forgotten
yeah it's so true
it's so true
and right now we're in these like
five-year Generations Now history has
Rewritten constantly
constantly medical medium put out the
original information on so many things
about Epstein-Barr and other stuff and
then they're just trying to rewrite
history now
the medical clinics never knew anything
about Epstein-Barr but now they're
actually rewriting things as if they did
and they're even back dating things
it's incredible how Sinister the world
really is
and yes things get forgotten and they
get forgotten even in like a five-year
clip
three-year clip and then there's all
these new people you know and boom
there's these new people trying to sell
all this gimmicky stuff and it's like
they just started eating better and
and everybody forgets like where were
they five years ago it's just crazy how
it works yeah I know it's not making
total sense because you have there's so
much to talk about with that but believe
me there's so much
so I mean just symptoms and conditions
right here
and it's endless humidity sensitivity
right and I talk about all this what I'm
talking about inside the book heat
sensitivity
hunting hens disease
hyperpigmentation how many people are
dealing with hyperpigmentation impulse
control issues inflammatory myopathy and
influenza inner ear disease insomnia it
keeps on going
there's so much here muscle weakness
muscle spasms when you go in here
there's over 300 symptoms conditions
and I explain in detail so many of them
Casey says which book will have info on
cyclic vomiting syndrome for children
pick up pick up both books is what I
recommend for everybody because they're
both they were one book one giant book
and I we couldn't publish it we could
it was one giant book it was impossible
for the printer to print it out
and it couldn't be published
had to break them into two
massive books
how to break them into two so just so
you know
getting both books is is really critical
sure you can start with one and then
eventually get the other if you'd like
but I recommend getting them both
because they were one huge big book
and it's just how it rolled when you're
trying to help heal people with chronic
illness
and you're trying to understand
what they're going through
and you're trying to do them Justice you
can't make pamphlets eat better books
that are just so many pages
and they're basically just eat better
books that are pamphlets and then start
up a podcast and now you're an eat
better doctor you can't on a podcast you
can't insult the chronically ill
and then bring on guests that
don't know what they're talking about
about chronic illness it's like you have
to treat The Chronic allele with the
utmost critical respect possible and you
have to understand what they've gone
through and you have to make sure you
have answers for them
and so I couldn't make a brain saver
pamphlet brain saver small book I had to
make sure that we're talking about the
brain comprehensive detail information
and answers have to be there
so both the books are critical I'm
giving you guys just to run down right
now
all the details are in both these brain
saver books
listen to the telegram message when you
guys get a chance so I did a telegram
message two days ago
if you can please go and listen to that
telegram message I was reading out of
the brain saver book a little bit in the
telegram message if you can get a chance
go check it out also sign up for the
brain saver challenge four days of it
it's free
and I still refuse at this moment even
to not have big promotional companies
hire big marketing companies
hire big PR companies charge every
everybody everybody make a paywall for
everybody on my website you guys
millions of people hit my website
millions of people hit medicalmedium.com
and I don't have a paywall
in the website
there's no paywall in the medicalme.com
website
I get ostracized for not running
advertisements in front of my podcast
and I get ostracized and beaten
for not running advertisements in front
of my YouTube
because
it's about you guys and people who are
suffering and struggling and sick it's
not about always Banking and it's also
not about
you know all merch and merch and merch
I put up all the free info it's free
it's not for me to create
all this content
to run a website it is literally content
that's only for you guys and it's free
so
I saw a question what about children
take the brain saver books to your
doctor ask your pediatrician if if
they're right for your child absolutely
take the brain saver books to your
doctor your practitioner your health
care provider your pediatrician
it cost me a tremendous amount of money
to create and build the website for you
guys to create build the website and not
have a firewall to pay all the help
so here's how it works you build up a
website you run a big firewall a paywall
you charge everybody for subscription
fees and courses and everything else so
you can pay the people who work for you
and you can pay yourself and get rich or
whatever I refuse to make paywalls in
all the medical meme.com I refuse to be
huge advertisers all in front of my
podcast medical medium podcast Health
podcast is the number one podcast
and I don't have advertisers in front of
it and commercials
and trust me I'm hated for it
by the big bad wolves
because you're supposed to and I don't
I'm in it for you guys in it for you
guys to move forward and heal
anyway
all right brain saver challenge did you
sign up you're not going to be
disappointed if you sign up for the
brand saver challenge you guys I want to
do more lives as soon as I get the
chance I want to talk to you guys I want
to answer really more questions or
actually communicate with you guys a lot
more I just have so much to relay I'll
see you tomorrow
I'm gonna do a live tomorrow all right
God bless you guys