medium we're live streaming right here
going to talk about the B12 show a
little bit the episode The B12 episode
really important because I'm getting a
lot of questions now coming in like do I
need B12 are my B12 levels okay they're
too high are they too low what does B12
do how does it work in my body and I
talk about it in the episode B12 trick
or treat you don't get it from me I talk
about it in that episode at Medical Me
podcast at Apple podcast you want to
check that episode out but I'm going to
talk about neurological symptoms too
because the B12 goes hand inand with
neurological symptoms if you're battling
something neurologically and you need
help neurologically B12 is one of the
key pieces that has to be involved and
it has to be the right kind of B12 it
can't be the wrong kind of B12 because
the wrong kind of B12 is not going to
get you improvements and then you'll be
like oh I tried that or I did that I
tried B12 and it didn't work and then
you get cheated out of healing or
cheated out of getting a chance to move
forward and do some healing and all that
guys great to see you so medical medum
podcast at Apple podcast that's the
official uncensored platform that's
where you hear it so make sure you hear
the B12 episode and the neurological
symptom episode and I want to talk about
both of them because there's so many
questions the B12 show just completely
kicks something off with everybody it
just it really kind of hit everybody in
a way where kind of like the apple cider
vinegar episode did you listen to the
apple cider vinegar episode um the teeth
dissolve
did you hear that episode um and I know
there's a lot of I know a lot of you
guys are apple cider vinegar Drinkers
and you're into it and I totally get it
it's the best one out there but if you
check out that episode you'll learn that
whoa it gives teeth problems even if you
dilute it doesn't matter if it touches
the teeth or not check that Apple set of
vinegar episode that really triggered
off the Torches and pitchforks and you
wouldn't believe you wouldn't believe
what was being fired at me with that one
bullets were being fired know anyway the
whole point is that I want to talk about
the B12 episode The neurological system
episode too because neurological
symptoms because both those relate to
each other they're so important and that
B12 episode about B12 not coming from
meat yes meat has it yeah you know I'm
I'm I'm look I'm Pro people who do the
animal based diets I'm Pro people who do
the plant-based diets and you know all
of it I just wants you to be able to get
what you need information you need so
you can heal and protect yourself so
that when you get your fatigue and your
aches and pains and your jaw pain and
your neck pain and your back pain and
your dizziness and your Vagas nerve your
Vagas nerve that I talk about all in the
neurological symptoms episode so
remember when you get any of these
things going on the the frenic nerve the
Vagas nerve that I've been talking about
for 35 years if something's going on you
get the dizziness the vertigo um
medical medium information is the first
that put out the dizziness the vertigo
the being involved with the Vegas nerve
the nausea being involved with Vagas
nerve all these different symptoms and
how B12 is critical when you're dealing
with Vagas nerve issues and the anxiety
vagus nerve and frenic nerve so anxiety
depression those two are really
important right there so medical medium
podcast at Apple podcast subscribe so
you can be notified you guys when the
episode comes out because each episode
coming out is at a different time
they're not on a schedule where it's
exactly the same day of the week or the
same hour of the week because I'm
sitting there working hard trying to get
these episodes done and get them out to
you and so it might be on a different
day and really you got to subscribe to
Apple podcast you know just just to the
medical medium podcast that's all you
don't have to you know kill yourself you
know subscribing to all this stuff no
just medical medum podcast at Apple
podcast so you can be notified when that
episode immediately goes out there like
when that episode boom gets launched out
there it's a free resource you don't
have to pull your wallet out it's a free
resource these are docu series style uh
episodes they're not throwaways they're
not Coffee Talk have guests on and you
do the coffee talk and it's just a
throwaway and another one guest on and
another one guest on you just throw them
away until there's just hundreds of them
it's not that kind of thing the medical
medum podcast is about saving lives it's
about information that has already saved
lives the record of saving lives proof
is in the pudding and the street cred is
there and it's about helping people heal
and people with neurological problems
people with all kinds of different
symptoms and conditions so it's about
inspiration it's about bringing lives
back it's about taking things to the
next level make sure you subscribe I'm
glad everybody's here so the B12 Julia
says the B12 episode amazed me will be
trying to spend more time in nature and
eating fruit from the trees to load on
microorganisms wow that's really
incredible it blows me away I'm so happy
to hear that it's a free resource link
is in the description so subscribe and
I'm saying subscribe because you guys
aren't going to know when the next
episode's going to come out cuz guess
what I have a surprise episode coming
out pretty soon but I'm not sure what
hour what day this week but it's coming
out and in order to hear you got to
subscribe so that boom you know right
away so important so and so let's talk
about B12 a little bit um uh Jen Jenny
says the B12 episode is amazing so much
information I've listened to it at least
four times so far so helpful so grateful
to you and spirit thanks for listening
to that one I'm so glad you heard that
one four times is really smart as far as
listening to it because if you listen to
it once you're not going to get the
information it's there's too much
information in there you guys so it's
not about listening to it once listen to
it again so you can learn and it's so
important it is so let's talk
B12 um uh Lana says what kind of B12
adinos adinos Sil calaman meth cabalan
both those combin you know you can check
out my directory medicalm medium.com so
you know the best stuff that I use for
my family that I use for my close dear
friends that I use personally at
medical.com
I have a supplement directory right
there and I'm not the owner of all those
or those companies I'm not the owner of
those companies um I'm not sponsored by
those companies so something to know
that's really important so it's just a
free it's another free resource so you
know what best be 12 to use what best
you know products to use so that's there
it's just there for you guys of course
you know you at least you have that
option um and uh you guys I you know I
want to make sure you get the
information you need the 12 episode hit
a lot of cords with people people some
people are freaking they're just like
okay wait a minute I had a blet test my
B12 was low what do I do you know I like
what do I what route do I go or my b12's
high wait a minute I don't get my B12
from meat and chicken and eggs so where
do I get it from and the episode's
packed with that information it's really
important to know um and Tammy says I'm
drinking my lemon water right now that's
incredible I'm drinking lemon bombb tea
right right now anyway that's what I
have right here so you guys it's really
important about hand inand the B12
making sure that's involved in your life
with neurological symptoms ticks spasms
burning skin jaw pain neck pain
trigeminal neuralgia vegus nerve issues
which is a big part of all this anxiety
depression right eye floaters ringing in
the ears popping buzzing humming in the
body restless leg syndrome uh and Omnia
I'm trying to think of more many more of
these symptoms you guys know any
neuropathy plr fasciitis that one alone
is just that's the nerves down there
right sciatic nerve issues back pain hip
pain anything neurological okay all of
it well hey these symptoms are important
burning tongue what about that
vibrations in the body all of that so
itchiness in weird places you know where
you're like well I'm scratching but it's
not taking care of it but I feel itchy
all these neurological symptoms you got
to listen to that episode neurological
symptoms that's an important one medical
meeting podcast at Apple podcast if you
just got on here please listen to the
episode
subscribe um that's it's medical Med
podcast at Apple podcast critical to
hear the episode it's a free resource
share it with others so people can heal
you know about the meditations jamilia
said I had the most amazing experience
listening subconsciously asleep to the
Moon meditation oh my God that is
incredible you can fall asleep during
these meditations there's the moon
meditation there's the brain meditation
there's a freas a bird meditation it's
really incredible you know hey Monica
says hi Anthony good to see you this
afternoon I'm glad to be here you guys
uh glad to be here Jennifer Mcall says
oh my God oh my God Souls gold the
episode oh my God fabulous you know you
guys you guys are the bottom line is
look you know the B12 check it out
that's important check that one out B12
um trick or treat you don't get it from
me and that's one thing that people are
so confused about it's like hey wait a
minute there's all these mediators in
the world why are they low in B12 how
come how come they're having problems
how come they're in their dentist chairs
how come all this other stuff and by the
way I mentioned dentist chair make sure
you listen to the Apple set of vinegar
episode teeth dissolver check it out
such an important episode um Monica says
love your podcast so happy that you do
you guys look I mean I want this podcast
to not be just this thing about me I
don't want it about me you know and
that's a thing I noticed I get it people
do their podcasts out there not
everybody but a lot of people do their
podcasts out there and they have guests
on and and they want to kind of like
talk about all kinds of stuff about
themselves and stuff it's like wait a
minute here this is about people who are
struggling people who have real symptoms
people who are suffering people people
who have conditions this has got to be
about you guys and the medical meting
podcast is like a docky series style
it's not it's not Coffee Talk throwa
away cotton candy episodes it it is
literally messages from Spirit in there
information from above lifechanging
information to help you heal and spirit
of compassion is all within these
episodes so it's really important to
have this information
Monica says you are so amazing Anthony
you care so much I was in tears
listening to your podcast wow that's
incredible I wonder what episode did you
hear did you do the
meditations uh Joshua Eldridge says I
love the explanation of microorganisms
it reminded me of a Marvel movie like
Ant-Man that's incredible um you know
people don't realize it that it's
microorganisms in your elium in your gut
in your elium and in that elium down
here okay it's really important that
these microorganisms get in there and we
only get them in once in a while like if
you had an apple off of a tree if you
had um you know a cucumber out of
somebody's Garden if you grew some
parsley out of a pot or you know a pot
you have like outside your little
Terrace there or maybe you're just you
know you're an apartment building and
all you have is your kitchen with a
little window and then you grow some
Sprouts like in a sprout tray you guys
and what happens is is these
microorganisms they actually appear they
do grow on all of this living produce
that we that we can grow like a little
garden with some kale growing out of it
maybe you have that option once in your
life it helps just to have it once and
then these little microorganisms are on
these plants and I talk about this at
the medical Me podcast at Apple podcast
the B12 episode you got to check it out
cuz I really go into it in depth in
there really and these microorganisms
when you eat them they bypass the
stomach they find their way to the ilum
and then they start producing the
co-enzyme but it's not quite 100% in its
you know valuable form yet until it hits
the liver and I talk all about it so
important Lorraine L I'm looking forward
to Full Moon next week next week
planning to do the moon meditation every
day I think I read a comment lorine that
you said that you you prefer you prefer
waiting for you did you've done the moon
meditation but I think you said
something like you were waiting for the
full moon coming and that's why you were
going to do it all over again so it's so
great that you're doing that um so proud
of you and people don't think I read the
comments but I read the comments you
know I just have uh I have so many
things going on all at once while I'm
trying to read them then it's hard for
me to respond because I have so many
things oh my God uh Karen love your
podcast really our life changing and we
should share it everywhere so more
people can listen to you and heal thank
you am honor Karen because sharing it's
really important you guys tell people to
subscribe please because it's important
at Apple podcast medical medium podcast
at Apple podcast so you're subscribing
to Medical medium podcast because what
happens is when I come out with the next
episode you want to know you want to be
there when you want to get the
notification that it's out now just just
so you don't miss it and time doesn't go
by and all this other stuff the link is
in the description check it out the link
is in the description um you guys so
proud of all you're doing so I just want
to go into this a little bit just
because our B12 is high doesn't mean we
are using it doesn't mean we're actually
utilizing it assimilating absorbing it
it could be in our bloodstream from the
animal products that we're eating but
yet it's not going into our nervous
system and as the years go by we start
getting some different symptoms you know
for all kinds of problems that I talk
about in the neurological episode so
what I recommend okay if you guys have a
chance what I recommend is listen to the
B12 episode and listen to the
neurological symptoms episode okay link
is in the description B12 episode and
neurological episode subscribe to the
medical meme podcast too and the reason
why it's important to listen to both of
those is because B12 is critical for
neurological symptoms and I talk about
why and everything Alexandra Sophia said
I did the moon meditation three times
last night after experiencing emotion
pain and the meditation completely
calmed me and took pain to zero oh my
God it's so important that's so
important um you know it helps with
anxiety it helps with depression it's um
it really helps with all of it the the
Moon meditation really helps with
anxiety really helps check it out the
moon meditation at Medical meeting
podcast at Apple podcast link is in the
description it helps with anxiety it
helps with the Vagas nerve helps with
our souls that it helps with our soul
with emotional injuries betrayal have
you guys ever been betrayed I mean in
your life I have in my life I have have
you guys ever been betrayed I mean if
you're you're lucky if you haven't had
that happen to you um broken trust have
you ever had that happen in your life
where your trust Gets Busted by others
you trust it okay that's in the episode
by the way um that's in the uh Moon
meditation episode I think it's in that
one you know I was shocked at how much
you know the thing is I'm trying to read
these comments they keep on flying up so
fast so it's hard you guys you know it's
it's the thing with the moon meditation
is when our souls get injured by so much
and I'm talking about broken trust
betrayal broken relationships hardships
losses all these different issues I got
to tell you guys it's really painful but
we carry these wounds with us and then
we're afraid to trust and then then
we're like well I can't trust I can't
trust that person and I can't trust this
person I don't know what to do I can't
trust this decision I'm supposed to do
like where do I where do I go and you
know what happens is that we get to a
place in our life where we just we just
you know we just don't trust anymore and
the wounds stick with us and I want you
guys to be able to release that and be
able to heal that I've used the
meditations my whole life to heal any
wounds that I've gotten over the years
and I want you guys to have that
opportunity this why the moon meditation
do it on a regular basis all that
Michelle Miller said laugh out loud I
love your
Rhymes yeah I mean you know I the next
episode I'm going to be cranking them
out cranking them out in the next
episode that's coming so wait till you
hear that too Katherine Elizabeth says
hey Katherine Elizabeth glad you're here
today the podcasts are eye openening and
the meditations are so powerful
incredible incredible Moon meditation is
awesome you know you guys I I want you
to have these meditations share with
others tell people tell people to
subscribe if you can that's really
important too so you can actually get
the next episode notification cuz I got
one coming out you know I wanted to like
tell you guys what was coming out and I
was going to do that but I gotta you got
to have a surprise it's a surprise I
think it's a really good one I think
it's a really good one I want you guys
to hear it um but the B12 really
important episode with the neurological
symptoms episode l says so to get
meditations I need to go to podcast
thank you thank you oh to get the
meditations it's for free okay the link
is in the description just go to Medical
meum podcast at Apple podcast medical
medum podcast at Apple podcast that's
where you go Danny um what are your
thoughts to Mono eating well there's a
book behind me right here okay cleanse
to heal I have have a whole mono eating
section right there people are healing
all around the world through the mono
eating diets the medical meeting mono
eating diets
and cleanses the mono eating cleans is
so important you can eat mono eating
that way and learn how to do it um Sundy
says hi Anthony I love all your podcasts
and I share them with everybody thank
you so much for the work that you do for
all of us can you please do one on mold
and go in depth with it since I got
fungus infection and got poison with it
please okay I will I will I'm going to
do one on mold there's no way I'm not
I'm going to do it I'm going to do it
soon I'm going to make sure it's in gear
because I want you to get those answers
um it's so important it really is I
really want to do one so ingred said
love your podcast thank you so glad so
you guys so I mean I don't know where to
go with these you got the b12 with all
the information on it how it works the
microorganisms how B12 works the Vegas
nerve the frenic nerves our nervous
system the neurological symptoms episode
you going listen to that if you get a
chance the brain fog episode listen to
that one if you get us a chance and then
the coffee caffeine right coffee matcha
tea chocolate caffeine that episode
right there have you guys heard that one
Trisha Marie's here today my gosh yes
molding chemicals have damaged me too oh
my God not good not good I want you to
heal I want you to get past that so I'll
do a mold one okay without a doubt
because with mold sensitivities and you
get chemical sensitivities too with all
of it they kind of come together so yeah
100% I have to do that so I'm going to
have to look out for you so uh
definitely TR so you guys all right so
what would I do if I had some
neurological symptoms okay so if I had
some ringing in the ears and some
dizziness feeling of being on a boat
aches and pains you know the anxiety the
ticks and spasms and all the other
different symptoms what I I would listen
to the podcast that's what I would do
learn about those neurological symptoms
listen to the B12 one see I'm kind of
giving you Direction you know like yeah
B12 plays a role and it big role in how
we get these neurological things under
control so important so there's that the
brain fog episode is another one you can
learn about what brain fog is that's a
neurological symptom by the way so
that's important um Na says I'm loving
the music and the podcast combined with
your voice it's so powerful that's
incredible I can't believe it um and so
Carmen said coffee matcha tea has truths
yeah totally that episode is really
really incredible um you know I'll tell
you I want you guys to have as much
information as you possibly can I want
you to heal these are not throw away
that what when you hear the word podcast
would what I always thought when I heard
the word podcast in the past I always
thought well because the old radio show
I did was never a podcast you know you
guys it was an old radio show and and
then you know yeah you could hear it as
a podcast but it wasn't a podcast this
is the official medical meaning podcast
right at Apple podcast and what I always
heard about podcast was I always thought
well throwaways you know it's just like
get as many guests as you can have on
talk a little bit about this and that
ask a few quick questions next next next
there's just like kind of like cotton
candy and you get a tidbit here get a
tidbit there but then there's all this
confusion well that's what I've always
thought about with podcast you know but
there's some good ones out there but
still but with this I said you know what
don't want to do that I don't want to do
that I want information packed line for
line I want people healing more people
healing just like they are with the
cleanse of heal book I want people
getting their lives back I want to make
sure this has messages in it this has
information in it that this is this is a
docu series style this is not coffee
talk I want you guys better and I want
you guys healing and that's what I want
so important um yeah and so the bottom
line is a B12 episode really important
there think about central nervous system
think about Vegas nerve think about an
frenic nerves think about back like
sciatic nerve okay tibial nerve all the
different nerves it's so
important um so I'm going to do Tracy
says do a podcast on eyes yeah okay I
will definitely do one on eyes
eventually I promise I'll try to get to
that Alexandra says all podcasts are
mindblowing Rel listen to fruit fear wow
fruit fear when you hear fruit fear a
second time just blows it blows your
mind it blew my mind when I hear it
again because it's like wait did I say
that did I actually say that in there
and then you hear it you're like what
you know it's that kind of thing um but
yeah the information is really packed
the whole bit uh Sergeant s says uh s
says hi Anthony please do a grounding
meditation I love all your podcasts a
grounding one oh my god do you mean like
the one in medical medium book one that
one the grounding one like you're a tree
and your and your feet go down into the
root like you're you grow roots off your
feet into the Earth well I have a
grounding one I will do that one make
sure it's a guided meditation eventually
for you guys I'll make that happen for
you guys too because that would be a
really powerful one for you guys
um definitely it's a medical me book one
um and anyway so kendice says how do you
know how much B12 to take I really
appreciate everything you're doing sir
you're a true savior Kenneth I'm really
glad you're here thank you for being
here so awesome to see you and um how do
you know how much B12 to take well it
works like this it's really tricky where
I put dosages all in cleanse the heel so
I do put dosages for all kinds of
different conditions in cleanse the heel
so people have an idea and they could
always do less they could talk to their
doctor they could do more whatever they
want to do but is but I always look at
it this way if you don't have any going
in you that's not going to help the
situation especially if you have
neurological symptoms or anything like
that so it's important to get enough in
you at the same time we burn through it
we burn through B12 we utilize it so
quickly are you under stress is anything
happening in your life did you have a
hardship did you were you under a lot of
pressure on something emotional struggle
did something happen
any of that are you working hard are are
you getting enough sleep and are are you
dealing with symptoms and conditions so
and if you're dealing with symptoms and
conditions then it's always good to take
more of it what do I do I mean if I had
a B12 in front of me right now I'd show
you right here but what I do is I take
myself personally is I'll take like two
dropper FS here two dropper FS there
depending on what's Happening and lately
I've been taking more I've been taking
two dropper fs and another two dropper
Fs in a day another two dber fools in a
day I've been doing like four to six for
me personally that's what I do
personally but that's me you know so I'm
just letting you know Amy says listening
to the coffee podcast and it's
mindblowing incredible by the way if you
guys guys um you know um check out
medical me.com if you if you know what
kind of if you have a B12 you like fine
but make sure there's no preservatives
in there make sure there's no alcohol in
there and all these different preser
preservatives no citric acid all this
junk in there and if you look at Medical
beam.com
you'll see I have supplement directory
with the right stuff that I use the
stuff that I use I know is safe um
Carmen says thank you for sharing more
details in these new podcasts I'm
sharing things in these podcasts I've
never shared anywhere neverwhere
anywhere it's Emma Grace hey Emma Your
Voice Sounds like Michael J fox laugh
out loud I love your podcast that's so
cool hey that's really cool you guys are
amazing um are you guys doing your
celery juice by the way I wish I had one
right he on
me anyway any of you guys have a celery
juice I could borrow right now I could
just reach through the video camera and
grab one off your kitchen counter and
then drink it that would be so cool um
you guys I just want to make sure you
guys get the information you need to get
healed link is in the description check
it out the link is in the description
it's a free resource don't just listen
to One listen to a bunch of them like
like take some time out listen to the
B12 listen to neurological do a
meditation listen to the coffee one
coffee Macha tea chocolate one listen to
that one by the way I'm kind of caught
don't know which one's my favorite one
anymore I think the coffee Maj tea and
chocolate I listen to that one again I
think it might be that one the air
fresheners episode that's a mindblower
the air fresheners episode check that
out you guys I I want to offer this free
resource there's no commercials there's
no advertisements there's no
infomercials at at least right now there
isn't and that's because I want to keep
it that way as long as I can but you
guys there's none of that there it's
free free free subscribe link is in the
description so you can be notified for
my next one and my next one is coming
out pretty darn soon and I hope it
doesn't disappoint because man I'm
making sure the information's in there I
really am because I want you guys
getting that information Peter Peter
says aw I'm a massage therapist by the
way which is I respect massage therapy
more than probably anything out there
because it's it's ancient number one
ancient massage goes back as far as
human beings existed goes all the way
back long before herbal medicine long
before anything long before anything uh
I'm a massage therapist I lost my faith
in massage can you do a podcast on
benefits of massage ther therapy
absolutely look there's no question I
can tell you right now it's the oldest
form of healing therapy the oldest
modality oldest the minute human beings
existed on planet Earth okay going all
the way back which is a whole another
thing too that I get information from
with Spirit of compassion which is
that's fun stuff I do on the side and
I'm like you know when I need to change
up I'm like hey when did this happen
when did this happen um but as far as
human beings have gone back in our
history that was the first first healing
modality for humankind and in by far
Still Still incredible and the best you
know I mean people say to me hey I got
this going on you need to get a massage
because you're getting touched by
another human that cares that wants to
make sure they actually you know they
move energetically all the energy there
there's there's light coming out of
their hands is they're working on you I
mean you name it I could talk about it
all day um anyway so but uh look you
guys you know you know link is in the
description you got the B12 episod
neurological episode I like those
together because it's like look B12
neurological um we want to get all those
neurological symptoms better well you
got the B12 you know like they got to be
linked in they got to be put together
that's how you do it listen to the apple
cider vinegar episode if you haven't
okay because I got to kind of look out
for you there to make sure you're not
down in this stuff hey I got six
tablespoons of apple cider vinegar in
here right now in my heral tea I put 6
there I'm just going to dissolve my
teeth right
now that's good and make sure that I
burn out my stomach glands like apple
CER vinegar does and and make sure I
cause some other problems you know like
all the other stuff it does but just
listen I don't have apple cider vinegar
in here just look out for that okay and
hear the episode if I just got you upset
please hear the episode Randy hey what's
up I have listened to every episode and
they are all fantastic yay that's the
best that's the best compliment you
listen to all the episodes that's a
chemtrail episode the egg episode the
fruit fear episode the air fresher
episode brain fog episode Moon
meditation brain meditation free as a
bird meditation uh Apple C of vinegar
B12 neurological symptoms probably
missing one I'm probably missing one um
that's really that's really great so
anyway you guys really really I stand
with you about all this stuff I want you
guys to heal I want you getting the
information I want you to have all that
you need and this is the new a new way
of doing it you know I try to give you
what I can here and you got cleanse to
heal to back you up you got that that's
a medical textbook with 75 recipes and
over 200 different symptoms and
conditions I talk about in there so make
sure you check out cleanse heel behind
me it's a New York Times bestselling
book that's my sixth book um New York
Times best-selling book uh it's all over
the world right now it's it's saving
lives check that out if you can it's on
sale at Amazon us get it free at the
library if you want and but you guys I
just want to make sure what can I do for
you what else I I put out the best most
comprehensive book on health ever that's
out there with cleansing and everything
else in recipes and conditions including
supplements and dosages I put that out
there for you um I got this podcast
going okay with this like and these are
docu series podcast episodes they're not
Coffee Talk throw it away and I got that
going
what else can I do I'm here I'm trying
to spend time with lives with you guys I
just love you guys and I just want you
guys to get a chance to heal cuz when I
go to bed at night it's like okay who's
suffering okay who's in bed who's who's
on mattress Island and they can't live
their best life are they getting any
answers you know I wake up in the
morning it's like what more can I do God
it's like God what more can I do what
more can I do I need to make sure you
guys get some healing one way another
the whole bit Alexandra says I want to
see cleanse to heal go to number one New
York Times bestseller um it's really
it's really a great book isn't it it's
really incredible ol says love all your
podcasts books and lives incredible
powerful very grateful for you energy
and comp care and compassion I'm glad
you guys like the podcast episodes you
know so every now and then you'll get a
troll that's like oh there he goes you
know he's he's all arrogant it's like
every now you get you'll get a Troll And
The Troll will be like here you here you
put your heart and soul into the podcast
episode right you give all this
information out that no one has out
there that nobody has right that's
proven to save lives too you give all
this information out there and then you
do it with an open heart because you
want to get somebody better and then a
troll will go there he goes he's
arrogant again on his episodes he's
being arrogant it's like okay if that's
if that's what you think Christina said
this podcast is the best thing ever
couldn't ask for anything else Christina
blown away I'm blown away okay because
that's why I'm doing it so that you know
like you get something that helps like
helps in any way and I hope you guys are
okay with my sense of humor that's in
the podcast episodes you know I mean
it's just you I don't know it's just one
of those things where it's a lot of
experiences that I've seen out there and
had and all this thing I talk to doctors
all the time and I you know I hear all
these experiences so I kind of like I
put the information in there so it's
important that you you have the
information Alexander says love all the
podcasts you're amazing so you guys the
B12 episode neurological episode focus
on those if you can maybe from there go
to the caffeine matcha tea Chocolate
Episode you don't have to quit your
caffeine but listen to the episode and
maybe you might you might you might want
to you never know and and then you can
you can check out the other episodes um
but you guys I'm really proud of all of
you I know you're working really hard so
hey I want you guys to know about B12
how it gets absorbed how we create it
all of it Kim West hey Kim love your
sense of humor it helps us to keep a
light heart as you say so cool Gina says
keep uh please keep the sense of humor
in your podcast okay I will I will I got
a a episode coming out I want you to
make sure you subscribe so you get the
episode you know right away uh Medical
podcast at Apple podcast link is in the
description uh so you can hear the what
I'm what kind of humor I might have
going on annab Beth podcasts are
absolutely fantastic I am a real doctor
and I thank you for everything thank you
for everyone who is sick thank you thank
you for doing the work you're doing
thank you for being here um that's so
great much light and love I love your
sense of humor keeps me laughing during
it yeah lud Mill says love your sense of
humor you you guys are the best Chris
lenel says love your sense of humor
that's funny you know the funny thing is
you guys when I'm when I'm doing when
i'm doing the podcast episode to get it
ready for you I end up laughing too with
it and and all of a sudden like you know
i' sometimes it it sometimes it makes me
laugh while I'm doing it a little too
hard but hey yeah I'm just being silly
you guys look I just want to make sure
you have every opportunity to heal
neurological symptoms really hard on
people and so many ways and then when
you learn about B12 and how it works and
you put those two together you got a
fighting chance I love you guys bless
your heart I will see you next time
check it out link is in the description
and uh take
care