right now
let's do this lentil tacos okay pan's
getting hot
for decades people have been made to be
crazy
depression anxiety ocd
anything the personalization bipolar
whatever it is that you're struggling
with emotionally like some kind of
mental health issue of any kind you're
crazy
because
there's nothing physically wrong with
you no no conventional medicine
right
no there's nothing physically wrong with
you
okay
you're having some kind of problem no
it's it's you right get your act
together it's your problem you got
depression no there's nothing wrong with
you we can't find anything wrong with
you we did the mris ma'am we did the cat
scans ma'am
we did all the medical testing
we did it all
and but there's nothing wrong with you
okay
right
because that's what everybody hears
maybe you'll hear something like this
there's a chemical imbalance but we
don't know really the chemicals
we don't know anything about the
chemicals
you still
you're still crazy
right
for decades and decades and if the
doctor doesn't say that because that's
not what they're saying they're not
saying hey you're crazy when you walk in
but
year after year every day
people are just made to feel crazy
because it's their problem their issue
that's you that's your problem you're
creating that you're making that happen
you got depression
you don't know why you're depressed
i don't know what to say
but here's what's really interesting
right
you get told that it's not physical
all the tests check out you get the
blood work
you get the mris everything's checking
out fine
but we're going to give you a pill
so the doctor's now going to give you a
pill
here's your prescription
ma'am
sir
here it is
a physical pill an actual physical pill
made
in a physical way
with physical drugs right
physical medications
okay
and
but think about that
an actual physical pill
for a problem that's not physical
for a problem that's not even what real
yeah your depression is real
right you see the commercials too
the commercials
and people are suffering from depression
if you're suffering from depression life
could be really hard
many people around the world suffer from
depression try this new drug
you know try this new drug
that's our new drug try this new drug
whatever the name is right
whatever the name is whatever name they
come up with
i'm not saying people get off their
medications if they're on their
medications you talk to your doctor so
i'm saying they give you a physical pill
a physical drug
for a problem the system doesn't even
believe is a physical problem now what's
wrong with that picture there
a physical drug
right so you've got your antidepressants
one day the antidepressant is in here
with your your anti-anxiety med right
here you bend it benzo your benzo's in
here with that and then here same thing
they're mixed you got that each day i'm
going to take my anti-anxieties my hands
anxiety my depression
with benzos all that i'm going to take
them each day
okay but i don't have a physical problem
wrong with me because the doctor can't
find anything wrong with me so there's
nothing physical wrong with me but i'm
taking all these physical pills and
medications is what i'm doing
that's
what's interesting right
and then
the funny thing is alternative medicine
okay
alternative medicine
well there's nothing wrong with you
nothing shows up
nothing we can see that's wrong with you
in your head
so i think you need to make sure you get
your meditations right i think you make
me you got to make sure you get your
your mental health
routine going and make sure that's right
because you're obviously creating it so
in the alternative medicine world that
you're creating it
the spiritual world you're creating it
too spiritual alternative health world
you're creating it your depression is
you're creating it
because it can't be a physical problem
because it's not a physical issue
right
so even in the alternative world
you're creating the problem
that's what's interesting you know and
it's been like this
so i don't know if you guys have the
audio so
you guys picking this up on facebook
we're live facebook youtube we're having
major tech problems today
so
and on telegram you guys only get the
audio and on rumble you only get the odd
go to rumble if you can maybe i think go
to rumble that
that should be good rumble.com
and find me on there
good to see you guys lorraine ellis
coming on jota good to see you
rumble at uh forward slash medical
medium find me on there
so
tech problems today
you got audio all right
so that's the thing guys let's make a
little food we're going to talk about
this okay he's going to cut up an onion
let's do that
good to see you guys coming on
excited about this
talking about
all the different mental health issues
right
different diagnosis people get i'm gonna
saute an onion i'm making some lentil
tacos hope you guys are okay with that
we're gonna have a little fun we're
gonna make a little food
right i'm gonna chop up an onion
let's see if the onion gets me
so
i think that
so many people
are not validated
they're misunderstood their conditions
are completely misunderstood that's for
sure right
their conditions are misunderstood
they're misunderstood with this
been happening for years they're just
it's they're nicer about it now though
right
but
so if it's not supposed to be a physical
problem whatsoever whatever mysterious
unexplained
mental health issue you're suffering
from
if it's not supposed to be a physical
problem what is it
just a bad person you haven't mastered
your mind you haven't mastered your
thoughts good
maybe you're weak is that what it is
faulty how about that one maybe faulty
it's none of that it's not at all
there's a real physical issue
the system doesn't want to know about
the real physical issues
right i'm putting some onion in here
okay guys i don't know if you guys can
see that right there
making lentil tacos
i'm putting some uh about a half cup of
veggie broth in here with the onion
i'm gonna get that in there
a little bit of vegetable broth right
so we'll get these we'll get these going
this is an amazing dish to tastes
incredible
we got the lettuce because that's gonna
be part of the recipe you put the
taco dish into the lettuce boats right
just like this
so we're made to feel
like there's something wrong with us
right as a person maybe something wrong
with who we are
so if we get this unexplainable mystery
condition this unexplainable mystery
anxiety issue right so your anxiety is
not physical no it's not but here's you
better get the anti anxiety medication
we're gonna give you a physical drug to
try to alter something in here but it's
not physical that's what they say so
conventional medicine is you don't have
a physical problem but let's do a
physical drug to try to alter
what alter what you're doing a physical
drug to alter my soul
you're doing a physical drug so is that
what it is we need a physical drug i'm
going to take a physical drug to alter
my soul what
like what it is so there's nothing wrong
with us physically
so oh i'm going to take a physical drug
to change me emotionally
i don't understand
if it's not physical why do we need a
physical drug
to try to change us
not physically
because that's what they're saying right
thoughts run on electricity every
thought you think
right is running on electricity keep
that in mind all right
so every thought you think is running on
electricity
it's in the electricity so your thoughts
actually in it's wired into the
electricity
that whole electrical grid right so
if
something's happening and you got the
ocd and something's happening or you got
the depression and that electricity is
circulating around your brain and you
got that unexplainable
unexplained mystery depression then you
got that mystery anxiety and you got
that mystery condition
then something is physically wrong
it's just that science is decades and
decades behind
the medical research and science doesn't
know
they don't know so they play guessing
games
so they try to drug
the person's brain right
so now
you know you don't have a physical
problem but we're going to physically
drug your brain to try to alter it
think about that does that make any
sense but you don't have a physical
problem
you know but we're gonna try to
physically change your brain
with a physical drug
but no you don't have a physical problem
because it's all in your mind
maybe you're just you need some
attention maybe you're just making it up
maybe you know you're just you're just
looking
just
you're you're looking for attention
it's all in your head
maybe it's all in your head
but it's not there's real physical
reasons why people are suffering from
anxiety
and ocd and bipolar
and mania
and depression neurosis and psychosis
and anything else or anything like that
there's real physical reasons why we're
actually struggling with all this
and
they throw out well
and here's the thing too i think people
over the years like patients over the
years they've gotten kind of wise to
that a little bit like wolf there's
nothing wrong with me
what is it what is it doctor
well we're told to say it could be a
chemical imbalance but we don't know the
chemicals and we don't know what's
imbalanced and no i we don't really know
you need to see a psychiatrist
right
the psychiatrist
will talk to you and find out if you're
crazy or not
is that how it works all these years
psychiatrists will talk to you to find
out if you're crazy or not and then
prescribe you a drug
like well
we're going to give you this drug
and see if that helps
because your depression
doesn't seem to be because you're
unhappy or you've got an unhappy life or
however it is your depression's really
severe
it's really clinical
so we're gonna need but there's nothing
wrong with you physically but we're
gonna need to make sure you're on a nice
strong antidepressant
but what the psychiatrist doesn't
understand and what the doctor doesn't
understand
there is something going on
there's a reason
why you're struggling there's a reason
why
you're living with this condition and
you're struggling like there's a real
reason it's there
it exists it's inside the brain
okay
problems happen inside our brain
real problems
okay you guys are making lentil tacos
i'm just sauteing some onions we're
doing a little cooking hope you guys are
okay with that
this is great
we're live on rumble
you guys should check out rumble
when you can
and um and even watch the show watch the
shows because i'm gonna do a lot of
stuff on rumble
totally check out telegram too right
of course you guys know about youtube
medical medium on youtube
feel free to give me a thumbs up
if you like the video
if you hate the video give me a thumbs
up
don't give me a middle finger
if you hate the video if you hate the
video give me a double thumbs up
we're making some food
and
i'm gonna chop up some
mushrooms
let's do that
get some mushrooms going here
right
some baby uh
so i'm gonna throw these in here
put a little bit of that in there
right
so we're gonna get down to what goes on
in our brain why we're depressed why we
have anxiety why we have conditions why
we get diagnosed with conditions
why we're up while we're down why why
we're all over the place while we're
bouncing off walls sometimes
why we can't still why we're feeling
symptoms while we feel like we're
suffocating
when the doctor says your pulmonary
tests are just fine
okay
why we feel tightness in the chest how
about that one
you got tightness in the chest
you got anxiety
you got these weird tingles and numbness
you get panic attacks
nothing wrong with you physically though
they say there's nothing wrong with you
physically
putting some mushrooms in here
yeah
it's
it's really just a mental health issue
so what are you doing for your mental
health package
like what kind of routine are you are
you you know doing
kind of mental health routine right the
next thing you know it's all about that
so you see where the blame
goes you guys know i love meditations
medical medium podcasts at apple podcast
i got meditations on there they heal the
soul
but let's not pretend
there's no physical problems happening
inside your brain even after
some trauma emotionally because
emotional trauma can cause damage to
brain tissue that science research
doesn't even know about or anybody else
knows about
let's not pretend that
it's on you man
it's on you you just haven't mastered it
yet you haven't done your meditations
right you're not doing your affirmations
right now i love all that
i love all that
but what about people that are severely
depressed they can't do a meditation and
it doesn't help when they do what about
someone who's severely anxiety written
you talk to somebody who's got panic
attacks all the time where literally
they're jumping out of their skin and
their stomach's flipping and flipping
and flipping right
and they're suffering they're struggling
just tell them to go do a meditation
they'll be fixed up and they'll go
they'll be fine
it's on you if you can't get better
because hey it checks out there's
nothing wrong with you physically so you
hear there's nothing wrong with you
physically so it's on you you just
haven't mastered your mind right are you
creating all this
right you guys are you creating all this
are you creating your anxiety your
depression your panic attacks your
tightness of chest
you can't breathe good you got all the
tingles and numbness that are freaking
out you're like you can't sleep your
your heart's racing are you are you
creating it
because in alternative medicine they
pretty much convinced everybody oh you
don't have your mental health package
right you're supposed to exercise and
have your physical package right you're
supposed to have your physical package
right what are you doing for your
workouts are you running what are you
doing for your exercise what do you what
do you got going there oh you got
problems you got problems you can't
shake what's your mental health package
oh you can't get rid of your your
anxiety depression must be that you're
just not good enough at your mental
health package
you need to go on a retreat
you need to go do this you need to go do
that you need breath work that'll do it
oh yeah tell somebody who's got
crippling anxiety their chest is all
tight you tell somebody who's got severe
depression and
you know depersonalization or they're
struggling and they they're having panic
attacks you tell them to go do breath
work god forbid
tell them they go do breath work they
suffer they'll be into a panic attack on
the ground going to the emergency room
[Music]
so
i'm going to pop some garlic in here
see
basically what it is is
nobody knows why anybody's sick with all
these symptoms
unexplained emotional health disorders
and health challenges and health issues
emotional
mental
all of it nobody knows why so it's put
on you you created it or you are
creating it i'm popping some garlic in
here the alternative movement is really
just getting ridiculous with this
because
of course the alternative movement
doesn't know why anybody's sick with
things because we know that medical
medium information has already shown
that all these years right
by providing answers
but
it's all blamed on everybody who has any
kind of
mental health challenge
of any kind struggle
disorder diagnosis
well i got depression so i better see
this new practitioner new practitioners
telling me to go to this go do this um
you know
go do these
techniques try these different things
everybody's overlooking a physical
problem is what i'm saying because you
can take somebody
who's never had to do anything for their
their their mental health they've never
had to do any kind of mental health
exercises they've never had to do any
kind of
meditation
i know people 75 80 years old they're
like what's that is that some newfangled
thing some new age thing i'm like no
everybody does all kinds of stuff i mean
they're like well i never needed to do
that that's because you don't you you're
not struggling with something physically
that someone else is struggling with
some something physically so they're
sent on a wild goose chase
i like meditations to heal the soul
soul healing
you can do that when you're struggling
with a physical problem
without a physical problem
but we can't just package everything up
and say it's on you
burnout
is a physical problem burn out
mental burnout
brain burnout that's a physical problem
okay
it is it's a physical problem it's not
because you're weak
because that's another thing anybody who
gets burnt out
they're told that they're just weak well
you need a vacation
and then what happens when you're on
vacation or taking a break for six
months or leave of absence somewhere and
you're still not better what's what um
you know what i mean
physical things happen that cause us to
get burnt out or symptoms of burnout
brain fog
and we're going to go into that a little
bit you guys we're just talking about
what's happening if you just came on
here just you know watch this from the
beginning if you can but we're talking
about here it is so your depression is
not physical but take a physical drug
does that make any sense your anxiety is
not physical but take an anti-anxiety
med
your bipolar is not physical at all no
that's just you
that's just you that's you being faulty
that's you being problematic that's you
creating it or maybe you're just cracked
and if you have mania and bipolar or
you're struggling with any kind of
emotional
mental disorder on any level that's you
just being crazy because we've done all
the mris and there's nothing wrong with
there's nothing wrong with you
physically
so we're going to try to take a bunch of
different physical drugs as you're in
that mental clinic
and we're gonna have to we're gonna have
to do a whole bunch of physical drugs to
try to calm you down we'll try to drug
you here then we'll try to make sure
there's plenty of antidepressants here
we'll do some sedating drugs here how
many people get tossed into clinics and
they're stuck in there and they're on
all these drugs
here's the sad part
they have a real physical problem that's
never addressed or never understood
nobody nobody knows what it is
and so they're just giving all these
physical drugs to try to like
balance their crazy
they're not crazy
they're suffering they're struggling
they're not crazy they're suffering and
struggling
with real
physical issues in the brain
so i'm just cooking this down a little
bit now i'm gonna add some seasonings
but i think i'm gonna put some lentils
in here it's time to pop some lentils in
some green lentils right here you guys
so these are lentil tacos i'm making
i haven't done any real cooking in a
while here
on camera so i'm gonna put some in here
there you go
got some lentils in there i'm gonna pop
some seasonings in here too
a little bit of paprika
right let's run through this a little
bit of cayenne these lentils are already
cooked keep that in mind they're already
cooked
don't pop in some hard lentils in there
right it's chili powder right
poulty powder
um cumin a little cumin in there
now i don't have poultry seasoning today
and it calls for poultry seasoning so
i'm gonna throw a little bit of thyme in
here
let's do my own poultry seasoning right
and i'm gonna put a little bit of sage
in here
boom
mari says so i just finished the detox
with tony robbins and life mastery first
time ever in years i'm not fatigued and
i have no brain fog you are an angel
mind blown so you did the medical medium
cleanse during tony robbins yeah i was
there i was there mari you were there
too incredible
yeah we were doing
um the medical medium cleanse right
for life mastery
and that cleanse is really powerful
i designed it for tony robbins
and sage
and
designed it for life mastery and i was
there it was fun it was incredible
actually
i'm glad it helped you that's that's
amazing
so what happens is that we
get thrown away
as far as like wait there has to be
something wrong with me physically you
know there isn't let's throw let's throw
that away let's throw you away
but there is something physically wrong
if you're struggling if you're
struggling with panic and anxiety or
years of it
and ocd and depression
i'm going to put a little bit of salt in
here now with salt you guys know
you don't see salt usually with me on
any level because everybody over salts
themselves they salt themselves they
dehydrate themselves they pickle
themselves they with vinegar and salt
they
you know the whole bit basically they
become salted the salt actually builds
up and deposits if you do too much of it
a little bit of salt on a recipe here
and there once in a while
it's not it's not a scary thing
like once every couple of weeks i'll use
a little tiny bit of it if i want a
little bit of that but the problem is
people just dump a lot of it in and they
have it in everything they're eating
every single thing they're eating has
salt in it
they're just salted out they're just
pickling their liver pickling their
organs dehydrating themselves and you've
got to be cautious with all that so i
just put a little tiny bit in there
okay
and i'm going to plate this up
i got some honey over here too
i was thinking about putting that in
maybe
so
i was going to let me put a little bit
of honey in here
there we go
we're led to believe
that
we're just
a bad unit
that's our fault that we're struggling
with this
mental condition
that if we don't get our crap together
we could you know
we're just gonna get more crazier
first of all
no one's crazy
they're physically injured
it's just that science and research in
the medical world doesn't know this at
all they don't know the subtle injuries
that can't be seen
can't see hardly anything with an mri in
a brain
besides a big tumor
so i'm going to plate this up
besides
things like that
so
these are lentil tacos
so i'm gonna get some lettuce out here
get the bigger ones out make little
lettuce boats
lettuce tacos you can do a couple things
you can take
three of these if you want to make a big
one so if you want to make a big one you
can do
three together like that right if you
don't have the big romaine pieces this
is a beautiful butter leaf lettuce right
here
just a gorgeous butter leaf lettuce
so i'm gonna fill this i put three
together and i'm making a big taco
right
that's one way to do it
now you have this beautiful big taco
right there
okay
you can also do
these little boats
so check this out
look at that look at these tacos
so i got a butter butter leaf lettuce
right here look at that okay
i see he showed us on rumble i thought i
saw it
sarah dillon's on rumble hello hello
i'm gonna make a couple more
just going to fill these up
and make these tacos
this is going to be so good
so good
and you don't need the chicken
you don't need the avocado
this is a fat free a radical fat free
dish
lentil tacos without oil in there you
guys there's no oil in here
okay
i see it every day people
trying to keep their weight down
they get older they can't keep the
weight down
every day they're exercising can keep
the weight down
one of the reasons they got a tired
liver and they're shoving down the fat
everywhere they can avocados nuts and
seeds nut butters chicken meat
fish oils everywhere and they're told
it's fine and they're just like
and i call it fatting yourself to death
but there's no fat in this dish
and that's a big deal if there's no fat
in this dish your liver is not
overburdened it can get a chance to heal
so this is actually a liver healing dish
it's also good for the brain which we'll
talk about in a minute
so you guys i'm making a quick
announcement right now
three-day
anti-bug cleanse coming up medical
medium
let me know
it's a free
cleanse so get ready for it it's the
anti-bug cleanse
i'm going to be doing it i hope you guys
are going to be with me on it remember
we did the mono cleanse challenge right
the mono blends challenge this is the
anti-bug cleanse challenge remember we
did the heavy metal
detox cleanse challenge
right
this is the anti-bug cleanse challenge
it's gonna be wicked cool wicked fun
it's coming up i'm gonna announce the
date pretty soon
so just look out for it we're doing the
anti-bug cleanse and cleanse the heel if
you guys want to get ready for it make
sure you have a cleanse the heel book
okay so amazon
us it's 1699 51 off which is incredible
okay or try to get it at the library if
you can too all right get it free at the
library the cleanse is free get the book
free of the library if you want
make sure you have a book we're doing
the anti-book cleanse
i'm pumped
this anti-bug cleanse is really cool i
never did one
like this with everybody i did it myself
i never did it like this so this is
going to be great it's going to be fun
talking about the brain a little bit i'm
just showing you guys on tick tock there
it goes
rumble
hey guys you guys go youtube telegram
what do you think these are a fat free
dish it's the lentil tacos
right there so you can just literally
take a boat like this it's so easy okay
and you can bite into it right
so good
we're gonna cover some um brain talk in
a couple of seconds i'm going to talk
about what's the cause of stuff i just
want to take one more bite
that's insane
wait you guys try that
that's really incredible all right
i'm gonna put this right here
the more aluminum you get inside your
brain
the more stuff's gonna happen
okay
the more mercury
you get inside your brain
what does that say right there
what's that say you guys
i'm hoping it's not backwards
fish oil
okay
one of the worst things ever a
practitioner or doctor or anybody could
recommend anybody to take
that's your ticket to alzheimer's
that's your ticket to alzheimer's land
dementia land sure you might be
industrial feeling now 20 years old i'm
never going to get alzheimer's i'm
taking my fish oil capsules i feel fine
you'll be there you'll be there
it's on the rise everybody's getting
alzheimer's if you live long enough
for alzheimer's to happen and not die of
something else earlier because that's
how it's bad it's getting out there now
right
but
stay away from fish oil
that fish oil those fish oil capsules
krill oil
whatever
will take you into the badlands severe
depression down the road anxiety
everything else that's mercury in the
brain right it's mercury
parkinson's
so medical medium
put out the first
pieces of truth and information about
parkinson's disease
and said that it was copper toxic heavy
metals and guess what science of
research says that parkinson's is
genetic
but there's a big lawsuit out there
because parkinson's is linked to
dangerous pesticides hmm i thought
parkinson's was genetic
i thought parkinson's was uh
genetic because that's what they say
but meanwhile there's a big lawsuit
because it's linked to dangerous
pesticides parkinson's and do you know
why because medical medium
knew this all along because i've talked
about it over and over again it's almost
like where they even get the information
maybe they got it for medical medium
but
because in pesticides
there's toxic heavy metals mercury
copper
and they use mercury in pesticides right
to short-circuit and kill bugs
and rodents and stuff like that it's
toxic heavy metal so aluminum are in
pesticides too
so
you guys are doing your colognes and
perfumes
how do you like the smell of pesticide
it smells good right
i don't want to i don't want to spray it
this time one time i opened up the cap i
don't know if you guys remember and i
sprayed it right in my face and maybe it
was a tick-tock video or something oh my
god
i mean it just stayed in the house for
like three weeks
right
so the toxic heavy metals settle in the
brain okay and then we get
lots of toxic heavy metals from
pharmaceuticals
of all kinds
of all kinds though
let me think
what's a pharmaceutical
um
cold medicines yeah that's
pharmaceutical um
uh what else just trying to think
antibiotics pharmaceuticals right
what else
can you use your imagination
what's
what's the hot topics of today
trying to remember
hmm
metals and lots of it so we get metals
from that so if we have a history of
that recreational drugs too metals and
that
man
weed is coated in metals i'm not saying
you do it's your life do what you want
do what you want it's your life
but weeds saturated with metals
okay
sure this weed is organic oh yeah i'd
like to watch you guys grow it
and check it out at the farm site let me
see what you're putting in there
because from what i've heard out there
it ain't kosher
okay of what they do
so
point is is like metals are everywhere
we can get it in every place every way
possible we can get the metals so the
metals build up
and i showed you guys i said the other
day
they sit on neurons that's a neuron it's
a pencil
by the way
the paint in a pencil if you've ever
bitten a pencil right all the pencil
biting okay
that paint is filled with metal
the lacquer is metal meaning there's
metal particles in the lacquer so if
you're chewing on if you're biting your
pencils
some people do you bite the eraser
that's the aluminum end right there
the eraser's got metal in it
so that's another thing too
so your neurons get metal on them this
is a neuron inside your brain there's
the metal inside there and then
electricity is trying to run over that
metal it's trying to run through that
metal it's hitting that metal if the
metal deposit is big enough the
electricity bounces back and what's in
your electricity is your thoughts
your thoughts
right so when it comes down to ocd
you've got terrible thoughts going on
because a lot of people suffer with ocd
they got these bad thoughts and they
just can't shake them and the thoughts
keep on recirculating like
something bad's gonna happen and
something's bad is gonna happen and
what's happening is
and while they're going through that
struggle with their thoughts and they're
suffering with the whole ocd and the
thought pattern right
electrical signals electrical impulses
are going down the neuron heading down
real fast i'm going down slow real fast
and they hit the metal deposits
and then they bounce back
sometimes they'll hit the metal deposit
and just explode and diffuse
this is advanced information medical
medium
and but a lot of times it hits
and ricochets back as it's ricocheting
back
you've got another electrical impulse
with a thought on it heading on down and
they collide and when those two
electrical impulses collide
we got ocd and that thought never leaves
starts to be obsessive starts to take
over
now you can have tiny bits of metal on
your neurons so let's do that a little
bit
let's do tiny bits right
not a lot of metal on your neurons tiny
bits in different places
so say your neuron is saturated with
tiny bits of metal in different places
inside the brain okay inside the brain
the electrical impulse is hitting it
and then bypassing it or going through
it
the information has been altered and
changed
send you into a depressive place
unexplained sadness that can't be
figured out like where is the origin of
the sadness where's the origin of this
depression where's the origin of this
anxiety and it's not explained you guys
just came on here this is all medical
medium information medical medium
doesn't use anybody else's information
ever it's always been original and
unique and instead everybody throughout
the world including science has taken
medical medium information after it's
been published and they put it out there
but mm info is always unique and
original always has for 35 years
and even longer since i was a kid
so
that metal on your neuron
interferes with your thought process
because your thought process is actually
in an electrical field it's on the
electricity it's in the electrical grid
it's in the electrical impulse traveling
down the neuron so you're going to end
up with depression then you're going to
end up with
anxiety and then you're going to end up
with brain fog and anything else
involved
anything else like that so this is
really important to know
that meal is helping my brain right now
i didn't eat today
much
and
so that meal just got me sparked up so
now i'm like jazzed up right now
okay
so
anxiety you got tightness to the chest
you got tightness in the throat you feel
like your throat's being strangled do
you have any of that do you have what
feels like butterflies flipping in your
stomach your abdomen so you've got some
flips in your abdomen and your stomach
and you're getting the butterflies are
you getting any of that
what about panic attacks what about you
can't feel like you can't breathe but
everything's working and you're getting
plenty of air right how many anxiety
issues have people have do you feel like
you can't sit still
do you feel like you can't shake the
anxiety in some way you got clenching in
your teeth that's what you're dealing
with
so
is it hard to make a decision and you
get all of a sudden an anxiety attack
because you can't make a decision what
about that you guys like you got this
anxiety attack and you can't make a
decision you have racing thoughts and
it's giving you anxiety because you've
got racing thoughts and it's giving you
anxiety
right
all this is happening because of the
vagus nerve okay
so the vegas
you guys i have
incredible information in the ponzi hill
book just wanted to make one more
announcement real quick before i forget
we're doing the medical medium anti-bug
cleanse
is what we're doing
it's coming up real soon
make sure you have a cleanse the heel
book
it's going to be a three-day cleanse
challenge
it is gonna be incredible it's gonna be
just as incredible as the other
challenges and maybe even better
okay so we're talking about anxiety this
is all medical medium
information your vagus nerve
your vagus nerves stemming out of the
brain stem
traveling down okay
wrapping sending nerves to intestinal
tract nerves to your heart
all right
what happens is when that vagus nerve is
inflamed
and inflamed by metals and viruses okay
so when that nerve is inflamed by metals
and viruses
it gets in it it gets irritated and when
it's irritated you're going to
experience all these different symptoms
tightness of chest
okay tightness of throat
weird sensations on your face and head
okay
if you heard about vagus nerve
information been teaching about it for
decades
and if you've heard about it anxiety
involved it's medical medium info it's
where it originated published first
with phrenic nerves and vagus nerves
so our vagus nerve gets inflamed it gets
irritated
irritable
it swells and when that vagus nerve
swells
we get all the different anxiety
symptoms but it makes you more
susceptible to trigger so if someone
gives you bad news or if someone
stresses you out or you're in a
relationship and there's a problem in
the relationship or you're you run into
confrontation you're gonna get more
anxiety than someone else does because
the vagus nerve is inflamed
and when the vagus nerve is inflamed
you're gonna be more triggered easy
more sensitive and that includes
you know a lot of different things that
can happen with that trigger so we just
made the lentil tacos we're talking
about real reasons why people have
anxiety and depression ocd bipolar so
we'll talk about bipolar for a second
up and down
everybody being like all over the place
so
you got the neurons and you got the
metal on the neurons okay
and
bipolar
is when
the electrical impulse
diffuses so as electrical impulse is
traveling down the neuron and it hits
metal it's diffusing
so you end up getting lows
so now you're really low and there comes
it comes a point where an override
occurs
that means
not enough thought power
going to the right direction because
it's being interfered with so the
electrical impulse is diffusing too much
and too long
after hours of this diffusing process
and maybe even a day or two this
defusing process and you're down in this
low
this bipolar low
a reversal occurs
all of a sudden the brain gets heated up
the electrical charge gets really strong
to try to fix the problem and override
the injury so then all of a sudden the
electrical is bright and strong so the
electrical grid gets really powered high
and that high powered electrical grid is
to fix the problem so it's our innate
body's ability
to
fix and repair a problem okay
so it ends up rushing through
powering through
and that grid is lit up for a day or
hours and now you're on this high you're
on this high you're on this high you're
on this high until the heat gets so
intense
that it just shuts down and you're back
to the lows lows lows it's advanced
information medical medium information
so
back to one back to where we're talking
about from the start so we get told
that there's nothing physically wrong
with us
that it's us causing the problem and if
you've got like mild depression mild
anxiety or any kind of mild form of of a
mental
health challenge disorder struggle
and it's mild you're definitely going to
be convinced
that
it's just you just need a little work
you need to get the mental health
package right
and that's really what it is it's me you
know i'm the problem i gotta get the
hell i gotta keep on working on this
mental health package because i'm the
issue because everybody else they seem
to be fine and i'm the one struggling
but that's a trap
you're actually perfect
never forget that
every one of you you're perfect
okay
your soul's perfect you're perfect
you're a good person there's just a
physical injury that's not seen by
alternative medicine not seen
by conventional medicine
and so what we do
is we fix problems we get the metals out
right and i just did
i talked about that we get the spirulina
we get the barley grass get the heavy
metal detox cleanse and smoothie going
right we get the metals out it's in the
book right here
so check out cleanse the heel
okay
and the street cred is here millions
healing worldwide so check this out and
get ready for that anti-bug cleanse you
guys were heading off
we're going to do it again i'm going to
cook the dish again if you guys want to
hang out it's going to be fun
and
we're turning telegram back on tick tock
back on we're gonna turn ig on
and uh if you guys get kicked off of ig
go to telegram then go to rumble
okay you get kicked off facebook go to
rumble all right subscribe to rumble at
rumble.com to the medical medium channel
because we're going to be doing a lot of
stuff it's going to be fun a lot of
different stuff a lot of unique stuff
there stuff i don't do anywhere else so
i'm really excited you guys i hope you
come aboard
and we have some fun and we learn and we
do some powerful healing all right love
you guys i'll see you in 10 minutes on
ig
i'm gonna put tick tock back on patel
graham back on