first of all I just want to say a couple
of things
first
foremost how much I'm honored to be a
part of your lives in any way I can
helping you guys get anything that you
need with this information I'm honored
to be in this lifetime with you at the
same time
it means the world to me seeing you guys
actually heal seeing you guys
get the information so I got the brain
saver books right here
I just wanna
let you guys know that
one of the things that happens with
medical medium information is that
it doesn't find its way back the people
who do use it out there don't find their
way back to the medical medium books
like this incredible scripture
that's helping so many people so if you
can this would be amazing if you can
like if you if you do say post about a
shot so say you post about for instance
a negative energy exposure shot
and you do a post on it is it possible
to put medical medium negative energy
exposure or if you do the Betrayal and
broken trust stabilizer medical medium
betrayal and broken trust stabilizer
because or the obsessive thought shifter
medical medium obsessive thought shifter
because here's how it works
what happens is the information gets out
there because right now Miracles are
happening
people who are using these brain shots
and SOC told me this would happen people
would start healing
and anybody who's using these incredible
brain shots right now
they're getting incredible healing
results so Miracles are actually
happening in people's lives right now
and it's it's incredible but the sad
part is is that it's gonna get out there
and people are not going to be able to
find their way back to the medical
medium information in books they won't
find their way back to brain saver
because what's going to happen is the
poachers
um the juice shops are all going to have
the shifter shots the stabilizers and
they're not going to really have too
much of an idea that it came from the
medical medium books
and so they're gonna start switching out
the ingredients people aren't going to
heal
these are put together in a way so
Miracles can happen so they're put
together from above so Miracles can
happen in people's health
so it's imperative that if you do like
because it's incredible you guys I
noticed you guys are talking about the
brain shot therapies and I'm like oh my
God this is like incredible because so
many people are going to get helped and
then I was realizing well only some
people are going to get help because
we have to put medical medium in front
of it so it's like medical medium
burnout stabilizer shot you know medical
medium brain shot therapy medical medium
guilt and shame shifter or whatever ones
you're using to heal because if we don't
it's going to get diluted along the way
and poached and go into all kinds of
different Avenues and then people are
going to be cheated out of the ability
to heal
and find their way to the books and all
of a sudden it's going to explode like
because what's happening is
the these are gifts from above
literally when people apply these brain
shot therapies their lives are going to
change it's it's like miraculous things
are going to happen and I knew this
because
I was told by Spirit of compassion
originally that
this is going to be
an incredible incredible experience for
so many people and so with that we want
more people to know about it so and and
find their way back
Elaine steinach says these shots are
incredible and they really are so if you
guys do a post or something or do a
story or anything
what I would do is
if you can put the put the medical
medium in front of it in the sense where
medical medium mold exposure shot
so they know that it's wait a minute
that's where you find the where the info
comes that's where you find the
incredible books with all the healing
information in them because you know how
things go it gets out there
and things happen
um you need to patent this stuff
so yeah so it's funny so the point is is
that it gets really sad because
it's going to get diluted it reminds me
of like the celery juice
movement right with the celery juice you
guys if you guys if you're looking at
all this you're like what is this I've
been doing interviews with some podcast
interviews and stuff like that
so I'm doing that stuff today but I
wanted to connect with you guys about
this for a minute
so the Miracles that are in these books
these brain saver books can only become
miracles for people in their healing
process if they know where it came from
and where the rest of the information is
and then it gets diluted remember how I
always said celery juice has to be
consumed alone by itself without adding
all this crazy stuff in there like
collagen powder and and squeezing lemon
in your celery juice and adding water
and ice remember how I told you it
dilutes it so then people don't heal
they won't get the benefits well
and that happened out there there's
millions of people around the world now
using celery juice but they don't get
the benefits so much because they're
putting all that in there well it's the
same thing that's going to happen with
the brain shot therapies these are
Miracles as they are in these books the
information here
the ingredients to exactly how much that
Spirit of compassion said to use the
exact amounts and what's here it's all
going to get diluted and distorted as it
goes outward in the world right and so
if you can it would be awesome if you
can't I understand but if you can put
medical medium adrenal fight or flight
stabilizer when you guys you know post
about it and stuff that would be
incredible I know a lot of you guys will
tag me
and you'll see it and that's fine of
course tag me but it also doesn't but
but it doesn't mean that someone's going
to know that that nerve shifter shot or
that guilt and shame shifter shot or the
dream shifter shot is the medical medium
info to get him back to brain saver so
they can heal and they can do the other
incredible miraculous shots and they can
do the seven brain shot therapy cleanses
and pick one for themselves or a loved
one and heal and then they can do the
heavy metal detox smoothly Advanced and
then they can do seven of the heavy
metal detox cleanses and then they can
do all the the brain healing recipes
that are in the book and then get the
information just to protect and save
their lives throughout the books so if
you guys can just let people know that
would be incredible because it helps the
mission is what it does and I would hate
for the because that's what's going to
happen all the juice bars across the
country they're going to be doing all
these shots now of these kinds using
these names they're not going to put the
medical medium involved that they're
going to change in the ingredients and
the altar all the stuff and it's all
going to just become this thing where
this is how the healing happens it's
from above
and it's exactly what the ingredients
are and the amount
and and then the information of how it
works and everything else that are in
the brain saver books just letting you
guys know that was one of the things I
wanted to mention to you
I also wanted to mention to you these
are 40 off right now
I can't even tell you how happy it's
bittersweet because it made you know to
40 off because these are like books that
should be 300 400 500 a piece or
something I don't know there's like 12
books in these two massive books but the
point is is they're 40 off at 26 dollars
29 on amazon.com us
and and the holidays are coming up and
if you got loved ones and you think the
brain saver books can help in any way
for loved ones and friends and
co-workers and people you care about and
all that
you think about the the sale on these
books at amazon.com us is utterly insane
and incredible and listen
if you don't have any money if you don't
have 26 dollars to spend on the book
if you don't have that
then just give it some time and wait
until it's in the library or go to your
library now and say I want you you I
want the library to have this book and
so that that you can take the book out
for free because I don't care I don't
care if if a million people go to the
library I don't care it doesn't matter
to me because
in the end when I leave this place in
the end years down the road God willing
right
and you know leave this place
and my time is up here
and I did all the work I can do
that millions of people got the books
for free from the library that would be
a godsend and a blessing in my eyes
because it's about people getting the
information no matter what how when
but if we don't say it back the medical
meaning I know you guys do
but if we don't cite back medical medium
sin others can't find it or know what it
really is or understand what the brain
saver book really is
then it kind of defeats some of the
purpose because you know I want people
to get what they need and get the
information you guys the brain shot
challenge it's free it's coming up this
week it's this week it's the 20th it's
October 20th it's Thursday go to
medicalmedium.com and sign up for free
and then you can download the PDF for
the information for your grocery list
your shopping list and get prepared how
incredible is that link is in the
description and it's in the profile too
The Free Medical medium brain shot
therapy challenge starts October 20th
Thursday
it's coming and we're doing 10 days
10 days which is absolutely incredible
it's going to be 10 days free
each day a different shot
I'm forewarning you if you haven't tried
the medical medium brain shot therapy
yet
just get ready
I'm giving you a little bit of a
forewarning
because immediate results
what I do is I sit down with the shot
and I just kind of like get in touch
with it
I get connected with it and I sip that
shot down sometimes I'll send it down
one shot like that too like boom right
but I I'll I'll sip the shot
is what I'll do is I'll sip it
that's what I'll do because I could just
let it go through me and I feel that
light and I feel that energy go through
me and I feel the power of the brain
shots
but what we have before us is a miracle
and it's a miracle from above
it really is and so when people Embark
in these brain saver books
it's going to be
in your Consciousness forever these
brain saver books once you hold them and
open them up and read that information
and if some of that information is
shocking
I just kind of sit with it for a little
bit if some of that information is
different that you've ever heard
this is so different let's just sit back
with it a little bit because every
single line in these brain saver books
there's two of them by the way
there's two of them every single line in
these brain saver books has something to
offer
it's empowerment for the consciousness
their spiritual power in these books
there's physical body power in these
books
They are packed
and overloaded
and the thing is if you can get through
both these books
and get to the other side of these books
just start over again because there's
that much information in there
yes the grocery lists will help I see
that comment right there definitely the
grocery list definitely download the
free PDF for the brain shot therapy
challenge
a comment uh here did the anger shot and
instantly felt better oh my God
I know people that are doing the shots
including cute guys too and
it is just unreal what's happening with
their health because of it but here's
here's the crazy thing here's the crazy
thing
it isn't just the instant relief or the
rewiring it's it compel is compiling on
itself you do it again the next day and
boom and you do it again the next day or
you do it periodically or even if you do
it once it's not just the relief of the
moment it changes your condition as the
days go on
which is another thing that's just
mind-blowing to me absolutely
I'm happy to shout out about these
credible shots from the rooftops it's
the least I can do they are amazing and
incredible thank you for saying that
truly and
I mean this is really what I call a
miracle and as I said before and I
believe in this wholeheartedly I have
every right to judge these books these
are the greatest Health books that we
will ever see in our history
they just are because I could judge
these books all the same because the
information came from above
and I confidently can say these are the
greatest Health books you won't see
these you won't see this written
anywhere else you won't find this in
anybody's Health books and eat better
book somewhere you can't find anything
like this
yes I felt a shift from the shots can
make permanent changes yes they can and
that's what's incredible about the shots
they can make permanent changes along
the way
I can tell you this
Spirit of compassion
told me
that people were going to experiencing
experience something great from these
books and from these shots and from the
rest of the information and other
cleanses that are in these books
and
but we're talking Miracles that's what's
happening I got a friend that reached
out that did
the brain shot therapy one of the
cleanses already
and his life is completely changed
totally lifted my mood today was going
to ask if they build on themselves they
do build on themselves was thinking they
probably did yes they do build up on
themselves they build upon themselves
indeed truly
and that's really important to know
so I'm almost a loss for words because I
I know what's in these I could feel it I
walk around with these everywhere I go
at this point everywhere
I take them into the bathroom
foreign
I take the books into the bathroom
I'm brushing my teeth I got the books on
the side here
I take them into the bathroom
anyway
absolutely incredible
so I want to give you guys a couple of
pieces of information right
if you sign up at medicalmedium.com for
the free medical meeting brain shot
therapy challenge
you get the PDF you can then down you
can download the PDF like your shopping
list everything else so let me just give
you a little
like inside of what we're doing right
day one is a negative energy shot
look out
there's any negative energy inside there
maybe you're not even aware of look out
the negative energy shot I love that one
okay and here's another one too day two
betrayal and broken trust stabilizer so
betrayal and broken trust oh that's a
negative energy exposure shot right
there
betrayal
broken trust stabilizer you guys ever
get betrayed by anything broken trust
any kind of letdowns maybe five years
ago eight years ago in the past still
sits inside of us sits inside of us
that's why we can be triggered
and what I love about the power of these
medical mean brain shot therapies is
because
it was designed from above to knock
stuff out of us that shouldn't be in
there right like the Betrayal that we've
had a wound in there and then the
triggers happen easy because we have
that wound
and when we knock that out oh my God
what could happen
it's unbelievable day three obsessive
thought shifter whoa so many people I've
known have thoughts in their head they
don't want in their head they got the
OCD they got all kinds of different
varieties of OCD all of that incredible
and you guys I just want to remind you
one more time
amazon.com
26.29 amazon.com us 40 off tell a friend
tell a friend if a friend says well
I don't know if I want to to do any
medical medium stuff be like look
you have to have one of these books and
then start reading it a little bit try
one of the brain shot therapies and see
for yourself
then day four is the EMF and 5G exposure
shot I heard I heard for like what three
years everybody's like medical medium
what do you think about 5G
medical medium 5G 5G 5G
I heard over and over comments 5G 5G to
try everything
all of it
day four is the EMF and 5G exposure shot
so we get
surrounded by the EMF
and then we learn what it's like to be
surrounded by the EMF and live with EMF
what happens when we take the EMF and 5G
exposure shot the brain shot therapy
what happens
huh
day five mold exposure shot
it's worth doing even if you don't think
you got mold around there's mold on
other people there's mold on other
people's clothings there's mold in
stores there's mold every interesting
try to get that in there
day six burnout stabilizer
the burnout stabilizer I am excited
about that day seven adrenal fight or
flight stabilizer because we're jacked
up
stress every well I okay I can't speak
for you guys then but I can speak for
myself man I'm jacked up with stress and
everything else okay I got so much going
on
if
a battling Darkness battling Giants and
Dragons that's what I'm doing people
have no idea they don't even know to the
level
anyway so
yeah day seven adrenal fight or flight
stabilizer I am pumped about that one
day eight
guilt and shame shifter yeah
the broken trust stabilizer instantly
helped me and got me out of depressive
episode that's what it's for right there
boom that's one of the reasons it's
there
incredible
so
how do you guys try the brain shots what
did you feel what were some of the
results you felt share them you know tag
medical medium and at Medical medium of
course and please put medical medium you
know negative energy exposure medical
medium brain betrayal and broken trust
stabilizer medical medium obsessive
thought shifter medical medium brain
shot therapy
because this is just getting out there
in the world and we got to at least let
the people know out there in the world
that there is a sanctuary in these books
there is a way to move forward there is
a way to do some healing
anyway day nine is the nerve shifter
whoa whoa whoa day 10 dreams shifter
I'm excited about day 10 on the medical
medium brain shot therapy challenge
right
The Free Medical medium brain shot
Challenge free
free free free free free free free
yeah
medicalmedium.com sign up to the medical
medium brain shot challenge
sign up get your PDF with your your
grocery shopping list all that stuff
incredible incredible incredible
the books are 40 off it costs way more
to print these books oh my God full
color the books are massive
really incredible
and you've got the brain shot therapies
and you got so much more I haven't even
begun to talk about and the levels of
healing that are in these books
so much to talk about really incredible
so I hope you guys
are doing good I hope you guys are
working on your healing I am blown away
truly I love the nerve shifter such a
beautiful feeling calm and peace came
over me and here's the thing it builds
on itself
and it builds on itself
why do you do it again you feel it boom
again
there's miracles in these books
they're the greatest books in health of
all time that's my opinion
I hope you guys read the books and see
what you think if you feel like they're
the greatest books of all time in health
if you've looked at other health books
out there all the different eat better
diets and all the other health books and
authors and stuff and health if you
think these things right here in front
of you are the greatest books of all
that you've felt and known
then then that's incredible
since shrinking the brain shots daily I
feel such a shift in my mood and energy
I cannot remember when I was happy for a
full week before this is what Spirit of
compassion told me would happen when I
was getting the information
I just read that in the comments right
there
this is what Spirit of compassion told
me would happen
and I remember on the first day I think
it was the first day you guys I told you
I just want to give you a forewarning
uh I don't want you caught off guard
when you do the brain shot therapies I
don't want you caught off guard meaning
that you will feel
what these offer
and that that's going to surprise you
and I didn't want you guys to be caught
off guard by those results buy those
instant results
because it's intense when you get those
instant results like that and you get
caught off guard like that
it really is
hey W I want to send them to everyone
laugh out loud
that's incredible
so you guys anyway I just wanted to and
just so you know if you're wondering
well is is these miraculous brain shot
therapies all he has in the books
and see I'm reading this comment
speaking your truth shot really works I
felt strong and could say my opinion
it gets into the soul it gets into the
Consciousness these shots are powerful
they get in there deep
then they get there fast
if you're somebody and you're like well
okay the brain saver books they're huge
books what do they have in there is it
just the brain shot Therapies
3 300 symptoms and conditions
protocols for them
seven heavy metal detox cleanses and
advanced heavy metal detox cleanse and
extractor because the world's only
getting dirtier and dirtier and more
people got more and more gunk in their
system
let's see here's a here's a comment uh I
tried the burnout shot this week and it
helped me go on and do a good day's work
after severe sleep deprivation it was a
lifesaver I got to tell you something
I actually did that one because I didn't
get a couple days ago I hardly got any
sleep I was working working and I pushed
I burned the candle at four four ends
again and I pushed and pushed I don't
know it was like a 25 hour 27 hour work
day and but yet I had more work I had to
do the next morning so I took an hour's
sleep it didn't do it for me an hour an
hour and do it I was like oh my God and
I took out the burnout stabilizer I got
the ingredients out of the fridge and I
just boom I knocked down two shots of
that one shot for a little while then
did another one boom Another Shot
hey W you are the only one out there
with a big Generous Heart
so
okay so shamima says aw you are the only
one out there with a big Generous Heart
everyone else is all about money but you
are not a big God blessed to you your
info is amazing
you guys I know I know the books the
books are for sale by the way and I know
that someone might judge me and be like
oh he wants to sell his book then go to
the library and get it for free
everybody go to the library and get it
for free everybody it doesn't matter
to me it doesn't matter and you won't
see a paywall with this brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge you won't see
a paywall and I know they say out there
you have to make paywalls you have to
charge a ton of money and that makes
people think it's valuable or something
but that's really insulting because
people can make up their own mind
towards valuable and they don't need a
five thousand dollar paywall to know
what's valuable or not that's just
ridiculous
wow I'm gonna read this comment wow I
finally process
something from three years ago it was
stuck and it moved forward clearing
that pink chemicals dust and loss at the
same time trauma shot OCD shots green
salads betrayal shot wow incredible I
love the portrayal and broken trust
shot I love that one I've been betrayed
duh
see here's a comment I took the nerve
shifter shot all the nerve shifter shots
amazing before dance class I was way
more chill and it was easier for me to
remember the choreographics of cool also
I didn't have the usual negative
thoughts amazing
what you're going to find with these
shots
is life-changing results
miracles in between those life-changing
results
you're going to feel things that you
haven't felt in years like some Joy come
out like if you haven't felt you're
going to have memories that like whoa I
didn't I forgot about that and that was
such a good thing that had a long time
ago and how come I lost touch with that
like all kinds of things are going to
happen
and that's the miracle about them Spirit
of compact I've been so busy trying to
let everybody know about these books I
haven't gone into a lot of detail about
how miraculous these shots are and how
Spirit of compassion told me people
would get these results
and I was like okay I am looking forward
to it because I need people who are
struggling to have to have a chance to
move forward in any way possible
got to make sure people who have any
chronic symptoms or suffering are
struggling they have a chance to move
forward because there's too much out
there that gets in the way of people's
healing in the books there's a list of
foods to focus on for healing and what
foods are filler Foods so in these books
there's a difference between filler
Foods
and then foods that are healing foods
I can take out just one little part of
one of these books and that little part
is worth everything
that's how powerful there's no fluff in
these books it's spiritual compassion's
just lying after line after incredible
information after therapy after therapy
spiritually emotionally physically
I am suffering with shingles on my neck
and the nerve shot has reduced from
itchiness and redness that is incredible
and you'll find that you'll find
that when you're doing these brain shots
that that's going to happen
aw I'm Blown Away by the information in
the cranial nerves chapter now
everyone's vagus nerve is a different
length
I like the the okay that's a really good
piece of information and that's what is
incredible about the medical medium info
in these books and all the medical
medium books you learn things that is so
Advanced no one has ever talked about
that science research doesn't even know
they don't even talk about that every
single person's vagus nerves are a
different length
it's really incredible
see Anthony what's the difference
between heavy metal detox smoothie and
heavy metal brain shot
heavy metal brain shot is for exposure
that just happened in the moment so
here's what happens if you went to the
dentist and you had a composite put in
because you guys even non amalgam
composites
have metal in them
everything at the dental dentist office
has metal in the metal they're using the
metal tools in the drill have metal in
them right everything at the dentist
office has metal so that would be a good
time for the exposure the heavy metal
exposure shot so the medical mean brain
shot therapy heavy metal exposure shot
that's a great time for that and the
heavy metal detox smoothie or the heavy
metal detox one of the heavy metal detox
cleanses but the exposure shot is for
that quick exposure you just had whoa
it's so great
see you need the grocery list yes then
go to medicalmedium.com or
the link right there in the description
in the profile and
yeah get onto the brain challenge sign
up to the brain challenge cleanse
the branch challenge brain shot therapy
Challenge and make sure you get the free
grocery list download the PDF
so so much information
I don't know if you guys know if anybody
a bunch of bunch of new people I think
are coming on the books are 40 off
amazon.com us they're brand new they're
huge books they're beautiful books
and the light inside of them you feel
see yes the healing foods and filler
food section is pure gold on its own oh
my God
it's actually really an incredible
section in the book but there's so many
of these you'll notice each section of
this book even the blood draw chapter in
Beyond intricate detail of how to
protect yourself blood draw protocols
you guys how many of you guys are
getting your blood work
you guys getting blood work been to the
doctor had another five you know vials
of blood seven vials of blood ten vials
of blood taken how many of you guys
getting blood drawn
there's a protocol before you get your
blood drawn in these books a protocol
after you catch your blood drawn in
these books
that alone is worth so much for people
for their healing process so critical
for their health and you can get the
books at the library if you want if you
don't have 20 something dollars for
these incredible books there's 12 13 14
books in these two books
are we out of luck if we can't get a
juicer right away
it's best to have a juicer but if you
only have a blender or a cheat you can
you can strain it through a cheesecloth
if you want to try that strain it
through a cheesecloth or a nut milk bag
or if you have some kind of juicer I
talk about the best juicers the ones
that save people money so I have that
you'll find if you look at the best
juicers I have they're on sale right now
the mm 1500 the mm-900 they're on sale
20 off
don't add water to these shots
Don't Drown these shots out with water
so when you do these brain shots
I like the mm 1500 you guys know I work
with them on that the mm1500 the mm-900
because it has this pressure where it
actually squeezes all the juice out so
you save all this money juicing and what
happens is you it ends up that money
saved ends up paying for the juicer over
and over again in my opinion
with the money I've saved with the mm
1500 and 900 and with the cost of food
oh my God those are the juicers because
I can't find that with any other juicer
that I've ever tried
and you'll see you'll see I I put that
in the information but check it out
medicalme.com sign up for the free brain
shot therapy cleanse if you can
sign up it's free
it's a 10 day we're doing 10-day brain
shot therapy the books are 40 off
on amazon.com I don't even know what to
say
and prepare yourself because there's
miracles in these books
let's see is the nerve gut acid shot the
one you'd recommend for a severe stomach
pain
if you look if you always have if you
have questions too you can always bring
the brain saver books to your
practitioner your doctor your healer too
your Healthcare practitioner if you ever
want you're welcome to bring these
powerful books to them there's a section
in the book that explains stomach
problems just so you know so there's so
so I think it's yep so the question is
on Facebook is the nerve gut acid
stabilizer
okay is it
um one that I would recommend for severe
stomach pain what I would recommend is
looking into the books at the stomach
problems protocols section and ask your
doctor what he thinks too or she thinks
incredible you guys incredible so
very excited I just wanted to let
everybody know
and just a little recap if you can if
you are posting about these incredible
miraculous brain shot therapies and you
are posting about any of the shots like
the burnout stabilizer or the adrenal
fight or flight or the Betrayal and
broken trust if you can post medical
medium in front of it so medical medium
negative energy exposure medical medium
petroleum broken trust stabilizer this
way when it gets out there and it gets
lost out there and the abyss of The
Ether that someone can find their way
back to where the shots are where they
can learn and heal and do them right
because it's all going to get out there
and it's all going to get distorted
otherwise and then it's going to be one
of these things where
only a few people get to heal and a
whole bunch won't and that right there
is is heartbreaking
anyway you guys
um sign up for the brain
shot therapy challenge when you get a
chance link is in the description and
the profile or medicalme.com
and it's going to be 10 days it starts
October 20th it's coming up and it's
free
it's free I'm not charging
not charging I refuse I don't care no
matter what
challenge starts Thursday I will be live
every day making the medical medium
brain shot therapies one day at a time
and answering your questions and I am
pumped and excited
and it get when you get a chance get a
hold one of these incredible books see
maybe two would even be better actually
I mean get both that's what you really
do need to do is have both there's no
question but you do the best you can
and there they are was one big massive
book
and
now there are two if you're wondering
which one to get
which one do you get here
you wonder which one
get both
and leave a review if you like the book
The Brain saver books or the brain shot
therapies feel good or they're turning
your life around or whatever just leave
a review if you can anyway forty percent
off the brain saver books amazon.com us
tell other people holidays are coming
really really incredible
okay
I will see you guys again I'm incredible
there is a section in the books
on so many things and so much
information
you guys look out for imposters by the
way my last little thing I'm going to
say look out for imposters they they ask
you if you want a consultation and they
there's book imposters too watch that
look out for book imposters look out for
Anthony William imposters look out for
all that I don't do consultations but
there's these imposters and they're
doing terrible things to people so look
out for imposters
um look out for imposter books it's
another thing too people will end up
purchasing an imposter book and then
they'll be like that book was terrible
and oh yeah and you guys when you get
your book from amazon.com keep in mind
that grease from the conveyor belt can
be actually on the book and you want to
actually put a little bit of moisture
like damp cloth a little bit of
dishwashing soap if you want and you
clean your books clean your books is
what you do
and it'll come out nice and clean
Amazon's conveyor belts are greasy they
throw them on the conveyor belt the
books get dirty and then you get this
brand new book
that was pristine and just incredible
and these books originally were stored
in warehouses that didn't have all that
chemical all that terrible scented
candle stuff and cologne perfume and
air freshener stuff and everything else
and detergents and all that it didn't
have any of that these are pristine
clean and what happens is they go to
warehouses and when they get shipped out
they could come with this temporary
smell from the warehouse that they were
shipped from like Amazon or somewhere
else
so
um here's a comment mine was torn then
what you do is you tell wherever you got
that book from because it wasn't torn
originally so if your cover was injured
or torn or anything get a new book for
free tell them it was torn or your cover
was torn
and then but if they come dirty you can
clean them in the whole bit
so you know I everybody has their Free
Will out there all these big warehouses
all these companies and you know
that's just what they do anyway you guys
incredible having this moment with you
guys and I hope to talk to you soon