we're talking about the power
of leafy greens
leafy greens
not iceberg lettuce
not
you know lettuce that's pale iceberg
lettuce this is not leafy greens right
and the power of herbal leafy greens i
mean you could do so much with leafy
greens it's not even funny you can make
leafy green salads
you can do that you can make
other things like that i got a leafy
green salad also somewhere around here
and i'm going to show you guys in just a
minute
hey you guys we're on right now we're
talking about the power leafy greens i i
recommend you stick around for the show
because
this
can really help because you might say
hey
i'm going to eat a little bit more green
i'm going to have a little bit more of
that leafy green
i want to make sure that my bones don't
dissolve
as the years go by i want to avoid
osteoporosis i want to avoid osteopenia
i want to avoid
spinal stenosis
i want to avoid degenerative discs
in my neck
thoracic
lumbar
i want to make sure that that's not
dissolving
on me as i'm living my life as i'm
drinking my caffeine
and eating my nutritional yeast which is
so acidic
and doing my kombucha tea which is so
acidic
having all my vinegar which is so acidic
my teeth are dissolving as the years go
by my bones are
caving in and nobody knows until i slip
when i'm 54 years old or 55 years old
and i slip and i crack my head
on the cement and the doctor says you
shouldn't have been able to crack your
head open but you did
because the bones start to dissolve
inside out
and so if you want to talk about
alkalinity my god
every single hack out there thinks they
know about alkalinity you've got the
alkaline alkalinity alkaline
leafy greens critical celery juice is
critical these are the things that are
so important mary says acidic okay you
guys we're live on tick tock live on
telegram you guys
we're live on rumble live on youtube
live on facebook i think we are so we're
here
and you guys i just want to let you know
that's the m900 hds
just so you know
90 off
unbelievable
and it's the money saver it's the
medicine maker
it's the medicine machine
it's the medical device it's medical
equipment
you know when you buy a juicer even if
you buy juicer it's not this one
then this one saves money it squeezes
more juice out of everything i know how
i told you guys that
how incredible that is even if you have
a juicer any kind of juicer even if you
get another juicer you're buying a
medicine maker you're buying a piece of
medical equipment because when you're
juicing for yourself
you can bring back years of damage
years of damage
it
fast tracks you and of course when you
run celery through there herbal medicine
it fast tracks you big time just so you
know okay
and so the juicer is the mm-900 hds
the link is in the bio on tiktok just so
you know
but yeah fast tracks you guys that's the
whole point so what i'm gonna do what i
never showed you about the mm-900 hds is
that i juice leafy greens in it i never
talk about it because everybody's like
celery celery celery
aw salary sellers celery i got celery
questions i got celery questions and i'm
like okay okay okay
let's talk about juicing a little bit of
kale
parsley it's talking about juicing a
little bit of cilantro fast tracking
those leafy greens
yeah christina says best juicer ever it
is it is by far it is it's incredible so
you guys so we're talking about leafy
greens we're talking about making sure
that you restore
something back into your teeth
your teeth
i'm just saying right which you won't
see with me you won't see veneers on me
there's nothing wrong with veneers you
won't see veneers on me you won't see
implants on me i got every one of my
teeth okay you don't see i don't have a
bunch of fillings everywhere okay
you don't see
any of that
with
my teeth i have all my teeth still and i
know people they're like in their 30s
and their teeth are just they're just
got so many fillings and they got root
canals and everybody's got root canals
and implants and i talk about that with
the podcast doctors that seem to know so
much about telomeres you're like we're
going to talk about telomeres telomeres
and dna um
yes this is how it works you can live
forever if you just crack the telomeres
science understands telomeres these days
oh my teeth
oh yeah no my dentist has just put up
two more three more implants in there oh
i'm gonna do my podcast now wait a
minute i have a bridge back here oh yeah
but i'm gonna talk about dna and
telomeres uh living longevity longevity
let me come out with another longevity
book oh wait a minute here oh no i had
the two root canals and i have a couple
crowns i have a few crowns here and a
few fillings here but let me talk about
longevity and dna so telomeres i can
give you five tips on how to strengthen
your telomeres
listen to you guys
we don't fool around
[Music]
we don't fool around here
we're about like the real stuff
you know and you might be somebody that
doesn't know medical media information
maybe you're somebody you just hopped on
tick tock or telegram you're like who is
this guy
who is this jackass who is this guy
sitting here right
he's not a doctor
right who is this guy
well medical medium book series has
saved millions of lives around the
planet it's the most popular book series
globally worldwide in health
for six and a half years running because
people get their lives back when they
utilize the protocols and the
information right
but what do i know
what do i know i'm just a dummy
but here's the thing
when it comes down to like serious stuff
like how to keep your teeth
how to keep your bones intact
how to not bathe your organs in acid do
you guys want your brains to shrink
because your brain will shrink when it
bathes in acids for too many years
that's what will happen your brain will
shrink
when it's bathing in a bowl of acid your
skull becomes like a bowl of acid more
kombucha tea
more vinegar do vinegar shots let me do
my apple cider gummies more
more caffeine
did i say that one already more kombucha
tea
say that one already probably point is
is that all these things we do make us
really acidic and then our diets are
really acidic they are
and so we basically bathe in assets and
we we're not putting anything back in
we're not putting anything back in we're
not nothing's going back in here
because you know why
stress
everything you're going through
everything we're up against
pollution falling out of the sky
crap falling out of the sky if you
listen to medical mean podcast at apple
podcast all these things
starts to eat away at us and our diet
isn't picking up the pieces it's not
picking up the slack
and then
exactly
you hear all the great health advisors
and health professionals in the circuit
out there and on the podcast and
everything
yeah caffeine green tea is good for you
top five things that are so good for you
green tea can sink you tell that to
somebody who's lying in bed dying with
chronic illness and and
they're on mattress island they're
suffering for 10 years they got the
worst problems they got vertigo and they
got tingles and numbness in their body
they got they can't they have serious
fatigue they got lupus and fibromyalgia
neurological line five tips that can
help you maybe that person laying in bed
with neurological lyme just needs my
green tea supplement
maybe on my podcast i'm dr jones show
and i have a green tea supplement just
for you
i've studied telomeres and green tea and
did you know that there's scientific
studies that say green tea are really
good for you and it's the green tea
are you on mattress island i've never
heard that term before what is that oh
it must be a medical medium term where
all the original information comes from
anyway but ho mattress island
you just need my green tea supplement
and my collagen supplement five best
supplements there are to buy collagen to
make sure your skin looks good like mine
even though i had two face lifts let's
see
here's another great one too try my
try my oh try my colostrum product yes
squeeze colostrum out of a bait it's
just a baby calf can't have colostrum
and then give it to people to eat and
that will help your telomeres let's see
what else we can do for you
when you really think about it it's
psycho that's what's happening in the
health movement today and that's why i'm
here to make sure people at least have a
fighting chance it's not because i'm
smart because i'm not smart
i'm not i don't have a college degree
i've said that a billion times my whole
life
i don't have i never went to college
right
right i said all those things but when i
was four years old i heard a voice
perfectly clear you guys know the story
and since then people have had their
lives saved on a level no one's ever
seen before and it's not because i'm a
great guy it's not you don't have to
like me you you don't have to like the
way i look
you can have to see that i don't have
perfect teeth because i don't have all
these perfect straight veneers and
everything else you can whatever
but just know that the information is
here to help you michelle l said i heard
it all okay you guys were talking about
the power of leafy greens we're live on
tick tock we're live on telegram i'm
honored you guys are here truly just
know that
just know that you know
you know the whole bit right
you know for people asking me on tick
tock about this because i'm seeing a lot
of stuff come up on tick tock
this is the mm-900 hds right it's at
omega juicers.com
it's 90
off it's a medical device is what i call
it the link is in the bio and the link
is in the description on on on rumble
and on on facebook and on youtube okay
it's 90 off sorry it's 90 off excuse me
90 off
20 20 25 off 90 off
and you'll see the discount when you
check out at the counter when you check
out it omega juicers.com and you check
out it's the mm-900 hds if you buy
another juicer there you're not going to
be able to do what you're going to
witness here
okay you're not going to be able to
juice celery and squeeze all the last
juices out of it you're not going to be
able to squeeze the last juice out of
kale you're not going to be able to
squeeze the last juice out of parsley
you're not going to be able to do it and
no other juicer can do it either so
let's start juicing
all right
tara tara horn says you are saving
lives
i'm honored truly honored
megan says thank you aw you are a
blessing and saving lives after 20 years
of suffering your ebv and strep oh my
god your poor thing
alex says that juicer is amazing
it saved me so much produce it does it
does had it for three days now i wish
i'd bought it sooner you know what's
crazy
i've had this for two years now right
what's really crazy is someone would get
a what's happening right now i want i'm
gonna shut this off
listen
i healthy it's good to see you right you
finally got it aw my god i'm honored
i gotta let you know something okay
there's juicer companies all the juicer
companies are upset right now
they're upset because of this remarkable
piece of equipment right and so they're
all fighting for their their they're
fighting for their corporate survival
i'm just you don't hear this stuff i
just want to i you know what i've always
done i've always just been straight up
about everything with you guys
all of it all of it right
and so with juicer companies are doing
now is they're paying trolls
to go on the medical medium feeds
that never bought the juicer never had
the juicer
to try to like confuse people left and
right right now
and it's a trick that corporate
corporate's actually doing
so just know i've had this for two years
i can't tell you how much money i've
saved how many times the juicer paid for
itself and if you have any problems with
the juicer call the company
get in touch with them make got great
customer service right now
omega juicers.com you can talk to them
and be like hey my green grommet went
down the disposal garbage disposal hey
you know i don't think my part is
working good you talk to them and you
get help
and i'm noticing and we're noticing and
we've been we've been actually able to
prove it too we've seen this
we're under attack by a barrage of paid
people and trolls working for corporate
at the other juicer companies to try to
stop the mm-900 from helping people
because it's that sick of a world right
now if they can't keep the mind their
own business it's that sick of a world
jeanette casper you have saved me from
bp have been following your instructions
and all of my problems were corrected i
even got your juicer and it works the
best thank you jeanette incredible you
guys this is the mm 900 hds
linda says i have this juicer it is
great
incredible it's a mm-900 hds if you
don't have it it's something to consider
down the road but it's 90
off right now free shipping at
omegajuicers.com it's the celery model
but it juices other stuff better than
anything else juices
that's what's really cool lorraine says
yes they need to mind their own business
and everybody asks me and here's the
thing you guys
everybody asks me
i can't stop them from asking they're
just going to ask karine says love the
juicer it is the best
i i love it
corinne says that so let's just get this
going so i got it running right now i'm
going to run some stuff don't miss the
sale the sale is on right now with 90
off free shipping that's the whole thing
so i'm gonna run some kale through here
okay
so i got a kale leaf right here and i'm
gonna put it in
right
now
what i love to do is i love to juice
leafy greens and i'll mix a little bit
of celery with it
there's nothing wrong with that because
you can use celery juice to juice with
other things but if you want the benefit
of celery by itself that's another game
but if you want the benefit of leafy
greens by themselves you can put a
celery stick or two in there too but you
get the benefits of the leafy green if
you want the celery by itself you do the
celery by itself right
so i'm running a little kale in here
what i love about the juicer it's quiet
i can juice it five in the morning and i
don't wake up the house
it's just what i love about it anthony
best thing i bought myself deborah said
deborah for bone
we're on this we're on the power of the
leafy greens is what we're talking about
i'm running leafy green through the
juicer
so right now i'm running hail through
the juicer just so you know g culligan
says are you juicing kale yes dinosaur
kale
which is a form of medicine now the
thing about dinosaur kale it's
practically an herb
it should not be listed as just
professors
right it shouldn't be listed as
kale as in just kale it shouldn't be
listed as just a green
yeah i mean that's so gabriella says i
didn't buy it because some videos on
youtube say the juicy's coming out a
little bit warm right
yeah
not mine
all juicers by the way every last one of
them
you know it doesn't come out icy cold
but mine doesn't come out hot my juice
doesn't come out hot it comes out pretty
much the same temperature
so i'm so i'm juicing right now the kale
we're talking about the power of leafy
greens so let's talk about that a little
bit
so
kale
really should be
considered an earth
it should take the herb title
is what it should do
because it has that kind of power
prevention realm good to see you it
depends on the temperature of the
produce you hit it right on the nose you
said it better than i would that's so
true when you do when you do juice you
juice it cold your produce when it's
cold
kat ledoux says this is a cold pressed
juice or not warm at all not cold either
but it doesn't heat it exactly but see
what happens is did you hear what
happened you guys
you hear that and i feel bad someone saw
some youtube videos
people know this juicer is medical
medium connection like this is the
connect this juicer they all know that
the mm-900 is is a medical medium thing
because of the fact that i'm working
with the company for with this juicer
right
and so i get hits everywhere i get
discrimination i get hits on every level
i get attacked on every level i get hate
on every level
because of the fact that i hear a voice
people
just can't handle
that i get my information from above and
it's all unique and original and they
can handle that so they're going to just
hit it in every way they can so i'm
juicing some kale in here
now this is a potent
kale
mixture right here
all right so i ran some kale in here now
here's what i do
leafy greens
come out really they come out really
potent and green and thick when you run
it from a juicer right the pulp is dry
that's what the machine does this
machine keeps it dryer than anything
else out there mariko says i love my
mm-900 hds it keeps it drier than any
other juicer that's what's amazing about
this slavka says love the juice the
mm-900 it's the best so what i'm going
to do is i'm going to run a celery stick
through here
okay
so i ran a celery stick through here
and i'm gonna run one more
do you have the green cap in elizabeth i
have the green cap in definitely because
i'm squeezing every last bit
out of there like every last bit out
there so i'm going to run one more
celery stick in there because i'm making
a potent little green
medicine
green leafy medicine
drink
is what i'm making
erica says don't worry anthony people
are jealous that's really good advice
thank you thank you
bless your heart
you guys you guys help me out you really
do and i love you for it because i know
you guys care and that just knowing you
care just
this makes me feel like warm and fuzzy
inside
all right
okay so
here we go
i just want to show you one thing right
here which is incredible we're talking
about the powers of leafy greens if you
guys already have a juicer and you say
well oh he's just trying to show us the
juicer let me go just stick around
because we're talking about leafy greens
things you need to know why it's
critical i was talking about the acidity
in the body i also want to talk about
antioxidants because leafy greens have a
really high level of antioxidants and i
want to talk about oxidation and how we
slowly oxidize
and that's important to know so the pulp
is dry right
that pulp is really dry compared to any
other juicer so
you would have to run double that kale
through there to get what you what you
just see in that tray
you would have to run double the celery
sticks and double the kale to see what's
in that tray right there and this stuff
is dry it's like bone dry in there okay
so i wanted to show you that
so let's do a little bit of a let's
strain this really quick okay
so what i'm doing is
pouring this in here we're making a
really strong leafy green shop
this is two celery sticks right
two celery sticks
and
a bunch of kale a whole bunch of kale in
there right of course i
think i made a mess so i'm just getting
this out getting this in here
and any left over you can let it drip
right back into the container if you
want to but i'm making a very potent
little
leafy green drink for the moment
get that back up here
that's why we're live
nothing better than bloopers pamela why
do you have to strain it after you
juiced it you don't have to strain this
one after you juice this one
you don't have to at all right
but i usually strain because i'm trying
to strain the celery
that's why
okay
and all juices
any juicer you do you got to strain it
every single juice you have to strain
any juicer you have to
so anyway
here we go so this is a really really
potent
kale tonic right there
all right
it's these pa the power of these leafy
greens
that can move us forward denise is
ordering it tonight awesome because
you'll make the sale the sale is going
to be running for a little while so i
think it's running even past tonight i
think it's going
easy for the next three days or four
days or something like that but good
thing you're ordering
and you're gonna you'll see that you'll
see the discount in the checkout the 90
discount the link is in the bio on tick
tock and it's in the description here
okay
to move our health forward fast
you need the antioxidants
you need something called phytochemical
compounds
chlorophyll does not work
by itself
chlorophyll has to be with every other
chemical compound
if you buy a chlorophyll supplement and
do the green drops in the water you are
never going to get any chlorophyll that
works the body will pee it out or you'll
just go to bathroom and eliminate it out
chlorophyll cannot be separated from the
rest of the properties in the green
i you guys are going to repeat myself
chlorophyll cannot be separated and work
if it's separated from the rest of the
phytochemical compounds from the leafy
greens it's empty and does not work by
itself chlorophyll supplements are one
of the biggest scams in snake oil and
everything else you want to call it out
there
and anytime you see somebody playing
around with chlorophyll as if they're
doing something for themselves and
trying to sell chlorophyll prop stuff it
never helped anyone in the past it never
will it doesn't make you alkaline it
can't neutralize acids it can't turn
your life around chlorophyll on its own
cannot work this is really important to
know if you only take that nugget here
and that's it
you're helping yourself so you don't
fall into the chlorophyll trap it's the
chlorophyll trap out there
keep that in mind if
if it's the only thing you take so when
you when you see out there somebody like
tom i'm doctor sean susha i'm doctors
intro i'm doctor
and i have to tell you about this
chlorophyll supplement we have it's a
great chlorophyll supplement and it's
made me rich i have a mansion because of
it in a yacht
oh all the instagram influencers are
using chlorophyll now because of me top
five ways to get yourself better make
sure you do your chlorophyll drops if
you get suckered into that
you're being screwed over
chlorophyll can only stay intact and
actually work if the phytochemical
compounds and the antioxidants and the
polyphenols and everything else is
connected with it if it's all connected
in the same spot where it came from it
can't be separated into a supplement
where you remove the chlorophyll
leafy greens
megan you're laughing leafy greens
plus the chlorophyll supplements they
add natural flavor citric acid and
alcohol and a terrible glycerin too
right
leafy greens have antioxidants them to
turn your life around
that's a type of antioxidant that's not
registered on the scale of research in
science and what they're doing with food
science food science hasn't picked up a
fraction of what's in a leafy green
they're not even studying leafy greens
and what's in there
so it's important to know why does
juicer why does the juicer parsley turn
into gel that's not that's
actually partially does that in any
juicer
because parsley has chemical compounds
okay
that dry really quick parsley juice
dries
exceptionally fast when it's juiced it's
instantly drying
because what it what it has is an
alkaloid in parsley that reverses the
minute you juice it it's reversing the
process not the juicing process but what
it's doing is the plant has protective
measures so when a deer comes along and
eats it so this is important to know
okay all right this is really important
now
this is probably one of the most
important things you can learn about
parsley by the way
okay so what's happening is when a deer
comes along parsley's a wild food
it's actually a wild food it's not
growing wild anymore where you where
they're picking it and putting in the
supermarket they're growing it for you
parsley is a leafy green which is an
herb and i call herb leafy green is so
powerful and so strong
because it's wild
that when a deer comes along
and goes into somebody's garden
right
hey i really like that parsley let me
have some of that
the parsley quickly sends an alkaloid to
the injured area of the plant to seal up
the juices to stop the juices from
running
isn't that incredible when you juice
parsley that phytochemical compound that
alkaloid is trying to try to literally
stop the juice from occurring it's
trying to harden the juice
so your juice is becoming gel when it's
parsley this this this is incredible
information it's it's medical medium
information it's not out there
because i don't use anybody's
information never have never will it's
all medical media and that's why
everybody gets better who's applying it
and everything else as they're going you
know using the information and changing
their lives
that's why nobody knew what celery juice
did ever yeah celery grew before i was
alive
yeah the 1800s they grew it yeah people
ate it in their crew today and they've
chopped it up and threw it in their tuna
salads but nobody knew how to use it
therapeutically and what it did for
anybody that's medical medium info
but anyway the whole point is parsley
has that phytochemical compound to stop
it
from bleeding
and so when you juice parsley you see it
gel quick
is what happens
so that's something that we should
that's good that we covered right now
okay
so
all right back
back to work
we're here you guys
all right so let's talk about this a
little bit
what you have in here
okay
is the skull thickener
basically what you're doing is you're
putting back
calcium nutrients other other other
chemical compounds
back into the bones because you're
neutralizing the acids inside the body
so you neutralize your acids inside the
body that's how you really do it not
from a fraudulent alkaline ionizer water
machine which poisons you
i can't tell you how many attacks i get
how many fake crap and fake stories and
fake all kinds of garbage and everything
else always gets propelled
by somebody behind the scenes that's
selling alkaline ionizer water machines
every time medical medium is under a new
attack
a new form of evil
it's always because the person who
started it we always find out it goes
right back to the alkaline ionizer water
crew
that's what we always find out
when we start doing our research
every fake story fake jab fake hit piece
fake everything every attack you trace
it back to the alkaline ionizer water
crew how come isn't that interesting
because i've told everybody something
very important the alkaline ionizer
water machines do not make you alkaline
they poison you with toxic heavy metals
from electricity hitting the metal
plates inside no matter what brand it is
and you know what bring it on man bring
it on so anyway the point is that makes
you alkaline right there
and that alkaline
alkalinity is critical to saving your
bones your teeth and everything
is wheatgrass juice a healing food yes
yes plung yes it is in fact you can run
your wheatgrass through this juicer
because i do i run wheatgrass for this
juicer too absolutely wheatgrass is
amazing
love wheatgrass
love it love it love it all right you
guys let's let's do something else at
the juicer we're having some fun this is
a kale tonic right here which is
absolutely incredible
let's run a little parsley through it
too
so many juicers out there have metal
gears
metal gears that go like this
and by the way some of those hit stories
those hit pieces on me too we find out
they come from the apple cider
corporations
we find out they come from the caffeine
industry
all the hits on medical media we trace
them back to the caffeine industry we
trace back the apple cider companies
kombucha tea companies that pay all
their people to try to take out medical
media
it's amazing anyway and the juicer
companies now are starting to do like
they're starting to like pay all their
trolls to say oh the mm-900 sucks oh it
sucks oh it does
it's only paid for itself about 20 times
already for me
anyway the metal gears in these juicers
and that's another reason why the juicer
companies hate me because they all many
of them are using metal gear so that
this is the the cold pressed juicers are
using metal gears the metal gears do
this
and you know what happens here's a gear
here's a gear there's the two gears you
ready you turn on the machine cranking
means
okay that's really smart what is that
that's metal on metal that's like your
car breaks when you lose your car brakes
and the rotors being hit by a metal
brake pad and you're like screeching
down the road going
that's real smart and then when you take
your car into the mechanic the mechanic
has to blow off all that brake metal
dust and say you need new rotors sir
you need new rotors man so there's
that's that so when you get the juicers
that have the metal gears going like
this it wears and tears and guess what
i've seen that i purchased those juicers
i've used them and i saw the wear and
tear on the metal gears
and was like oh that's metal going
in me
that's particles of metal going into me
oh that's real smart
that's why i like this juicer
all right let's have some fun
just a little bit more
i'm gonna juice a little bit of ginger
so i'm gonna take i have two of these
right because every time i lend out my
juicer i never get it back so i happen
to have another one but i don't want to
like waste time cleaning this even
though it's only a four minute process
what i'm gonna do is
pop on another one really quick and
juice a little bit of ginger
so let's do that
so i'm gonna make a ginger turmeric shot
right
i don't know if you guys are excited
about that but i'm gonna do a little
ginger tumeric shot
you guys i was just live on amazon so
even though this was a leafy this is a
leafy green show we're doing the power
of leafy greens right
i still have cucumbers here and i got
like zucchinis and i got sweet potatoes
right here
and i just gobbled down half my stew
so i just i just made on amazon live
this incredible stew right here but i
gobbled it down in between
and says my old juicer with the metal
gears had magnet at the bottom of the
juice collection container now this
makes sense
dear lord that's the scariest thing i've
ever heard
that's some scary stuff
yeah it had a magnet at the bottom
exactly
see and meanwhile those fairy companies
are throwing people on my feet
everywhere commenting like oh the mm-900
sucks
and they're paid by these juicer
companies it's like is there any like
integrity left man
whatever
all right let's go let's do some let's
go some ginger and turmeric
the thing is like this look
i like
you know
i like making sure everything
is just up front
and and just straight out
if the juicer has metal gears it's got
metal gears it's an ionizer water
machine it's got metal plates and it's
leaching toxic heavy metal corroded
metals gotta be straight out about it
i mean it just is what it is
all right so what i'm doing you guys
is i'm going to juice a little bit of
ginger and turmeric
right
now what i do is i do ginger turmeric
celery shots is what i like
jenmorland says the mm900 is the best
hope is the driest i have ever seen
it really is incredible
wild green you met w green you missed
dang i missed amazon
well you can watch the replay go to
amazon live and follow so you can watch
the shows and when i'm doing them live
it's really important you know to catch
them live sometimes for fun link is in
the description about the amazon live
show you know and in the bio t1 tick
tock you guys
so how many of you guys run ginger
through your juicers how many of you
guys run turmeric through your juicers
right how do we clean turmeric stains
now
turmeric stains are never any fun i use
bon ami but it's never any fun it just
isn't
you know
so what i'm going to do is i'm going to
run a little bit of this let me get my
cap back on because i i actually
put it over here
so i want to show you something about
this cache
why do you have to change the attachment
to make the shot i don't actually have
to i want the shot to see i just ran
really dark rich
leafy greens in here
so pia what happened was but i want to
make a turmeric ginger shot
and i want to see the the turmeric color
and you're not going to see the turmeric
color from the turmeric ginger shot
because i would have to clean the unit
and spend like three four minutes
cleaning the unit i don't want to waste
your guys time
so that's all so i just i put another i
put another unit on here so i didn't
have to do that it's just that that
leafy green that's gonna you won't see
the turmeric ginger shot it'll just look
like that
it'll look like this you won't be able
to see it so i want you to be able to
see it if you make a ginger turmeric
shot you know one day it's just that i'm
trying to do a bunch of things at once
that's why
so i'm cutting some ginger here now the
thing is with ginger
okay it's really strong you don't need a
lot
that's for sure that ginger is that
ginger bites you know the one thing
about ginger that i've always found is
it it's sometimes it's hotter than
cayenne to me
for me which is really i mean i i
haven't heard that too often but
sometimes ginger can be so
so spicy right
so you want to sip it probably over time
and not go
throw it down right
so i'm going to do that and i got some
turmeric over here too
okay now turmeric i peel the skin
right if you're interested in the um
kelly warring says you can only see the
most recent amazon live you can't see
any previous ones disappointing i missed
the guacamole one and wanted to see the
replay you can go see it go see the link
so kelly go to the link in the
description
and you can see all the previous lives
go to link in the in the description
make sure you follow me but you can see
the link in the description and see all
the previous lives on there what i do is
i like to peel the turmeric i take the
skin off of tumeric
this is a rhizome that's really potent
turmeric right
but you want to get the skin off you
don't have to get the skin off you can
keep it with the skin on
but the skin's got a really potent
potent um
chemical compound in the alkaloid family
that makes it
not as tasty
you can keep the skin on i like to take
the skin off there's nothing wrong with
peeling back the skin
on on that
that tumeric okay
now i leave the skin on the ginger and
you can peel back the ginger skin too
you don't have to keep that on there too
but i do keep it on a lot of times all
right so what i'm doing is
i'm gonna run
this in
here okay
so i got the juicer on
i'm gonna put turmeric through here
i'm gonna put some ginger pieces in here
that's just pouring out nicely
i know you guys might not be able to see
nice piece of turmeric i'm running some
ginger through here
this is a celery juicer model but it
juices other things better than any
juicer out there now i run a celery
stick through here is what i do okay now
run a celery stick through you can drink
it straight just like that the juice is
in here you can make a shot just like
that i tend to run
like a celery stick through here
the way i like it
okay
you can run one
you can run two
i'm gonna go with one it really did the
job
now you can put orange in there too
so i got a nice orange here
so i'm gonna do is is
peel this orange
and throw that in there
i gotta show you some of the orange tips
that i can show you on the amazon live
you guys the amazon live medical medium
cooking show is so cool i'm showing all
these tips i don't i don't show anywhere
else because i'm doing other things like
i am here so it's great to catch me on
all the different platforms
if you can you know
selena simon says after doing two weeks
of the mono eating cleanse which is one
of my favorite cleanses the mono eating
cleanse my taste buds have changed so
much already i wasn't a big fan of figs
and today i had some dried ones and they
taste it like candy and croissants to me
that's actually incredible
you know why man when you clean up you
heighten the senses and then you can
your senses get heightened with
everything and you experience life in a
different way that's an incredible
cleanse if you guys don't know that
cleanse right here you gotta pick up
cleanse the heel amazon.com right now
okay it's 51
off or go to the library get it for free
but that book is so good with that
information in there
okay so i got an orange right here i'm
just sectioning the orange i'll show you
guys so we're making some different
juices if you just got on here we're
using the mm-900 hds 90 off
it pays for itself
it's an incredible juicer
i ran one celery stick
and now i'm running some orange in here
right i had a nice piece of turmeric
there we go
now just so you know the turmeric is
coming out like powder it comes out that
dry with this machine
this is so cool
this is just so cool
i want to show you guys this okay
that's like powder coming out you see
that
look at that
look at this
bone dry
that's bone dry
i'm still using the green grommet
absolutely
because i'm squeezing every last drop
out of my produce that's how incredible
this machine is
look at that
it juices better than any of the other
juicers out there
and that's what's incredible about the
mm-900 now you guys know why i backed
this thing now you guys know why i
endorsed it because that's what i did i
endorsed it i worked with a company
endorsed it said i'll endorse it i'll
endorse the crap out of that thing i
love it so much
and that's what i do that's why i
endorse it that came out bone dry that's
the tumeric bone dry
when you can squeeze everything out of
turmeric look at this when you can
squeeze everything out of turmeric
you know you're saving money
you know you're saving money and there's
no metal in there
there's no metal particles
from those centric centrifuge juicers
all that metal in there
and then
then the grind the other ones that have
the gears
i get it and the companies get mad at me
and so they'll still send out another 20
hit men
out out on the internet to try to like
stop this stop him
stop him from telling the truth stop the
guy he's ruining the juicer business out
there
we never we never thought of how to do
it so we're just totally we we but we
can't fix it now
stop him
and that's what's incredible right there
it's it's like sand it's like now dry
sand at this point you guys
i mean right
the best juicer at the price point is
what i'm saying too like the price point
ninety dollars off
free shipping you see it in the checkout
when you check out the megajuicers.com
link is there megajuicers.com it's the
celery model mm-900 hds you wanna so i
want an mm900 to juice greens with
johanna says
it's really great it's really great okay
so here's a turmeric shot right here i'm
mixing it up
so we're gonna talk about teeth for a
minute
two
got a little
when you juice
leafy greens with your mm-900
you're putting back into your teeth for
the future is what you're doing so you
can save your teeth for down the road
now i strain it you don't have to strain
this one you definitely don't have to
strain this one okay
i strain it but you don't have to
right
just so you know
and it's look it's still there's still
some dripping in there and i'm gonna use
every last bit of that which is
incredible
so right here you have a gingeric ginger
gingeric
turmeric and ginger put together you got
a gingerix shot
can you freeze them in ice cube trays
yeah you can do that that's fine
right
that's it right there
it came out bone it was coming out bone
dry like dry powder
i mean right
you guys i'm just excited about it
because
it's a medical device
right
it's like i would rather be on this
thing
rather be on this thing than
you know like
[Music]
beep
beep nurse
mersey have all my medical devices in me
there's moose
nurse
beep
there's a beep does it machine beeper
say nurse when it beeps
okay you guys
the next live i'm gonna do eventually
right here on youtube and and um
rumble and facebook and all that i'll
show you how to clean this machine i'm
not gonna do that one today
but yeah it's a medical device so let's
talk about leafy greens for a couple of
minutes
because that's important
so
i want to show you something here
you guys i basically just ate a whole
stew in between these lives like right
after the amazon live show i eat a whole
stew basically like a big old stew i
cooked i ate a whole stew right and i
don't feel bogged down i don't feel like
i need to go to bed
because it didn't have anything bad in
it i didn't even feel like i need to go
to bed anyway that's a salad right you
see some kale chopped on there but you
see underneath there you've got you got
parsley
chopped up in that leafy green salad you
got cilantro chopped up in that leafy
green
salad so good so good you guys
right i bet you this piggy would love
that leafy green salad i bet you this
cow would love that leafy green salad
right
so we'll talk about teeth for a little
bit which is really important
all right i'm getting reminded over here
uh by my crew to try to keep it together
cold light springs some juice companies
are doing some kind of
magnetic stuff now
they talk about i ionizing that is scary
as hell
that's when mistakes are made all the
time may that's when mistakes are made
all the time
all the time it's so sad so here's the
thing about leafy greens you guys leafy
greens is a chance to reverse teeth
damage it's a chance to get teeth back
on track to slow the progression of
teeth from falling apart inside and out
it's a chance to neutralize acids leafy
greens are a chance to get antioxidants
to help you really heal
leafy greens help stop your brain from
atrophying it helps to stop your brain
from atrophying i got a phone call i got
a
i got a phone call coming in it stops
your brain from shrinking and that's
important to know
like you know because
everybody's on brain shrinkers
that's what they are
they're all on brain shrinkers
that's what people do they're on brain
shrinkers
i'm
doctors
hello
yes
i have an apple cider vinegar line i
have a green tea line a kombucha t-line
a collagen line
i have other lines too
yes
that's the brain-shrinking line
oh not supposed to say that
yes
uh-huh
how much have i made this month
i made two point how much
i made 10.5 million dollars this month
how much advertising did we do
we did two million dollars of
advertising this month
we advertised all those suckers
yeah
i'm doctor yeah
[Music]
i'm just racist guys
i'm doctor
i'm not just just anything
huh
yeah
two million dollars in advertising to
all the suckers out there
yes
how many people bought my collagen which
shrinks the brain
uh-huh
how many people
how many people bought all my green tea
supplement extracts
yes
i told them they would live forever
hello
okay i gotta go
the leafy greens is a whole entire other
experience
it's an entire entirely different
situation for getting your life back
it's a part of it you you have to have
the leafy greens they have to be in
there because
if they're not
things go wrong
you don't have to eat a lot of them if
you don't want to but we have to start
bringing in the spinach we have to start
bringing in the different things okay
we have to start bringing in the stuff
we have to start bringing in the parsley
we have to start bringing the cilantro
the mache let's bring in the mosh
to bring in the mosh
right you know mosh is that green
is it kind of buttery i'm not talking
about a mosh pit i don't mean a mosh pit
at a concert i'm talking about mosh the
green the green
spirit of compassion said that somebody
thought i was talking about like the
mosh pit at a concert
it's about using these herbs leafy green
herbs
so important it's the leafy green herbs
ashley kevin says you're such a good
dancer who are you talking to
ashley are you talking to this guy here
can't be talking about me
you guys i don't have any moves are you
kidding
i have no moves you can tell me dance
and i'll be like
i could only do the robot
it's all i could do is the robot that's
it
so you guys
i'm heading off to instagram
that's where i'm going i'm going to turn
tick-tock back on i'm going to turn
instagram back on i'm going to turn
well i'm going to turn instagram on i'm
going to turn telegram back on
okay you guys
exactly so i can't wait you guys i'm
looking forward to it we're going to be
live in about 15 minutes 10 15 minutes i
hope to see you soon i'm just gonna
straighten up
love you guys much okay