of propolis pure right here talking
about the powers cat's claw the power of
total immune why the immune system needs
to stay strong how critical that is you
hear somebody that's told they're
autoimmune what's going on there their
immune systems compromised their immune
system is breaking down something is
wrong with their immune system bottom
line people sick all the time then you
hear about longevity right why is
everybody so interested about longevity
how come they're interested in that so
much they weren't years and years ago
did you know that people just lived did
you know they just lived no one was
worried about longevity years ago they
just lived you lived your life and that
was it right now but everybody is
freaking out about longevity now you
know why everybody's sick everybody's
sick and people are dying left and right
so people are like oh crap I better pull
it together let me check out longevity
let me figure out this longevity thing
because I just watch family members go
down I just watch friends go down
strokes this that heart problems
sickness all kinds of different things
going on cancer whatever it is I'm
watching friends go left and right
family members that's what people are
saying every day out there right now I
talk to people and they're like oh my
God my friend went my this this person
went my family member that's happening
out there and everybody's like longevity
longevity because everybody's freaking
out like what is going on people are
sick but years ago people weren't
talking about longevity do you know that
you just lived your life you lived your
life and if you got sick later on or
something happened then okay right but
now people are just freaking out anyway
talking about the immune system what I
what I have right here is the vimergy
propolis pure that's an experience if
you ever ever have an opportunity to
have that bottle in your hand and to
actually taste it and use it you'll
you'll feel the frequency it's unmatched
it's unbelievable the frequency that's
in there the living corsin that's
actually in there so living corsin is in
the propolis pure and this is the vimer
propolis pure okay if you don't know the
company it's V as and Victor i m as in
Mary e r g why and you guys know I
endorse these guys and it's for a reason
because there's nothing like it out
there when it comes down to immune
system if if I'm if I just go oh
whatever don't even bother telling
people anymore don't even whatever
people get sick out there then that is
just that is wrong I have to fight for
it I have to tell people what can help
them I have to tell them look this is
what's going on with your immune system
you need a maintenance you need a
maintenance plan of some kind that's
critical because in the end people are
just getting sick they got symptoms and
there's a reason and guess what it's
because their immune system is breaking
down it's because their immune system is
falling apart yes let's be honest let's
be straight out with it let's call it
like it is if someone's sick their
immune system system is not functioning
properly it was compromised to such a
degree that it can't do its job
compromised so it actually can't do its
job think about that for a minute right
there if we're walking around sick and
we got aches and pains and Tinkles and
numbness and our jaw hurts and our neck
hurts and our head hurts and we have
migraines and we have restless leg
syndrome and planter fasciitis and
problems with our feet we got fungus all
over our
feet yeah immune system you got toenail
fungus immune system you got fingernail
fungus immune system you got anything
like that going on immune system if you
had Lyme disease if you have this if you
have that condition this condition
fibromyalgia ra whatever it is
autoimmune a thyroid problem of some
kind hypothyroidism immune system
hyperthyroidism immune system
Graves and that's what happens and
people don't realize it cysts nodules
tumors whatever that's happening inside
our body calcification throughout our
body kidney weak weaknesses adrenal
problems all immune system based think
about that for a minute right there okay
and if we don't call it like it is and
if we play footsies with it because
that's what's happening out there I see
it every day out there you see all these
people out there these coaches and these
practitioners and all these gurus out
there and they're all playing footsies
with people yeah you can have longevity
just go and take this and do this oh you
can have this but nobody's calling it
like it it is and saying the immune
system is compromised in this world in
people's Health the immune system is
actually falling apart that's why people
are having autoimmune in all these
different symptoms and conditions and if
we don't address the immune system if we
don't want to know what's bothering our
immune system that's one thing and we're
going to cover that and that's what
we're talking about today if we don't
want to know what's bothering our immune
system which is antagonizing our immune
system we actually have to at least know
how to protect our immune system or keep
it strong and help rebuild it if we want
to be in the dark about what's causing
our immune system problems it's one
thing we have to at least not be in the
dark and actually support our immune
system and do what we need to do so
right here in front of me I got the
propolis pure right there okay I was
telling you guys yesterday about mouth
ulcers oral health so many people are
obviously into oral health they're
worried about their mouth they're
worried about their teeth and their gums
they're worried about their tongue yeah
their tongue there's people out there
and they're scraping their tongue and
they're doing all this on their tongue
and they got sores on their tongue that
they don't understand they feel
something in the roof of their mouth and
they're playing with their tongue all
the time because and they're feeling
teeth and they're feeling their gums and
like what's wrong here what's wrong
there they go to the dentist they go to
the doctor they're looking at their
mouth and then they're checking their
stools and checking everything else
they're like well I don't know if you
got thrush or this or mouth ulcers or or
canker saurs people with oral health
they're swishing around coconut oil as
if that's going to do anything and I
talked about that and I've written about
that in the medical medium books where
it doesn't do anything and now people
are actually poaching that info and
they're like yeah bacteria is on their
teeth and gums and coating it with
coconut oil doesn't stop the bacteria
from eating away the teeth and gums
medical medium
information the point is with propolis
pure it's for oral health big part of
your immune system is your mouth it's
your mouth that's a big part of your
immune system and so that's why propolis
is so critical I just saw somebody it's
viy vimergy.com V is in Victor i m is in
Mary E RG y so that's propolis pure I'll
talking about that and probably we'll
talk more about it and then you got the
cats claw which we can go into so let's
let's get into our immune system a
little bit I want to do a little bit
more of the bloodstream right here okay
you guys little bit more of the
bloodstream
all right there it is your
bloodstream okay right and in your
bloodstream okay you have your blood
there it
is inside your
bloodstream all right your bloodstreams
moving you got immune cells you got
immune cells in here in your
bloodstream these immune cells travel
with your blood many of them swim up
stream that's right many of them swim
upstream a lot of immune cells have the
ability to swim isn't that interesting
they can travel on their own Propel
themselves on their own now in order to
stay healthy throughout your life it's
more than just hey you know uh let me
support my immune system it's more than
that it's also understanding what your
immune system is even doing because you
need to connect to it critical to
connect to your immune cells and so
knowing that your immune cells sit
inside your bloodstream and they swim
Downstream on the river in the river and
some of them swim upstream against the
current okay so I want to show you what
happens so this is going this is going
right that's your that's your direction
that's your stream I'm just going to
show you right here it's going this way
check this out this is really
interesting okay you got immune cells
right
here and in your bloodstream you got
immune cells that are traveling with
your blood and they're going this way
they're going in this direction okay but
then you have immune cells that are
going the opposite direction why would
they do that why would immune Cells Go
the opposite direction you ready for
this they're going the opposite
direction because they're looking out
for
Invaders they're looking out for
Invaders so your immune cells many of
them will swim the opposite direction
look at this you see the arrow going the
opposite direction you guys your
bloodstreams going this
direction you got immune cells that are
actually going the opposite direction
interesting they have power strength
they can do that and they usually do
that by do walking the lining of your
veins and arteries see this now what
happens is the reason why they go the
other direction is because they're
trying to stop something and catch
something you
ready they're trying to catch something
they're trying to catch an
Invader okay that's right viruses and
any bacteria here it is you got the
viruses coming through and the bacteria
look at this okay check that out
pathogens they're trying to stop
pathogens the Invaders so your immune
Cells Go go
backwards they actually go backwards
because they need to it's critical that
they try to stop the Invaders when
they're actually swimming Upstream when
they're swimming sorry Downstream with
your bloodstream like that Invaders like
to go with the stream of your blood they
like to travel with the stream of your
blood that's how the Epstein bar the
hhv6 the ceglar virus the herpes simplex
one herpes simplex 2 the shingles all
the HHS that are undiscovered HH uh V10
through 16 right that medical be
information talks about and all the
different variations the 100 varieties
of EPC bar because the varieties are
expanding every single day it's not it's
no longer 60 varieties like I've
actually put in the books it's way more
now and it's the same thing with
shingles okay all those bugs and viruses
are partly responsible for why your
immune system is giving up on people and
that's a good point is it giving up is
it not no it's not it's fighting like
hell it's fighting hard so what happens
is your immune cells they walk backwards
because you're trying to stop the
pathogens that are in the bloodstream
the reason why they go backwards is they
battle head on with the pathogen as the
pathogen is coming in head on collision
so that's what they do it's like a car
going down the highway and somebody
getting on the wrong exit and coming
back on the highway and here we go we
got a car coming down at 70 M an hour
and then we got right we got another car
coming up at 70 M an hour totally
confused doesn't know they're on the
wrong side of the highway and then they
crash same thing the immune cells are
actually going Upstream the pathogens
are cruising Downstream and then they
crash that's how it's done the reason
why it's done like that is immune cells
have a difficult time fighting pathogens
while they're all swimming Downstream at
the same time very important to know why
is it important it's part of connecting
to our immune system every little bit we
know strengthens the immune system so
when you fortify it you're not only just
fortifying it with tools like the
propolis pure right propolis and the
Kats claw and the total immune which is
Molen in time you're not just fortifying
your immune cells which we're going to
cover in a minute you're actually
connecting you're you're understanding
what you're immune cells are trying to
accomplish the Consciousness Connection
matters because our immune system can
talk to our Consciousness they can work
together very important
here so as Invaders are going Downstream
like this you got immune cells walking
Upstream to try to crash into them it's
a surprise attack on the Invader The
Invader doesn't expect it as it's
cruising around going down the street it
doesn't expect a surprise attack a car
coming up the highway the wrong way you
don't expect that either if you're on
the highway and a car comes on the exit
the wrong way and and is going up the
highway while you're going down the
highway you're not expecting it and then
boom that's how it works the immune
cells know in your body that the Invader
the Epstein bar yes the shingles the
hhv6 is not expecting a headon
collision that's how how it's done but
in order you're ready for this in order
for your immune cells to have the
strength strength it needs to swim
upstream it needs to be
fed it needs to be supported it's why
it's critical to have a
maintenance critical not just a onetime
thing like I'll take this one year for a
month and that's it or I'll take this
for a week it needs support all the time
a maintenance support so it can keep its
strength up now somebody somebody might
have a weakened immune system so when
pathogens are going Downstream here we
go pathogens are going Downstream right
there they go going
Downstream as they're going Downstream
your immune cells can't walk back they
don't have the strength to actually walk
back they can't do the surprise element
the surprise attack is not easy for them
they can't do the head-on collision and
because they can't do the head-on
collision there you go you break out in
shingles finally in your life you break
out shingles or there you go you have a
non rashing shingles and that non-
rashing shingles is kicking your butt
and you got pain everywhere in your body
and you're hurting all kinds of ways
your tongue your tongue hurts it's
buzzing it's tingling it's numb your
body hurts and that's how it goes or you
got trigeminal neuralgic because your
herpes simplex one is going out of
control and it's getting into the
trigeminal nerve or the shingles virus
is getting into the trigeminal nerve if
we don't do a maintenance and take care
of our immune system you guys what
happens is your immune cells they lose
their strength and they can't do the
head-on collision
backwards they can't they can't do the
surprise element the surprise attack
which is the
pathogen is Flowing Downstream nice and
fast here it is and when a pathogen
flows Downstream get ready for
this it stays
strong when a pathogen like an Epstein
bar virus or any kind of bacteria strep
bacteria when it flows Downstream with
the river of your blood it stays nice
and strong the reason why it stays nice
and strong because it doesn't have to do
anything it's flowing with the river but
your immune cells they have to work hard
and they need strength they need a
maintenance for strength because they
have to go upstream and when the immune
Cells Go Upstream it takes so much
energy and so much strength and they
need that strength so when your Epstein
bar leaves your liver because it's going
for hay mononucleosis again it's going
for hey another another infection low
grade infection it's going again for
another high grade infection your epine
VAR here it goes you've been under
stress all kinds of problems you got
exposure exposure to poisons and toxins
and chemicals or whatever it is and here
it is there goes your epscene bar it's
flowing Downstream guess what it has all
the strength in the world because it
doesn't have to do anything it's flowing
with the stream right and guess what
it's doing it's feeding on all kinds of
poisons and crap and toxins and all
kinds of garbage in your blood and it's
having a field day A Feast while it's
swimming Downstream just relaxing and
flowing Downstream and then your immune
cells right here see these they have to
go the opposite way they have to have
strength they have to have stamina and
they have to go the opposite way to do a
head-on
collision with that virus or that
pathogen so your immune Cells Go
Downstream go upstream and they go
against the current and then they crash
right there with that pathogen and they
need strength and that's why they need a
maintenance because people's immune
systems are breaking down they're
weakened every single day and as they're
weakened and broken down guess what our
immune cells can't go Upstream easy in
fact a lot of people their immune cells
can't go Upstream at all can't even they
don't even have the strength to go
Upstream at all and so if we're not
doing something if we're not feeding our
immune cells and strengthening them and
knocking pathogens down
ourselves we can get in trouble 10
symptoms now we got 20 symptoms yeah
that's right now you got 30 symptoms a
lot of people have 100 symptoms they can
count them they have them they they
actually Journal them I have a pain in
my jaw that just came back again I got a
ringing in my ear that just came back
again I got ringing in both ears that's
another symptom I have I was a little
dizzy the other day that's another
symptom I had a panic attack that's
another symptom they add up real quick
real
quick love and healing says over there
in IG I haven't been sick longer than 2
days because of vimergy supplements in
the last 3 and a half years along with
medical mean and Protocols of course
it's so amazing now I look I give a lot
of credit a lot of credit to a really
high powered good supplement okay I give
a lot of credit to that I do when it's
one that actually works and I know it's
as pure and clean as it is a lot of
credit to it and I've seen that propolis
right here I've seen this perform things
like certain Miracles with people that
are just mindblowing that's what I've
seen okay same thing with the cat's claw
that's another one right there too and
the total immune as well really
Incredible God was with us last night
our home was hit by a tornado storm
sounded like a train coming through our
house so much work to be done but so
thankful and blessed I healed with
medical medium to handle it first of all
look God bless you and I'm so sorry sole
purpose with Sarah I'm so sorry you
actually have gone through that I've
been in some storms I've been in some
hurricanes I've been in a tornado right
not as close as that not as close as
that we I haven't been in one in that
the way you have um Sarah that's that's
terrifying okay I've been in hurricanes
really bad ones and been in the uh the
the Eye of Hur hurricanes but not
tornado have been near tornadoes but
that's scary and and incredible that you
actually have the strength now to power
through that so I'm talking about the
immune system if you guys just got on
here why it's critical for maintenance
and what our immune system does lay over
there on YouTube since I am doing your
protocols I am not sick every month
before my menstration so that that's
interesting BEC that's so powerful what
happens is menstruation knocks the
immune system down naturally because a
woman's immune system has to go to the
reproductive system during menstration
and so it leaves less of an immune
system other places so women get all
kinds of different symptoms before
menstration during menstration and
shortly after they get all kinds of
symptoms they get all kinds of things
that happen and so your immune system
strengthening that means the 20% of your
immune system that is still everywhere
else during your menstration it's
stronger it's stronger than what it used
to be so you actually not getting sick
before menstruation means that the the
part of your immune system that's
handling everything else is actually
stronger than it used to be that's
powerful that's incredible so we're
talking about the bloodstream the
bloodstream flows right the river that
flows okay and in that River all
right pathogens and toxins flow
Downstream that's what they do because
the reason why pathogens flow
Downstream is so the pathogen doesn't
have to use strength and energy keeps
the pathogen nice and strong so the
pathogen flows right
Downstream just like this with the blood
pathogen flows Downstream just like this
with the blood okay it makes it so the
pathogen doesn't have to expel any
energy it makes it so the pathogen
doesn't have to weaken okay immune cell
in order to have the surprise element
and the surprise attack your immune
Cells Go Upstream like I was saying
before the goal surprise attack on the
pathogen slam the pathogen head on and
engulf the pathogen so here's how it
works your immune cells are supposed to
devour a pathogen keep this in mind
there's your immune Cell It's supposed
to engulf a pathogen like eat it up and
devour it so you're immune cell is
supposed to actually engulf the pathogen
so the pathogen is gone right check that
out this is interesting
now guess how guess what helps your
immune cell to engulf a
pathogen headon Collision going Upstream
while the pathogen is going Downstream
you ready for this here's your immune
cell it's going Upstream it needs the
strength to swim upstream here it's
going pathogen is going Downstream boom
as they Li your white blood cell tries
to engulf the pathogen in one shot
swallowing and devouring
it and all that is fine and
dandy if your immune cells have the
strength to do it because they're
supposed to do that so you don't get the
next flare so you don't have a new
flare a flare up that's right so now
you're all flared up
you need the strong immune system the
immune cells need to have that strength
so when they go head on like that they
engulf that immune that that the immune
cell engulfs that pathogen that virus
like the Epstein bar the hhv6 the
shingles C cegal virus
HPV even
HPV hpylori
bacteria
strep other bacteria and engulfs it and
devours it because it goes upstream and
it hits it head on and when it hits it
head on it can swallow it inlf it it can
go right through its membrane into the
immune cell and then it can actually eat
that pathogen and explode it and kill it
but you got to have a maintenance you
got to be doing things to be feeding
your immune cells and keeping them
strong that's what's critical Max vond
over there on YouTube hey how you doing
wow I have a new respect for my immune
cells and that respect is the connection
that's the whole point you got to have
that connection to your immune cells and
know what they're doing so that when you
support it you're supporting it slim
over there on IG I've been on celery
juice nice I've been on celery juice HMT
hmds since August and it's been
lifechanging brain fog Gone Gone
ADHD amazing totally off Aderall
boom thyroid medication almost
completely off boom thank you aw and
so incredible I just got to sit with
that for a second is that okay you guys
because think about think about his
journey think about his journey it's
incredible
incredible having this connection to our
immune cells means a lot because it
helps us keep on track it helps us
realize what our immune cells have to do
how how hard they work having this
understanding is a big deal right and
then being able to fortify our AB it's
one thing to say you know because I I
look I talked to Spirit of compassion
and I'm like well I tell people about
their immune system I'm only human I'm
doing my best I'm I'm only I'm doing my
best I have all these books I'm out
there talking about the immune system
Spirit I'm trying my
best what more can I do and so is like
explain the immune system talk about it
show people what their immune cell is
actually doing and have them connect to
it so they can get out of chronic
illness survive their chronic
illnesses because the immune system is
under respected
undervalued and so is like underr it
undervalued immune systems
taken for granted we take our immune
cells for granted and you know what even
when we get sick people take it for
granted and they still do and so it's
critical to know how it works what's
going on and what's supportive so what
can we do about it first of all you know
you want to avoid all the different
toxins the best you can throw out the
air fresheners throw out the scented
candles get rid of the Clones get rid of
the perfumes get rid of the fabric
softeners that are blowing out all that
chemical get rid of all the detergents
that are blowing out all that chemical
right be cautious which with bleach be
cautious if you're if you're a bleach
user that's an immune system
dropper you smell bleach immune system
drops you smell bleach it gets in you
immune system drops
bleach yes
right bleach actually meaning you know
what I mean any kind of thing like that
chlorine
you know anything like that immune
system drops and that's important to
know how it works these people don't
realize it they you know they smell
things and they don't know what those
things are doing okay when you're
filling your tank try to look for the
breeze that's going the opposite way go
on the other side of the the nozzle you
know when you're holding that nozzle and
you're breathing in all that
petrochemical and everything try to kind
of stand back a little bit if you can
set the nozzle you set the nozzle and
you stand back a little bit while it's
filling or trying to get kind of like
away from the the fumes that are coming
into you that lowers the immune system
don't get your carpets
cleaned you get your carpets cleaned
with conventional cleaning you know like
detergents and stuff like that they come
in that chemical is just going in you
constantly knowing what your immune
system is up against is part of the
problem it's connecting to that being
aware and proactive keep that in mind so
you're being proactive because you know
what your immune system is up against
that's a big thing so it's about like
different chemicals now we we might not
be able to avoid all the chemicals
falling out of the sky and we we might
not be able to avoid the cologne that's
you know someone's living with you and
they're saturated and we got to breathe
it in all the time but it's important
because we can get rid of what we what
we can get rid of move things away from
us that that are intoxicating us being
cautious and that helps the immune
system okay prevents taking your immune
system for granted we're aware of it all
the time it's deeply connected to no
connecting to no this here's how it
works if we just say oh yeah I don't
like scented candles fragrances aren't
good for you fine if we say fragrances
are actually challenging our immune
cells as they go Upstream then we're
we're not that's not good it's good to
know that but it's not good to know it's
not good that it's happening so
fragrances travel in the bloodstream too
you smell it on the outside it's on the
inside you smell cologne you have
cologne in your
bloodstream did you know that if you're
smelling cologne it's in your
bloodstream if you smell air freshener
it's in your bloodstream if you smell
petrochemical coming out of the the gas
the gas nozzle it's in your bloodstream
and that that stuff is traveling with
your bloodstream so pathogens love to
eat that stuff feed on all those toxins
and chemicals the pathogens love that
stuff right but when our immune cells
right here when they got to walk back
and swim upstream they're getting
slammed with all kinds of different
chemicals our immune cells need to be
protected so let's talk about how to
protect that immune cell right there
here's our immune cells right here okay
going to draw a few of them right
here okay we got our immune cells right
here here they
are so how does an immune cell get
stronger
ER
okay it gets stronger by being
fed immune cells feed on phytochemical
compounds that aren't even detected by
science and research yet it's going to
take a trillion dollars and more
trillions of dollars throughout the next
hundred years for science and research
to look into every phytochemical
compound just a b alone pick up nectar
and pollen
somewhere right you're talking about
hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of
photochemical compounds that are
undiscovered by science of research just
from a bee grabbing some
pollen that's what we're talking about
our immune system
okay is gobbling things down that we
don't even
understand when you eat
something okay when you eat something or
immune cells are taking from that
food okay when you eat something when
you eat something our immune cells are
taking from that food see this you guys
they're taking things from the food you
don't know about they're taking things
from the food no one knows about science
doesn't know about nothing knows
about and that's what our immune cells
doing they're eating things we do not
have our finger on the pulse of keep
that in mind that's what immune cell do
and then when it comes down to powerful
herbs like Thy like in the total immune
Thyme and
Molen those are immune system enhancer
and Builders because there are things
constituents in these these herbs like
Thyme and
Molen that enter into the immune
cell very important to
know and the immune cell gains strength
and radiate strength
when that's entering in look immune
cells gaining strength and vibrancy
that's how you have to see your immune
cells you guys see that you need to see
them strong radiating outward
right so when you're doing your propolis
pure envision your immune cells feeding
off of that propolis pure envision your
immune cells feeding off of that cat's
claw the phytochemical compounds and
cats claw that enhance the immune system
envision your immune cells feeding off
of time and
Mullen and even zinc and restoring and
strengthening it's easy to get
distracted out there with so much
information coming at you all day long
on social and everything top five this
top three this for your whatever top
seven things you can do for your sex
life top eight things you can do it long
for longevity number one eat colostrum
that's not that's no that's not good for
you it's not good for
you point is is that what that's what
we're up against but we don't realize
what our immune system needs and then we
don't realize our immune system is
screwing up how many people get sick
with a symptom go to the
doctor an immune system wasn't even
mentioned even if some someone gets an
autoimmune
diagnosis it's not about like your
immune system needing to heal and get
stronger and strengthen it's about your
immune system attacking itself attacking
your body attacking your organs doesn't
even make any sense because our immune
system doesn't attack our own organs
doesn't attack her own glands that was a
theory in
1950 the point is is our immune
cells they need strength they need
Vitality they need energy and we need to
give them things on a maintenance level
so they can strengthen so they can swim
upstream and clobber the pathogens that
are making everybody sick and toxins and
pathogens you need that immune cell to
be strong as an ox to go swim upstream
why the pathogen is going Downstream
relaxing it's got its shades on it's
chilling it's got its lawn chair it's
just going for a ride that's what the
upen bar is doing and then your white
blood's cell needs to collide and Gobble
it down and engulf it just like
that order to do that strengthen the
ammun system you need maintenance stuff
Julie Tuesday Julie Tuesday 144 I see on
YouTube all the time a w how can we
support our bone marrow so that it can
birth stronger immune
cells okay getting toxic heavy metals
out is a big part of that okay all the
different books on that medical medium
books right all the different stuff the
brain saver books okay I'm hiding behind
here right now if you guys don't mind
voila here I
am okay getting the metals out
strengthens the bone marrow for immune
Health notice that very interesting
Spirit of compassion huh yep the
original heavy metal detox that medical
me put out there nobody talked about
Metals all these years
medical medum information put it out
there the original heavy metal detox the
one that actually works I love how
people have done all kinds of spin-offs
I'm going to put this in here I'm going
to put great it's not going to work
anymore great you did a disservice to
people the heavy metal detox right there
that gets the metals out the heavy metal
detox is really critical for getting
Metals out of Bones and bone marrow and
that improves the immune cells
interesting boots McGee what's going on
there on YouTube since taking total
immune I haven't gotten sick and have
been traveling more than I have in my
entire life and guess what boots McGee
someone just recently told me that that
since they were taking total
immune same thing you guys know I work
with fmer vimer is the best stuff there
is hands down and I don't want it to go
away I don't want it to just go away
because you don't know what you got
until it's gone and people are going to
be sorry if it ever goes away
people are going to be sorry the people
that know are going to be sorry people
who don't know they're just going to
whatever and be sick and that's it you
know and so um and I use I use this for
my friends and family my family and I
use vimer G like we take it every single
day I'm telling you right now that's
what we do um there's something I was
going to tell you guys too a bunch of
different stuff I'm putting some
propolis in here if you guys don't M
mind here real quick
move
this pop a little bit in
here little cat's car right there little
bit of total immune I'm going to take a
shot put that right there I saw somebody
ask like what what is this brand and so
forth v v is in Victor i m is in Mary E
RG y don't miss out get your immune
system supported I'm gonna take a
shot nice so good you
guys just a little reminder I don't know
if you guys have signed up um I'm going
to be in person June 15th just letting
you guys know I'm going to be in person
June 15th so um I don't know if you guys
want to come out there it's going to be
really cool I'm going to talk more about
it I'm going to
probably put some information out in the
email and stuff but it's Culver City
June 15th aan right collaboration heavy
metal detox Iran is putting it on the
menu and I am blown away blown away so
the anyway I'm going to be there in
person and I'm going to be signing some
books I'm going to be there and I'll
give you some more information
additional information than that too
just just want to remind everybody in
case they don't know or do know details
are on medical medium.com
medicalmedium.com
details are on there so um I haven't
been in person in almost a decade just
let you guys know I'm in person here but
I haven't been in person physically
somewhere like that in in almost a
decade I don't know if it's eight years
now so I'm just letting you know that
this is like like I haven't actually
signed a book signing ever in my life in
my career of the medical me book series
maybe it's the only one I do I don't
know but
anyway just a little reminder so you
guys um check out the
viy hey Richardson over there on YouTube
I was told my body was attacking itself
repeatedly on the East Coast West Coast
and even the UK for over 30 years thank
you for help
thank you truly a Richardson Isn't it
nice to know that your your immune
system isn't attacking itself that it
doesn't attack lands and organs you know
what it's trying to do it's trying to
stop
pathogens it's either weakened in a
weakened state or in in its strength any
strength that it has in it it's trying
to save the person and actually
attacking pathogens viruses all kinds of
different bacteria and so forth and
that's what our immune system is doing
and busy doing that's what it's busy
doing you guys check out medical me
podcast at Apple podcast if you
can um they're not putting out
notifications I think so just check to
know that I have a podcast episode every
week so check it out so um notifications
aren't aren't really getting out there
so I'm just letting you know so if
you're relying on notifications just
keep on checking the podcast is out each
week lately that's what's been happening
I have an Epstein bar episode that I
just put out on Epstein bar I just
released it
the other day so keep keep that in mind
I have an episode called The Taste demon
and how our taste buds literally can
Trash our abilities to
heal our taste buds can stop us from
healing did you guys know that did you
know your taste buds can stop you from
healing it's incredible so check out the
taste demon that episode's really
powerful Raven Savory over there on
YouTube I have all of your amazing books
are you planning to start working on
your newest book on spirituality again I
was super excited about it I swear I
will do that
someday it's the last thing I
do I will get the spirituality book out
it's just not coming right now so don't
don't don't hold your breath please
don't hold your breath your podcasts are
amazing over there Lara over there on
YouTube thank you I'm honored
incredible amazing
you guys I'm proud of all of you guys um
Smoky man Paradise you're loving the
podcast
incredible you guys take one day at a
time easy on yourself anyway check out
the propolis pure right that has living
cortin in it different than dead
cortin people don't realize it and for
oral health it is
unbelievable it's unmatched that's all I
can say from the what I'm seeing out
there happen
it's unbelievable so that's the propolis
pure and so many people are saying that
boom they're they Simplex ones boom like
all kinds of stuff like that's how
powerful it is it's crazy that's what
people are saying just over there [__]
please talk more about painful
aggressive fullbody shingles oh my God
from the neck down to the back in the
glutes and all the way down the legs
with nerve and muscle pain that can
knock you out let's talk a little bit
about that right now
okay let's talk about the shingles a
little bit
um because honestly because you're
suffering like
that that's that's just it's just
horrifying it's
horrifying just just know my heart pours
out to you for
real and that's why I do what I do all
these years regardless of opposition and
and naysayers and hate groups and I mean
it's unbelievable what's going on I mean
there's hate groups now that just
literally are trying to
just destroy anything they can medical
medium it's unbelievable let's talk
about the shingles a little bit
okay all
right shingles
virus
okay all right
over there [__] Cherry saver said
followed you for ages and just now it
clicked thank
you I have a lot to say about that by
the way I'm not going to say it I I'm
choosing not to say it right now I got a
lot to say about
that exactly you've been following me on
IG but for some right reason can't see
my Ig and yeah so are a lot of people
right because it's strange how it works
algorithms are so weird all right let's
go so we got the shingles virus and
inside the shingles virus you got a
little bit of a nucleus okay
right shingles
virus has a really really toxic outer
membran really highly toxic okay and
with the shingles virus does is it
releases a dermatoxin out of this
membrane okay but that dermatoxin
Shields the virus the reason why people
suffer from the shingle so much is it's
a hard bug to kill but you got to be
smart about it got to be really smart
about it you got to know information you
have to know information see this book
right here see now you see it now you
don't see the book the shingle virus
very very
toxic outer layer and inside layer of a
membrane right the nucleus produces a
tremendous amount of
dermatoxin it's a
factory the amount of dermatoxin that
spews out of shingles and then leeches
everywhere on the
body is is
terrifying that
nucleus releases is all that dermatoxin
and here it
goes okay boom here's the
dermatoxin here it is watch
this watch this see the dermatoxin
coming out of the shingles virus you
guys and this is why people suffer let
me show you this get this get
ready
okay and here's your nerves you
ready there's your nerv nerves your
vagus
nerves your tibial nerves your frenic
nerves you guys want to pick a nerve for
me your sciatic nerve here they are
here's your
nerves tibial sciatic frenic
Vegas okay get
ready all of that dermatoxin saturates
the nerves you see this so poisonous
that your nerves get
inflamed right there that's the shingles
virus the nucleus producing dermatoxin
the dermatoxin leaving the membrane
going into the membrane the membrane
becoming hot and toxic then spewing out
the dermatoxin and then it hitting all
your nerves your sciatic nerve yep your
tibial nerve
yep all the different nerves okay your
trien
nerve all of them so many different
nerves your veg nerves your frenic
nerves and what happens is those nerves
get lit here's the problem that
dermatoxin it stays on those
nerves and then you just suffer in pain
what we have to do is we have to kill
the virus we have to kill the virus we
have to strengthen our immune system
and we need the maintenance to do that
kind of stuff we need it to do that kind
of stuff
strengthen the immune cells so we can
kill this virus and then over time the
dermatoxin waxes and wains and it drops
back and drops back and drops back and
then you come out now you're rehabbing
you're rehabbing and you're like oh my
God I'm getting past the shingles attack
and I'm rehabbing and that's what happen
happens okay I think I think you were
saying I saw another comment that you're
were
saying it finally clicked in the
information you've been following me for
years or you clicked it and could see me
that's what it was either one but yep
okay you guys pretty
amazing anyway check out the vimergy
stuff for maintenance like the propolis
for cats claw in the total
immune and make sure you're like staying
away from foods that will feed your
pathogens that's a big one all on its
own it's a big one all on its own Max
vond over there on YouTube why does
shingles itching come to me just as I'm
starting to meditate or when I'm almost
falling asleep it's like it knows when
to hit me first of all when you're
almost falling asleep right you're not
you're not like doing things and
everything you're you're almost falling
asleep you're going to feel things more
or right when you can feel a pee under
the mattress you can feel a marble under
the mattress right before falling asleep
a lot of people you can hear the wind
blow outside when you're falling asleep
you can hear the floorboards Creak when
you're falling asleep right you know you
can hear your heartbeat how many people
hear their heartbeat before they fall
asleep they feel their pulse before they
fall asleep right you can hear it in
your ear a lot of people hear it in
their ear as they're falling asleep and
you're going to feel the itching come up
on when you're falling asleep too that's
one thing but yes at the same time our
weakest point of time our immune system
is is at the end of the day our immune
system is at its weakest at the end of
the day it's why when I'm always telling
people to do the maintenance like
friends and family and everything with
the propolis and the cat's claw I'm like
make sure you take some at the end of
the day too make sure you take some at
night before you go to bed because
that's important because the weakest
point in time where our immune cells are
at their weakest is at the end of the
day at at night and they're stronger in
the morning after a little bit of rest
even two hours of sleep 1 hour of sleep
half an hour of sleep they get a Little
Bit Stronger but at night at the end of
the day they're at their weakest and
yeah your viral flares could be edging
up that could be making you itchy itchy
too people itchy and all irritated and
stuff and everything else but at the end
of the day your immune system is at its
weakest it's weaker keep in mind about
that and so I tell like friends and
family and I tell doctor friends make
sure you're doing
you right you know your maintenance also
at the end of the day make sure you're
getting you know boom support for your
immune system at the end of the day
anyway you guys check out medical medum
podcast at Apple podcast check out my
telegram I'm going to start leaving um
new audio messages on my telegram so
that that time is coming so get ready
for that check out my old audio messages
on telegram like Pride and Prejudice how
I what I talked about with Pride and
Prejudice and all that information which
I'm going to talk about
again and I just saw um a comment there
okay oh wow that explained a lot I get
symptoms at the end of the day cold
white spring cold white spring
amazing and um yeah you guys all good
stuff all good stuff I saw a comment
talking about um lymphatic drainage I'm
not against lymphatic massage or
drainage I think it helps people I do
I'm not against it at all I'm not
against massage massage I think is
incredible for people I'm not against
lymphatic drainage I think that's great
all of that but I'm just saying I I only
talk about how if we don't address
what's behind our lymphatic system the
root cause and then you know that's
that's a whole another thing so that's
it it's about cleaning up the liver
cleaning up the lymphatic system
internally strengthening the lymphatic
system's immune system let's hit that
one one per a minute this is important
right here
okay this next thing I'm going to talk
about is very very important
it's immune system
related lymphatic
system can get toxic and clogged up yes
but your lymphocytes are critical to
understand but if you're really really
sick and you and and if you're really
sick and in a weakened State you got to
be careful you know and you're and
you're swelling there's information you
can learn about that too on on medical
meem podcast check out my
my swelling episode right there all
right let's get this going
here all right let's make a little bit
of a lymphatic system
here little bit of a lymphatic system
you
guys
okay all
right got a lymphatic
system
okay an incredible artist at
hand there's an artist in in person here
um so I want to talk about this right
here so as you got fluid in your
lymphatic
system keep in mind that
you got
lymphocytes here
lymphocytes they need to be fed your
lymphocytes that are in your lymphatic
system those lymphocytes
devour pathogens in your lymphatic
system keep that in mind right there if
you don't address the
liver and your lymphatic system is
constantly dirty and clogged you're
keeping your immune system weakened okay
so yes I'm not against lymphatic
drainage but what needs to be done is
the core root cause of your lymphatic
problems which is your liver being
stagnant sluggish filled the toxins and
poisons that's one thing and the other
aspect of the immune system which is
your
lymphocytes no one's talking about
lymphocytes they're talking about that
part of your immune system which is
critical right you still have to do
maintenance and you still have to feed
your lymphocytes if you don't feed them
and they're
weak they can't work for you and they
can't catch pathogens and they can't
catch
poisons and if you're playing with your
lymphatic system too much and you're and
it's being manipulated and purged and
squeezed your lymphocytes are having a
hard time trying to to find balance in
that they're being pushed
around and they need their natural
habitat to be slightly undisturbed in
certain areas so when people go through
the roof crazy with lymphatic
drainage they're they're manipulating
the habitat of the of the
lymphocyte and that can weaken the
lymphatic immune
system so it there's a there's a there's
a place where we can get massage and
drainage lymphatic drainage gentle
gentle drainage but there's also a fine
line between if we do
extremism with the lymphatic system and
we
weaken the lymphatic systems
lymphocytic system all the time and
we're trying to push fluid and push
fluid and push fluid so we can a look
better or feel better in a bikini or
whatever it is if we're
literally water boarding and literally
crushing down on our lymphatic vessels
and trying to squeeze every last bit of
fluid out of them we just manipulated
our lymphocytes and our immune cells
which weakens our immune system so we
have to be careful with how much
manipulation we do on on our lympo on on
our lymphatic system so we can protect
our
lymphocytes what I'm trying to say is
your lymphatic
system your lymph your lymph system has
the lymphocytes big part of your immune
system but if we're beating the crap out
of our lymphatic system just so we can
push fluid around we are manipulating
and pushing lymphocytes around and they
take the hit and they get
damaged so every time we get a lymphatic
draining session like a really deep
one our lymphocytes need time to recover
and
replenish and maybe even need time to
restore because we can hinder our
lymphocytes but I do still like
lymphatic drainage especially if you're
sary and you can't you can't move around
I want people to still get it if they
can I still want them to get
it but the fluid is there to protect the
lymphocyte too keep that in mind so if
you're really toxic and you're trying to
move toxins through your lymphatic fluid
keep in mind that when we're moving
those toxins around we're pushing our
lymphocytes into those toxins manually
we're
manipulating our lymphatic systems
immune system so we have to be careful
to some degree so what I tell people a
lot of people ask me like what do you
think about lymphatic massage I say it's
great just don't go extremism
where you're doing it every day you're
not giving your lymphocytes a chance to
recovery build reestablish themselves
and don't go so crazy where you have
machines on you and you're trying to use
the machines the vibrating machines
where you're trying to literally get
every little scrap of juice out of some
of your lymphatic
system we retain fluid in our lymphatic
system to dilute the toxins so here
people are actually trying to push our
fluid out
but toxins still stay behind and sludge
still stays behind and what they're
doing is they're trying to manually push
out all the fluid but toxins are still
staying behind so keep in mind that we
do want some fluid left in our lymphatic
system because I see people using a lot
of tools and a lot of lymphatic
machinery and I'm like oh dear Lord
You're squeezing fluid out but a lot of
sludge and toxins are staying behind
without fluid anymore in there to
actually protect you and your immune
system system and you're also
manipulating and pushing
lymphatic lymphocyte cells out when you
need them in there to protect you from
pathogens and so forth the lymphocytes
die quickly if it's too toxic in there
but they die quickly if we're also
manipulating them and grinding them into
nothing because we're using so much
manipulation with the lymphatic drainage
Styles and techniques now it's not just
what it used to be people are getting
like obsessed and they're using machines
and rollers and they're trying to
squeeze every last bit of juice out of
people I'm sure that's not probably what
you're doing you might just be getting a
normal lymphatic drainage session I
think that's great I think it's
supportive but we also have to work on
the liver and we have to protect we have
to at least feed our lymphocytes that's
why I talk about the maintenance stuff
with the propolis pure and the cats claw
and and the total immune to feed our
lymphocytes as well over there in IG
ingred says what's the brand for the
propolis and the cats clots vimergy V is
in Victor i m is in Mary E RG
y.com link is in the description I think
and all that so you
guys Incredible One Day at a Time keep
up all your healing but this is another
you know another show about the immune
system learning all these different
things about the immune system very
important because we can forget take it
for granted not realize what's going on
we lose we lose our Direction and then
we're sick and we stay sick for years
and we're confused and we're just
watching social and the internet and
we're seeing every new you know new
flashy thing that comes up and we're
grabbing this and doing this meanwhile
our immune system is struggling it needs
support we need to learn about our
immune system all that's critical all
right you guys guys know I love
you incredible to be here again and um
I'll see you guys soon