fiber
the fiber farce
what pray tell do i have to say about
fiber
well let's go into it if you're somebody
that's suffering
suffering and sickness and chronic
illness and
and mental illness and your suffering
don't worry fiber fix it
fiber
that'll fix it
more fiber
that person just needs a little more
fiber did you try fiber
hey
oh whoa you got severe eczema and
psoriasis
and you you got weakness in the limbs
and you're fatigued and you got
severe depression do you think fiber
will fix it
maybe you need some more fiber
hey
fiber police come out here and tell
every sick person on the planet it's
because they need more fiber
that's what it is perfect
we got the answer because you guys know
we have the answer to why everybody's
sick everybody's suffering from the
plague out there right now oh the last
two years it's fiber they just needed
fiber
for god's sake that's all they needed
was some fiber
brilliant
so glad everybody's on the same page it
just needed a little bit of fiber
you know i'll tell you right now
once again it's it's unbelievable
because nobody knows why anybody is sick
medical research and science doesn't
know why anybody is sick
they don't
they chalk it up to your jeans your
genes are bad and that's why you're sick
it's your genes or it's your body
attacking itself autoimmune right your
body is destroying itself well that that
theory right maybe you're just creating
it
bad karma baby
maybe it's bad karma that's your karma
you're sick in bed now
what comes around goes around it's your
karma it's gotta be that
oh maybe you're sick and you can't
function because you had your head
chopped off in 1602
you know and maybe something maybe you
died in a fire in 1715 somewhere maybe
something else happened you know and so
you know and what happens is we don't
know why anybody's sick nobody knows why
anybody's sick
and people are getting sicker and sicker
and faster and faster and life
expectancy is dropping life expectancy
is dropping and dropping
guess what they're hiding it too
they're hiding life expectancy they're
actually
hiding it
it's dropping faster than they say they
need you to be under the illusion that
everybody's living longer and living
healthier and living happier that the
illusion is there and hey if you're not
living longer and healthier you probably
just needed some fiber
you
know the world is so screwed up
in so many ways
that when
it's screwed up in the health realm it's
really bad because hey
everybody says oh health is wealth oh
man when i hear that i just
i hate that one
[Laughter]
health is wealth
right that one
yeah well it's good thing you're taking
care of yourself health is wealth
you know
people don't realize
that
there's sinister reasons
why people are sick
sinister reasons the system is built to
take people down destroy them and kill
them
the sith the illumination needs to
eliminate people so they set up the
system to purposely eliminate people and
that's how the system is set up and at
the same time completely
everybody that life expectancy is
getting better and better and better and
better
it's almost like you just brain screw
you along the way and then some doctor
will come out hey i'm doctors
this is my five best tips to get more
fiber into your life i'll even come out
with maybe another book or a next book
about fiber you just need fiber in your
life that's the answer lots of fiber in
your life will take care of everything
let's talk about fiber let's let's let's
go you guys just so you know
you're looking at the mm-900 hds and the
sale is gonna eventually end
it's gonna get there
and then
when i'm sitting in a car somewhere i'm
gonna have to roll down the window and
scream my head off when i see someone
leave a comment saying
how did i miss the sale
hey do you have a juicer out there that
works really good
the sale is coming to an end it's the
mm-900 hds if you hang on i'm going to
show you how the dry pulp it's not a
magic trick how the pulp is dry and you
save money someone left a comment said
yeah in 20 years you'll save money on
that juicer in 20 years are you kidding
the juicer paid for itself over and over
again with just just my juicer meaning
like me juicing has paid for itself over
and over again i got family members that
use the juicer and they're like you know
i saved this much i'm keeping track i
bought less produce it's adding up it's
now like 50 a month
and then boom paid for a juicer
that's incredible
okay let's talk about fiber
so the big attack
is you need your fiber if you've got to
have your fiber that's what it is and
it's an attack on the juicy world but
it's not just attack on the juicing
world it's attack on your your mental
consciousness it's attack on you because
you're gonna think maybe that's why i'm
sick
you can you can be someone that eats
white bread processed white dough
and you don't get sick
you can be somebody that eats gluten
filled processed
white dough white flour dough balls and
then fries them in oil
and not be sick
i know
some people over the years
literally living on fried dough and
they're not sick and they're pooping
just fine they got no fiber in their
diet and they're pooping
that's what's happening i know people
that are eating white bread a loaf of
white bread and butter and they can poo
just fine
and they're not sick and then
i know people that are eating fruits and
vegetables
and can't poo at all
i know people that are eating
plenty of fiber but they still have to
take
fiber supplements and fiber drinks and
prescribed fiber medications because
something's wrong inside fiber has
nothing to do
with something going wrong and something
being wrong inside of you it's not the
fiber that keeps cancer away it's not
the fiber that keeps disease away it's
what was in the plant that wasn't the
fiber the fiber is not where the
medicine is the medicine is in the juice
of the plant you guys this is so
critical
the fiber
in the plant
is your bones in a human being
fiber growing a plant out of a ground
the fiber's just there so the plant can
erect itself and reach the sun
that's what fiber is fiber fibrin and
asparagus okay you guys is to get the
asparagus shoot
to actually reach up for the sun that's
what fiber's for the fiber in a plant
isn't there to save your life it's a
good thing
fiber is a good thing if fiber's not a
terrible thing fiber is not a bad thing
no no no
it's not
fiber is a good thing but the fiber is
to bring the plant to the sun it's the
skeleton is what it is and it's bringing
the plant to the sun so that the platzo
fiber in here
you won't be able to digest the fiber
the fiber will be just eliminated and
we'll be you'll be eliminating it you'll
be getting it out of your body when you
go to bathroom
but the fiber
is a skeleton
of the plant to get the plant to have
to have stability and strength to to to
not just lay like this on the ground the
fiber is to help the plant actually
become something right
that's what it's for
it's critical to know this
but the medicine that stops you from
getting sick is not the fiber the
medicine that stops you from getting
sick is the phytochemical compounds
is to trace minerals
fiber is not a trace mineral
fiber is not a trace mineral fiber is
not zinc
fiber
is not zinc
fiber's not boron
fiber isn't magnesium
fiber's not anthocyanins
fiber is not resveratrol
fiber's not vitamin c fiber is not b12
fibers does this make any sense
fiber is not
phytochemical compounds that stop cancer
and stop disease
fiber is not antiviral compounds and
antibacterial compounds that's not fiber
did you guys know that it's those things
that stop disease and illness
fiber
is the skeleton
of the plant
so the plant can stand up straight and
get some sun
that's what fibrous
fiber is similar not the same thing
but similar by the way my skeleton lost
the leg
fiber
is similar to your bones
your bones
are there so you can stand up straight
that's what your bones are there for so
you can stand up straight it's there for
the animal to stand up straight it's
there for the dog to stand up straight
the dog's fiber really is the bones of
the dog right so the dog can stand up
straight so the pig can stand up
straight that's the fiber that's part of
it meaning that's what it's like for
plants it's not exactly like that
totally like for humans but but that's
what i'm using its example
fiber in the plant is so the plant can
get to the sun so it can be seen so it
can rise above the other plants so
they're having a fiber war plants have a
fiber war to try to rise up off the
ground so they can get the sun and they
can get what they need so they can
create those nutrients
it's critical to know
right
good to see you guys by the way i'm
going to be juicing some celery
i'm going to talk about the mm-900 hds
fiber
can't be digested at all
when you have nothing wrong with your
gut
you can still go to bathroom
no matter what you can go to bathroom if
just
water goes in you if just juice goes in
you it's just a liquid goes in you it's
just bread goes in you if dough it's
doughnuts
i know people that don't have anything
wrong with their gut they don't have all
the bad bacteria that ripped apart their
gut they don't have all kinds of
different viruses yet they don't have
these things they don't have metals in
their brain messing up their peristaltic
action so because they don't have that
yet and maybe they're working on it but
they don't have it maybe they're working
on catching a virus maybe they're
working on catching bacteria maybe
they're working on catching so i mean
getting contamination by something but
what happens is they can still go to
bathroom
they can eat bread and butter and drink
beer
and they'll be on the toilet go in the
bathroom as if nothing was wrong they
didn't need any fiber
because
and then there's people that get all the
fiber you want but they can lose all
peristaltic action you guys this is
important to know there's people okay
that have that that eat all the fiber
you can put all the fiber you want in
them but they've got no peristaltic
action they can't go to bathroom they're
still in there because they're inflamed
they have problems inside the gut
problems
juicing helps to fix but meanwhile the
anti-juicing world the fiber freaks
the fiber cult
yeah the fiber cold the fiber freaks
they want to scare you
people can put all the fiber they want
but if they got something corking out
their vagus nerve if they got
peristaltic action that died because
they got gastroparesis because they got
severe problems they got neurological
problems that aren't allowing
gastroparesis
fiber can't fix it
in fact they can't even eat fiber it
moistens their condition
and here's the irony fibers in
everything you're never going to be
fiber free 100 unless you want to go on
bread you want to go on bread you're
never going to get any fiber sure
you can go on a loaf of bread got some
mock bread right here
some fake bread
you can go on some bread
i'm talking about processed white bread
not talking about whole grain fibrous
bread
hi uw i miss your shows
thank you missy for being here i i
appreciate you guys on tick tock good to
see you guys to see you guys coming on
i'm glad you guys are coming out we're
live by the way i don't know if i told
you guys we're live live live live we
got the mm-900 hds the sale is going to
be running out eventually so i have to
let you guys know but we're covering hot
topics we're covering powerful
information
juicing is just a powerful addition to
all the good things you're having i want
people to get fiber but i'm not saying
get fiber i'm saying get your antiviral
medicine get your
antibacterial medicine
get your phytochemical compounds and
your trace mineral salts get those right
get your critical glucose get your
sulfur which is a chemical compound and
say a food like cabbage cruciferous
chemical compounds like sulfur get that
in your life get anti-viral compounds
fiber
that's automatically there
so we need other things from all the
fruits and vegetables leafy greens and
wild foods and everything else and herbs
we get we need more
we're getting more than fiber
fiber's an in it's a guarantee unless
there's somebody just unprocessed flour
only like i know some people and they
still go to bathroom fine
it's a guarantee you're fibered out
you've got plenty of fiber going in
there
you're eating your fiber it's there if
you can't go to bathroom we got another
problem we got inflammation around the
bend
this is a highway right here and if you
picture a car going through here it's
like this
whoa go around that bend
oh
and that's what's happening is the car
is going through here
[Music]
all around the bend right and all of a
sudden you've got food and it's going
uh
and it's stuck
that means
something's wrong
and you've been eating fiber your whole
life you can go and get the greasiest
double bacon double cheeseburger and
they'll be probably still more fiber in
that greasy
gross bacon double cheeseburger
then you can think of there's still some
fiber in there
but if you can't go to bathroom anymore
you got something stuck
you got a problem in there or you're
getting a mixed signal it's mixed it's
coming from the vagus nerve so the vagus
nerves
right are shooting out of your brain
stem
two vagus nerves
coming out of your brain stem
two
right
you got your vagus nerves coming out of
your brain stem and they're coming down
all through here they're rerouting and
they're sending signals to your gut and
they're telling your gut to peristaltic
action you've got a peristaltic action
go ahead and twist twist and turn get
the get the poo to move through get
whatever it is you're eating to move
through get your food to move through
get your fiber to move through whatever
you want to call it get it to move
through and if it's not moving through
we're inflamed
or there's a miss messages mixed
messages coming from the brain through
the vagus nerves on down the path to the
intestinal tract and guess what
we have a problem
and that's what's going on
so then
you talk to a health professional and
the health professional is just going to
be like you know like
oh all you need is a little bit of fiber
did you increase your water
how many times do i have to insult you
you probably never tried to increase
water yet oh you have
oh what do you mean it's the first thing
you learned nonsense
you didn't increase your water or your
fiber
increase your water and your fiber
if that doesn't fix it it's your jeans
you're just a broken toy
you're just broken your jeans are broken
if fiber and water doesn't fix it
then maybe you have lectin problems oh
wait a minute maybe you have celacic
acid problems i read an article about
that
maybe you got oxalate issues
oh
can't go to bathroom probably oxalate
issues
anyway
the one thing to know there's a lot of
different important things to think
about okay
the one thing to know
is that you can't fall into the fiber
trap you're getting fiber
you're getting fiber you can go to bed
at night and recite it to yourself
you're getting fiber
but you know what you're not getting if
you're not juicing your celery juice
you're not getting the sodium cluster
salts that are anti-viral antibacterial
you're not getting the vitamin c that
doesn't have to be converted by the
liver
you're not getting the things you need
and that's critical to know
pathogens inflame the intestinal tract
so what happens is we get pathogens
inside the intestinal intestinal tract
there they go
and they get in there they find their
way in there and they find their way
real easy too they get into that
intestinal tract real easy they get into
the colon really easy when they get in
there and they're in
you've got colitis
you've got celiac
you got ibs you got sibo you got crohn's
you've got gastric spasms you've got
gastroparesis you've got all kinds of
other things it's it's the bugs inside
your gut and those bugs can get in there
and cause a lot of problems and if
that's not all it's the heavy metals
that get inside the brain and all those
toxic heavy metals and they're sending
signals down your vagus nerves shooting
out of your brain stem under here so
right under here you've got your vagus
nerves and the signal's going out and as
the signal is going out
you're getting a message to here that's
not making it twist so we're not
twisting
we're not twisting anymore
and if you're eating gluten you're
feeding the pathogen so it only gets
worse
fiber
won't fix it because it can't be an
antiviral your fiber's not an
antibacterial your fiber is not medicine
i love it when someone wakes up one
morning and they come out of a stupor in
the health field somebody maybe an md or
an nd or some kind of practitioner or a
dietitian they wake up one morning and
they're like
i think i got the problem it's fiber
i'm going to do an article now about how
fiber is so important and let me
research all the other bs about fiber
that's been talked about for years it's
like a train of misinformation that's
gone wrong you can hop on there and play
on google all day long and play on the
internet and play on social media and be
like i found another article on fiverr
this was written in 2012. well this
article here in fiber's written in 2014.
here's an article about the best ways to
get fiber in you and how important it is
and next thing you know you're gone
you're lost you're gone and if you're a
practitioner or a health person and make
a somebody that's in the field of
medicine you're really now screwed
because now you're going to be telling
your patients
maybe it's more fiber you need i've read
an interest interesting article juicing
what
no no no don't juice that would be
really bad
you guys we're live right now having a
little fun we're talking about fiber
talking about the fiber farce how about
that
fiber does not have nutrients in it
fiber
is empty
fiber is the skeleton of the plant
fiber's not the reason why anybody's
sick
very important to know
we're juicing celery right now a couple
tips gotta strain your celery juice at
the end i'll show you how that works
michelle l says fiber hurts for a lot of
people with intestinal problems fiber
hurts
don't get cheated
out of benefiting your life changing
your life turning it around don't get
cheated out of that because somebody
throws the whole you should be getting
the fiber so don't juice don't let
someone cheat you out of that
beautiful privilege that we can get and
obtain which is actually being able to
bring our lives back from juicing
this is a medicine maker you're seeing
herbal medicine be made in front of your
eyes right now sure we can take it for
granted
we can take it for granted
i can take this machine for granted i
can take juicing celery for granted
definitely
but when you really think what's
happening it's pretty incredible
go back to a few hundred years ago go
back to a few hundred years ago right
okay
you got someone that's trying to pull
water out of a well a muddy well
right
think about it
okay
and
they're slaughtering the only animal
they have
to survive
they're slaughtering their cow that
creates the dairy they need because it's
the winter
right
and they're they're now cooking animal
meat which i'm not against animal
protein eaters i'm not against
plant-based people right
okay
they got some leftover
grain
got some leftover barley or wheat most
likely wheat they got leftover wheat
so they have leftover wheat
they get some well water from their well
muddy well water
they're cooking their last animals to
survive to get to spring right
and if you if you knocked on their door
on that colonial house
and knocked down that door or wherever
they were in this world and you knocked
on their door and you went back in the
past because you're from the future
you're from 2021 and you went back in
the past and you knocked on that door
he said i want to show you guys
something and you had a stack of celery
and you brought this machine in and
magically had the ability to have power
because the story is
magical anyway
and you popped a juicer in front of them
and you said
we're going to clear up your
deficiencies we're going to bring your
home we're gonna bring you back you're
gonna have you're not gonna have the
scurvy we're gonna get rid of any scurvy
we're gonna get rid of rickets
your children aren't gonna be deficient
we're gonna give you a fresh glass of
celery juice right out of the future and
we're going to juice it in an herbal
medicine maker
they would probably
have a heart attack
because their mind would be so blown
you couldn't
even when you really think about your
mind would be so blown
you guys
i don't i don't take it for granted i
know what this is
it's a way to bring back our health
it's a way to take control over our
lives right
and that's what this is and that's
what's really special about it
that's just one thing
but i love when nobody knows why
anybody's big
but they got so many answers out there
so many answers they don't know why
anybody's sick
nobody knows
it's all a guessing game
mary says doesn't fiber move poo out of
the system
fiber doesn't move poo out of the system
your intestinal tract moves the poo out
of your system
you can be somebody
that's literally on white bread
processed bread dough
doughnuts
and your peristaltic action
you're gonna you could be somebody
that's on meat which has no fiber in it
and you're gonna in your peristaltic
action if it's working mary
it's gonna push the meat out and the
dough
you can be somebody that lives off of
white bread meat sandwiches
white
processed bread meat sandwiches
and you can be eating a white bread meat
sandwich and people will poo it out
because their peristaltic action is is
doing the contorting act to get it out
and squeeze it out you can be on just
meat
plain old meat
and you literally your if your
peristaltic action is working because
you don't have any problems you'll be
getting it out but if you can't
poo because you need all this fiber then
you have a problem
a problem that you're using fiber as a
tool
because you can't go anymore because you
actually have a physical problem going
inside the body making it so you can't
go to bathroom
so then
you might be somebody or anybody that
ends up knocking on some doctors george
is greater practitioner's door and read
an article and it says don't juice
because it minim it gets rid of the
fiber and all of a sudden you're scared
but the juicing is what fixes the
problem inside the intestinal tract in
the gut so that you can get peristaltic
action to go to bathroom without having
any fiber
and be like someone who doesn't have a
problem in their intestinal tract i know
some people they can live off of donuts
and they'll poo it out just fine they
don't have any problems like fiber
they're like what
we need fiber for
is that just a new age word they'll be
like whatever i'm going to bathroom fine
but does your health get worse if you're
just on white bread yes for other
reasons because you don't get protected
by the antiviral compounds and the
medicine and the trace mineral salt you
don't get protected by the by the by the
anthocyanins right there see the
anthocyanins right there you don't get
protected by the anthocyanins
you see them right that's the purple you
don't get protected by those those are
the antioxidants those are the antiviral
compounds antibacterial compounds and
trace mineral salts
so what you'll find with the mm-900 is
it saves you money and the pulp comes
out dry that's what happens the pulp
comes out dry
it's it's not
it's not sopping wet you have a dry bowl
got a dry ball
link is in profile link is in the
description on on the juicer it's coming
down to the end of the sale
and i can't express how important
juicing is
for somebody to stay healthy and if
someone has talked out of juicing in
their life
use any juicer you have forget the
mm-900 the mm-900 saves people money it
squeezes every last drop it pulverizes
like no other juicer does
but if you have any juicer i'll take it
i'm on board
i'm on board keep the juicer you have
if you have any juicer i don't care if
it's a ten dollar juicer and it's got a
crank on it and you're and you're doing
a ten dollar juicer and you've got a
crank on it i will be patting you on the
back until you don't even get the mm-900
fine just keep what you're doing because
you're juicing and it's the juicing part
yeah this is an incredible machine
it saves you money you end up saved and
it pays for itself and and basically you
get into a dry ball of pulp and it and
and you're now buying half the celery
and half this and half that and if you
want to juice something else like a
carrot you're buying less carrots you're
buying less cucumbers right but the
point is in pomegranate the same thing
you bring less pomegranate and it adds
up adds up big time in the food prices
are going up so this machine became like
this blessing
it became this blessing
the mm-900 hds
i endorsed it i endorsed the company
because i know what it's doing and i
know what it's doing for people but if
you have any juicer you guys i stand
behind it 100
meaning like i'm on board you use the
juicer you have just make juice please
please i beg of you to make juice with
the juicer you have you don't have to
get the mm-900
because i know how important juicing is
if i don't have passion towards the
juicing and if i don't have a mission
towards the juicing how is it going to
stay alive to keep people alive because
there's always an attack
to take the good down out there with
celery juice don't add anything
don't add anything i love how the pulp
is dry i just love that it's my favorite
it's my favorite thing
it's barely it's damp it's it's
incredible how that works right
don't put any ice in there don't put any
lemon in there don't put anything like
that okay
don't put ice don't put lemon
don't put anything like that you want 16
to 32 ounces i'm throwing it in a mug
right now
throw it in a glass mug to show you
right
always strain it
16 to 32 ounces
right
and
empty stomach first thing in the morning
it's herbal medicine
that's what it is
it's herbal medicine at its best and
keep that in mind
how long will it keep us see on tick
tock
i mean you could put it in the in the
fridge for for a day
you want to drink it right away but i've
had celery juice in the fridge for three
days and i've consumed it and still
beats anything in the store that's in a
bottle or anything
so
so why does julie really good question i
want to answer that one it's fantastic
fiber doesn't feed first of all julia
want to answer that question but i want
to talk about something fiber doesn't
feed good bacteria
fiber cannot be broken down
it can't be consumed
so you we need to know how that works
that's a theory because you because the
theorists in medicine and health they
don't want to lose the fiber
tune
they want to sing the fiber tune over
and over again like
fiber
yeah fiber is everything it's fiber
right they don't want to lose that so
all of a sudden now we've learned about
there's good bacteria in the gut i bet
you fiber has a lot to do with that what
else right
hey vitamin d is important for people i
bet your fiber has everything to do with
that vitamin d being important okay what
else um people need vitamin c fiber i
bet you is everything to do with that um
people need it's fiber see they they
just lump it all into each other without
knowing why anybody's sick or how to
heal right
so fiber doesn't feed bacteria fiber
gets discarded
it gets discarded because it's waste and
it doesn't have any nutrients in it
that's how it works with fiber your body
can't break it down can't digest it nor
can bacteria can't break down and digest
fiber
it can't
fiber stays fiber
is what it does
very important now
but good bacteria
feeds on
the juice that cracked
out
of the pulp of something
you bite a lemon
you bite the lemon pulp you squeeze that
lemon juice in that good bacteria
will feed off of that lemon juice
good bacteria feeds off of the juices of
those important phytochemical compounds
of those important vegetables and fruits
and leafy greens and herbs
good bacteria feeds off the juices
you want to save any good bacteria you
make sure you give them lots of juice
that's how it works so there's a
question about coffee i don't want to
lose why does coffee move things
there's a question right here i think it
was on youtube or facebook why does
coffee move things
coffee moves things because coffee
stimulates your adrenals
caffeine makes your adrenals dump
epinephrine into your bloodstream
epinephrine is fight or flight
and you have to poo
while you're either getting killed
or you're running from someone trying to
kill you
see how it works
when you get scared
you your pants
there's a reason why that term exists
when you get scared out of your mind you
your pants
you pee your pants
the reason why you pee
and poo your pants when you get scared
to death
is because that's an adrenaline reaction
to empty you
so you can have more ability to fight
and run
someone comes to attack you
you need to evacuate
animals in the wild
eliminate everything inside of them
before the deer
you chase a deer
if a wolf chases a deer the deer will
empty out its entire
innards basically
all the deer poop will go flying out of
the deer as it's running it's fight or
flight
we have it too
when you drink caffeine you told your
adrenals
were fight or flight you're either gonna
get killed or be killed or run
kill or be killed or whatever
fight or flight whatever
and so coffee all that caffeine makes
the adrenals go oh my god there's a
problem oh i gotta go to the bathroom
now i gotta do my bowel movement
caffeine's a poison too
and poisons need to be
eliminated so it's a combination of that
you know what's interesting about
medical medium information
thank god you guys know this
but it's information you won't hear
anywhere else and
and melton said that
milton just said
this info you won't hear anywhere else
i'm honored truly i am
warms my heart you know that it really
does
and people steal it and they won't cite
it back trust me that will be all
through the vegan movement in about
the vegans especially like a vegan
movement people not vegans
but like
the people trying to get to the top of
the vegan movement you know to become a
speaker or a book writer or whatever it
is right it's happened the last 35 years
they love taking medical medium tidbits
injecting it into the vegan movement
and then telling other people don't
listen to that medical medium
that's classic actually with the vegan
movement
i think you know what happens is that
and again i'm pro-vegan pro-plant-based
and i'm also pro-animal protein a
pro-pescetarian i'm pro-vegetarian
vegetarians can eat terrible
vegetarians
horrible
vegans can eat horrible animal protein
can be hard could eat a horrible
terrible they can eat
anyway
this is the mm-900 hds
it's a very special machine
it's on sale right now 90
off
you'll see the sale in the checkout at
omegajuicers.com so you go to
megajuicers.com the link is in the bio
you guys on tick tock
the link is in the bio
the link is in the description
you guys you guys sign up to my
newsletter
themedicalmedium.com go to
medicalmedium.com please sign up to my
newsletter the link is in the bio as
well and in the description right
and
and also follow me on amazon live
all right i just made a quiche today
so i made this quiche today
here it is i made this quiche
i made this beautiful quiche right here
it's a chickpea quiche it's gluten free
dairy free
it's an incredible quiche i can't wait
to down that later and when i'm eating
and i'm not going to think about the
fiber aspect yeah there's lots of fiber
in there there's tons of fiber in there
that's not what i care about i care
about the phytochemical compounds that's
the critical thing
they got the broccoli in there it's
incredible onions you got the garlic in
there the link is in the bio by the way
to sign up to the amazon live not sign
up but to follow me on amazon live to
the medical medium cooking show which is
really cool and that's where i made this
quiche today
but you guys
look for my newsletter follow me on my
podcast medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast
check out my newsletter so you know
where i'm at and everything else would
love the chickpea tea shrek recipe wow
that's in liver rescue it's an
incredible recipe too you guys
here we are i know you guys have seen
this isn't liver rescue
there you are
liver rescue is an incredible book
it is
and um i don't know if anybody has it
but you'll see a little picture of me
when i was four years old
holding a baby bird and
begging spirit of compassion
to give me any kind of guidance and
ability to heal it
and that was a long time ago anyway i
love you guys i'm going to
i'm going to instagram i'm turning tick
tock back on and i'm turning telegram
back on
i love you guys
and uh just know i care