[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead what's out there now this
is the only Health show where the
information here doesn't come from
interest groups or medical funding with
strings attached botched research
lobbyists internal Kickbacks persuaded
belief systems private panels of
influencers and health field payoffs are
trendy traps that are both in
conventional and alternative medical
community's
information because hey all of the
health information I share Here Comes
from a pure untampered with Advanced
Clean Source a higher source the spirit
of compassion there's nothing more
healing than compassion so who has 10 or
20 years to wait for answers we have to
start our healing now we need every
answer we can get now and as a child
when the gift first came to me to hear
Spirit perfectly clear and spirit
appeared and gave me information for my
grandmother and for other people for the
rest of my life and gave me that ability
to see when that first happened Spirit
was saying people need these answers
they need them now cuz I always asked
all the time I always said well why you
know who cares who cares you know when I
was a kid I was like who cares I I you
know I can't be bothered with this I
just want to ride my bicycle I just want
to do things I want to have fun I don't
want to know what's going inside of
people and what's going inside in in in
them and what's happening and that's
what I would say to Spirit spirit said
you have to care you have to learn to
care at a young age I had to tap into
that I had to root into that and care
about other people meaning truly care
about other people people I didn't know
people that I never really knew people
that you know strangers I had to root
into that it had to it had to become
ingrained in me toare because we need
this information and spirit taught me
that this information was really
important for people to know and as I've
seen over the Decades of doing this
being a servant to Spirit and to the
people and the communities and
everything else as I've seen I've seen
the changes I've seen the Miracles I've
seen what's happened with spirit's
information and spirit was right right
all along so hey Today's Show is about
inflammation this is an important show
it really is inflammation is is
something that we need to talk about for
a lot of reasons it's one of my favorite
words in a way because it's it's an easy
word to use like for for instance okay
you guys the mistake is not trying to
fix inflammation because you know I'm
always always looking for mistakes it's
not trying to fix inflammation or trying
to relieve inflammation or watching out
for it because there's some mistakes
with inflammation and I'm going to I'm
going to let you know what's going on
with it it's it's it's a word we throw
around so liberally we just throw it
around we you know a lot of
practitioners throw it away well you're
inflamed well it's got to be some kind
of inflammation well you know there must
be some inflammation there you know
maybe hey look it looks like you're
inflamed you know whatever the MRI might
show hey you have some inflammation in
here wherever we use the word it hurts
there's pain so well you're inflamed you
know there's some pain there so yeah
there's there's it's probably some kind
of
inflammation and so that's a word we
kind of throw around but it's a lazy
term hey I've used it I even use it I
mean you know I I I'll use it it's a
lazy term it really is and I'm going to
tell you why it's a lazy term and and
what's going on with that I mean you're
probably figuring that out right now um
but so it's it's not it's okay to use it
because we want to relieve inflammation
we want to be looking out for it we do
we want to we want to look out for it
and we want to try to fix it and we want
to care about that we do want to care
about that come on we want to try to fix
inflammation we know that but we do use
it as a lazy term because I'll tell you
why we use it as a lazy term and I'll
tell you why it's not good I'll tell you
why it's not good to use it like we do
because inflammation
is not something that's a lone wolf it's
not something that appears on its own
okay it's not something that just
evolves and appears like magically just
you know or
curse I mean a curse whatever right I
mean it's not it's not something that
just develops it's not a lone wolf okay
I'm trying to paint the picture here I'm
trying to paint the picture here for you
instead it's it's a sign okay it's a
sign but there's there's a problem here
okay there's a problem think about this
for a second okay here's the problem you
know
inflammation is not an answer it's not
an answer I'm just telling you right now
it's not the answer it's not a answer so
my back hurts you know it's inflamed oh
that's the answer okay that's it no it's
not the
answer it's not it's my knee my knee
hurts it's been inflamed for a while
it's I don't know what's going on with
it my knee's inflamed um you know or no
my knee hurts sorry about that my knee
hurts you go to a practition or my knee
hurts it's inflamed oh it's inflamed
that's all okay it's inflamed no that's
not it yeah yeah of course there's
inflammation there but that's not it am
I being a little too silly today is that
what's happening so listen it you know
that's not the
answer right right so you know that's
the whole point oh you know my gut I
don't know what's going in my gut
there's something going on there um you
go to a practitioner well you know
there's inflammation in there oh okay
that's what it is I'm inflamed all right
okay no that's not what it is it's not
the answer so inflammation as answer is
equals wrong which equals big mistake
actually it's one of the great mistakes
one of the great mistakes you know I
talk about great mistakes it's important
to really just know those but you know
and I go into great detail great detail
about inflammation that I'm not even
going to cover today I go in great
detail in uh the thyroid healing book
that I can't even there's no way to
cover all that that thing's so packed I
can't even I can't even go there in a
show but but the bottom line is is that
you know it's not the answer it's not
aone wolf it's mysterious it's
mysterious and to the medical community
is alternative conventional it is a lone
wolf it is and it's a mysterious Lone
Wolf but it's not it's not
mysterious there's there's something
behind the mystery there's answers
behind the mystery there's there's
reasons see
inflammation
occurs from two things two things just
two can you believe it we have the human
body we have the human body your body
right our bodies right we have that and
look what's going on millions and
millions and millions and hundreds of
millions of
functions thousands and thousands and
thousands of chemical
functions per cubic inch of the physical
human body scien research hasn't tapped
into any of them okay and and all that
going on all that mystery all that
mystery I mean my brain Burns to the
ground when I start going into a asking
question war with Spirit when I start
doing that when I start saying you know
if I'm saying if I'm if I'm feeling kind
of fresh if I'm feeling kind of fresh
and I want to torture myself and I'm up
for torturing myself and torturing my
brain and and exploding it I'll just go
you know I used to do it a lot more with
Spirit but right now I just do it for
the books I do it for the books I try to
I try to you know I try to pull as much
truth as I can out of spirits much
unbelievable information that's
incredible for our healing to move us
forward on this planet advaned
information and I and to for the books
and I I I burn my brain out just just
asking Spirit of zillion questions and
getting and then you know and going on a
spirit's on a tangent with information
that's just too much for me and you know
what happens is and you know when I'm
doing that when I'm doing that spirit
will be like well this organ has this
many chemical functions and these are
some of the chemical functions and it's
like too much it's like oh my God I
can't even believe that that that that
will be in that will be in textbooks
down the road hopefully if science gets
there 500 years from now but the point
is the amount the body is doing the
amount the the body is
doing is is so vast and what's happening
but guess what there's only two
things two groups of of
things that cause inflammation can you
believe that right that's simplistic
spirit said to me there's two things I
said there can't be two things because
I've talked to you uh uh thousands of
times spirit in my life and you you the
the human body is way too complex when
we even go to the brain you know with
what's happening with the different
varieties of heavy metals and how they
group and how they create Al Alo and how
they interact with each other with radio
signals and all kinds of stuff things
that nobody knows about nobody knows in
the health field Spirit tells me about
and how can there be just two things for
inflammation and spirit said there is
there's injury I was like oh okay so you
mean you bang yourself or car crash or
you know you hit your elbow the other
day boy my knee my knee hit the corner
of a chair the other day I got to tell
you guys that was that Lit it right up I
was just like wow that was I was I was
really walking quick I had a piece of
paper in my hand I was walking quick I
was trying to get around to the office
and banged my knee on a real you know
uneasy chair sticking out so hey here's
the deal so injury is one so you
everybody's had some form an injury
right no matter what it is Sports Injury
exercise injury um you anything anything
you could be walking along and twist
your ankle could be walking along I've
done that I've done that remember years
ago I was just
walking um and and you know wasn't
thinking I was just you know was just
listening to Spirit was totally into
What Spirit was saying you know I was I
I walked off of a curb kind of twisted
my ankle a little bit was like geez PE
you know you can and I've seen people
really who have come to me that have
they've Fallen you know really hard you
can injure yourself ice forget it ice
that's a whole another game every winter
I hear it all the time every single
winter people like just break
their break their butts and you know
here's the deal that's that's one way to
get inflamed and the other one is
there's only other there's only one
other only one other and you're going to
say how can that be this is this is
what's really cool here how can that be
where it's just one other when you know
there's this other practitioner or
doctor or expert says that you know this
food can inflame you and this food can
inflame you and this causes this and
this causes this and we're going to air
that out no there's one other thing and
it's an Invader it's an
Invader an
Invader okay that's the other
inflammatory maker too that's it human
body is so so darn complex with so many
chemical functions and so much going on
it is utterly utterly insane and you
know two things for
inflammation okay injury sure you can
injure yourself in hundreds of different
ways but injury or Invader and there's
hundreds of different different Invaders
that's right hundreds of different
Invaders but it's two things so so
here's the deal though you know you tell
somebody else that you know you tell say
uh you know you tell a hip doctor that
that's you know totally in alternative
medicine conventional mix and they're
doing great things totally respected
absolutely I know a whole bunch of
amazing people in the industry and
people I don't even know and they'll say
no no you know wheat wheat causes
inflammation that inflames you um you
know certain foods uh can inflame
people no no not at
all see wheat gluten gluten itself
doesn't inflame you what gluten does it
feeds something it feeds something that
inflames you it feeds an Invader and
that is not out there now and what
little is is because I've I've killed
myself to try to get that out there in
every way
possible and that's how it
works it's important to know I mean I
know people in their 80s I mean the crap
they eat I can't I mean I can't even
tell you maybe you know somebody I mean
they're eating pound cake for God's
sake or whatever they're eating you know
cupcakes I'm not talking about like a
brand muffin which still is loaded with
God knows what in in so many cases
talking about cupcakes you know
cupcakes right with fondant on top or
whatever you call that
stuff you know and and I mean they're
fine they're not even in I look at them
I can't find inflammation in them I
can't find inflammation unless they
twist their hip or something they're 85
and they bang their you know back
against something they fall they you
know then I see the inflammation but
I've had you know people at 80 years old
people at at 70 years old people at 90
over the years I'm not talking about a
lot of them but they've had them and I
mean they're eating chocolate cake I'm
talking like just horrible chocolate
cake you you know in a
restaurant not talking about some kind
of holistic restaurant or health food
store that's got a somewhat of a healthy
chocolate cake that's still got coconut
o not coconut you know canola oil in it
and still got you know natural flavoring
and and and the icing or whatever it is
that's that's bad the point is is that
talking about the real bad stuff just
lar just Pig lard
and just and God knows what okay
chemicals and everything right I'm sure
you guys have you know tried your fair
share over the years of some something
like that but the point is the
inflammation is not off the chart is
very little very little existing and
some people have seen and it's like you
just shake your head you shake your head
and you say to Spirit well what the hell
is going on here and spirit says well
that they're missing something I said
what are they missing they're missing an
Invader or they're missing an
Invader that is doing something that's
you know you know real dormant Invader
hasn't even come out it's just not even
coming out to play so it won't even
create inflammation it's so dormant
or they're missing an Invader completely
I've run across a couple of people what
am I talking about Invader talking about
pathogen pathogen I like the word
Invader now because when I say pathogen
people are like what what's that
pathogen you know I run across that a
lot well I could totally get it pathogen
is just a weird I don't know like who
knows what a pathogen is it it's crazy I
was even talking to a friend I haven't
talked to years I was like yeah well you
know I think you know I think what
you're dealing with I said is a pathogen
because be showing me this right here
and they said what's a
pathogen I said an
Invader and he said an Invader what do
you mean and
he here's here's here's the deal so
could you to run across people that
don't have it they could eat all the
gluten they want they could eat bread
they could have sourdough whatever right
and and and they could have
baguettes with fet of cheese on it like
lots of feta cheese on a bag baguette
they can have a brisca with mozzarella
cheese on wheat
bread okay so they can you can keep on
going on they get a fish sticks and
batter fish sticks they can eat fish
sticks all day long fish sticks with
Mercury fish sticks with Mercury and and
and some kind of you know really low
grade egg wheat batter corn wheat egg
batter on it fish stick
I don't know if you guys have ever had a
fish stick um know chicken fingers in
some you know terrible restaurant
terrible restaurant or fast food
restaurant chicken
fingers the point is is they could eat
this stuff yeah sure sure sure there's
other things in that food that could
eventually tip something off like create
the worst
worst kidney stone ever the worst gall
stone ever yeah and I see that in these
people say sure I'll see an 80-year-old
that has a whole pile of
stones he Stones
everywhere all right because they've
been eating that that chocolate cake
they've been eating those cupcakes with
that crazy fondant on there they've been
eating whatever and you know and they
got those big big stones and sure maybe
that stone hasn't aggravated that that
gallbladder by trying to get stuck in
the duct remember that's an injury
that's an
injury the gall stone gets just stuck in
that gallbladder there and it's jammed
in the duck
that's an injury that's not an Invader
so then inflammation starts that's an
injury that's an internal
injury okay that's an internal
injury you see
and my annoying today or what with this
inflammation thing it's just it's it's
fun to talk about inflammation but it's
not fun to have it I'm going to tell you
right now I've seen people so inflamed
it's
heartbreaking and and it and and it can
it can injure the soul it hurts so much
it hurts I've be seeing people suffer
and we're going to go into some
different kinds of inflammation so you
you get you kind of get what is going
on so when it comes down it's it's this
catch all we throw around it's just
catch all word we throw around now in
the industry we just throw it around but
it's not the answer so important to know
what's going on so if you got something
like a knee surgery you had because your
knee wore out
and it wore out so you got a knee
replacement but you're not
recovering and the doctor doesn't know
why and they're thinking about going in
there again and doing some work the
surgeon is thinking about going in there
again and doing some work and it's just
not calming down nothing's
happening that's because something else
is happening in the body and then you
get somebody else meaning like meaning
somebody else might just get a you need
replacement they're perfectly fine
nothing going on they're walking in 3
days and healing really quick the other
person has 6 months of recovery and it's
swelling all the time that's from
having an Invader in the body too so the
Invader was most likely there putting
inflammation that was chronic on the
joint to begin with on the knee joint to
begin with which then led to the the
knee to wear out cartilage bone on bone
metal on metal we call it like the brake
system on a car and then knee
replacement occurred but no one fixed
the
pathogen The Invader that was in the
body which is normally Epstein bar when
that happens with knee Replacements and
hip replacements and people don't
recover quick enough and it takes time
and but that's what I mean that's how it
works giving you kind of a kind of a you
know quick rundown of different ways
that's happening so inflammation alone
is a great mistake but the mistake is
not trying to fix inflammation even
though mistakes are made trying to fix
inflammation all the time the mistake
isn't made relieving it even though
sometimes mistakes made relieving it but
no it's still we're watching out for it
the mistake is using it as an
answer it's a lazy lazy
term but I'm trying to you know give you
truth trying to give you truth truth
that's not tampered with truth that's
clean I have to say that a lot now you
someone said to me the other day are you
really going to say this at the
beginning of your
shows about the clean information versus
you know inflammation that's been you
know with strings attached and all this
other all this other crap and all this
stuff are you really going to say this I
go yeah because people don't realize it
people I had somebody actually say
something to me a while back and say oh
oh your information you're in your show
I mean you're probably just picking it
up from everybody else there's more
advanced in no it's not true that's not
true that's not true that stuff's
contaminated most of it is anyway
because of because of funding funding
has to go into it when funding goes into
it the outcome has to turn out a certain
way or you going to pissed off your
investors and that's how health
information is created both alternative
alternatively
conventionally um and and chronic
illness especially chronic illness
especially that's what I mean and so
let's talk about these Foods so you talk
to somebody and they're like no no there
there's foods that can inflame you no
there's foods that will feed a pathogen
to cause more
inflammation that's what's going
on like for you know Celiac and the gut
or anything there's different kinds of
inflammation in different places
and you know let's cover some of it all
right you you're with me on this you got
hey did you fasten your seat belts got
to say it again terrible I got to always
say it I know did you your seat belts
there's different kinds of inflammation
you ready brain
inflammation brain
inflammation it's easy to get different
kinds of brain inflammation and nerves
in the brain that go to the brain and
run down through the body those nerves
can get inflammation neural neurological
inflammation that's nerve
inflammation different nerves can be
inflamed from
pathogens pathogens heavy metals
technically don't inflame something they
feed a pathogen or Invader to inflame
something because heavy metals is a food
had another practitioner a long time ago
um because I'll never forget this I
think it was about I don't know a year
ago or something over a year ago so it's
quite a while back and this practitioner
said to me you know heavy metals cause
inflammation I go no heavy metals feed
they have to feed something to cause
inflammation they're like I just it it's
it's this is important information from
Spirit that we have to know I I you know
having everybody in the dark too long
it's just it's getting too painful I'm
getting older it was cute and fuzzy and
fun when I was younger and thought I'd
live forever
okay I thought I'd live to be 500 years
old because when you're younger you just
you just feel indestructible even though
Spirit made it clear to me I wasn't as
much as possible but the point is the
point is is when you're younger you you
think you got all the Time in the World
is what I'm trying to say to get this
information out I remember telling
spirit I remember saying yeah yeah yeah
there's plenty of time for that we'll
let the information out and spirit's
like no you you don't you don't get
it you got your life time to get it out
but it's it's there it's it's going
backwards out there you have to try you
can't just click on the
TV and sit inside your living room and
expect this information from me being
Spirit to get out there and change the
course change the course of time to
change the course of Health change the
course of what's going
on I'm like no there's no rush I'll just
watch this old episode of some sitcom
there's no rush you know being a kid but
there but but it matters it matters and
I'm and I'm I'm I'm on the train of
rushing it so brain inflammation gut
inflammation gut small intestinal tract
inflammation you know like sibo for
instance trepac cacus we covered that in
the sibo show right colon information
such as like the shingles virus that's
causing
colitis or even a basic you know
irritable bow you know strep causing
irritable vow strep is a real big
irritable vow IBS
deal you know pathogens pathogens and if
you're a big parasite believer real big
parasite believer just know that these
are the the very things that show off
shell casings and show off um all the
different broken uh viral bodies and
showcasing that science doesn't have the
tag on so when it comes out to a stool
sample you're alternative practition say
you got parasites I don't care what name
you use you want to use parasites you
use the word parasites are there
parasites yes there's parasites but
parasites let's talk about parasites for
a second going to have to do a show on
actually you know what I'll do a whole
show on parasites because that because
it's going to get everybody angry
because the belief system around
parasites is so tightly woven right now
that I'm afraid to even touch it because
I'm just going to get just get people
are going to want to punch my lights out
so I have to make sure it's explained
with all the details from Spirit so it
can be easily
understood instead of just saying a one
blank statement you know don't get lost
in the parasitical thing because there's
a lot of problems going on with that
that I got to explained and then
somebody getting really mad so we're
going to do a whole show on that there
are parasites okay for anybody who's all
of a sudden starting to freak out right
now there are parasites okay so don't
don't don't worry okay I'm just going to
explain really what's happening and uh
hopefully by the end of that show you're
you're not angry as a Bee
um it's all about it's you know it's all
about you know you know getting the
information out and and trying to get it
out in a way that that obviously works
for all of us here's the deal here's the
deal um with with like the gut
inflammation we have all these different
pathogens that get inside the gut and
cause an inflammation in the gut I mean
you got se you got you got a whole bunch
of different bacteria bacteria is really
a leading thing that sits inside the
colon in the gut and everything and then
you got the viruses you know all
different kinds cytoma virus you got all
the different herpetic viruses you got
all the shingle viruses you got the
Epstein bar varieties you got all the
mutated hhv 6es and everything else you
got them all undiscovered hhv 10 11 12
the whole name it all Gets In The Cut
causes trouble so then when you eat some
wheat or you know whatever wheat gluten
and you eat it goes down the a pike and
it finally gets there there's a Feeding
Frenzy and now you're like oh my God I'm
constipated I'm feeling a belly ache I'm
feeling you know I'm wheat intolerant
I'm gluten intolerant um you know I got
Celiac the doctor says I have Celiac
Celiac is just an it's just it's not a
genetic not a genetic disease or illness
it's an
inflammatory illness it's an
inflammatory illness because pathogens
so um so so then next thing you know you
know Celiac you got that going on
and um and this is this is due to all
that kind kind of stuff in the gut organ
inflammation organ dense organs so forth
you know not just Hollow inflammation in
the organs any organ really liver can be
inflamed how does the liver get
inflamed how why would a liver get
inflamed every you know you wouldn't
believe how many livers are inflamed I
can't even I I hate going out I hate
going out I hate leaving the
office okay and I hate having to go
somewhere I hate having to have my
assistant drive me around in the car and
go somewhere cuz I'm just going to be
read I'm just going to be reading liver
inflammation but what's under and what's
causing the liver inflammation I mean
literally drive you insane you're just
spirit's just talking to you like just
just literally talking to you there's no
there's no shutting that off can't shut
that off I can't be like oh I'll go on a
cruise with my friend I'm a psychic
medium medium or I'll go here and do
this and no there's no shutting it off I
can't do that I can't have the fun in
between at
all so you know be in the car and just
literally at the stoplight that person's
got a liver problem that person's got
inflammation of the liver that person
has inflammation of the liver you know
you go into a restaurant I had to meet
somebody in a restaurant and I'm in a
restaurant and I'm like asking spirit is
there food poisoning on this is this was
there was was the chef playing around
with raw chicken and then and then put
my salad together I mean was you know or
put my dish together was the million
questions I have to ask Spirit while I'm
in a restaurant to make sure that I
don't get the worst food poisoning of a
lifetime end up in the in the ER and
intensive care seen people in intensive
care because of food poisoning it breaks
your heart over just stupid mistakes
done in the kitchen and restaurants so
you know it's all that but the liver I
see I see people the liver problems is
unbelievable
unbelievable and um so the bottom line
is what's inflaming the liver pathogens
pathogens whether it triggers off liver
en enzyme issues you know whatever Bly
Rin issues whatever it's triggering
off it you know whether the MRI and Cat
Scan starts seeing damage and then tell
somebody they have Hepatitis C by the
way that's Epstein bar long-term damage
in the liver causing hepatitis C ABD
ABCD is all
viral but but you might you might say
well ABD ABC d got to learn my alphabet
today you might say that that's you know
hepatitis A B C and
D tongue twister you might say that they
already know that that's viral they
don't know what virus it is did you know
that medical research and science
doesn't know what virus it is they just
go by inflammatory
markers they go by CAT scans MRIs and
inflammation they don't know what kind
of virus it
is Hepatitis B they don't know what kind
it's just a that's just a stage of
inflammation they don't know what kind
of bug it is I'm going to tell you right
now hepatitis C no one knows what kind
of bug that is hepatic liver inflamed
liver viral they find you know what's
amazing about research and science they
actually know this is amazing I find
this incredible they actually know you
know and I used I shouldn't have said
this years ago I think it was I think I
was being challenged by a couple of
doctor doctors they were really upset at
me they were upset because I was I was
you know had this information it was
like and they were like and this is in
the early days this is in the early days
this was like 15 years
ago and there's earlier days than that
but what what was happening 15 years ago
and a couple of doctors wanted to talk
to me because they wanted to know how I
figured out something and it was
accurate I told them how I figured it
out and how how it happened he said that
just doesn't make sense hear your voice
told you that this is what's going
on and I said yeah yeah yeah hear it
again here we go here we go here we go
again I was I know was like probably 17
or 18 years ago or
something and and you know and and and
they were like well no you couldn't have
heard a voice to know this you couldn't
have known that this liver was this bad
off and had the scar tissue it had in
the corner with a cyst in the corner ALS
scarred up and hepatitis C at the same
time there's no way you knew that
without some kind of documentation tests
and to confirm it some kind of blood
work where did you get this information
I said well I'm telling you where I got
it and you know and then and they said
and they said you know what I we were
going to we were going to we we wanted
to congratulate you on figuring this out
as a colleague but because you said you
heard it from The Source you heard it
from which is Spirit we're not going to
do that we're not going to we're not
going to give you any we're not going to
congratulate you I said you know what
you know what I was going to
congratulate you because what you stand
behind the research and science that's
given to you you actually know that
hepatitis C is a virus you know you
don't know what kind of virus it is but
you know it's a virus and I was going to
congratulate you guys for the fact that
you even know it's virus
but now I'm not even going to do that
I'm not going to congratulate you either
and they sat there they were baffled
because because yeah because they didn't
know what kind of virus it was but they
knew it was viral and they were like oh
yeah well okay and it's true because
it's hard for research and Science and
no and with the liver with hepatitis A B
and C and D it's a hepatic inflamed
liver they haven't singled out those
viruses they're not singled out I don't
care what anybody says because they have
not singled out those bugs at the blood
lab I'm telling you right now it's 17
years later still hav figured it out and
it's it's it's a herpetic
virus it gets in the liver and causes
different stages of what they deem
hepatitis different stages of
inflammation inflammation is not the
answer what's behind the inflammation is
the answer that's the great mistake
Ste do you guys still with me you still
with me skin inflammation you know we
also you know we see inflammation as the
body attacking itself that's a whole
another thing the body's attacking
itself you know autoimmune that's a
disaster disaster the body doesn't
attack itself I said it a million times
in these shows inflammation there's a
cause for inflammation and the cause
will never be the body attacking itself
and that's what happens with liver
problems too with mystery liver mystery
liver inflammation inflammation and be
like well it's autoimmune in liver it's
autoimmune hepatic problems it's
autoimmune uh um going on in the liver a
doctor will say profession will say
medical communities is say no there's a
cause so you
know here the bottom line is is that the
body doesn't attack itself we get
inflamed for those two reasons I told
you you can cut get a cut it's an injury
you can get dental work it's an
injury you can get an injury it's you
know you could bang your elbow against a
wall it's an injury you can get hit by
something it's an injury the other one
is the other side is pathogen Invader
okay whatever that Invader sinus
inflammation whole another one whole
another one inflame sinuses that's
always strap that's strap that's inside
the the the canal sinus Canal that's
that's always strap inside the Linings
sitting in there forever I'm not talking
about when someone has a bout of strep
and they got the fever in the strep
throat and it's at that stage talking
about chronic long-term bending your
system since you're a child sitting in
the
sinuses unless you catch the flu cuz
there really are no
colds it's really all flu it dominated
there are no just Rhino viruses anymore
those are those are dead and gone those
got taken
over that's the flu is the flu is the
owner of all colds whether small great
large the flu is the owner of them so
you get the flu whether it's in the
spring because there's a flu every every
two months All Summer Long all spring
long all winter long it there there
there's a flu going
on causing inflammation when it gets in
you that week or two man you're inflamed
I it could blow out your adrenals it can
inflame everything the flu inflames the
gut it's a virus it's an invader it
gives you sinuses in inflammation chest
inflammation causes bronchitis you're
coughing your butt off it's inflaming
your
lungs so you know and then eye
inflammation you can have eye
inflammation from anything any kind of
meaning any kind of bacteria gets in
there sty you're you know you touch a
door handle you're going into an office
building and 50 people grabbed that
handle and didn't wash their hands when
they went to bathroom that morning or
came came from the coffee shop and
touched every dirty handle and device
there is and didn't use a handy wipe and
they're all touching the door at the
office and you just go and grab that
door and open it up and you're running
into a coworker and they got you busy
and then you rub your eye and now you
got a sty or you rub your eye and you
got the flu three days later four days
later or you rub your eye and you got
some other staff in there causing it to
run and and and give you like sneezing
and running because that's how you get
the inflammation in
there glaucoma glaucoma is a virus
that's actually one of the viruses from
the Epstein bar family one of the
mutated forms that goes after the eyes
causes eye problems like glaucoma it's a
whole different kind if you got Epstein
bar doesn't mean you have any of the
Epstein bar varieties that do any of
this there's a lot of different
varieties I could talk about the
different groups of medical meum book
one if you don't have medical medium
book one and you're listening to the
show I I'm sad I'm sad
I want you to get it because you need to
read
it and
um anyway so so that's giving you a kind
of the gist on this of how it works like
what's happening and giving information
around all these things neurological
inflammation nerve inflammation
fibromyalgia
fibromyalgia severe chronic fatigue
syndrome chronic fatigue syndrome is is
is uh brain inflammation it's
neurological fatigue very mild brain
inflammation somebody can't do anything
they can't even function their brain's
inflamed
and the uh the fibromyalgia but you know
inflammation is not enough you go to the
best specialist there is with
CFS I mean all the different varieties
of CFS they keep on renaming it all the
different varieties of
CFS you know you go to the best
specialist they might you might get
somebody to say you know I think you had
brain inflammation
but from
what from what virus we're still so far
off we're still so far off I mean I'm
lucky I don't know about lucky but I
could ask spirit and say well what wood
virus is in this person's brain that's
inflaming them so bad that they can't
get out of bed at all and they can't
even walk or talk what virus is it and
spirit will tell me spirit will say well
it's you know it's Epstein bar spirit
will say it's Epstein bar and shingles
it's both spirit will say it's Epstein
bar shingles and
hhv6 you know I'm lucky I can get that
so I can get the information for people
in the
world but you need you go into you go
into chronic illness world of today and
you just can't get
answers and and yeah sure I didn't
realize that when I was when I was 10
years old 11 years old Spirit kept on
telling me and said you don't understand
Anthony this has to get out there and
you have to work harder on it and you
have to care you also have to care and I
do
um you know this just kills me actually
so what people go through
so let's talk about some other things
with this with all of this so we got the
fibromyalgia I was mentioning we got the
rheumatoid arthritis which is
inflammation that's not the body
attacking itself they're going to chalk
up fibro eventually to being completely
autoimmune which I think they already
did I think they might have thrown that
one in there by now where the body's you
know body's destroying
itself and the body's not destroying
itself cu the body doesn't attack itself
the body is there helping you protecting
you and an Invader is causing the
inflammation so you know here's here's
the deal with inflammatory
tests let's cover a couple of them all
right you got the C reactive protein
test which is worthless because it's
it's just roundabout getting you know
looking for inflammation in in different
ways this is just just to let the doctor
know there's
inflammation and then you have the ESR
Rosy sedimentation rate I don't know if
you've ever had that one but that's
another one the doctor can order at the
lab and that one is just another type of
inflammatory test to see if you got some
some type of inflammation and maybe they
can throw a bogus label like lupus on
you because they don't even know what
lupus is or how it works or anything I
don't even the best guys don't even know
yet and I wish they did I I say these
things because I hope it's it it
instigates someone to say okay I am
going to go out and find those answers I
am going to get funding without without
the thumb scale being pushed by by you
know by interest groups I am going to
get clean funding I am going to get the
answers for this so we can figure it out
I'm I'm not going to just blame
everything on genes anymore because
that's where science wants to go because
that's where the money's going and so it
puts the blame on you I want to find the
answers that's what I hope someday
because I can't do this alone and you
know I rely on you guys too you know
getting the information out so there's
another test called PV plasma viscosity
it's another inflammatory
test and but that's another one that
that just looks for around about
inflammation okay there's another test
IG you you guys know the IgA
test and what about the you know
immunoglobulin G test which is
IGG you know that one okay it's just an
inflammatory test that's what that is in
the end you still don't know what is
causing the inflammation this is so
important to know I hope I'm not boring
you guys today I'm hoping I hope I'm not
I hope I'm not um ana anti-nuclear
antibod test and we also call it antibod
antinuclear antigen test I've seen you
know a lot of practitioners call it that
I've called it
that and that's one too round about
inflammation liver
enzyme blood work
test that's another one that's another
one and it's got a couple of cousins too
there's a couple of cousins also that
are being used meaning cousins not
people but uh tests called cousins
Sister Sister
sister tests of some of these liver
enzymes and other these tests that are
being developed but they're just for
inflammation they don't discover what's
wrong and the cause of your inflammation
and that's where it hurts man that's
where it hurts I call these guest tests
these are called guest tests that's what
they are and here's the problem here's
the scary part here's the problem that
really Spooks me if there's something
that wakes me up at night I'm going to
tell you what it it is and if this gets
you angry if this gets you angry just
you know don't don't quit listening to
the shows because I need your help I
need you learning this information don't
quit listening to the shows don't stop
you know don't get
mad but here's the problem all those um
inflammatory guest tests are being used
against us with Lyme disease because
what they're doing is they're filling in
the blank they're putting in their own
names of bacteria next to those
inflammatory markers but yet not finding
the bacteria itself and that's what
they're doing all at the new
labs and it's painstaking and
painful and so then you know you get a
lime D so all you need is a little bit
of inflammation and you got a lime
diagnosis now like honestly everything's
getting funnel to Lime before you
explode or get mad listen to my lime
show or I'm going to do an update at
lime show or or go to the lime chapter
and medical meeting book one if you if
you haven't gotten that you have to get
that you can't just get mad at me for
talking about Lyme disease because of a
ingrained belief system you might have
and not get that chapter out of medical
medium book one and read it it's unfair
you got to you got to get it and read
it
and even I mean really cuz I want to
help it's about helping and if you're
suffering even more so
reason even more so
reason so what happens is the all the
anti-inflammatory tests are being used
in the labs and it's a disconnect from
the doctor the doctor who orders the
Lyme disease test has no clue that the
labs are actually taking all those
inflammatory tests and then they're
filling in the blank with the
bacteria if that wasn't the case there
would never be a borderline you either
have it or you don't you either have the
bacteria whether it's Boreal b bellia or
some other bacteria or babesia whatever
it is a parasite whatever it is you
think you have it's either you have it
or you don't
not borderline so when the labs do the
inflammatory tests and they put the name
bellia next to a little bit of
inflammation on the score sheet ship it
to the doctor and the doctor has no idea
that they didn't identify the bug why do
you think so many people come back
borderline you either have the bug or
you don't it's one of the mistakes that
they're probably going to fix it the
labs because they know someone's
catching
on just telling you
so here's the deal here's the deal
everything's getting funneled into
inflammation but with no
answers the only thing I like about the
lime disease trap the lime trap which is
very little the only thing I like is
that they're actually equating
inflammation to a pathogen even if they
have the wrong
pathogens even if they have the wrong
pathogens even if they're picking on
bacteria that isn't what's behind
people's lme suffering and there's
another pathogen behind people's Lyme
suff suffering why do you think every 10
years they're going to come up with a
new
bacteria and say then and then basically
Outcast the old
ones why do you think when Lyme disease
was first discovered in 1973 when it was
first discovered right around on that
time the every doctor every doctor on
every board knew it was viral and they
all agreed it was viral but there was no
treatment so they had to go to
antibiotics and then demon bacteria
later in 1981 the point
is and if you're getting upset about
this listen uh it's all good call listen
it's all good let's you know we're going
to do a new show on that we have to it's
about time the bottom line
is I'm just glad in the lime world
they're equating inflammation to a
pathogen thank God thank God I'm so
happy for that so if you want if you
want to know the truth I'm happy about
something because that's the whole point
like I said back to square one there's
two things for inflammation there's
injury and there's pathogen even if you
got the wrong pathogen even if the
doctors got the wrong pathogen they
think it's a bacteria they don't think
this even if the doctors don't know
hepatitis C is Epstein bar even if the
doctors don't know that this is you know
this is this this inflammation from this
is this kind of pathogen if they think
pathogens related we've already moved
forward thank God and that's the whole
point and I love that part about it so
don't get mad if you hear me talking
about lime if you're a big lime fan just
you know just look into what I've
already talked about before and it'll
make more sense because I can't do it
justice in four minutes let's talk about
Foods anti-inflamatory Foods I pulled
these right out of the life-changing
Foods book pull them right out of the
life-changing Foods book how do you like
that Spirit created life-changing
Foods the book life-changing Foods so I
can now go to it spirit said don't go
around me I said what do you mean it's
your information it's in the book spirit
said don't go around me ask me Direct
don't go into the book I said what are
you talking about and then spirit said
fine I guess Spirit was Spirit didn't
want me going around
them even though it's his information in
the book in the book it says garlic is
anti-inflammatory why because it kills
pathogens figs are anti-inflammatory why
because it kills pathogens in the gut
figs just don't eat so many of them
where you're just just just you're
eating too many just take it easy CU if
you're filled with pathogens the figs
can be tough kiwis are actually
anti-pathogen in the body and in the gut
lemons and limes are antiviral
antipathogen anti- Invader they're
anti-inflammatory these are why these
foods are anti-inflammatory pears pears
are
anti-inflammatory anti-inflammatory for
bacteria eoli salmonella everything
anti-inflammatory for all pathogens
strep viruses Epstein bar pears for
God's sake
AE Rosemary time Sage oregano and your
food is anti-inflammatory why it kills
off pathogens you guys nettle Leaf kills
off pathogens lemon bomb kills off
pathogens licorice fruit licorice fruit
tea kills pathogens why because licorice
root is the the enemy the enemy at
Epstein bar cyega virus hhv6 Jingles h v
h v VS1 herpes simplex one Simplex 2
and all of its cousins licorice root is
an enemy because it's anti-inflammatory
because it kills it aloe vera you do the
aloe vera water go to my blog I know I
got the aloe vera water there somewhere
do the aloe vera water look at
life-changing Foods Book You'll see the
aloe water right there you'll see the
aloe and you know that's one something
right there you'll know how to prepare
it know how to use it it's right there
the anti-inflammatory
but there's other foods that have
life-changing foods that kill off
viruses and kill off things apples
incredible wild blueberries amazing
anti-inflammatory food okay different
greens all the you know ruga incredible
for you in anti-inflammatory lettuce is
anti-inflammatory any kind kale
anti-inflammatory kale kills off Epstein
bar that gets inside the thyroid causing
Hashimoto which till this day you you
know I can't believe even our best
experts on hashimotos don't don't
understand how that works yet get the
thyroid book the thyroid healing book if
you can just you know order it when you
can just uh you know please have that in
your library because you're going to you
won't be sorry you won't be sorry I
didn't let you down with life-changing
food somebody told me recently they said
you're right you know I heard you on the
radio show you said life-changing Foods
is is you know you're not going to let
us down and I doubted it I got the book
you didn't let me down so I'm going to
get the next book don't miss my live
webinar autoimmune answers go to
medicalmedium.com and sign up and um
look
guys when when it's about healing let's
get in more more those fruits and
vegetables keep out the
anti-inflammatory foods keep out the
wheat keep out the gluten keep out the
dairy milk cheese butter milk cheese
butter yogurt kefir keep it all out keep
it all out if you're inflamed if you
think you're inflamed keep milk cheese
butter yogurt keep it all out okay keep
out the eggs keep out the pork keep out
the canola oil keep out the corn bring
in some more of these Foods you know
what to do you know what to do okay
apples peaches plums nectarines Cherries
Berries bring them all in melons mangoes
papaya papaya is an incredible
anti-inflammatory food for the gut it's
amazing bring in different herbal
teas and you know start
healing God bless you I love you guys
thank you for hanging with me thank you
for go you know going for the ride with
me take care you know I care bless you
byebye see you next time okay