on and i want to give everybody the
4-1-1
that's what's happening i want to answer
a couple questions too so
i want to make sure i'm helpful i answer
a couple of questions
i'm here but i'm going on tick-tock
live in a little while so when i go on
tick tock live i'm going to be doing a
bunch of different stuff i'm going to be
answering questions
thoroughly that's what i've been doing
on the tick tock lives
answering questions thoroughly another
thing too
not only that making things yesterday's
tick tock live
i made my salad right there the whole
bid because it was really cool
doing all that and then also today on
tick tock live
i'm gonna be making food i might even
make cranberry water
the famous medical medium cranberry
water i'm going to see i might do that
so that's coming too so on tick tock
live that's what i'm going to be doing
and i'll answer a couple questions here
but
but letting you know that on tick tock
live i'm going to be answering questions
thoroughly if you haven't set up your
your tick tock account you really should
um because honestly i'm doing all kinds
of stuff i'm doing different content
doing stuff i never did anywhere else
and in the whole bit it's so i'm letting
you know
it's it's you know it's really i'm
looking forward to having you guys come
there
and uh but you got to keep your
notifications on on tick tock so what
you do is you
hit the me at the right hand corner at
the bottom right hand
and you hit the me then then you see the
three dots at the top on the right hand
up there
you hit that and then you go in you'll
see the notifications you want to put
your notification on for the live stream
and um and and you really also want to
go to your tick tock app to the app
itself and make sure you're set for
notifications as well
but you don't want to miss these a lot
of stuff
while agreeing said hi anthony love
seeing you play the drums yesterday
that's the tick tock uh it's really
funny
um live in concert um
joanne moore says hair loss for years
for women's hair loss it's a lot
different than
it's entirely different than men's hair
loss women's adrenals
have a hormone in them
that is what keeps hair on
your head and that so that's what what
happens there and so
women lose that hormone inside their
adrenals that one specific hormone
that keeps the hair follicles alive and
they lose it because of years of
caffeine from years before
so years of caffeine of all kinds
chocolate
coffee tea whatever and and even if it's
green tea
and so no one tells you the caffeine
industry and i talk about this medical
media podcast at apple podcast you guys
should be listening
to the 17 episodes that just did at
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
it's it's a docu-series it's free it's
it's you just can't miss out on it so
packed with
information to heal and so in the
caffeine episode i talk about this
the the hair loss that comes years later
but the caffeine industry they don't
care
they won't they don't they don't care
the industry itself it's just
drink the coffee drink the tea eat the
chocolate
and then boom hair falls out down the
road and and it's
it's doesn't have to be that way but
this is what they do
um so we got to restore adrenals joanne
for sure we got to go into adrenals i
don't know if you have plans to heal i
even have a protocol on that for hair
loss
uh for women so you might want to check
that out you get this free at the
library
i mean you can i had a friend the other
day that just walked into a library
and got a copy of cleanse the heel out
of there um
so you can get it amazon too but um
but let me letting you know that that
i'm gonna be live on tick tock
and it's it's a whole different type of
live
whole different type of experience um
i'm gonna be making food gonna be making
some cranberry water i think i'm gonna
be doing that gonna probably make a
salad medical medium salad
at least a salad for me to eat today
because
so if you don't mind i'll be eating with
you too and
so i'm going to be doing that i'm going
to be answering questions thoroughly
lorraine ells here hello hey hello
lorraine
hope you're doing good hope all's well
i'm proud of you i know you're working
hard on everything you're doing all the
meditations you're doing
you're doing all the good stuff and um
and you're you're an expert in medical
medium information i mean from what i
can see
i read your comments and in youtube i
see your comments in youtube all the
time and
and incredible what you're what you do
incredible what you do
um so yeah um so look
i'm just letting you guys know this i'm
here right now too and i wanted to touch
base have you guys listened to the
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
though i mean
in all the different episodes the egg
episode
i mean that one alone neurological
symptoms episode the air fresheners
episode
anxiety episode the caffeine episode
fruit fear episode
chemtrail episode chemtrail episode
scary oh my god
it's scary and um and then all brain fog
episode
the uh the whole bit and i got another
one coming soon but
letting you guys know hey jessica
caldwell
says did the fruit picking meditation
and slept so soundly afterwards
that's what i hear out there the medical
meeting meditations
the fruit picking one the brain
meditation the moon meditation the
stargazing meditation the fruit
i would said the fruit picking
meditation already right and freeze the
bird meditation
they re they really help heal on a
subconscious level
heal the soul and the emotional turmoil
in people
and it puts you to sleep at the same
time while your subconscious mind is
being guided in healing
um so sonja says the podcasts
how do we access them um medical medium
go
go to apple apple podcast and look up
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
that's the best way to do it because
that's the uncensored
platform if you have an android and for
some reason you're having a
trouble i hear people can get to apple
podcast with an android
but if you're having trouble go to
medicalmedium.com go to the menu you'll
see my
you'll see podcasts in the menu you can
listen to it there
um uh deanna says i fall asleep
listening and wake up to episode in the
archive that's funny
in the archives right you'll you end up
listening to one of those
we're live right now guys that's what we
are
um deanna good to see you this time i
know you're here
all the time or every now and then it's
good to see you know i recognize
the faces so glad everybody's coming on
board um
so i'm gonna be on tick tock today it's
probably gonna be i'm gonna do an
instagram live for a short time
after i leave here and then from there
i'm going to tick tock live
really set up your account you know set
it for notifications for a live stream
you won't be disappointed i'm going to
be making food i'm going to be answering
questions
thoroughly thoroughly i want people to
heal i want you guys heal um
you guys know i'm censored on this
platform right and just letting you know
i'm sensor i'm censored on youtube
censored on facebook and i'm censored on
instagram i don't know if you guys ever
knew that
okay uh so anyway
sandy says loved your drumming and
singing i also love the fruit picking
meditation
actually all of them are so healing
sandy you actually you did the uh
stargazing one too
and you did the moon meditation i'm
honored i'm honored incredible
incredible secret journey uh you got a
question
how to heal chronic pancreatitis the
first thing i would do if i had chronic
pancreatitis
if i had that first thing i would do is
lower fats
you've got to lower fats and then i
would bring in like kabocha squash i
would bring in delicata squash i would
bring in some potato
i would bring in all that i would bring
in some fruit i would bring in
of course some leafy greens but what i
what i would do is not bring in the nut
butters
not bring in the oils not bring in the
chicken
meat chronic pancreatitis get off animal
products
and i'm not anti-animal products i mean
i'm pro-vegan
i'm pro-plant-based for sure for pro
plant-based and pro-vegan but i'm also
i'm pro-animal products
diets if you if that's what someone
wants to do but when i'm not pro
is doing everything wrong and people do
vegan diets wrong
plant-based diets wrong animal protein
diets wrong they just do the diets wrong
and but if i had chronic pancreatitis
i would get off the animal products gone
right there because you can't
heal pancreatitis while eating pork
while eating
chicken fat you just kill your pancreas
you want your better
you can go back to that if you want uh
byra says i love the meditations and
have been doing them almost
every night sometimes two to three in a
row
please keep on doing them because then i
know you're healing share them with
other people please please
uh leave a review at apple podcast leave
a review at medically podcast
apple podcast please leave a review if
you liked them
it helps because i get trolled out they
just they just
troll me out and they just it's amazing
you know
the uh the uh discrimination because of
where i get my information
and because i hear a voice since a child
like haven't i've been through enough
you guys have no idea like
pete they have no idea you guys have an
idea but um
but yeah so lucas says
can you explain function of tonsils
please
mine are swollen very often any idea
thank you much anthony
um that well first of all your your
tonsils are part of your immune system
right there that they're part of your
immune system so your lymphatic system
and tonsils are hand in hand okay that's
to protect you right
but what happens is the tonsils get
inflamed when we get streptococcus that
are
that's chronic doesn't mean you're gonna
see it so when the doctor does a swab on
your throat
on your tonsils doesn't mean they're
gonna they're gonna be able to culture
that
because it gets deep in the tonsils not
on the surface
streptococcus epstein bar mono all those
things those are the things
that keep tonsils swollen but they go in
undiagnosed doctors don't know
so if you were a family member or
somebody they can because i had a family
member come to me last month with
swollen tonsils
and a cousin and i was like look
that's that's low grade viral and
streptococcus go to your doctor
talk to them about it but that's what
that is and so what i would do if
my tonsils were swollen is is i would do
um some some epstein-barr protocols or
some
you know anything in the medical mean
books i would heck you know what i would
do
is um i would go back into all the
different symptoms and conditions back
here
and i would look at the mono one or
anything like that i would go back there
and look at that
that that's something that i would do
take it to your doctor you could talk to
them
um glenda says thanks for all you do for
us i'm honored are you going to
tick-tock with me
in a little while um keep your
notification on for the live stream you
guys
the videos don't save at tick-tock so
once i do that live stream that's the
only way you're going to catch me
i'm going to do things on there like i
have been in the last three lives on
tick tock that i don't do anywhere else
i answer questions thoroughly not only
that
not only do i do that but i'm going to
be making food i'm going to be eating
with you guys whatever we're going to do
so i'm letting you know so i hope you
come over with me it's going to be in a
little bit
after i get off here i'm going to go to
insta and then i'm going to go there
i mean seriously i hope you guys come
phoebe says meditations are all on the
new podcast
absolutely are that's where they are
five meditations
holy cow medical beam podcast at apple
podcast you can't miss those
um luke luke skull can you heal your
eyes
you're always got glasses on it mustn't
be good too good
well luke here's how it works with my
eyes okay so that you know
and if it depends on how long you've
known me
because a lot of uh people who know the
medical medium information and know
about me and stuff
i could see fine i could read all your
comments just like this
there's there's nothing wrong there what
happens is
i hear a voice and when i hear that
voice
that voice is very hard on me and i hear
it very
loud and then because all you guys are
on
all right i'm getting information so
information just comes through while i'm
here with you
then i get what's called snow blindness
because of it since i was age four
when i get the information from spirit
of compassion and i start
getting that the visuals and start the
the reeds start coming in and all that
stuff
it squints my eyes i squint them so if
you want to see me squint
you're going to see me squint this way
if you put the glasses on you're not
going to see me squint so much the
glasses kind of hide it
it's a technique i've used my whole life
don't need them
you know i don't have to have them but
then my whole life people are going to
see me and once i get the reads
once spirits talking to me once that
white light is coming down
i'm going to start squinting a little
bit like this you see this that's how it
works
so when that happens it's better when
these are on when that's happening
that's how it works i don't need to heal
my eyes i got the best vision there is
actually that anybody can have
so i'm just letting you know right there
and how it works for squinting and
everything
lorraine l um i'm so you know you know
lorraine l says i'm still in love with
all the meditations nothing else like
them so i mean i could read perfectly
fine
and that's not a problem got great
eyesight for that you know so
heather says any help for psoriasis so i
don't need the glasses
and i people have said that before but
when you learn about medical medium
information you saturate yourself in the
books
you won't have questions like that or
concerns or however
but but good question good question and
i hope you come to tick tock
um so yeah so here's the deal you guys
so manny says i'm having trouble
accessing the apple podcast huh
i don't know why i'm i'm wondering why
you're having trouble with that when
it's at your bummer because
that would be so great um go to
medicalmedium.com
so go to medical mandy go to
go to the menu and you'll see podcast in
the menu access it that way if you're
having a hard time try that
chalene said alzheimer's advice
absolutely
um toxic heavy metals
toxic heavy metals tell your doctor
about heavy metals
that's the thing right there maybe maybe
the heavy metal detox
cleanse in here bring that to your
doctor if you want have them see if they
they like the idea um
and so because the toxic heavy metals
oxidized but if you go to tick tock i'm
going to answer questions
thoroughly it's something that that that
no one's really seen me do quite quite
over
in recent times anyway so when i go
there so i'm going to go to tick tock
going to be on there live set your
notifications get you know all of it
hey lorraine says brilliant answer to
the glasses question
that's funny you make me laugh lorraine
you make me laugh plus you got a really
good sense of humor i've seen that in
the comments in youtube
um so
darlene says my gut is not well even
with celery juice how much celery juice
are you doing how long have you been
doing it are you keeping the eggs out
the dairy products milk cheese butter
think about those things are you keeping
gluten out keep that in mind
christos has a spirit inform you about
the coming
world war three so well i all i can tell
you is this just so you know
as far as anything my my hobby
my part-time hobby is getting that one
minute a day
where i can ask spirit of compassion
questions i want
answers for about the world and
anything happening and what's going on
you heard me talk a little bit of that
in the chemtrail episode
listen to the chemtrail episode and
medical media podcast at apple podcast
and you kind of get it just on how
spirit of compassion works
how the information comes um
so yeah so mia why do i get loose bowel
diarrhea about 20 minutes after celery
juice should i do less you can do less
of course you can do less and bring it
down
you're killing bugs back to bad bacteria
in the intestinal tract that's why
you're killing
bad bacteria and you're flushing out
garbage that's been attached to your
colon for
years that's why that's why you guys
i'm heading over to tiktok though i'm
going to go to instagram for a couple of
minutes
then i'm heading over to tiktok i'm
going to be making food if you guys want
to eat with me that's great
i hope you all listen to the medical
queen podcast at apple podcast
and listen to the 17 episodes really
it's packed with information it's for
free and there's no commercials in there
and it's not making me a penny
so when you listen to it you don't have
to sit there saying oh i'm getting this
guy rich
i have no advertisements on it no money
coming in from it
it's solely a work of love to make sure
you
heal medical mean podcast at apple
podcast it's a docu-series
i got the brain fog episode the anxiety
episode the neurological symptoms
episode
i got all that but just checked it out
but listen
get your tic toc tick tock account going
make sure you set your notifications for
the live stream live stream coming up
the live stream coming up hey we're live
there you go make sure you set your
notifications for the live stream
on tick tock i'm going to be making
foods and answering questions
to the tilt and anyway
love you guys bless your heart okay i'm
going to instagram for a couple minutes
to let them
all know about tick tock