and this is in a nutshell to make it as
easy as possible you need two things to
be chronically ill two things to have a
symptom that won't go away two things
that makes your life say let you know
the less quality of life two things have
to be there toxins and pathogens you
need two things there that's what you
need and that's what's happening
everyone's building a lot of toxins up
and they're catching a lot of pathogens
that's what's happening and bottom line
all these illnesses everything behind
autoimmune is a virus or even bacteria
involved or both and some poisons for it
to feed on so to make it really simple
really simple you have certain toxins in
your body and they become food for
certain bugs pathogens pathogens eat the
toxins they release a poison and we all
get sick and sicker and sicker