have you guys had a chance to do the
meditations
the moon meditation that's a really good
one to do
it's free it's a medical meme podcast at
apple podcast
star gazing meditation that one right
there
really powerful another one too fruit
picking meditation
free is a bird meditation when you take
a flight so healing for the soul
and the brain meditation to that one too
have you guys been doing them
um
geneva says premenstrual syndrome
yeah we what happens with that is
because 80
of the immune system goes to
your reproductive system during your
cycle and right before your cycle you
start
you start what happens with women is
their immune system starts to
to reduce everywhere else in the body
and right when you're coming on to your
cycle
the immune system goes to the
reproductive system
and then all this pms happens and the
pms could be
anything because anything else you're
struggling with
anything it comes to surface
and it comes to surface in a big way and
then it gets blamed on the woman
in so many ways like oh it's your pms oh
it's just your pms
your pmsing you know that's your problem
that's your hormones you're hormonal
you're just crazy
you know that's what they did all these
years they blamed it on the women it's
just like oh it's your pms that's what
it is but really that's not what it is
there really is stuff going on like real
things happening
it's just and your immune system is
going to your reproductive system
and when it does that um
everything else just comes out other
problems that are really in there like
adrenal imbalances
digestive issues
streptococcus you know acne can come out
anything and when all you know just
being real tired and you get cranky he's
tired you don't feel good and that's
what's really happening hey everybody
glad to see everybody here i'm actually
excited about tick tock because
i don't know if you see in this frame
right here this picture frame over here
what side is it is it that time you see
over there you'll see some food and
stuff
i'm actually going to be making dinner
on tick tock and answering questions
thoroughly
um cool cornelius says hello anthony
just got notification for this live
awesome so glad you're here that's so
great um
not so great so good to see you guys
livia says hi
hey how are you um amazing
good afternoon lee awesome michelle l's
here
why don't we have more help to support
our cycles
um well that's the thing you know it's
the the things that we deal with now
in our life in the last 100 years didn't
exist 200 years
ago didn't exist 300 years ago and what
people don't realize is
chronic illness with women that's new
yeah yeah there was disease sure
but it but not what we have today as far
as
all of the path pathogen and heavy metal
toxicity based conditions
and other toxin based conditions and
we never had all this and so women are
up against things that
weren't meant they weren't meant to be
up against this wasn't supposed to
happen in human nature
but but you know evil evil evil people
on this planet
created a lot of bad situations and it
fell upon
women and men too it fell upon men too
but it fell upon women and
that's how this world's designed i mean
this world is can be a really dark place
i mean let's be
let's be straight about that i mean you
you gas and and murder six million jews
yeah
that think about and then genocide all
around this planet in different ways and
places and you think about that this
place is a really dark place
and yeah we could see the light in it
and we can see the good in it too
i mean the good that is here on earth
but wow
some bad stuff and from bad people and
so
and so yeah we're not supposed to have
all these pathogens that
medical research and science the private
industry did and did you hear about that
in my medical
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
i talked about this medical mean podcast
at apple podcast the egg episode i
talked about what happened there
what they did to our egg all of this and
but yeah no we're adapting michelle
we're i see your question there
we're not adapting though we are we are
we just have to use the tools to adapt
we have to keep on using the tools to
adapt and we can override these things
we can get better we could rise above it
absolutely so i don't want you thinking
otherwise because you can get better
i know michelle you're dealing with a
lot of strep and other stuff and
um yeah you can get better so i want you
to know that
alexandra i did mm to support my cycles
it transformed my periods from painful
my whole life to normal
all mm protocol amazing alexandria
incredible
um dixie d says you're so right
um yeah and
you know you guys it's like it the
bottom line is i want want to make sure
you get this
information and you heal and i
appreciate it everybody coming on right
now i'm just looking at all the comments
as everybody's
pouring on here so that's really cool
i'm doing tick tock
pretty shortly after this i'm just going
to spend a couple minutes here you guys
with you guys
and then from here michelle said
genocide indeed yeah totally
and from here i'm going to ig for a few
minutes too
just not yet deanna dia you're here
what's cooking today glad you're here
awesome
and from there i'm going to tick-tock
when i go to tick-tock we're we're gonna
be making
food and we're gonna be answering
questions thoroughly i hope you guys
come there terry king
says love the tick tock caffeine video
chewing
last night i started the moon meditation
automatically
as it was setting so oh awesome at
bedtime the star gazing seemed automatic
as well
who knows next i knew it was morning
whoa
that's really cool yeah the caffeine
episode or episode the caffeine video on
tick tock
and did you guys see that did you see
that video
i want to give you one inside piece of
information about that video okay
it was not sped up it's in real time
because someone said to me a family
member said to me who saw it today
said was that like sped up and no you
can't speed it up on tick tock when the
music's playing
you'll see me lip sync sing the lyrics
yeah there's you can't speed up you have
to be in just real time
that's the only way the app works and i
just want to let you know that that was
in real time that was not sped up a
little inside piece of information there
lorraine l hey you're on here hi anthony
tick tock is really embracing you and
people are loving it congrats thanks
they can't believe it
that's i'm so glad you feel that way and
you're seeing that
um so yeah you guys um
anyway i'm excited about making some
food on they're gonna make my dinner
and gonna answer questions thoroughly so
you guys are doing the meditations i see
that
you guys are you guys are taking
advantage of those free meditations
um and i'm glad you guys you guys don't
want me to charge for him or anything
because i was asking you guys i think i
was asking on tick tock
i was asking do you guys want me to
charge for those maybe
that should that should that happen or
it's like 500
for a package of meditation so this way
this way
people feel like you know they they
since they pay for it because that's the
word out there in the street
once you pay for something then people
really take it seriously
and um i don't believe that's true i
think that i call bs on that
i think if you make it free and it's a
quality product actually a quality
healing tool and practice somebody can
get their
life back i think people can recognize
that i know you guys do
um rachel brown says suggestions for
healing with
graves disease that's the epstein-barr
okay
so it's it's it's in order to get better
it's important to in order to get better
it's important to know
like the information of why you're sick
it's one thing to have graves
but what is it um okay well
you know you had you had a blood test
the doctor says well you got a thyroid
problem you got graves
it's an autoimmune condition but where's
the answer
like i want to know where's the answer
so if i had graves disease i want to
know what that's going on like
what's wrong like what what's happening
does that mean my body's attacking
itself what's going wrong and
so that's what i would want and i would
want an answer
you get an answer and then you could
really heal because then you know what
you're doing you know where you're going
and so i put information in here for
hyperthyroid hypothyroid hypo hyperol
that graves
so it's in here so you know what's wrong
and then some protocols you could take
them to your doctor if you want to
totally do that um says love the
meditation's incredible
that's incredible so yeah you guys um
draker says i appreciate you doing this
what a service thank you so much liver
cleanse has been very helpful to me
awesome uh draker that's that's really
cool
uh christina i joined tick tock and
followed you yesterday but haven't seen
any lives
ah the live is gonna be shortly after
here david witchen's on here just saw
that
the live is gonna be shortly after here
so i'm going to go to
to ig and spend 10 minutes on there and
then boom
i'm on the tick tock live have your
notifications ready i'd love to see
there i'm making dinner and i'm
answering questions thoroughly and it's
going to be very
very consistent and we're going to do
what we need to do
you guys i'm heading over to ig now uh
brutina
bettina says you're too generous you
guys are generous too i love you guys
listen uh peggy schneider i just saw
listen you guys i'm heading over to ig
now
i'm going to be on there for 10 minutes
and then going right to tick-tock
and making it happen fast today so
people get a chance to see from
different parts of the world
i noticed that i've been doing them
later and what's happening is
that people aren't able to see it so all
right heading
over to to ig live i love you guys
keep the faith polite heart have
compassion for yourself
keep on working on your healing process
you can get better you can get better
take care