that's the question and um i'm going to
be on tick tock live
uh from here i'll go to instagram live
real quick for a bit and then
tik tok live gonna make dinner i got
some of it prepared over there i can see
it in the back in the back
corner there a little bit's prepared
some is not
quite ready but a little bit's ready and
who knows what i'm going to throw
together today
so that's going to be fun um i want to
answer some questions too why i'm here
of course
and help out in any way i can i want to
help you guys
for sure um anyway
excited hello good to see you guys great
to be here hi
hello hello everybody saying hi um
morning in australia huh incredible
when's the next podcast episode i'm
working on it
i'm working on it have you guys listened
to all the podcast episodes it's been a
lot of incredible podcast episode 17
powerful ones five meditations really
incredible
hey love from sweden sweden amazing i
want to answer questions for you guys
there's alexandra
i know michelle elson i know you guys
are on
there's nicole elise good to see you um
rick's on so many people on here this is
incredible you guys
josh is on and so i want to answer some
questions i want to help out in any way
i can
it's important because i want everybody
to be able to move forward and heal
and get better and get better and get
better and get better because it
matters it matters you guys have to
remember your body
wants to heal it's looking to heal
and it wants to heal you always have to
remember that i know that when you're
going through it
and you're sick or you've got a symptom
or a diagnosis and you're struggling
and you know you're just in it and
you're in it for so long right
i know when that happens that that it
feels like you're not going to heal
or it feels like how can i heal i still
got these symptoms or my body is
struggling
and it feels like you're not going to
get anywhere with it
but the truth is your body
wants to heal it just needs to tools to
heal
long enough it just needs enough tools
in your tool chest to heal long enough
meaning
it just needs some tools applied and
then them
used long enough so you can heal
it's such an important thing to know
because your body
your immune system is working for you
it's
working for you you just have to support
it you have to acknowledge it
you wake up in the morning feel like my
immune system is working
it got restored last night it's going to
help me get better
my symptoms are going to get better i'm
going to get stronger
and stronger and that's what's going to
happen so you got to remember that you
go to bed at night
and you're like my immune system is
working for me my body is working for me
i live my
liver is going to do some healing
tonight some deep healing
it's all this matters you got to
remember that you guys i wanna invite
you over to dinner
at tiktok i got some food in the back
you'll see it
i see you back there okay um and
michelle l says my immune system got
sick of me
that's pretty funny no your immune
system
loves you it loves you your body loves
you unconditionally you know that
michelle
your body loves you unconditionally and
it wants you to heal
carolina frisk says love your tick tocks
incredible i'm honored
and i'm excited to do more tick tocks
you guys the tick tocks are going to be
like this some of them
some of them are going to be
informational you know me like talking
about certain things like juicing celery
or something like that
and or holding up a fruit and talking
about or a vegetable or a leafy green or
herb or wild food
and then the others also are going to
probably be a little bit a little bit of
fun a little bit of humor too okay
like you guys know um with a message in
it with a message in it of some kind
right
monica says good evening from austria
amazing
uh so you guys i want to answer a few
questions i'm here i'm talking about
stuff
what stacy what am i drinking lemon balm
tea what does lemon balm do it's
antiviral
it's antibacterial antiviral
antibacterial okay you could also take
it in
tincture form two that's the tincture
right there that's
that's the vimergy one but you can take
it in tincture
it's the only one that i really love the
most but that's it right there that's a
powerful lemon balm tincture right there
and i talk about this for anxiety
anxiousness tightness of the chest
you know that feeling of you know a
feeling of
you know panic attacks to you coming on
all of that
but that's the real this stuff is really
potent i mean i drink
the lemon balm tea but i take the lemon
balm anyway
just just every day that's what i do i
almost missed and almost
i almost missed and almost squirted it
off to the other direction
that would have been really bad a mess
um but yeah that's that's the beverage
lemon balm using victor i am is mary e
rgy i'm not sponsored or anything but
i love that company i love a lot of
companies i talk about a lot of
companies talk about the wyman's
blueberry wild blueberries i love
and other things like that
bridget bridget says i need to heal from
anxiety
well did you first of all bridget
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
did you
listen to the anxiety episode so much
information to help you heal in there
and then there's the cleanse the heel
book which you see behind me right there
you see the cleanse the heel book
and it's called cleanse the heel get
that on amazon
or free at the library i have an anxiety
section in there you should have that
too i mean seriously you can really
heal when you have the tools it's so
important
um but i'll give you a little quick
rundown too on
anxiety that's the vagus nerve and the
phrenic nerves so the vagus nerve and
the phrenic nerves
right there so if you're having
tightness a chest if you're having
panic if you're feeling like you're over
stimulated if you look at the tingles
and numbness from having a panic attack
if you feel like you can't breathe if
you feel like you want to just
run away and scream if you feel
claustrophobic in a car
if you feel like you can't you feel like
you're going to always have these weird
feelings in the stomach and the gut the
like anxiety in there
whatever's going on and i talk about all
the symptoms in the anxiety show the
the medical mean podcast but but i'm
just covering a little bit
those nerves are inflamed that's one
thing that can happen the phrenic nerves
the vagus nerve
so that your anxiety nerves right there
you get the nausea with it my god you
can't get the nausea but that's the
anxiety nerves right there you got the
vagus nerve you got the phrenic nerves
right you guys
and anxiety is a neurological condition
and it's from real things happening you
know
two things happening low-grade viral
issue like having the epsine bar in your
system all these years
and the epstein-barr can release a
neurotoxin the neurotoxin swells up the
vagus nerve and phrenic nerves and then
you're dealing with mystery anxiety and
you're like oh my
god what am i going to do i got panic
attacks anxiety attacks right
and then also toxic heavy metals can do
it too
mercury aluminum right mercury and
aluminum we have them in our brain we
have a monovagus nerve we have a
monophrenic nerve we have them in our
liver and that metal
can also do it too these two things
toxic heavy metals and viral issues and
then there's emotional wounds too you
guys
you can get the anxiety from emotional
hits emotional blows emotional bullets
and betrayal broken trust
getting your back stabbed getting you
know getting like
broken promises trust broken you know it
could be divorces broken relationships
broken friendships
losses and then that heats up
the emotional center of your brain so
when you get
you know like something comes your way
like what what kind of news is that by
the way the anxiety
you can look in here and you can find it
right in this book you'll see anxiety in
this book
and um i mean this book is so packed you
guys know that i think you guys have
this book
every time i think everybody has the
book nobody has the book or something
it's really strange
when so many people do around the world
so that's anxiety and anxiousness i talk
about supplementation protocols dosages
take it to your doctor you can take it
to your doctor and talk about the true
cause of anxiety
and take the book to your doctor
and ask them for help you know you trust
your doctor you love your doctor take it
to your doctor and be like look here's
the anxiety here's the dosages and
supplements
and ask your doctor's advice if you want
um
but i gotta tell you those the emotional
center of the brain the emotional core
okay the emotional center of the brain
it gets calloused
because it heats up so it's like you get
told something bad it's like hey
oh my god what is this wait what ha
what's going on this is terrible getting
broken up with wait a minute you
promised this
i'm having a or having a dispute or
something with a friendship with a
friendship or a friend or whatever it is
whatever gets sent your way or you read
an email and it's disheartening whatever
happens in your life you
the the brain heats up it heats up right
in the core just starts heating up
and once it starts heating up then
anything can go wrong and one of the
things that goes wrong is from that
constant heating you can get a little
bit of a wear and tear
on brain tissue on neurons on brain
cells right in there in the emotional
center of the brain
and you get a little tiny callous they
can heal up but
but that's what goes on there i talk
about in detail in the anxiety episode
medical mean podcast at apple podcast um
clarissa how to get rid of rosacea now
you got to learn
what rosacea is for what it's really
important to know what it is
and what's causing it and all that get a
little bit of mercury in the intestinal
tract
go tell your doctor about that you know
so they learn but you get a little
he gets a little bit of strep in the
system a little bit of ebv in the system
so you know what happens is when people
have bacteria and
and viruses in their body and in their
system they'll get the rosacea all over
the place
so that's that's the toxins at surface
um toxic heavy metals are involved with
that too
um i mean if i had rosacea
if i had any kind of rosacea stuff i
would i would do
probably like three six nine cleanse
that's what i would do personally i just
put a
a friend that uh that contacted me with
rosacea and they said how do i get rid
of my rosacea and i was helping them out
telling them what to do 369 cleanse they
could do the original
or the advanced one if they want um
but you know you can do what you want to
do and say what you want to do talk to
your doctor too
i you know and another thing is if i had
rosacea i would make sure the gluten
wasn't there right no gluten
i would make sure that milk cheese
butter milk
cheese yogurt kefir butter
sour cream i don't know i can't anything
else i would make sure it's not there
and you know it's gone i would make sure
the eggs weren't there
and i would start thinking about
bringing in some of the foods that you
see over there
because i'm inviting you guys over to
dinner to tick-tock live
i'm going to answer questions thoroughly
and i'm going to be making food so and
it's soon too it's actually
coming up pretty soon i'm going to go to
ig and then go to there but
that's what i would do rosacea is making
sure that there's no there's no
nutritional yeast
because nutritional yeast will keep
rosacea around i'm not saying you eat it
but it might be in a packaged treat
or it might be something you know that
you're doing or in a
in a restaurant dish just look out for
nutritional yeast
um that's one thing i would would kind
of keep away from
also kind of if you want another tip
it's
keeping your fats a little lower just
try not to make your day all about fats
and you know that's all these animal
proteins all day long
or all these plant fats all day long
try not to keep the fat so high you know
lower it a little bit if you want to get
rid of rosacea
that's important right there like what
i'm saying is maybe do the medical
medium morning cleanse
celery juice uh lemon water first
celery juice and maybe one of the
medical medium smoothies
uh maybe the heavy metal detox smoothie
so you can you can get rid of things
you can heal people heal thousands of
people have
a lot more than that actually for sure
so yeah
so much you know so you guys were
heading over to tick tock that's where
we're going pretty soon just giving you
the 4-1-1 having
having dinner the whole bit and you guys
going to have dinner with me because i'm
excited all right
i'm excited about it because i'm gonna
answer questions thoroughly and i got
the food
all getting ready over there so yeah
anyway guys which brand of liquid
vitamins do you recommend
selena it's the vimergy it's the best
one there is
and out there without a doubt hands
hands
hands down um and that's the lemon balm
right there says vimergy v is in victor
i
am as in mary e rgy that's their b12
that's their liquid b12
check them out vimrgy.com or go to
medicalmeme.com
uh the directory i got there it's
definitely the best company ever
i mean it just is do a little b12 right
here
but it's the best company um
for a lot of reasons because they
actually don't play that game where they
put
cheap stuff all the companies put cheap
most almost every company puts cheap
ingredients in
and they're all about how many pennies
they can
save and then put out this product and
it's really a game
and it's terrible you know and they put
other stuff in there and the whole bit
it's just really a horrible thing this
company doesn't do that
anyway i'm not sponsored by the way i'm
not sponsored i'm not a sales rep
and i'm not sponsored i'm not sponsored
by wyman's either or traditional
medicinals
companies i love i'm not sponsored
always got to say that
because it's important to know i mean it
just is so yeah
can i talk about keratosis polaris um
you just you honestly when you get your
liver a little bit better
and you get your hydrochloric acid
stronger are you doing celery juice are
you doing 32 ounces of celery juice are
you doing
16 to 32 ounces of celery juice every
single morning you could do even more
start cleaning that gunk up that that
dehydrated
putrefied junk that's on the linings of
the colon and intestinal tract and that
rancid fat that's on the lining in the
colon in the intestinal tract
and you just start drinking that celery
juice clean up some of those
troublemaker foods i talk about in
cleanse of heal
you know and work on getting getting
that better and you can
you can uh teresa says you're truly
amazing
sending you love from australia
incredible
um all that you guys back here i'm just
saying
i got the i got some food back there
letting you know
and looks good i see some scallions
sticking up back there
i see some peppers i see some broccoli
all kinds of things i'm going to make
dinner with you guys on tick tock
i'm really excited really excited
um you guys
so anyway look i'm going to go to ig for
a little bit
and then from ig i'm going to go right
to tick-tock so it's not going to take
too
long and then that's where i'm going to
answer questions thoroughly and i'm
going to make dinner
it's going to be fun and i'm actually
really excited
vanessa says love traditional medicinals
thank you traditional medicinals
best tea brand the best tea brand i've
come across
ever um lorraine says nice and uh so
best tea brand i come across yeah and
i'm not a sales rep for them
i'm not sponsored but i'll tell you
right now because your stuff is so
incredible
i'll shout it out and i'll shout it out
let's what you guys do
about medical medium information you're
like his books to save me
you guys always like do shout outs and
stuff on the books to get people better
out there same with the podcast i know
you guys share
it the meditations remember
think about doing the meditations the
moon meditation you should be doing
right now
definitely should be doing the moon
meditation right now without a doubt
um because of the half moon this is the
time period around that you should be
doing that
um tammy says i'm drinking lemon balm
and hibiscus too
incredible that's so good for you so
good for you
pressing princess here nice from the uk
right
but i got to tell you i got to tell you
overall just so you know the meditations
are a big deal medical medium podcast at
apple podcast
do the moon meditation right now for
sure and maybe the star gazing
meditation okay guys i'm going to head
over to ig i love you much and ig for a
little bit and then boom
tick tock we're doing it fast all right
bless your heart love you guys
i'd say about you know right now it's a
half moon so just letting you guys know
right now is a half moon time to do the
moon meditation this is the time to do
it right now just letting you know
so yeah keep that in mind hey loon
loon's here lunell
whoa and uh luna are you going on tick
tock
i hope i hope you guys are going on lune
you did that potato poem
and i heard that potato poem the night
spry the
the potatoes the night's bride and the
whole bit in there
actually it was a really amazing poem
that was a really amazing poem she's
gonna tell you right now all right yep
okay guys um catherine henderson says
bought your book cleanse the heel whoa
and can't find the moon meditation you
had mentioned
oh my god medical medium podcast at
apple podcast
17 meditations i mean 55 meditations
there will be 17 meditations over time
five meditations 17 episodes
and you can't miss it they're there the
moon meditation
you can't miss it um
natalia says i did the moon meditation
an hour ago
awesome all right guys i'm heading to ig
just for a short time
and then boom tick tock live probably
will be
um hey profile um
the pro my profile lights up
when i'm live on tick tock just just so
you know that my profile lights up when
i'm live on tick tock
pressing prince said moon meditation is
awesome absolutely love it so my photo
so my photo lights up on tick tock when
i'm live i'm letting you guys know all
right jill says how do i sign up for
tick tock
um let's go to the tick tock app that's
it and
and sign up you don't want to miss this
you guys it's so incredible
all right love you