new war waged against veganism and
plant-based people but just want to say
right now just a little disclaimer okay
you don't see on the medical medum book
series like veganism or vegan's the best
in the world or be vegan or these aren't
in the vegan section of the bookstores
either the medical medium books
plant-based vegan is great if you do it
stay with it but learn how to do it
right carnivore meat keto stay with it
but learn how to do it right that's how
it's done half of the medical medum
community eats meat the other half
plant-based you got to learn how to use
the tools and to apply it to what you're
doing and we're going to go into detail
about that but we're going to talk about
the war that's happening and how
veganism
is crashing down it's going down without
a doubt there's no doubt it is it's
going down now there and look before I
go into the war against veganism and
plant-based movement I want to talk
about an announcement okay the Gia heel
conference is November 9th you probably
don't know about it yet the guia heel
conference is November 9th I'm going to
be speaking there okay you can get
tickets tickets are limited check out
the link in the profile Link in the
description go to medical.com you'll see
the banner on my website so you'll know
hey that's how you can get there get a
ticket if you want to be there live to
see me okay I'll be doing a light blast
there and it's going to be superpowered
so I'm letting you know I'm going to be
doing a light blast there and I actually
at first when I you know when guia and I
were talking about hey do you know
you're coming to do this I'm like I'm
there I'm doing it and I was like do I
do a light blast do I not do a light
blast do I do a light blast do I not do
a light blast I'm doing a light blast I
don't care I don't care what happens I
just got to do it and I'm going to be
there okay because you know what it is
you know when I do a light blast it say
medical mean EV event it's you know it's
really comfortable right but I'm going
to be in Colorado I'm going to be on
guia stage and I'm just going to do that
light blast there and just say you know
what it doesn't matter I'm going to do
it I'm going to make sure it is a
slamming slamming light blast because
that's what we're going to do all right
so anyway um link is in the description
link is in the bio for the guia heel
conference I'm going to be there live
speaking tickets are limited you could
also see it live stream so I just want
to let everybody know about that so
let's go into it first of all by the way
Millet and Herb salad is what I'm making
right there so if you guys want to know
what's on the menu today you'll see all
kinds of stuff I got green onions right
there I got Tomatoes I got celery I got
a cucumber I got parsley I got all kinds
of herbs and then I also have some stuff
on the side right here I got some Millet
and I have some honey and some other
stuff so letting you know okay and uh
and I got some onions too got some
onions behind me I got to go and grab so
that's the recipe I'm going to be making
so I'm just going to get some Millet
going in here now because we have to
cook that Millet so let me get some
water really quick um I'm going to do
four cups of water
and I'm going to do two cups of millet
so four cups of water and two cups of
millet and doesn't mean I'm going to use
all that Millet I'm going to use some
doesn't mean I'm going to use all of it
so let me just get some more water here
okay boom
boom all right there we go I'm going to
get this Heat going all right here's
some Millet right here I'm going to drop
two cups right in there okay four cups
of water I think that's what I did all
right get that going I got my lemon bomm
tea right here too with
honey so okay let's go into
it have you noticed have you noticed the
new
war I mean they're armed with demons the
goal is to take down the vegan movement
have you seen it and so what happened
was as the in the last few years as the
carnivore world started to rise up they
got crafted
so the meat eater guys the dudes that
started hitting social right they
started hitting social and they're like
you know what we're going to take down
that vegan crap we're going to take down
veganism we're going to take down the
plant-based movement and we're going to
search to chip away at the Men start you
know calling them weak calling them
frail you know calling them feminized
that's one of the things that happened
so it was an incredible technique in war
and so the
the the animal-based movement the new
animal based movement which is basically
Atkins but then turned into something a
little different we're going to go into
that in detail too basically it's the
Akin
diet without some of the garbage in some
of the junk and then it's rangle and
repackaged into it's like the Atkins
movement the paleo diet movement both
ref
finagled reclaimed and turned into this
new version this mutation of carnivore
and keto and then dudes rose out of it
on social that's what happened they rose
out of it ready to slay and that's
really what happened and they're like
we're going to slay those vegans and
those plant-based people and we're going
to use all kinds of techniques we're
going to tell women that they can't be
fertile without meat that's the first
thing so all these women that were
plant-based and vegan and went there
because they weren't feeling well and
they weren't feeling sick decided like
wait a minute here I'm not going to be
fertile infertility is going to happen
I'm seeing dudes that are looking pretty
good on social they're talking about hey
if I stay vegan If I Stay plant-based if
I'm not eating meat I'm not going to
keep my hormones balanced I'm going to
have fertility issues I'm not going to
be able to have a baby when I meet the
right guy
you know something like that so what's
happening and basically that's what it
is that's what's happening out there
basically so a lot of women were falling
from Grace vegans were falling from
Grace so they would do all their posts
and all their social media posts and
they would say hey they would start out
like look you know my symptoms are kind
of coming back I've been you know vegan
for quite a while I gave it a year now
I'm kind of incorporating some raw milk
now I'm incorporating you know back to
some raw eggs or back to eggs or raw
eggs now I'm incorporating some meat now
and so their whole their whole platform
would be like wait a minute you had us
on this vegan ride for a year and now
you're telling us that you know our
hormones aren't really going to be
balanced and all these women are like
now you're telling us we're not going to
be fertile now you're telling us that
you're Switching gears and you're eating
eggs and you're eating meat and that's
what I should do and then the protein
scare the reinvention of the protein
scare developed where once again all
these dudes rising up on social all
trying to say Hey you know like let's
take out the vegans let's take out the
plant-based people let's hit them with
the protein fears again let's feed that
back on people amino acids proteins
let's feed all of that back on people
and then things like choline choline
choline you need choline you're not
going to get that you need the right
vitamins you need iron right back to
those old f years that our grandmothers
had right that are grandmothers had back
to some of those like iron right that
one too now you need to be eating liver
now you need to be eating beef organs
now you need to be eating hearts and
that's what you should be doing so this
movement's growing and growing and it
it's been the last four years but
getting a little heavier and a little
heavier and so the vegans and the
plant-based people have been dropping
like flies mostly the women just
dropping like flies
getting scared because they don't
understand their symptoms and they're
just getting the minute a vegan person
or a plant-based person gets a symptom
boom they're like now they're doubting
everything they're doubting the
plant-based thing and then they hear
dudes that are working out in the gym
and training and they're on social and
they're sitting there and they're
ripping apart soy boys and stuff and
they're making you know women feel like
their men are weak and fragile and just
they're soy boys and they're feminine in
and then they get told it's all out
there that if you're plant-based as a
dude you're feminized and so that's
another thing too so a whole massive
campaign of bullying has been coming
down on the vegans and the plant-based
people right so I don't know if you guys
have seen it but it's been happening so
all the dudes are being they're all
called soy boys now right they're all
feminized and so a lot of women are like
wait a minute I'm not going to get
fertile I'm going to have infertility my
dude is you know he's feminized my
dude's a soy boy this doesn't look good
I got you know so what's happening is
this war has been really really smart in
a lot of ways to take down the vegan and
plant-based movement and it did I'm
sorry but it did it pretty much
slaughtered it okay I I believe from
what I can see and tell and information
that I get above and all in the above
that the vegan movement was
bigger at at a around
pre-2000 than it is today right now the
plant-based movement and the vegan
movement was bigger a little bit pre
2000 than it is right now so this is
something to think about okay now if you
just got on here you're thinking wait a
minute wait a minute how you know how
does this work medical M information
medical M information is not against
plant-based it's not against veganism
it's not against animal protein it's not
against people that want to keto or
whatever they want to eat animal
products instead it's these powerful
tools that you can incorporate and then
you can learn what to avoid as a
plant-based person as a vegan person as
an animal person as a keto person
whatever it is things you can avoid so
you can take your healing to the next
level that's what medical medium
information always was and people used
to ask me all the time plant-based
doctors used to reach out to me some
I've known some I didn't know and would
say are you a plant-based book or not I
saw your book in the bookstore it wasn't
with all the plantbased people what is
going on aw what are you and what are
you not I'm like why does it have to be
that way my books are fill the tools you
can apply for both right there for both
meat animal you know plant-based the
whole bit and so there's always been two
sides of the aisle two sides of the
aisle you guys know this right you're
either plant if you want to call it
veganism because you're you don't want
to wear leather shoes and you don't want
to eat honey it's either plant and vegan
or animal and that animal can be in any
form Atkins
paleo um keto uh carnivore whatever it's
either plant-based vegan or animal those
are the two sides of the aisle that's
how the game's been played but in the
last few
years the vegans and the plant-base have
been
slaughtered slaughtered they have the
amount of animal protein doctors coming
out of the woodwork going on social
waging you know War campaigns the amount
of the amount of influencers that are
dudes that are just worried about their
masculinity and just you know trying to
say you got to eat meat and you know and
and the dudes that are plant-based are
just weak and you know frail and they're
thin and and all this stuff and so
they've really done a number and then
you know that wasn't totally enough to
push women out of veganism to push women
out of plant-base the key was you're not
going to be fertile your reproductive
system is going to dry up you're going
to have infertility if you're
plant-based you're not going to be able
to have a baby that was the kicker right
there your hormones aren't going to be
balanced properly balanced that was the
nail in the coffin right there so the
Meat Heads okay they did a good one with
that one and the soy boys they're kind
of like stuck because they don't know
the difference they don't know what's
right or wrong the soy boys they don't
know they don't know really what you
have to do to keep yourself healthy
they're just staying away from animal
right they don't know okay and then the
Meat Heads they like they put the nail
in the coffin on that one they just
hammered it in they they did it and they
did a good job they slammed that one
down everybody's throat and they were
like this is what's going to happen to
you you're a girl you want to be
plant-based that's not going to work for
you you're not going to be fertile
you're going to have infertility and
everybody went running and screaming for
the most part they pretty much won the
war just going to say right there pretty
much won the war now let's go into it a
little bit now some other stuff about it
so
uh are you guys with me so far we're
making some killer food which is really
amazing here crispy perspective Meat
Heads versus soy boys laugh out loud
that's what it is it's Meat Heads versus
soy boys and the soy boys don't really
know how to defend themselves and I'll
tell you why so get this this is really
an important part right
here they don't know how to defend
themselves because they don't know
medical medium information they don't
know why people are sick so when the
Meat Heads who get sick who get sick the
Meat Heads say to the soy
boys okay you're not going to get your
protein you're going to get sick you're
going to have this problem that person
problem your women aren't going to be
able to have babies when they do that
the soy boys they can't defend
themselves because they don't know
medical medium information they don't
know about the mineral salts they don't
know about the glucose they don't know
about how you can be keto and do it all
wrong you can be animal and do it all
wrong they don't know that vegan isn't
just vegan and period black and white
they don't know that plant-based is just
plant-based period in black and white
they don't know that so anybody who's
adopted different plant-based diets or
or vegan diets they did it high fat and
then the women that got on plant-based
did it high fat and when they did at
high fat they did not get rid of their
symptoms maybe they did for the first
few months and things were going along
or the first year and then it all fell
apart and that's a big deal all on its
own so I'm just turning this down a
little
bit the plant-based movement did not did
not learn the medical medium information
to save itself and now it's going
down it did not learn the information it
needed to learn to go into war with the
Meat Heads it did not learn this and for
that reason it's going down it is I
remember specifically four or five years
ago I was doing an Instagram live one of
those lives or something like that and
somebody came on there just like you
don't know it was it was it was some
plant-based people I think it was two
plant-based women or three there was
like one plant-based woman and then her
friend came on there too and they're
like you don't know what's going on out
there you don't understand this and that
and this and and all that I can
guarantee you right now they're not
plant-based anymore I can guarantee you
they've been switched over to animal
protein like probably a year after that
they got a symptom their symptom didn't
go away the Meat Heads came up told them
they weren't going to be fertile gone
boom gone they got eaten up because the
vegan movement and the plant-based
movement did not understand medical
medium information and did not learn it
they drowned themselves in fats
they got they got the natural flavorings
in the way the MSG in the way and didn't
know it kept them sick they got the
citric acid in the way they kept the
apple cider vinegar sure they were
plant-based but they kept the apple
cider vinegar and they kept the fake
cheeses the fake cheeses and they got
eaten up Alive by the animal kingdom
people they've eaten them up alive buy
shootout spit out the vegan movement's
pretty much dead gone bottom line get
this now here's another thing very
interesting okay somebody can go vegan
because they're worried about animal
rights they're worried about animals
they're worried about animals being hurt
animals being killed we know that
animals have souls yes but what people
don't realize is the minute their
symptoms came on that wasn't enough to
keep them in the game there's very few
women left in the vegan movement that
were worried about animals and leather
and worried about animal torture they
got symptoms wor heard some heard a meat
head talk about infertility and they're
gone boom gone didn't matter at all
about animals being hacked to death and
killed it didn't matter about cows being
knocked in the head pigs going into Pig
machines and all coming out ground up it
didn't matter
anymore yeah they got into veganism
became a vegan they did they didn't want
they all got vegan
shoes definitely and vegan sandals and
vegan high heels and whatever shoes that
they want vegan sneakers vegan whatever
the vegan boots they got all those okay
they they they were vegan for a while
and then they got their first or second
symptom again or they got symptoms for
the first time in their life because
they they went vegan because they were
worried about animal cruelty and animals
and all that stuff and then they got
their first symptoms and then their
doctors like you're not getting enough
protein or they go on social and they
see a doctor now on Social cuz what
happened was social media did not have
hardly any doctors on social media
hardly any were on social media years
ago they were just in practice they were
practicing and then the birth of the
social media doctor who doesn't practice
so it's the birth now of the social
media doctor who does not practice and
does not know their patients pain and
suffering who doesn't know really how to
heal their patient who's dealing with
pain and suffering they became a doctor
didn't want to do it it was too nasty
and dirty work they didn't want to
communicate with people one-on-one in
the office they couldn't stand people
sitting there complaining to them about
how they're sick and how this medication
didn't help or how this herb didn't help
that was in this mixture of stuff with
probiotics and they left they didn't
really get into it and they left so
there's a birthing of doctors that never
practiced they're not seasoned doctors
They Don't Know Jack they don't know
squat and they're out there on social
media screaming away and screaming away
and and and getting all kinds of bits
and pieces of information that's not
even from scientific studies and so
forth right also poaching and stealing
medical medium information along the way
as well get rid of medals you do it this
way get rid of medals do it this way
they didn't even know about medals they
went to regular medical school didn't
want to practice anymore got interested
in health now they're on social media
it's a group of them too that took down
the vegan movement that did a great
job it's a group of those doctors that
destroyed the vegan movement destroyed
it destroyed it it's a ghost right now
it's a ghost and I'm not on here
screaming because I want everybody vegan
and plant-based that's not it at all it
doesn't matter to me if you want to heal
plant-based you can do it through
medical meme information you do the 369
you do it you push through if you want
to heal doing animal learn how to do it
learn how to do it right with the animal
stuff and you can do it and you can push
through and you can heal I never took a
side of the aisle do you guys know this
you guys must know this
right you guys must know this hey so
when I turned plant-base there were many
vegan people with symptoms on social
social and vegan influencers did not
have answers they would always say you
are either detoxing or not do it right
and that buried them it did it did it
did they didn't want to know medical
medium information the vegan movement
the social the social media vegan
movement they didn't understand medical
medium information maybe they understood
some tidbits they were even adverse to
celery juice didn't even want to do
celery juice or they did it privately
secretly but that's all they did they
did not want to learn how to heal while
being plant-based so they all jumped
ship and they started going to animal
animal animal and it started out it
started out with a lot of women
influencers young women influencers that
were vegan for a little while or
plant-based for a little while and they
started out with their social media
platform with their so first social
media post it just turns on and they're
like so yeah I've been vegan I've been
plant-based for like I don't know like a
year and a half like what's my boyfriend
doing Hey listen put the dog can you put
the dog in the cat out and I and I have
to tell you I got sick and I went to the
doctor and the doctor said like he said
like I had like a protein deficiency so
listen girls I know that you like I know
that I've been doing the vegan thing for
like a year year and a half and you know
me and I've been doing it so good I've
been doing it to the
letter I think that I'm changing now and
I'm doing some raw milk and actually
think my Skin's getting better and I'm
starting to come around that was the
first ones right there the very first
ones right
there okay and then it went from those
very first ones it went from those very
first ones to the second ones and then
it went to the third ones what I mean by
that is then then all of a sudden
another Army of young women coming out
of the plant-based vegan movement would
be like I'm not getting enough protein
I'm actually going to be my amino acid
structures are wrong I went to this
doctor I saw a guy on social media you
should follow him too and it went to the
next level went to the next level
so and it's just next level and Next
Level and where were the dudes where
were the vegan dudes if you looked at
the soy
boys wherever they were whoever they are
if you looked at the vegan dudes they
didn't know how to stand up for
themselves they didn't know how to how
to fix things they didn't know how to
get women to be like wait a minute no
wait a minute something's wrong here it
something's wrong here right they didn't
know how to stand up for the plant-based
movement and It Came Crashing Down
crashing down and the trainers and the
weightlifters and the buff dudes and
that they got they even have credentials
some of them are like nutritionist PS pH
PhD MD chiropractor and they're coming
up and they're just like in the gym and
they're like you need your protein girls
you need your protein you need this
you're going to be in you're going to
have infertility you're going to need
your hormones balanced you need meat
meat's got B6 be this be this like
they're doing this and then women are
just like totally mind totally mind like
totally and so the vegan movement Came
Crashing Down it's a ghost of what it
was it's a fraction of what it was and
it's going down fast I'm talking to a
complete burn unless you're doing
medical medium information and you learn
how to heal and you understand how to do
plant-base properly for your body and
what you need as you're healing same
thing if you're a me eat or two whatever
in the whole bit Alissa says over there
on YouTube it's so funny hearing you
talk about this because I've seen this
all happen I was following those
influencers it's crazy there's a war on
I hinted about the war six seven years
ago in the books I hinted about the war
five years ago I hinted about the war
four years ago hinted about it and
talked about it 3 years ago and then it
took over over and that's it people are
clobbered clobbered and there's Carnage
Carnage from
it and The Spoils of War and how how
much pork
fat money was made on the flip side how
much money was made from the influencers
pushing meat believe it or not I mean
they slaughtered the plant-based
movement basically now here's what's
happened and I talked about the mistakes
the carore movement made where I told
you about that you want to watch the
last live I did you to hear
that but now we have basically the
Atkins diet refled into a keto diet the
keto diet is really some medical medium
tools mixed in with meat that's what
they did they were so smart that they
learned how to poach medical medium
information so the meat eaters and the
Meat Heads in industry the influencers
they learned how to poach key things for
medical medium information stay away
from MSG stay away from all kinds of
stuff be cautious about corn stay away
from all corn that was medical medium
information meanwhile the vegans were
eating all the corn all all the organic
corn gobbling down organic corn organic
corn organic
corn the plant-based movement raw
organic corn raw organic corn corn corn
soy the vegan movement soy soy soy soy
soy organic soy organic soy medical
medium information it's all GMO it's all
GMO that was medical medium
information the vegan information right
check this out the vegans we're doing
soy corn organic corn feeling safe
feeling comfortable nutritional yeast
nutritional yeast nutritional yeast
chocolate chocolate chocolate chocolate
chocolate chocolate and they got
themselves sick they stayed sick and
then the animal protein movement the new
one I'm talking about the dudes were
smart they were listening to Medical
medium podcasts how do I know a podcast
would come out and two to three of the
meat head influencers would be saying
the same thing that was in the podcast
word for word like
plagiarizing so they were listening to
Medical medium information they were
listening to the podcast they were
looking through the books and they saw
stay away from nutrition East and they
saw stay away from corn it's all all GMO
and they saw stay away from soy it's all
GMO and they used it and poached it they
added it to their fancy keto diet and
they crushed the plant-based movement
because the plant-based people they
didn't want to know enough about medical
medium information to keep them afloat
to keep them safe to keep them able to
do it it's Carnage it's Spoils of War
it happened the war on veganism and how
smart the Meat Heads were to be able to
collaberate and even take medical medium
information and do
so they're so smart they started
screaming no natural flavors no MSG no
natural flavors no MSG they got it from
medical medium information but they got
it and they
robed the plant-based movement do you
guys understand what happened
it's
unbelievable I don't disrespect you know
anybody and I have respect for everybody
I even have respect for these idiots
that did that to the plant-based
movement because they were they were
thinking at least evil evil but thinking
they were thinking let's steal this from
mm let's use it against a plant-based
movement plant-based movement's not like
let's take this from mm no they're just
like oh guys's a
medium what does it say in the Bible you
know oh if you're a medium you're a
sorcerer oh you're going to hell you
know what I mean so what happened was a
plant-based movement if you believe in
karma if that's what you believe they
got
Karma they did slammed slammed
the Meat Heads let's see an IG love the
beach the Meat Heads versus the soy boys
the new Westside
Story okay IG you're absolutely right
many people who are vegan convert it to
meat and eggs again not just many almost
all of them thanks uh thanks vegan
snia very important to know so why does
this
matter I think it's
important I think it's important because
a couple of things that are critical
when it comes down to chronic
illness you have to know what caused it
you have to know what caused it I'll see
it 10 times in a row and you can say aw
is repeating himself you have to know
what caused it then you have to know
what to do for it it's not about what
side of the aisle you're on you want to
be plant-based damn it you stay
plant-based that's what you do you stay
plant-based I support plant-based that's
right I do I do big time and you
actually can heal and get down to the
nitty gritty inside and you can help
detoxify you can help restore your
immune system and do it plant-based but
you got to do it right and you got to
customize it right to yourself and you
can't get thrown off and what happened
was the vegan movement was just a whole
bunch of people people all t one big
tumble weed of people and they didn't
know the medical medium
information they were just eating
whatever and eating vegan Donuts vegan
cookies vegan this vegan soy vegan
cheese vegan that vegan this vegan
sausages and you know what's really
sad is the fake processed Meats in the
vegetarian movement so that was thrown
on the vegans this was a really
brilliant move right here so the Meat
Heads the ones with now like they're
flashing whatever nutritionist degree
they have they're in the gym they're
talking about how you need this amino
acid they're talking about how you know
soy kills right and they're talking
about all these
things and they and it's information
they gleaned from medical medium really
smart how they poached some good pieces
really good pieces that they could have
used that they could use that they did
but the plant-based movement could have
used those tools and they didn't they
didn't what was wrong with
them they didn't they didn't take the mm
info and use the tools to battle the
Meat Heads who have taken them
down but let's go into the fake
processed meat game
whoa whoa what a great tool the
influencers that are doing the keto and
the meat and the carnivore whatever you
want to you know chalk it all up into
one big ball those meet either influen
your trainer weightlifter dudes that are
all into that those dudes they figured
something else out they figured out that
they can rank on the processed fake
meats that vegans get blamed for what a
win what a win because in those fake
processed meats you got all kinds of MSG
you got gluten you got everything bad in
that stuff chemicals everything Galore
and so these influencers are just like
screaming you're the fake process meat
people and you're doing soy and you're
doing this and you're doing that it's an
incredible weapon they use and here's
the stupid part those guys don't even
realize it those influencers that are
using that weapon against the
plant-based movement don't even realize
something that wasn't the vegan movement
that created all those fake processed
meats that vegans tend to Love
sometimes it wasn't that those fake
processed Meats with all that [__] in
them was designed for the vegetar Arians
which are now Dead and
Gone
vegetarians gone there might be a few
lingering around and there might be a
few in the medical M community that say
they're vegetarians and see themselves
as that but they're mostly all gone the
fake processed Meats were created for
the vegetarians in the 60s the 70s the
80s the90s or the 70s ' 80s the '90s the
early 2000s it was designed for the
vegetarian the bean and riser that ate
eggs and dairy products as well the
vegetarian the vegetarian that drank
goat's milk cow's milk raw milk cooked
milk cheese kefir feta cheese ricotta
cheese
whatever the
vegetarian the vegetarian that buried
everything in nutritional yeast ate a
pile of beans with cheese on it d cow
cheese on it the
vegetarian the vegetarian that ate lots
of eggs in the morning and then wanted
some fake
sausage so the industry the food
industry created for vegetarians and the
vegetarian movement fake processed Meats
they weren't even for the vegans and the
plant-based people sure I'm sure a vegan
that wanted to become vegan or a person
that became vegan went and bought one of
those turkeys that was actually
processed meat with MSG and gluten but
the point is it was created for the
vegetarians so the Meat Heads
influencers trainers PhD guys whatever
you want to call them that have crushed
the vegan movement saying that all their
women are going to be infertile and all
it takes is one woman who's vegan or
plant-based one woman who's vegan or
plant-based who can't have a baby and
they're going to be convinced it's
because those Meat Heads are right and
those influencers are right it's going
to they're going to be convinced that
they totally went down the wrong track
being plant-based and they're not going
to have a baby now and that these dudes
know better out there that are on social
screaming away on how all their women
are going to go infertile and I'm going
to tell you what a weapon that was that
was brilliant brilliant for their side
to win the
war you just got on the live you got to
rewatch it from the beginning every
single word is
important once it's posted
processed fake Meats with all the gluten
and all the MSG and all the garbage in
it and everything else you guys the
processed fake Meats were for the
vegetarians not for the vegans the
vegans were never supposed to eat it
they was never created for them it was
created for the vegetarian and what
happened was these influencers these
Meatheads these keto these carnivore
influencers and and and everything above
including their doctor friends and PhD
friends and everything else what they
did was they pulled a real good fast one
on those vegans and what they did was
they convinced everybody that the
processed fake Meats were vegan were for
vegans they were made for vegans they
were created for vegans and the vegans
just slobbered it and ate it all down
and that was it really good move but
guess what the plant-based people in the
vegans can't stick up for themselves cuz
a they're probably not watching medical
medium stuff really B they don't want to
learn C there was a way to battle that
one easily cuz that was for the
vegetarians not for the plant-based
people
so let's get down to the
nitty-gritty a so over there on YouTube
when I turned plant base there were many
vegan people with symptoms on social and
vegan influencers did not have answers
they would always say you are either
detoxing or not doing it right correct
that's what they would always say you're
detoxing too much you're detoxing too
much that's what they would always say
but they didn't know information they
didn't know that it's not detoxing too
much they didn't know it was you got
viruses you got pathogens you're not
eating the right way to support going
against those pathogens they didn't know
why you were sick they didn't know
autoimmune a farce they didn't know
anything Brook over there on YouTube I'm
a perfect example of this I was vegan
for over 10 years before I had my health
challenges after having my first
baby over there Michael Charles over
there on YouTube You're going to be
deficient quotation marks there is what
they'll say not knowing anything about
the B12 that's in your book and the B12
information okay great one so Mye
Charles that's really a really important
one and I want to talk about that for a
second okay great one okay the B12
weapon is a great one too that's what
he's saying it's these influencers like
I said before the Meat Heads the
trainers whatever you want to call it
the bodybuilders or just the doctors
that don't want to work on patients
they're just they're wealthy doctors
don't need to work ever a day in their
life their mommy and daddy paid for
their medical their medical uh school
they they went through Medical School
whatever it is all paid for by Mommy and
Daddy they got which is fine whatever
that's fine they got they got they got
their medical license but realize they
don't want to practice they don't want
to touch dirty people they're too you
know above that they don't want to deal
with people complaining and crying in
the waiting rooms and them just trying
to like offer a drug or whatever it is
so they just went on social there's a
massive upsurge of these what I call
fake doctors because they don't want to
practice and they don't have
experiencing practice experience
practice right they don't have that so
what they're rising up right now and
they're the ones that are taking down
the vegan movement and the plant-based
movement they Ed the B12 example right
there so Mike they Ed the B12 example
and but what the vegans and the
plant-based people did not adopt what
they did not do is no medical medium
information enough to know that
everybody's B12 deficient all the meat
eaters are B12 deficient and the
B12 in meat is not even synergistic to
your body it's not even
bioidentical so you can't even use that
B12 the B12 in meat isn't B12 your body
uses so you become B12 deficient even if
your blood test says you have
B12 and so that's why millions of meat
eaters are getting sick every single day
millions of Keto people millions of the
Paleo people in the past millions of the
Atkins people millions of the new
carnivore people well there isn't
millions of those millions of the keto
people they're all getting sick too and
they're all getting like lots of
different symptoms and they're getting
B12 deficient you can be B12 deficient
both as a plant-based person and a vegan
person and as a keto person carnivore
person or any kind of animal protein
person you can be B12 deficient and
guess what every everybody really is
even if their blood test says a certain
thing if you learn medical medum
information you can learn how to heal
the details matter but guess what the
pl-based movement many of them didn't
really want to learn or know or didn't
really look at it and they got burned
they got convinced and pushed out of
something that intuitively they knew was
good for them keep that in mind a lot of
people that went plant-based intuitively
thought this was good for me they used
their intuition and they knew that the
plant-based movement was good for them
but then they got psyched out by demons
demons in the hellfield that actually
took them out and that's what this is
about it's the war the Meat Heads
against the soy
boys and as soy boy lost because I don't
know about a recovery from this I really
don't a recovery for the vegan movement
is going to be really hard and I know
what you're thinking you're thinking at
the last vegan Festival there was 20,000
people there 15,000 people there that's
a joke
that's a joke for the vegan movement for
the plant-based movement that's really
sad really
sad really is and half those people were
still half to three4 of those people are
still doing animal products here and
there and that leads me to the next part
of the
topic there's not a lot of people that
were truly plant-based they always they
were plant-based for a month and then
not anymore for a day plant-based for
another month and not anymore for a day
then they ate a piece of cheese at a
friend's house then they ate a piece of
cheese here then they ate an egg two
weeks later there really wasn't a lot of
people that were plant-based plant-based
plant-based they wanted to be they were
trying but they just couldn't do it and
they just they caved in and they ate an
egg and they ate a piece of cheese and
that's what they
did but there's a lot of people that
thought when they were vegans and they
were being a vegan and they thought
animal cruelty and animals dying and
getting slaughtered and pigs getting
slaughtered and killed they were like
that was enough for them to not do
anything animal so they're really strict
like no animal animal no animal and then
when they got 24 years old 25 years old
and they got their first symptoms and
something went wrong and they found
something on their skin and everything
they panicked and it wasn't about the
animals anymore forget the animals who
cares if they die I got a problem on my
skin I'm protein deficient now and or
they
believe so the plant-based movement was
always high fat High high fat high fat
even when it was lowfat a little bit it
wasn't low it wasn't low of fat enough
for somebody that had a serious health
condition that needed to heal so
therefore there's really nowhere to go
you go into the vegan plant-based
movement you're kind of stuck you're in
high-fat land you're in all this other
stuff you're using canola oil you're
eating canola oil without even realizing
it all these
things nutritional yeast vinegars canola
oils mixed all this stuff citric acid
all these things right you're eating
corn you're eating corn but you think
it's organic but it's but it's not and
it's not organic and it's GMO and you're
eating soy and you think it's organic
and then like I said
earlier the winners of the war the
winners of the war they won they learned
medical medium information they learn
that all soy was bad they learned that
all corn was bad they learned that and
by the way corn and soy Fe pathogens so
here you are a plant-based person eating
lots of organic corn all the time not
just one or two ears of corn in the
summertime you're eating it every day
and this is key medical beam information
you're eating it every day you're
feeding pathogens so here you are as a
plant-based person and you're feeding
pathogens and you're getting sick and
symptoms because of all the corn you're
eating but you're plant-based you're
confused so now you're running back to
eggs you're running back to things you
see an influencer you see all the women
influencers the young women influencers
that try tried the plant-based movement
and now they're on their feeds talking
about their protein deficiencies and how
they don't have they're not fertile or
they don't know if they're fertile
enough you hear that and then you're
another woman too and you're just like
oh my God I'm hearing that I'm running
from this I'm getting a symptom I didn't
know it was because I'm eating corn
every other day I'm getting a symptom I
better get out of this like they're
getting out of this and I better get on
some eggs and some dairy products and
whatever else I better start eating meat
and choking that stuff down no matter
what I better learn how to choke it down
yeah important to know and I talked
about the last live anybody that's on a
carnivore diet keep in mind you're going
to hit the wall at some point you're
just going to hit the wall at some point
you're going to get gluc glucose
deficient in your
brain you're going to get bogged down
with all that fat that animal fat you're
going to get nutrient deficient for real
it's going to show up a couple years
down the road and you're going to have
to do what the carnivore people do which
is bringing honey and lemon that's
medical medium information bringing
honey and lemon and then you're going to
have to bringing fruit medical medium
information again remember I was the one
that broke fruit fear do you guys
remember that medical medium information
broke the whole fruit fear thing broke
the whole fruit fear thing so that
carnivore could have S could save its
skin did you know that I made Fruit
acceptable in the health World which
means the carnivore people now saved
their butts when they were dying from
just eating meat alone they saved their
butts by now bringing in Fruit that's
medical medium information that allowed
the carnivore people to eat fruit they
would have never touched fruit in a
million
years in a million
years if it wasn't for medical medium
spending all those years all that time
publishing all that stuff about fruit
fear and making it acceptable so people
would bring in their fruits and not be
afraid and ostracized right and bring in
their fruits so when the new keto
influencer SL you know
phdd bodybuilder SLT triner SL meat had
came up on social media they were like
I'm eating fruit now with my meat I'm
eating fruit now with this you know with
this with my chicken whatever I'm
meaning fruit and they're doing it
because I made it safe for them they
were smart they took that information
and they used it and it's protecting
them while they're slaughtering the
plant-based in vegan
movement another thing they did was they
weaponized not only the infertility they
weaponized the hormones being imbalanced
in women with their reproductive system
they weaponized
that they weaponized the soy and the
corn information from medical medium
they took that information they
weaponized
that and they
[Music]
weaponized the feminization
Factor
feminizing they weaponize that they
convince the plant-based women and the
vegan women that the dudes that are
vegan are feminized they're feminine now
from what they were doing and that's not
going to help them you know with
fertility too their sperm is not going
to be strong so the influencer the
meater influencer now the new one that
I'm talking about out there the new ones
they're like my sperm is strong that's
what they're all basically trying to say
and they actually do say that
too some not all of them but some of
them say that and how to get strong
sperm and ladies that's what's going on
here your soy boys they're weak they're
infertile their sperm isn't working
right they're eating soy they're flimsy
guys they're soft guys they're weak guys
they've completely coined the
plant-based movement and the vegan
movement with that kind of
thing as a brilliant game and
strategy and from what I see I don't
think the plant-based movement and the
vegan movements coming out of it Toby
777 on YouTube the details are so so
important they are you can be a
plant-based
person and you can heal you can heal
from dastardly stuff bad chronic illness
you can heal multiple sclerosis you can
heal okay someone over there
see over there on YouTube there are a
lot of people who have been eating only
meat for many years have a lot of energy
and don't drink coffee they are you like
being lied to you like being lied to see
you're actually one of those that
believes every single thing someone says
on social media about what they're doing
so you don't think anybody lies nobody
lies nobody's a
liar they're
lying because I'll tell you right now if
you're a woman and you only eat meat and
you don't bring in any anything else
just eat meat Watch What Happens in 6
months watch your skin fall apart watch
your collagen basically dissolve in your
body watch your face change watch
everything get really
bad it's really
sad they have to bring a caffeine in
order to function and they do bring in
caffeine in order to function but in
order to keep a good social media
profile going and a good social media
campaign going they're not going to tell
you what they dip into once in a while
and what they eat once in a while and
what they grab and the Apple they ate
last week or three days ago they're not
going to tell you what they're doing to
scam that you know scam you and get by
and what binge they're on when they when
they binge and when they do it and the
time they did it they're not going to do
that because that's going to destroy
their platform now their platform is
destroyed it's not going to be helpful
for them they're not going to be able to
bank and Bank
The Spoils of War man slaughtering the
vegan and plant-based movement they did
a great job and they did it they did it
is there any hope there's always
hope I don't see the vegan and
plant-based movement coming out of it
anytime soon I see it going down even to
a darker pit in a deeper rabbit hole is
where it's going if you're plant-based
stay plant-based but learn how to do it
right if you're plant-based stay
plant-based learn how to do it right
okay it's very important right there
learn how to do it right save yourself
cuz you will be on meet at some point in
your life because you'll be so confused
you won't even know 10 ways a Sunday you
won't even have any clue and you'll be
back on eggs and whatever else and meat
and whatever else confused doing the
ring around the rosie doing the musical
chairs
doing you know you're going to be in
that big old forever Catch 22 not
knowing what to do not knowing how to
heal symptoms still coming symptoms
still kind of going up and down new
symptoms appearing that's what where
you'll be if you're plant-based stay
plant-based but learn how to do it and
customize it to what you need
critical maram right there it is so true
I read books by MDS to help my brain and
it was all about keto it made me worse
of course cuz keto can't help a brain
thank goodness I found medical medium
through a friend and and that takes me
to the next part you can't fix a brain
you can't detox a brain when you're on
keto
it just can't but if you're 24 years old
and you're working out every day and you
really you didn't have a sick moment in
your life yet you just got some athletes
foot and you just got some fungus on
your feet because all those dudes got
fungus on their feet and I'm going to
tell you right now because I know this
because I know I've talked to enough
people enough times I also got a little
voice in my ear and so they still got
athletes foot they still got jockage
fungus that comes in goes with creams
they still got all that but they're not
exhibiting that neurological fatigue yet
or anything like that that comes later
that comes later when they hit the wall
and they get their first batch of
shingles all over the side of their body
on the side of their torso and they're
in they're into that whole thing now
they're just you know in that place and
they're confused and like what's going
on here it comes sickness comes every or
they just have a heart
attack like so many people are doing
every single day right now at age 20 2
age 30 the heart attacks are crazy right
now the amount of people that are dying
with heart problems is unbelievable just
like I predicted Tressa says can we also
talk about all those Meat Heads in shape
claiming they look buff from carnivore
when they're doing steroids and of
course not mentioning it of course they
do a lot of steroids and a lot of guys
do they don't do steroids like the
steroid days like the old days they
don't do that like the old days they do
testosterone
they don't do the they don't do the
steroids that they did back back then
just so you know and the growth hormones
and the in the steroids they just do
testosterone right the doctors are
giving them all testosterone they want
their testosterone to be somewhere
around
1,200 1,400 1,600 1,800 so they want
that they want to see testosterone
levels like 1,800 on their blood test
and they and then they want to even take
more testosterone than that so they are
on steroids they up their testosterone
they're working out that's what they're
doing that's a big part of it too out
there you know the other big part of it
is that the ones you see on social they
don't have a job most of them they don't
work a job they're in the gym they're in
the gym four hours a day they pamper
themselves they self-care themselves to
death they can do it day in and day out
haven't gotten sick yet their stress is
really low to down real low those are
the ones you see on social those are the
said to Mommy and Daddy are you guys all
right I want to have a family meeting
here is Dad around I want to have a
family meeting is Dad around and what
they do is then they go and they have a
family meeting and it's like hey I just
want to tell you guys Mom Dad I know you
gave me $250,000 to do you know medical
school and I know that I I passed
medical school but I just it it's not
it's not speaking to me right now son
you are supposed to be a doctor it's not
speaking to me right now but I was
hoping that you're okay if um if I just
play on social media for a while and try
to find myself I hear a lot of people
are making money and I want to help
people through that oh that's a really
good idea that's a great that's a great
idea you should do that honey oh I guess
so why not you're you're our son and
that's what's happening right now is
these all these doctors are literally
they're all just playing the field now
on social and they're not practicing and
they're able to selfcare themselves to
death and do four hours in the gym every
day and if that's what they want to do
fine they're on testosterone they're
doing stuff like that and some do
regular steroids definitely some still
do regular steroids
so
um you're getting a well-rounded episode
dror Fawn a real doctor if not on
testosterone testosterone
precursors like
HCG oh my God
exactly I agree I
agree all right so quick little rundown
a couple little couple more things about
it
so there's so many fighting words and
strategies and techniques that the Meat
Heads have now you just can't beat it if
you're a vegetarian vegan
plant-based they can't beat it they can
Hammer you with the protein Fe Hammer
you with the b112
deficiency they can Hammer you with the
soy and the
corn they can Hammer you with the you
know the oils cuz they took information
medical medium information like the soy
corn the the oils they can Hammer you
with the nutritional yeast they took
from medical medium I was the first to
tell you the stuff was dangerous bad and
crappy and bad for you and everybody was
just pissed at me I probably lost so
many followers because I went after
nutritional yeast because people use
that like
crack and the Meat Heads they took that
information and they have so many
weapons and they took infertility for
the women and they took they took the
whole thing where the soy boys the men
are feminized and they took all of that
and they weaponized all these bits in
pieces and they did a good
job and they're not even done they're
not even
done and they put the last nail in the
coffin with that fertility crap right
they knock that one
in not going to be a lot of women left
doing plant-based or vegan so they're
going to be sick either way if they
don't learn the medical medium
information this isn't about medical
medium medical medium is not on either
side this is just what's happening in
the world right now I need people to
know I'm not sitting here trying to
fight for
vegans I'm not sitting you're trying to
vegans I'm not
you can do animal proteins in a way to
still use medical medium and heal
they're figuring it out those Meat Heads
are partially figuring it out they
brought the fruit
in they know to stay away from corn and
soy yeah they know to stay away from all
the MSG and all the you know weird
ambiguous places they they're
learning and they're figuring it out and
they're getting some benefits from it
and they're moving forward and they're
able to get on their social media
platform and say my skin was yucky I had
acne now it's getting a little bit
better and then you got some girl who's
plant-based who's following this dude's
account and she's plant-based and her
acne is blowing up because she doesn't
know medical medium information about
how to get rid of acne while you're
plant-based how you can do that while
you're plant-based she's not going to
know that so then she's watching the
dude and she's just plant-based
movements just going to be gone I think
it's probably probably on its last leg
just in this the rest of this year early
next year a whole another level
wonderful wondering wishing says over on
YouTube aw I finally tried spinach soup
again oh my God that's such a healing
tool medical M healing tool but prayed
to let but I prayed to like it I have
now had it every day for two weeks in a
row and love the taste major
improvements in my health definitely
Missing Link thank you it is a missing
link and I want to tell you something
about the spinach soup the medical beam
spinach soup I'm going to make it for
you next live I do because I want to
show you different like variables that
make it taste better and how how to do
it just right and what you can do with
that what you can do with that it's
incredible one of the weapons that the
meat hads used which was being anti
vegetable and anti- leafy
green another really good weapon of
choice against the plant-based people
because they know that the plant-based
people are eating their salads and
plant-based women are eating their
salads they know that plant-based women
love salads and they know women love
salads so another way to really wipe the
floor clean of the with the plant-based
movement was to hit the vegetables are
bad they're toxic here's the reasons why
out in nature what happens is this
greens are bad they took that like paleo
information of vegetables being
de and they Incorporated it and they
used it as a weapon against a
plant-based movement so the plant-based
girls plant-based women would be like
well I'm not supposed to be eating these
vegetables either this dude's saying
that these things are
toxic and it's it's another great weapon
that happened and descended upon the
plant-based movement now if you don't
see any of this out there happening it's
out there happening and it's rampid and
it is going a mile a minute right now so
I'm giving you all the different
variations the understandings of of
what's Happening kind of how it was
derived around the time frame it was
derived what's going on with
it and you're going to see pretty soon
all of the fashion companies are not
going to be offering vegan leather
pretty soon they're going to be only
offering one shoe in vegan leather Two
Shoes in vegan leather you're going to
see that next year you're G to see
fashion designers not offering it
companies and fashion brands not
offering it you'll see going out to
pasture is where you're going to see
that go that's going to be in the next
coming couple of
years
because because veganism is dying
veganism is practically dead plant-based
movement is just about on its way
let's start making some food and I'll
cover a little bit
more back to this if you're this is
important I'm not pining for either
side I feel bad for the plant-based
people there's a way to be
plant-based and there's a way to heal
there's a way to fix your problems
plant-based Bela says I've been
listening to you and reading your books
for like eight years I see people and
companies all the time now saying things
I first heard from you it's so strange
and that's what they're doing they've
gone into the medical medium series the
medical medium Bibles and they poached
the crap out of them now here's what I
was supposed to do but I wouldn't
wouldn't have done it
anyway so I have people coming to me
that that because I don't have like I
don't have PR firms working for me I
don't do the pr firm thing and you know
the branding thing you know how I don't
do that you guys it's it was organic the
books went out there people healed and
told somebody
else so PR marketing firms come up to me
all the time that like support people's
brands or you know take on people's
Brands they knock on my door and they
say can I get a meeting with aw and I'll
be like okay if they a pain in the butt
enough I'll be like what what what do
you want and they'll talk to me and
they'll say
this okay they'll say these things
they'll say why did you put all that
information for free in nine books over
the last 10 years why didn't you take
pieces of this because it was original
information it wasn't out there why
didn't you package and sell each
individual
thing and and and you could be a
billionaire by now they say it all the
time I say because that's that's that's
not the way to do it I want to offer
these books you can go in the library
and get them for free you can buy one
for 20 bucks I mean that's free also in
hundreds and hundreds of live streams
and podcasts they also poach the
information and so what happened is what
you see now is all this early medical
medium information being weaponized and
used it is and you see people talking
about it you see podcast doctors talking
about it you see it out there right
exactly they took the info and they're
using it and they're weedling it into
their own belief systems like carnivore
and like keto and like even some
plant-based people are doing it too but
plant based people could not save the
movement because they didn't want to
know medical medium information
enough
Cynthia over there in IG I'm a doctor
who take care of sick people in the ER
for the past 15 years so proud to use
medical medium information to help my
patients thank God for medical medium
information as I can set people
straight thank you aw I just got
emotional reading
that because it it's really special it's
really special
it is you
know okay so I got some mil right
here first let me make
um it's more to talk about I just know
that I got to get going on this a little
bit so let me make make this um fun
little thing right here so I need some
lemons get them right here you guys just
walk away for a
second my lemons
nice going to have a little onion here
too okay so I'm going to get some lemon
juice going right
now CU don't mine I put this in my back
pocket all right this dish is really
simple it's easy it's it's fun to make
too love it okay and um
okay squeeze some lemon right
there all
right after watching this and learning
this information you're going to see it
more than ever you're going to be wise
to it and you're going to understand
what
happened it's a sad sad thing that
happened if you want to be animal
protein you can and do medical medium I
never ever said meat was poison meat was
terrible for your health in the sense
where it's highly toxic and poisonous I
never said don't eat meat I never said
people are stupid by eating meat I never
said anything of the
sort but what I have said all these
years is if you want to go the meat root
there's a way to do it you can heal you
can work on your healing process and you
can do
it okay little bit more lemon juice in
here I think I'm going to go with two
lemons I was never on one side of the
aisle and one side only because you got
to customize it to the way you need it
to way your body needs it everything
about it but what I did say though you
can fat yourself to
death you can eat so much overt fat that
you can really decline in so many ways
that's one thing all on its own I mean
that's one aspect of it okay so I got
the lemon juice in there you guys okay
two tablespoons of raw
honey pop that in
here little bit of honey you guys don't
mind here we
go put that in there I'm going to get a
little whisk I think I'm going to use a
fork to whisk it okay um half a teaspoon
of pepper flakes right
here there we go those are hot pepper
flakes red pepper flakes okay I got some
garlic powder right here teaspoon of
garlic
powder that in there nice okay so I need
one um before I put all the vegetables
in there and everything like that and
fruits and all that that I'm going to
put in there I'm going to mix this up I
think I got this all set you can use
maple syrup keep that in mind I just put
honey in here so I'm going to do a
little
whisk and then I'm going to start adding
everything in this
bowl are you guys I mean have you guys
been seeing any you some of you said
already you've seen some of what I'm
talking about you haven't seen it yet by
the beginning of
2025 the winter of
2025 and maybe that's the summer on the
other side of the planet but the winter
of
2025 would be
probably the veganism and plant-based
movement um
funeral by the winter of
2025 that will be the plant-base and
vegan movement funeral
there'll be some scraggler left there'll
be a few a few people left but pretty
much all
gone except the medical M Community cuz
you can be plant-based here and
heal and like I said you can eat meat
and heal you got to learn how to do it
there's ways to do it so this is the
Millet and Herb salad and now I'm moving
on to
um here it is that's what I'm making
check it out
all right let's get
uh let's get
moving okay I'm going to chop some stuff
up this is out of the brains saer book
I'll show you again in a minute let's
get some things chopped
up all right I'm going to chop up some
parsley in a little while let me just
get started with a
cucumber I'm going to peel the Cucumber
are you guys okay with that you don't
have to when I grow them in the garden
When I grow them in the garden I don't I
don't peel them when I buy them in the
store like I did here I bought this in
the
store I peel them if I bought them in
store
okay there's um I've been saying this
for years skin of the Cucumber when you
buy it in the store
could have a lot of stuff in it I cheed
about how organic produce is sprayed
three times a week Organic Farms spray
their organic produce three times a week
another thing the Meat Heads have
adopted for medical medium information
on how there's basically spray on
everything and there's metals on
everything and metals in everything all
the different tidbits they're
taking okay so I'm going to chop up this
cucumber bear with me here
all you need is about a cup in this
recipe okay so I'm going to dice these
up there we go and these like nice
little like kind of like triangly
squares you don't want them too thin you
want them to have a little bit
of structure to
them that's how I like it for these
there we
go might have a big one in there right
I'm going to drop this in right here
what's great about this cutting board
right here I can do
this okay next one right
there okay Victoria rising out of the
ashes rising from the ashes apologize
for that what they on YouTube I noticed
at my local organic store things used to
cater to a lot of vegans but in the past
year or more that changed and I didn't
understand why catering to vegans is
disappearing absolutely it's definitely
disappearing farmers markets all
included it's um and menus too in
restaurants as well menus are not going
to cater as much you're going to see
less and less on the menus there's going
to be less vegans going into places and
that's that's the thing and asking for
things and that's what's happening which
is is you
know which is really really annoying for
so many people because why when I talk
about truths a lot of people get
offended and then they're upset and then
I don't make friends um my podcast
episodes Don't Make Friends especially
the one that I'm putting out next week
you know like there's there's it's like
yeah a lot of things that I've said over
these years the fragrance thing right I
broke the fragrance thing out in the
world now it's of course getting all
poached right there's a new person every
day like fragrances it's always some PhD
guy or something
and um and they're like fragrances are
bad got I'm chopping up some tomato but
I when I broke the fragrance thing the
hate man the hate was so thick when you
break the stuff out first and you teach
about it and stuff and you message about
it especially from Spirit like all the
info oh my God the amount of the hate
was crazy but then weeks or months or
years later those same people who were
hating on me talking crap about me on
social media they're all using the
information benefiting it and passing it
around like they're the
experts when you do things like that you
have to reckon with that when you leave
here I think that's something
that you know Spirit of compassion told
me that when I was
younger that when you purposely do evil
[__] like that or you purposely do evil
stuff with intentions behind it you sit
there and you try to demean and hurt
someone like you know you you're you're
you're a medical medium hater you're
ranking on what he what the medical
medium is talking about the information
right and you're ruining people's
chances of healing because they get
thrown by it right think about that and
then a year later two years later 3
years later you take medical me
information you never apologize for what
you've done you never said how you were
wrong and and Anthony William had it
right and then you end up using it well
what happens is when you purposely do
that
purposely it's something that has to be
resolved before you die so when you're
80 years old 90 years old 70 years old
whatever it is 60 years old or whatever
is going to happen with someone in their
life and you're on your
deathbed that gets brought before you
Spirit of compassion has always told me
that gets brought before
you it does and it's basically like you
remember when you purposely
intentionally were just evil and you
thwarted people's healing process and
you said all these things and then you
took the information and then you
benefited from it and never apologized
and never came clean you remember that
and you were evil when you did it that
has to be resolved before you pass on
and so I see all these people doing that
and I'm like you think that's just like
that that's it nothing to worry about
anymore that's it it's over you totally
screw me over like that you know you
tell people this and that you do this
then you take the info that info comes
from
above that info you learned and you're
spreading around and using against me
and using for yourself the benefit and
doing these evil you know these evil
things that's information that came from
a Divine Source from
above you don't think down the road
there may be some payment for that in a
on a spiritual level well you'll
say all right let's get some chopped up
celery sticks in here a couple celery
sticks I've been helping people for over
years and I have not just U social media
or anything like that 35 years have been
helping people
All Around the
World Erica Brown a vegan restaurant
near me is recently no longer vegan they
started adding meat dishes to their
menu bye
bye this American
Pie JS J jzs funny that you say that
because I went to Whole Food and they
stopped making vegan cupcakes and I
couldn't understand why now I
know see you later
alligator see you later
[Music]
alligator
yep it's over all right just in a little
bit more time okay so I'm going to put a
little green onion in here really quick
okay so some green
onion you guys this dish is really
delicious if you're a meat eater and
you're somebody that's on keto or
whatever and you're watching this and
you're not sure if you hate me or like
me even though you you kind of probably
heard you can do animal products I never
ripped down meat and ripped it apart and
attacked people support or anything like
that have always been supportive if
you're an animal protein dude or or you
know person of some kind and you're you
know you're an animal protein person
here's what I would do I would make this
dish I would take the Millet and move
the Millet out and not use it in this
dish and I would put a small portion of
your favorite meat in the dish that's
what I would do that's all if you're a
meat eater that's what I would do I
would not do it with the Millet in there
I would replace the Millet with the meat
and I wouldn't use a lot of meat I'd use
a little bit of meat because the meat is
an overt fat and you don't want to over
fat your dish too high you're not going
to heal if you over fat your dish too
high and then I would make sure that
that was pretty much your only meat for
the day if you're trying to heal if
you're chronically
sick all right what else we got cooking
here um I'm going to um cut up an onion
a little bit okay let me do
that see is this an onion that's a good
onion it is a good onion right
here another thing too marketing wise
marketing the meat found a great way to
Market great techniques great tactics as
well they really can do a lot of damage
to the plant-based
movement the take down of the
plant-based
movement was on
purpose it was to get plant-based people
to buy their stuff and do their stuff
buy their protein powders by all their
things it was to get people that were on
plant Pro protein powders to go and buy
the Meat Heads protein
powders it was a cash cow
man Cash Cow all right so I put some
onion in
there okay and I got some green onion in
there a little bit of
onion
um all right I'm going to mix that up in
a little bit we're almost
there I'm going to put some parsley in
here I got a mix right here of some
parsley with some cilantro wrapped up
together so I'm going to chop up this
parsley right here you can use a lot of
it you can use a little bit of it I'm
I'm like a big fan of leafy green herbs
I've been um talking about that
messaging that for years that you use
your green leafy herbs as green leafy
greens that's what you do with it now
you can just take some of this and put
it on top of it at the you know after
you make it I'm going to mix this
in but I'm not going to have just um big
pieces of this I'm going to go with kind
of
like there you
go all
right I'm going to pop some in now a
little bit and then I'm going to leave
some on the side for now
now all right and then I got some mint
right here too so let's get some mint in
here I'm not going to use a lot of
mint I'm just going to eat a little bit
of mint today not a lot of it I'm going
to eat a little bit of it okay there we
go
there coming together you guys coming
together so we got Millet so we can do
we can do a little bit of millet half
cup a full cup whatever you would like
I'm going to do a scoop gauge
it two cups you can do
so I'm going to take some freshly cooked
Millet here it's cooked perfectly too as
well see what you don't do is you don't
put an over it fat you don't put oil in
here with this Millet you don't do that
you keep you keep the fats
out and list if you're if you're
somebody that's you know you just don't
want to do the Millet you don't have to
do the Millet do it without the Millet
if you're a meat eater take the Millet
out replace it with some meat but do it
the way I was talking about going to put
a little bit more here cuz I want
roughly around two cups so I'm going to
put a little bit more in here there you
go see how that
looks nice looking real
good give it a good mix
I think it's got a great balance of
everything in
there I can put it in a different
Bowl Millet is one of my favorite grains
it's a grain that can help you heal it
can offers a lot of nutrition a lot of
phytochemical
compounds it's not that you should be un
Mill it every day it's one of these
things though you can use as a tool if
you use it just
right if you mix Millet with a whole
bunch of oil and a whole bunch of nut
butter or tahini it's not a good it's
not a good use of it if you're
healing cweed hero says no radical
fat just conservative fat really
smart so yeah so there we go I made the
dish I made it in this bowl I could set
it up in a different Bowl though
potentially make it kind of look look
okay uh you can do it in different ways
here and maybe I can even do this really
quick can do something like this
too and what you can do is just
basically plac in this
beautiful like little white Bowl here
and there we we
go that was not an exhaustive
list I can talk about the war against
the plant-based movement and the vegan
movement all day long but I want to save
some for my
podcast like the Gory stuff I want to
save the Gory stuff the more Sinister
stuff the medical medum podcast at Apple
podcast have you checked out the medical
medum podcast the nature episode I just
did have you got to listen to on that
please check it out when you get a
chance go to Medical Me podcast at Apple
podcast listen to the nature one I just
did that'd be amazing Spotify please go
to
Spotify that's a place to definitely go
so what I'm going to do is add a little
bit of parsley cilantro right on the top
right here over there in IG I love your
new podcast about nature amazing check
it out when you guys get a chance and
please listen out on my telegram because
I'm leaving telegram messages almost
every single
night and they're not messages like hey
everybody what's
happening Wendy says over there on
YouTube thank you for the telegram
messages and the new podcast aw thanks
Wendy the telegram
messages you know they're from my heart
and soul and from Spirit of compassion
and and a lot to do with healing it's
very very um powerful information
there's Tools in there just to
understand that information can help
someone Jay over there on YouTube your
last Light blast in calabases took my
foot pain totally away thank you Spirit
of
compassion Spirit of compassion um told
me that it it took the pain away from a
lot of people there there were many
people somebody had a really bad elbow
problem where they had pain pain and
they didn't know why they had an elbow
surgery and it didn't fix it um Spirit
of compassion said that the person's
elbow it kept them up at night they were
trying to keep away from painkillers and
after the life blast they never had it
again the elbow pain so and I'm so glad
that happened for you too um Spirit of
compassions also has told me that many
people weeks after have gotten like
symptom relief where symptoms have
finally gone away after the light blast
so everything they've been doing all in
the
above um Jay markwell says hi Anthony
can't wait to see you at Cafe Gratitude
I am going to be a Cafe Gratitude on the
21st 22nd 23rd 24th have you gotten a
ticket 21st 22nd 23rd 24th did you get a
ticket did you get in because they were
all sold out the menu launches a Cafe
Gratitude it launches October 15th in LA
Cafe Gratitude October 15th the menu
medical medium menu that's going to be
on Cafe gratitudes menu starts October
15th I'm so excited you should come down
and check it out even if you didn't get
a ticket to the Cafe Gratitude gig where
I'm going to be meeting and greeting
everybody I'm going to be eating I'm
going to be talking I'm going to be um
even potentially doing a light blast you
never know but it's going to be
incredible I'll tell you that like true
medical medium fashion it's going to be
incredible so we'll see what happens
maybe you know maybe we'll just we'll
just have fun
but um just letting everybody know
though that the menu though October 15th
it starts medical meem menus are going
to be on the menu then and I'm going to
be coming in there periodically I'm
going to be there
so
anyway but I mean who knows who knows
what going to happen we'll see I just
know I'm going to be there and it's
going to be a great meet and
greet you guys I'm going to eat I'm
excited I'm going to dig in right now
and just see how good this
is so good so
good it's refreshing tastes so
good amazing so check out my
telegram look out
from my podcast on
Spotify CN toopa over there on YouTube
says I love your podcasts I listen to
them every day on my drive to and from
work love your telegram messages too
incredible and I want to tell you guys
too anybody who got who literally got
harmed by that storm by
hen my heart's with you my prayers are
with you I pray every single night for
anyone and everyone that was
harmed in in in that Storm's
way and that you know and has suffered
and is suffering right now today I know
that's like literally like a war zone
there people are just suffering so bad
and they're without so many things and
so many
resources it's just catastrophic it
breaks my heart it kills me to know
people are suffering on that level after
that storm blew
through truly truly evil storm in so
many ways um no doubt propelled by
um
illumination really sick really sick
anyway you guys just know my heart's
with you anyone that
is is um struggling right now through
that through the aftermath of that storm
just it kills me my prayers are out out
there all the time I'm putting prayers
out I'm sending light all the time I'm
asking Spirit of compass passion to
please um send
light
anyway you guys crisy says best podcast
on
Earth I'm blown
away that's a
compliment there's a lot of podcasts out
there that's a that's a compliment okay
that is well you know it's not a coffee
talk show right so one thing about the
medical Mee podcast it's there to help
people it's not a Coffee Talk Show where
it's just like coffee talk you know and
everybody just says diarrhea of the
mouth it doesn't mean if it helps
anybody or not the medical podcast is
about helping
people Amber Gardner aw your telegram
messages heal me amazing I will leave
another one tonight and I will continue
to leave one did you listen to The Pride
and Prejudice ones The Pride and
Prejudice episode I talk about not
episode but the Pride and Prejudice film
that was done in 1995 how no dark
Darkness was involved and how demons
were left at the door the actresses and
actresses demons were left at the door
the film Crews demons were left at the
door um like everything was was it was
like an Angelic an Angelic veil was put
over that entire filming process over
that entire
movie at series it's a 1995 version of
Pride and Prejudice make sure you're on
the medical medium newsletter please
tell other people let people know how to
get on the medical medium newsletter so
you can know what's going on so you can
be you know in on the know and overtime
I'm going to be putting all kinds of
great stuff on there Copa says I love
your podcasts listen to them every day
on my drive to work I read that one
amazing love your telegram messages too
thank you thank
you that's a message to read
twice yep I love you
guys all right I'll see you
keep a light heart please pat yourself
on the back have compassion for yourself
know that I care if you're suffering and
you're struggling with chronic illness
you just hang in there you can heal
please know that and you will heal you
take one day at a time you you
incorporate little pieces of information
take the books to the doctor if you want
you incorporate little bits and pieces
of the information a little bit at a
time whether it's the golden seal you
bring in whether it's something else and
you just take one day at a time and you
just get there and you get there and you
get there August Soha says yes keep the
telegram messages going they make my day
thank you for listening to them I'm so
happy you listen to them and you enjoy
them I see some PMP stuff PMP PMP
PMP yeah it's really great please share
them can I ask a favor can you please
share the telegram messages because it's
hard to get people you know telegram to
hear them it's hard to get people there
you know what I mean telegram's a little
trickier it's it's an amazing platform
but it's it's hard to get people there
anyway definitely if you guys can please
share T telegram messages and the
podcast please share the podcast as well
that would be incredible as well you
guys know I care truly if you're
struggling just hang in there hang in
there if you're on couch Island and
Mattress Island hang in there and know
that I care about you guys deeply and I
understand I understand you know Spirit
of compassion has taught me very early
on in my life to um see things
differently and see things that no one
can see out there when it comes down to
the suffering and suffering of chronic
illness and I can see the little nuances
that you're going through in your life
as you're going through it and I
understand
them give this live stream a thumbs
up if you like it if you hate it give it
a thumbs up
lra 144 aw see you and Cafe gratitud see
you you got
in you got a ticket amazing Nina Nova
and believe me at Cafe grud I am GNA see
you I am GNA see you at Cafe
Gratitude like literally I'm going to
see you it's just the restaurant I'm
going to be in the restaurant with you
Nina NOA my doctor recommends the
medical medium book
indeed indeed I have to put an indeed
after that
wow wow
amazing
whoa uh Jackie says over there on
YouTube I have a ticket for someone
whoa that is cool that is cool wrangling
over there on YouTube thanks heaps for
the telegram messages aw it means a lot
to me please do have light Blast for us
too
you mean like the one the virtual light
blast that I did I think like a year and
a half ago I think I did one right the
virtual light blast I'll try to do that
in the future if I
can did you guys remember what happened
125,000
people were on that light blast and
300,000 people crashed it and it all
went down anyway for a little bit and
then we got it back up Sinister King
over there on YouTube says great stream
aw I'm honored truly
honored Deli over there on YouTube which
book is the recipe
whoa brain saver protocols brain saver
protocol there it is do you have the
brains saver books the recipe is millet
and Herb salad it's so good I can't wait
to have it Chad and Kayla over there on
YouTube my husband and I have both been
suffering from shinkles oo terrible mono
for over a year mono with no hope until
we've been practicing your info thanks
so much of what you're doing with s so
and that's the thing the medical me
information has all this information so
you can heal and if you don't have mono
in the moment you don't have shingles
think about what it can do for all your
other symptoms and conditions and
everything else think about how it can
help you think about how it got people
out of wheelchairs think about what it
did for people's skin conditions their
Vitiligo their psorasis think about all
the different stuff about medical mem
information getting people out of bed
getting them better reversing ALS
Parkinson's so many people had
Parkinson's got Parkinson's better and
you know it's crazy out there one person
one person in the health space out there
an influencer or somebody or a PhD or
some kind of doctor they get one person
better and they're screaming and
screaming and they want PR firms coming
on board telling everybody how do we get
this out there you're amazing you're a
hero you got one person better medical
meme information got millions better
around the world people like all walks
of
life and I don't want a medal I just
want you better and healing I do want
the darkness to stop but the vegan
movement and the plant-based movement
they being clobbered and that's what
this episode was about you
guys
um
yep Cotto over there in IG I healed my
TM J shingles with this information and
that right there is something that's
very powerful and I'll tell you why cuz
I've seen
shingles and I've seen
hsv2 you know hsv1 I've seen
shingles really cause problems with
people with the TMJ the jaw pain the
burning gums burning tongue or the the
Mand joints all messed up swollen and
inflamed and the teeth hurting
and the suffering where people can't
even chew they can't even do this people
at TMJ with mysterious neurological
viral TMJ like the shingles TMJ that
nobody knew existed it was medical mem
information that put it out there that
you know I used to get punished for just
saying that every minute back years ago
people would come on how dare you stick
up for your own information Aw how dare
you say that that's your information oh
my God the amount of people that were
just so jealous and jealous why it's
here for them too so they can heal like
why be jealous people can't even do
this when they have that TMJ so bad and
I think about that a
[Music]
lot I don't take it for granted myself
that I could sit there and chew and be
happy and swallow these people have so
much gastroparesis so much
TMJ so many neurological problems or
Vegas nurse and medical medium
information can help people through all
that love you guys