anthony william live right here
and you guys i'm going to be going on
tick tock i want to let you know about
that
a little later on keep your
notifications on because i'm answering
questions
thoroughly on there and i mean the kind
of thoroughly that
i haven't had time to do all this time
so it's going to be really incredible on
that level when answering health
questions
hey everybody so i want to keep you keep
that in mind also i'm
juicing too like yesterday on tick tock
i was juicing and talking
in and out about all the juicing tips
for celery
what it does for a body all of it so it
was really really packed with
information on tick tock so
and it's a whole different kind of
platform a whole different kind of thing
the way i'm doing it on there so i don't
want you to miss out
so i'm going to be on here for a little
bit talk to you guys of course and
everything and then
i got to do instagram live for just a
couple minutes and then i'm going on
tick tock to do the juicing and
answering health questions
thoroughly i want you to have your
notifications on for that because
they don't save the video on tick tock
so the live won't be saved you can't
just say hey i'll watch that live later
on or i'll watch that live some other
time
it doesn't work like that um so the live
disappears but what i'm going to do in
that live on tic tac toc
is really going to be providing
tremendous amounts of health information
i'm going to answer questions thoroughly
um all of that you guys are all coming
on here it's incredible i'm glad we got
a chance because i want to answer some
questions here while i'm here too for a
little bit
but so i wanted to fill you in on that
and it's really important because um
basically you guys know i'm censored
censored an instant censored on here
everybody gets kicked off no one can you
know watch
or anything it happens all the time you
guys you could be lucky and then boom
you're kicked off like one second you
know how it works but
so um but i'm gonna be have a lot more
freedom
on the tick tock the tick tock app so
you know tick tock dot com forward slash
at medical medium
you know and so you can watch it i'm
going on there later i'm gonna have the
juicer out i'm gonna be juicing celery
because i have to juice a lot of celery
to put i'm going to put some in the
fridge
for tonight for tomorrow and then we're
answering
questions about celery juice in depth on
what it does inside the body so tick
tock dot com forward slash
medical medium and um link is in the
description too so you know and go to
the app get the tick tock app but i'm
not some
it's not that i'm trying to push you
guys out of here because i always want
to be on facebook and i always want to
be on
youtube and that's not it at all it's
just that i'm going to have a lot more
freedom to be able to
answer questions really thoroughly in a
way that's not
censored see i don't know if you guys
know that but
but literally i'm sensor centered except
for the medical medium podcast medical
media podcast at apple podcast 17
episodes
already and i'm not censored on that and
as long as it's on apple podcast i'm not
so but i'm glad that you guys are here
um and i'm excited about this really so
and but the thing is they don't save on
tick tick tick tock they don't save
the videos so it's going to be a live
it's probably going to be a
a solid one i'm going to be answering
lots of questions
and i'm going to be juicing and talking
about so much information
so important like you guys got questions
here and i i i'm censored on this
platform so i can answer a few questions
but i can't go
crazy and i was talking about like
removing tattoos i was talking about all
kinds of stuff on tick tock
um but i'm going to do daily lives
every single day on tick tock so have
your notifications on and you're going
to get notified
that's the whole thing look you know you
guys out of the 3.5 million followers
i have on facebook i think only uh
800 of you guys get notified or
something
and then you know on instagram i think
only like i don't know a couple hundred
get notified
if at best i don't even think that
anymore anyway so uh it's interesting so
i'm letting you guys know that i'm going
to be on there
today going to do a killer juicing
deal with the just sending the celery
through there
creating uh herbal medicine talk about
what that herbal medicine does inside of
us
so i'm really excited and um
so the i just saw a cellulite question
by the way um
that's the liver for sure so if you want
to get rid of cellulite
if you want to like move that away from
your you know your life and put that
behind you
that's you know that's when you got to
do a lot of good tools you got to like
some of the tools and you got to make
sure you're doing no fats like
that's when i would go like three six
nine cleanse if you got the cellulite
clean up the liver do the 369 advanced
cleanse so important
jennifer jennifer says if i have
hypothyroidism which book should i start
with
okay look i mean i gotta i got the
thyroid healing book an incredible book
because it
covers everything from a to z about the
thyroid but you can do it in cleanse the
heel because
i talk about the thyroid and the
supplementation in cleansing heal i'd
probably go with cleanse to heal
maybe get both but cleansing heal would
be good because you can look in there
you'll see supplementation about
hypothyroidism hyperthyroidism nodules
cysts
hashimoto's thyroiditis and
you'll see information in here and also
you got the cleanses in there the
supplementation
so that's really cool too and so but
yeah
and what about potato kim said what
about potato starch did you listen to
the potato episode
the potato episode is like
really packed with information so
medical media podcast apple podcast i
mean honestly
if you missed that it's a docu-series
episode
it's for free i'm not selling anything
i'm not selling anything for god's sake
it's it's free so medical mean podcast
at apple podcast
i got a whole episode on potato
every the ins and outs night shade not
night shade all of that you guys
they should check that out potato starch
yeah potato starch is
incredible glucose for our bloodstream
blood
sugar you need blood sugar and that's
the best one there
shauna says shauna bill says you've been
doing zing shock therapy
incredible medical medium zinc shock
therapy um
so that's that's amazing that you're
doing that make sure though it's a zinc
that
that i use personally um it's the best
sync the whole bit you can go to see it
on my directory medicalmeme.com
it's at my directory michelle l's here
they're already watching everyone
everywhere
yeah aren't they ever and you know
so um that's funny and uh
so tina says your tick tock
i love it uh you make me smile and learn
that's great it's really gonna be fun
because what i'm gonna be able to do on
there
is just to help people and get
information out there it's going to be
so cool
like already i'm going to do the live
today and i'm going to talk about things
i don't talk about
i'm going to talk about stuff i'm going
to answer questions i don't answer
um because yeah i mean it's important so
um it's gonna be like new content you
know all medical medium information is
unique
original and from source for 35 years so
if you hear bits and pieces of it out
there you think it's already been out
there like it's crazy like i see people
out there saying things like
toxic heavy metals cause anxiety
dude that only comes from one source
there's no research in science that came
out with a paper saying metals heavy
metals cause anxiety
it only comes from medical medium
information it always has
there's nothing there's no study out
there that shows that but yet people
like even
practitioners out there will say anxiety
uh
you know metals have something to do
with anxiety are you kidding uh
that only comes from the source so
why don't you cite it please because
that's not from a research study paper
it's kind of funny how it goes um and um
so the thing is is that with this with
you know the live i'm going to do on
tick tock you guys got to know
i'm going to be juicing celery but i'm
going to be answering questions
thoroughly you don't want to miss that i
mean it was
it was a blast yesterday on that tick
tock live and the video is not saved so
you have to have your notifications on
so you go to the app
i would go to the app and i would i
would sign up ticktock.com
forward slash uh medical media link is
in profile
so you don't miss out because honestly
you guys i'm serious like
it's a whole different thing i'm gonna
be doing the link is in the description
link is in the description it's a whole
different thing i'm going to be doing
i'm
really going to try to help you guys
what happens is i try to help you anyway
i try to help you on here
wherever i am you know all the lives
i've done talking about all the
different
diseases symptoms and conditions all of
it but i just want to keep on
going as far as i can then i get
censored then it gets censored that's
why the medical media podcast is out
at apple podcast so that's the whole
point
and uh it's really important so if you
get kicked off right now just because
everybody's just gets kicked off my
platforms for some reason no one gets
notified you get kicked off
so you at least know where you're going
to find me all the time so
um anyway from here i'm going to go to
ig and then i'm going to
go to tick tock so i wanted to give you
guys that 4-1-1
and that's cool um uh lenin says
can you tell us the times beforehand so
we know when you're going live and tick
tock
to honestly subscribe to my page on tick
tock this way you get the notification
right when i go live you get the
notification and because honestly i
won't know what time
it's not the same time every day i wish
i wish i could and all that
vicki b says hey anthony can you
recommend anything for burning mouth
syndrome caused by nerve damage yeah
that's the
that's if it has if you didn't have an
actual injury that's the shingles virus
that causes
all that nerve stuff burning mouth
burning gums jaw pain
all of that and that that's when you can
easily go to the shingle section and
cleanse the heel easily get the book
free the library if you don't want it's
on sale at amazon
i mean but you can get it free
collaborate um so yeah
so uh see there's just there's so many
things there's so many things
you can do so many tools you can use
that like the medical means zinc shock
therapy
that we were talking about earlier it's
incredible for the immune system you
feel like you're coming down with
something or something's going on but if
you use the wrong zinc it could have
citric acid in it could have some kind
of preservative in it so just make sure
if you're ever going to do that i do the
vimergy that's what i would do
that's what i tell my family and friends
to do is the vimergy
zinc it's the only one that i trust to
do any kind of any kind of sync
supplement
won't be the thing but that one is um
going live
today in the next 30 to 45 minutes
on tick tock so the next in 30 to 45
minutes i'm going live on tick tock
letting you guys know i just gonna go to
instagram in a minute
and then after that be on there for
about five minutes or so and then 30
minutes from now i'll be on
because i got to prep things i'm going
to be prep getting the juicer out i'm
going to be getting ready
because we're going to cover questions
on health everything
anyway you guys running to instagram now
i love you greatly and
proud of all you guys