later and if you guys have been there
i'm going to be making myself
dinner or lunch or however you call it
going to be making myself dinner lunch
talking about the foods that i'm working
with because
i got to make myself something to eat so
i'm going to be doing that i'm also
going to be answering questions
thoroughly so um i'm really excited
about that so
hope you guys set your notifications on
for tick tock
a little while from here i'm going to go
to instagram and then from instagram i'm
going to go right to tiktok
and hope you guys actually are there so
i'm answering questions
i'm actually cooking in my kitchen
and making food and all of that so
and answering questions and all that so
i'm hoping you guys are there for that i
hope you don't miss out
and you set your notifications on tick
tock just set your notifications so you
don't
miss it so you don't miss it that's the
whole point um yeah david david witching
tick tock live later were you there
yesterday
right right and uh it's really cool so
i'm gonna answer a couple questions here
right now though so i am gonna do that
i'm gonna
say hi to you guys answer a couple
questions um hello from france
regina hey from france amazing what a
great place
um beautiful beautiful country out there
so you guys i'm excited i'm going to be
going on tik tok
live and they're not recorded so you
can't just see
them later like facebook we can't just
post it or anything
and i'm going to be on there for a good
old hour and i'm going to be covering
lots of different questions i want to
answer lots of questions i'm going to be
making myself
food because i got to eat later so i'm
not sure what i'm making yet
not quite sure yesterday i did the
cranberry water i made myself a big
salad all of that so very vegan says
what should i do for chronic hives
um so for chronic hives you got to think
about this okay so
why is there is there this reaction in
the body
what's happening like why is the body
reacting
well what happens with hives is our body
reacts to a toxin
a toxin and then we get these hives a
result from this toxin
and the hives come and go they'll come
up they'll go down
they'll come up they'll go down and what
happens is that
there's a toxin coming from some place
and it comes from the liver
and so as blood's coming out of your
liver it's going to take some of that
toxin and sweep it out of the liver
send it through your bloodstream send it
to the skin and you're just going to
react and react and react so what kind
of toxin
is it well a lot of little things can do
that okay
so a little bit of pathogen material
like a byproduct from
the old mono bug the epstein-barr bug
that sits inside her liver
for years and years and years that
releases poisons those poisons go out
we react we react and then streptococcus
if you ever had strep throat when you
were younger or a kid or ear infections
or
a stye or uti that strep is still in her
system and once in a while a little
pocket of that junk just swoops out of
the liver
and it causes a hive and then if you run
into different other
exposures and triggers like toxins like
mold or air fresheners and scented
candles
that's going to really instigate it
that's really going to instigate it or
conventional cleaning supplies or bleach
that's really going to instigate it so
that's how it works so um you can clean
that up you can clean the liver up you
can work with your foods
medical medium information you can you
know do that because you can i would do
just steamed potatoes celery juice and
butter leaf lettuce for like a month and
try to get rid of those hives that's
what i would do
um it would go with the mono eating i
would do the moderating cleanse and
cleanse the heal that's that's and just
do the potato mono eating cleanse with
you see since you're vegan you shouldn't
have a problem doing steamed potatoes
twice a day have salads with it lettuces
romaine lettuce butter leaf lettuce red
leaf lettuce and do your celery juice
do your lemon water maybe the heavy
metal detox smoothie and just do that
every day that's what i would do i would
do that every day for a month
get rid of the hives clean up that liver
and all of that hello yesterday's tick
tock was great
kesha wasn't it so cool my god i can't
believe it you were there
i can't believe it and you're gonna be
there today because i'm doing today's
tick tock and i'm going to answer
questions
i hope i see your comment come up
because a lot of comments come up lately
so i hope i see it
and so i can answer your question um
ruth says best foods and supplements
from
for rheumatoid arthritis so
ra that's caused by ebv
because that's what causes ra it causes
hashimoto's it causes fibromyalgia
that's what it causes it causes a lot of
different conditions it causes the
hashimoto's thyroiditis
and so ra that is the true
cause people don't know that it's it's
ebv so
if you're going to be eating foods or
you're going to be taking care of
yourself or supplements you want to be
anti-viral
and that's what you want to do you can
always take that information to the
doctor and learn about
r.a and everything but i'm going to be
answering questions extra thoroughly
on tick-tock so uh mika says love your
tick-tock videos
and that's so cool did you guys see the
egg one on tick-tock
you saw the egg video that i did um
that was a fun one that was a fun one it
really was it really was so
yeah um you guys so i'm gonna be on
there in a little while
okay and i hope you set your
notifications because
and you know what in order to in the
link is in the description
go to the app to get tick-tock app and
learn how to do it but you have to
you have to set the notification on the
tick tock
app and then you have to set it in your
you know you have to set it in your
your your your profile all that you have
to make sure that notification is set in
every way possible in order to get it
because some people say well i'm not
getting it
i'm not getting it that's what you got
to do um
so but i'm looking forward to answer a
ton of questions i'm going to be cooking
in my kitchen
so i'm going to get the food out i'm
going to be making my dinner
and i'm not sure exactly what i'm going
to make yet so antonia
from hello from queens new york whoa
queens so cool and michelle uh
snape hi from australia i love the land
down under
are you kidding that's incredible
jennifer hi anthony i'm here
yay i'm glad you're here awesome that's
incredible
um uh donnie says
which book would be best to share as a
starting point for a friend with
crohn's or ibs i would share cleanse the
heel that's the one i would share
mono-eating cleanses for ibs um crohn's
colitis bloating just the mono-eating
cleanse that's why they're in here that
would be so
so important right there um
so eunice says hi how can i find the
episode or podcast about why i feel
hurt do you niece have you checked out
the
neurological symptom well your feet hurt
um
can you check out the neurological
symptom podcast and look at that one
feet hurt body pain neck pain back pain
feet pain head pain
dizziness fatigue medical medium podcast
at apple podcast you guys are you
have you heard those episodes the five
meditations
i know i sound like a broken record
lately but have you done them
have you done all five meditations
medically podcasted apple podcast
heather says
i have questions about eggs how do we
substitute for them
or is it possible to eat them in foods
that are cooked
with them without being immune
compromised
look heather you know if you got like
something going on
aches and pains fatigue if you've been
diagnosed with any kind of symptom or
condition
if you're somebody that's living with
something that you don't want to live
with some kind of symptom
some kind of condition i would keep the
eggs out even in cooked food
i would keep the eggs out even when it's
in food
it's in something else and it's mixed i
would just keep it away if you can
because
that would that it could get us in
trouble so what's your egg replacement
avocado in a potato
i would replace egg with avocado or
potato
or if you really want both you know
that's what i would do i'd replace it
with both of those things avocado and
potato that's what i would do
um i would consider that charo says yep
just done the star meditation yay
cool awesome awesome because it's
powerful one
really powerful meditation really is
chris says what is the best way to
address multiple health diagnoses so you
got multiple health diagnoses so what
i've always said is
which one here's the thing which one
bothers you the most
so that's what i've always said and you
can go in here find out which one
bothers you the most
you can look into it and work that way
if if you want you can maybe one that
bothers you less that's okay too and
start with that but what you're going to
find out about is
that if you address one of your
conditions in here you're going to
notice
other things going away because they're
all connected
julie says fruit picking meditation is
wonderful yay
i love that one so much it's so
healing it's so healing joelle says your
information
saved my husband from psoriasis thank
you i love all your meditations we're
live right now you guys by the way we're
live
that's it joelle that's incredible hey
actually episode
applesauce is here favorite meditation
so far is moon meditation
incredible ashley that's so great that's
so great
i'm so happy to hear that believe me um
alexandra you're here the meditations
are helping me process so much grief and
let it go
and surprising surprising how
gentle the meditations make it that's
the whole point the meditations are
there to help you release things in a
way that's
healing and gentle and not hard work
that's the point they're guided
meditations you guys you guys know that
deanna's here hi hi deanna deanna d
deanna dia is that how you say your last
name um
elizabeth you're here too the half moon
is coming up elizabeth the half moon is
coming up
yep and it is and the half moon's coming
up it's moon meditation time you guys
seriously it's moon meditation guys it's
time
i mean you do it in the full moon and
you do it in the week of the half moon
or three days around the half moon
that's that's the powerhouse right there
because the magnetic pull of a half moon
does
different things than the magnetic pull
of a full moon
take advantage of the moon meditation
whatever you do take advantage of it
it's free
definitely do it so we're gonna get
there we're gonna get there
it's coming up um
so uh marissa juicing celery as we speak
while listening to you laugh marissa do
you have the tic tac talk account set up
are you going to tic toc to do the live
cause i'm going to be making food
i'm going to be making food i'm going to
be eating we're going to be talking
we're going to be answering
questions thoroughly margie cameron's
here
hey you're here incredible it's honor
i'm honored
coach johnson whoa cleanse the heel is
saving me from neuropathy in both feet
and psoriasis whoa you're doing cleanse
the heel psoriasis
i am out of the wheelchair coach
that is a big deal that is a big deal
and i'm
blown away and so proud of you
unbelievable so proud of you you don't
even know you don't even know how proud
i am of you you don't even know
i mean seriously seriously um
joanne says i react to everything some i
become allergic some is multiple
chemical sensitivity plus i have
fibromyalgia arthritis osteoporosis
contact dermatitis ibs and more
i can't take anything for pain i'm
allergic to meds
think about the mono heating cleanse
joanne that that's what i would do i
would recommend that
to a family member and i did actually i
think was a couple of months ago maybe
three months ago it was three months ago
a family member came to me
okay reached out to me i haven't talked
to in a long time from out of state
and um and from maine and you know and
where i come from and the thing is is
that family member
said to me you know i'm sensitive to
everything what do i do i was like the
monolithic cleanse the monolining
cleanse pick
one and work with it then pick another
out of the monolithing cleanse
that that's that's where you go and take
it to the doctor take it take the book
to your doctor if you want
get it free at the library if you don't
want to buy it on amazon even though
it's on sale
um lizzie stewart hello first time
texted here laugh out loud list i'm glad
you're here okay
what you'll learn about the medical me
medium community is this the community
is incredible okay people with
compassion are here
real compassion they've been through
hell and back some letting you know liz
how it works
we got the most most
integrity-filled faith-powered up people
just
just the most incredible compassionate
people here
in the medical medium community and you
need to know that because
it is what it is totally um
dory russell where are your meditations
okay dory medical medium podcast
at apple podcast that's where it's free
free okay and link is in the description
link is in the description you'll get
all the meditations for free
i could package them up and sell them
okay i've been told to do them like no
i don't do that i don't do that they're
so healing
you must try them the moon meditation is
critical right now
because the half moon is it's coming up
and the magnetic pull the half moon
is powerful just like the full moon
powerful
um colleen fleming hey colleen all the
meditation podcasts are great
honors you think so honored you feel
that way blows my
mind and everything so you guys i'm
heading off
to instagram now i have to alert
everybody about tick tock because i'm
gonna be doing the tick tock live
don't miss it because you guys i'm doing
things on tick tock
i can't do anywhere else because i'm
censored so i have to be very careful on
here even though i'm with you guys and
i'm talking i'm answering questions
i have to be careful to the extent
sometimes of what i say are the
questions and stuff
and i'm just censored everywhere you
guys know i'm censored on youtube
they don't show my youtube videos to
anybody they don't whatever it's just
how it works and i'm censored on
facebook and instagram so
i'm going to go on there and let
everybody know that i'm going to be on
tick tock
and then we're going to do major major
educational session session there
answering questions
getting like thoroughly answering
questions make sure you get your
notepads
make sure you have your notepad so you
can take down information okay because
the
the video isn't saved all right and
so really important to know um ichoda i
love that part too actually it's always
moves me to tears
showed i'm glad you're here i'm going to
tic tac soon but i'm going to hit
instagram real quick i love you guys
bless your heart