this is important please if you guys
have a second to listen to this we Soul
search because of life's hardships the
hardship scale I've seen people go
through atrocities and I had
unbelievable hardships where if they
tell someone you don't have words you
can't fathom what that's like and those
hardships take them to a place of
soul-searching and then you have people
where they had hardships too but the
scale is so different for everyone
there's different levels of hardships
but it depends on which world you live
in you can be someone who's silver spoon
fed great support system not a care in
the world no financial problems
whatsoever a family giving you support
you go off to private schools
everybody's worried about you everybody
is taking care of you you don't have to
worry about anything and you can still
have a hardship still have a hardship
and still get affected like the scale is
different for everyone and then you can
be someone that comes from nothing and
got hit by a train or a bus but you are
not weak you are not weak regardless and
you're not weak just because you're
chronically sick you're still not weak
strongest people I've ever seen and let
me go into this part you know how strong
people who have chronic illness really
are people who have been sick for years
they're strong I can guarantee you that
if you take someone who's an athlete
maybe a professional athlete in football
or basketball or professional swimmer or
something and they get chronic illness
screaming like a baby screaming and
screaming like a baby can't handle it
for more than six months can't handle it
for more than two months there's people
out there who are chronically sick for
five six years bent every doctor been to
everything they've been through hell and
back but they're strong really strong
they may not seem strong they can't run
a marathon but then you take somebody
who's been stronger their whole life
they run marathons and everything and
they finally get sick they are screaming
bloody murder because they can't take it
for a minute because it's it's stopping
them from doing what they want to do and
and feel and be indestructible and they
can't handle it it's amazing how it
works the most strongest people I've
ever known are people that have been
through it and they understand and
they've been sick did you guys sign up
because the collecting Stone's
meditation journey is going to blow your
mind it's going to be like nothing
you've ever experienced you'll never
forget it collecting Stones meditation
Journey registration is open the journey
starts July 19th you will never ever
ever forget it