[Music]
I'm at Cafe Gratitude right now what
you're looking at is the collaboration
of Cafe Gratitude medical medium the
West reset cleanse right in front of me
let's go into this a little bit why is
this the best cleanse to begin with
celery juice it actually gets into your
gastric glands it restores them your HCL
Rises up you digest food proteins they
don't rot in the gut you don't get that
ammonia gas out celery juice helps to
cleanse all this junk out but it helps
to restore the gastric glands and the
liver let's get into the heavy metal
detox millions of people around the
world do this heavy metal detox right
here people have mercury aluminum lead
arsenic Nickel in their body this helps
to bring it out it's in the wellness
reset so here you are you go into your
celery juice now boom you're going into
your heavy metal detox how incredible is
that Cravings shifter shot why is this
important because people in cleanses end
up blowing their cleans
have you been on a cleanse before do you
know what that's like where all of a
sudden you can't help it anymore you're
like and you start grabbing food and
you're just like emotionally eating this
helps to stop that this is the craving
shifter shot and this is a very powerful
shot indeed spice squash soup squash is
healing it's hearty and healing it
brings glucose to the brain so that
you're not short circuiting and that's
the whole point cleanses hurt the brain
out there people do all kinds of
cleanses but it's it's not fortifying
it's not restoring brain cells it's not
restoring gal cells it's not restoring
neurons and what you have here is a
cleanse that helps do that so you can
cleanse and heal and give your body what
it needs brain Soother juice
electrolytes boom here you are it's
coming towards the middle of the day the
end of the day and you're getting the
brain Soother juice in you and it's
helping to bring back all these
nutrients the electrolytes and
everything to your neurons here we go
healing broth soup right there power ful
soup all in its own it's a recipe that's
been around this is the medical medium
healing broth soup people use it when
they get the flu they feel under the
weather help support their immune system
that's in this cleanse dream shifter
shot why is this important because when
you're really cleansing you dream lots
of emotions come up hardships you may
have had in your life trauma in your
life all of that stuff surfaces or
resurfaces and triggers happen too when
people cleanse out there this cleanse
helps so you can do it feel strong feel
satisfied and the dream shifter shot is
something to help you heal while you're
sleeping so you get this you send it
down you go down for the night your
dreams are happening you're healing
through your dreams emotions are coming
up junk is processing coming out of the
body you wake up in the morning boom
you're back to the celery juice you're
pulling all this stuff out more metals
are loosening up boom heavy metal detox
is pulling out all the metals back to
the Cravings shifter shot CU you're
going to be thinking for a second wait a
minute because you're healing so much
you need something to back down some of
the Cravings boom you got your spice
squash soup it's hearty it's going to
feel good it's going to fuel your brain
brain Soother juice it's going to give
you electrolytes give you the
restoration you need for the brain cells
healing broth soup for the immune system
building it up and back again to the
dream shifter shot for all those
emotions and all that trauma coming out
there's not a cleanse out there like
this if you don't live in LA and you
don't have the Cafe Gratitude nearby
it's worth taking a trip from around the
world to get here move yourself forward
experience it and feel it because
there's nothing out there like this
you're not going to see anything like
this you're not going to ever try
anything like this unless you try it
here at Cafe Gratitude I'm medical
meeting Anthony William this is an
incredible cleanse in front of me I hope
you try it
[Music]