I can't wait to talk about it brain
saver books both of them two brain saver
books greatest books of all time history
my opinion
and I promise you be the judge of it
when you get your brain saver books you
will feel the same way they're filled
with light you feel them the power in
them to empower you it's all incredible
it blows my mind I'm talking about
supplements today
damaging problematic to the brain
supplementation reading right out of
brain saver protocols right here
brain saver
brain saver protocols it's two books
released at one time it's an incredible
thing I just want to say this one thing
before I start
people judge people
they judge people they judge them by the
way they look
they judge people
by the way they act they judge people
by their sense of humor they judge
people by the way they sound they judge
people
through their voice the way they hear it
people judge people and I want to tell
you something
if you're somebody doesn't like my voice
don't like my snarkiness sometimes or if
you're somebody you just don't like the
way I look you don't like my hat you
don't like whatever my shirt
or if you're somebody that just isn't
like
I don't know
the way I am
regardless you know billionaire friend
of mine told me this guy got a ton of
money right made it big in the world
incredible guy big business man guy and
all that and he was checking on me he
wanted to see how he's doing it's like
hey W how you doing because I know
you're killing yourself I know you work
hard what's going on how are you I'm
like okay okay you know some people they
like me some people they don't like me
and he said they probably don't like
that the fact that
you you're like you're like working
class you weren't a trust funder you
weren't you didn't go to colleges you
didn't go to fancy universities you
didn't you know you weren't a trust fund
or kid you weren't you just came from
nothing and they Pro he was telling me
he goes some people probably smell it on
you they just smell it on you and they
don't like it because they're probably
snobs and you know and he said to some
people probably just don't like your
sense of humor or some people don't like
whatever but one thing's for certain
these are the greatest books of all time
and do not
let a judgment get in your way if you're
somebody new in the community and you're
like judging me trying to figure me out
like what's this guy really about he's
not a doctor he's not an MD don't cheat
yourself out of healing don't cheat
yourself out of an opportunity
to save someone's life to protect
someone's life to protect your brain to
help you don't cheat yourself out of
that opportunity these are powerful
books incredible powerful books
and keep that in mind when you open them
and you receive them let's talk about
supplementation a little bit I'm opening
up the brainstorm protocols I want to
make one quick announcement announcement
announcement
next week and I don't know the day yet
but next week
doing a brain shot therapy cleanse okay
next week we're doing a brain shot
therapy cleanse next week so I'm just
letting you know so that's coming up
next week it's free it's free so listen
out for my emails listen out sign up to
my email list and all that listen out so
you can take a look there okay
and so there's definitely some glitches
on on Tech today there's definitely some
glitches on social media looks like a
lot of you guys are being kicked off
like rapidly like never before so so
anyway but the bottom line is it's not
on my side the glitches aren't on my
side the glitches are on the apps
obviously they're not on my side so I'm
sorry if you guys can't even view this
or you're missing so much of this right
now can you screen shoot
can you screen shoot a video you guys of
what's happening to you guys as you're
getting like kicked off and all that can
you screen shoot that and DM that to me
if you guys can do that so I can get
assistance Tech assistance on the apps
so if you see that happening so like for
instance IG Instagram I see everybody's
getting kicked off like everybody so if
you can screen shoot that
watch on telegram or rumble on medical
medium.com on how to do it but if you
can you know watch it there I mean if
you need to go there if you're getting
kicked off left and right to watch it on
telegram right now so I'm live on
telegram I'm live on
YouTube right now okay I'm live on
medicalmedium.com right now so you can
watch me on there too but if you can
screen shoot how you're being kicked off
and how everything's glitching out and
glitching out because they're asking me
to get some data so they can help me so
on IG they're asking me how you know how
can we help you so if you guys could do
that and then send it to my DM
you know DM me the uh the uh video you
know recording of How It's kicking you
off and all this other stuff's happening
sorry to throw that in there right now
it's just that it's unfair for you guys
because I know you guys can't see this
most of you all right so we're in the
book right now
and a reminder that next week I'm
excited about this brain shots
so we're going to be doing the brain
shot
cleanse together okay so medical mean
brain shot therapy cleanse together next
week so I'm excited about that you don't
want to miss that you want to be in that
one with me we're gonna be live we're
gonna be doing it together next week I
don't know the day yet so sign up to my
email list so you can actually receive
the information to know when it's
happening and we're going to be making
the brain shots together and we're going
to be doing a 10 day
brain shot therapy cleanse the medical
mean brain shot therapy challenge that's
what it is
so I'm excited about this so next week I
just want you to know because I see more
people trying to come on
medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse out of brain saver
we're going to do 10 days
live in person
free
you don't have to pay for it you don't
have to do it you know it's free so
that's what's incredible so I'm really
excited about this
so it's a challenge brain shot therapy
challenge coming up next week I want to
let everybody know and I'm going to
mention it a couple times during this
little talk we're doing right now
because I want you guys to all know
about it I'm pumped can't even tell you
incredible this is
so I'm in a book right now I'm in the
protocols book as we speak put brain
saver right over here
[Music]
some of the medical medium protocols and
I'm in
brain betrayer supplements this is
really important because you guys know
I've been doing a couple of lives just
about this
these supplements fall into four main
categories I have to talk about that
again problematic and damaging
supplements
problematic and damaging supplements
mildly problematic supplements
overrated or overused supplements
quality concerns supplements where it's
especially important to seek out high
quality forms because they're frequently
produced with low quality ingredients or
problematic additives or preservatives
there's four categories
in this list of problematic and damaging
supplements I got alkaline ionizer water
machines apple cider vinegar products
taken internally Bentonite and other
Clays when taken internally
caffeine-based energy supplements taken
internally obviously charcoal taken
internally Chlorella
chlorine dioxide
cod liver oil or shark liver oil
colostrum deer antler or also called
deer velvet
diatomaceous earth digestive bitters
essential oils taken internally so don't
get upset about that for the moment with
essential oil things I know that oh my
God the crap I get for even saying
essential oil I mean I'm saying take it
internally that's the problem right
there
fat burners because there's fat burners
people are doing fat burners fish oil
and krill oil yeah you know me people
that are on krill oil it's insane not
good terrible gut powder blends
herbal tinctures and alcohol
hydrochloric acid supplements you know
what I mean HCL supplements L-Carnitine
supplements or L-Arginine supplements
mineral oil mushroom coffee with
caffeine oyster supplements Pearl powder
sodium bicarbonate you know the whole
sodium bicarbonate thing right where you
take all you mix it all and we'll drink
it all down and take oh man turpentine
oil whey protein powder and zeolites
those are the problematic and damaging
supplement list
so I went through a bunch of these the
other day I didn't go through all of
them but I went through colostrum I did
chlorella the day before I talked about
charcoal I talked about all these I'm
giving you this before warning here
alkaline ionized or water machines why
they're bad when you see the book you
can read all about it and you'll be mind
blown because it's protecting you the
information which is incredible
I talked about the zeolites now I want
to say something about the zeolite thing
because recently some stuff popped up
because of this right
so someone will say well it's a zeolite
that you know I've been doing you know
I've been doing the heavy metal detox
smoothie and as soon as I brought in a
little zeolite things seemed to move
along it's like well you have to
understand how the heavy metal detox
smoothie works when you're doing the
heavy metal detox smoothie for months
it'll finally get to a point where it
removes just enough metal where now
results are starting to happen
sometimes people get really quick
results from the heavy metal detox
smoothie but when you have metal deep in
the brain
it can take months and months of getting
the metal out from the midline canal
zeolite doesn't cross the blood-brain
barrier zeolite does not enter the
bloodstream so zeolite cannot get toxic
heavy metals out of a child's brain it
cannot get toxic heavy metals out of an
adult's brain it's impossible it's like
a clay it sits in the intestinal tract
and it can't get into the bloodstream or
cross the blood-brain barrier you have
to understand clay can't enter your
bloodstream or you will die
clay can only stay in the intestinal
tract
and cling to the lining it can't enter
your bloodstream
zeolite cannot enter your bloodstream or
you'll get a stroke and a blood clot and
die
see how it works
you can't have zeolite or clay float
around in your bloodstream it will
literally give you an aneurysm embolism
a blood clot it'll blow out it'll blow
out a blood vessel you will have a
stroke and die
so what I'm trying to tell you is
zeolite can't get Metals out of your
brain
the heavy metal detox smoothie in the
medical medium books gets metal out of
people's brains
and there's a different story it's a
different thing so you can be doing the
heavy metal detox smoothie for a while
and it's taking you to just about that
threshold of healing and then you try
something else you put some coconut oil
and you're like two weeks later after
doing a little coconut oil you're like
oh it's the coconut oil me no it was the
three months of heavy metal detox
smoothies you did or I tried a little
zeolite spray
um three months into it and three weeks
later it started to change that's from
three months of the heavy metal detox
smoothie or six months of the heavy
metal detox smoothie or one month of the
heavy metal detox smoothie
Clays and zeolite cannot enter into the
bloodstream nor can it cross the
blood-brain barrier nor can it enter the
brain critical to know so this is a
really the details are so important in
the books the brain saver books that go
into depth details about the heavy metal
detox movie how it works how the
ingredients work together and so much
information about how Metals work that
no one has really amazing information
you guys so let's talk about the zeolite
thing one more time because I want to
run I want to run by this because I saw
some comments saying someone say oh yeah
no uh the Zeal I was doing the heavy
metal detox smoothie for a few months
and then after like a few weeks of
trying a zeolite things started moving
forward um no that was after three
months
things started moving forward take the
heavy metal detox smoothie out of your
life completely remove all medical
medium tools remove everything and then
you try the zeolite on its own and see
where you stand and see where it goes
you'll end up like people did 15 years
ago
where they all tried the zeolites and
nobody got better until they've learned
about the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie it was the opposite
people were all on their zeolites the
zeolite craze already happened and no
one got better from years ago but no one
knows about that because every five
years history just boom repeats itself
you get a whole bunch of new suckers and
then it moves forward and moves forward
like that
so in the zeolite talk this is a really
important aspect of it because when
you're doing the heavy metal detox movie
then you see the results as you go along
and anything you bring in sure you could
just be like oh I was
I don't know
I was doing a lot of oregano uh for a
week and then two months later I started
getting better it must have been the
regular no it's not the heavy metal it's
not the heavy metal detox movie it was
the oregano no so here's how it works
like in the past 20 years ago 18 years
ago 16 years ago when the zeolite craze
came in
and all the big marketing companies were
trying to push it
and all the lies about how it worked all
came in because it never leaves the
intestinal tract because Eli can't get
out of your intestinal tract it's a clay
if it goes in your bloodstream if it
actually really physically went into
your bloodstream you would die of a
stroke it would get to your brain clog
you up and you would die of a stroke
Ella says Nano side seal Light May well
enter the bloodstream it doesn't well
enter the bloodstream at all and cross
the blood brain barrier first Ella
that's not true they've never seen it
they've never tested for it they don't
have one document that shows it and they
don't have any signs that shows it
either
it doesn't reach the bloodstream that's
what they tell you and but that's not
accurate first of all clay
can't reach the bloodstream
clay and zeolite it's all the same it
can't reach the bloodstream it can't
enter into it it stays in your
intestinal tract but that's where you're
fooled and the thing is
It's tricky because they get you on the
MLM maybe not UL but they get you on and
and I appreciate your comment they get
you on the the the whole thing where
it's the MLM thing out there or they get
you on that whole thing where
everybody's selling it and so
everybody's sparking out the same stuff
but just so you know they've been saying
it crosses the blood-brain barrier for
20 years and 20 years ago Ella just for
the record
anybody who's using zeolites never moved
forward it never did anything
it was that it was I had thousands of
people call my office thousands saying
that I've been on zeolite and I had to
get them on the heavy metal detox movie
to change their lives the heavy metal
detox movie that's worldwide famous
right now because it's literally changed
so many people's lives and in the brain
saver books
there's a seven okay the seven levels of
the head seven different heavy metal
detox cleanses by the way but it's got
street cred it saved people's lives for
years before I even put it in the books
and I had to do that because zeolite
wasn't working so they've done a flip
now everybody's on the heavy metal detox
movie
and then
the sales reps of zeolite try to get the
medical medium community on the zeolite
because they know it's a Sure Shot
because the the medical medium
communities on the heavy metal detox
smoothie
so when they throw in zeolite it's like
a Sure Shot
because they're already getting better
from the heavy metal detox smoothie
so
let's go into this look the claims they
are making about zeolite are not true
out there
and I talk about that in the brain saver
books but it's important to know what I
recommend if you're big on zeolite then
throw away all your medical medium tools
and you rely on your zeolite and see how
far you go like people did in the past
throw away your your celery juice throw
away your leafy greens throw away throw
away all your berries because that guess
what berries were anti-in Health it was
all anti-berries
keto movements all the movements it
wouldn't even allow a piece of fruit
that's all medical medium that brought
in all the fruit in the last 25 years so
take away all the medical medium tools
get rid of all your fruit and your
berries and your Apples because it was
illegal to eat a red apple on any diet
program in the last 25 years so get rid
of all the medical medium the kale
which medical mean brought in get rid of
the lemon water and medical medium
brought in get rid of all medical medium
tools
and just focus on your zeolite and see
how far that goes it won't go anywhere
seal lights are not safe now because
they're cross-contaminated so let's talk
about it right now I'm in the brain
saver book okay and someone who has a
problem with their intestinal tract it's
a whole other story but let's just go
into it in recent years
inedible varieties of zeolites have been
Unearthed and manufactured in the same
places as edible zeolites causing
cross-contamination so here's what's
happening now
all the zeolites have
cross-contamination of inedible zeolites
and I have to be the messenger for this
which is really important because when
you're sick
you don't have time and room to play
neither edible nor inedible zeolites
cross the blood-brain barrier if you
hear that you guys neither edible or
inedible zeolites cross the blood-brain
barrier
nor do they enter the brain
cross-contaminated zeolites varieties
stay in the intestinal tract and
irritate the lining causing dehydration
and vagus nerve sensitivities
there has never been any proof in our
history that has shown a zeolite
crossing the blood-brain barrier nor
entering the bloodstream
that's how demented the whole thing is
too
edible zeolites even if you have every
insurance that they're not
cross-contaminated should not be taken
in high dosages or long term because
even edible zeolite varieties build up
inside the gut creating imbalances in
dehydration so if you're you're somebody
dealing with a neurological problem and
this is what I saw anyone taking too
much zeolite with neurological problems
it would dehydrate them and bring down
their electrolytes robbing electrolytes
large dosages of zeolites can create a
trace mineral imbalance because zeolites
don't have a discernment between what's
toxic heavy metals and what's a precious
Trace mineral so get this one
when you take zeolites
the zeolite doesn't have any discernment
between a heavy metal or your precious
trace minerals
your precious trace minerals
that's a really big important one right
there all on its own
large dosages of zeolite can create
Trace mineral imbalances because zeoids
don't have this discernment which is
really important zeolites do not travel
into the bloodstream binding onto toxic
heavy metals their zeolites are not a
reliable binder
zeolites only stay in the intestinal
tract just like clay as zeolite sit
inside the intestinal tract they can
interrupt trace minerals from leaving
the intestinal tract and entering the
liver anyway I'm just covering zeolites
a little bit more because it breaks my
heart
to see people who are sick and
struggling
get the scale tipped the wrong way all
the time
it's like who has that time and energy
when you're sick and chronically ill the
brain saver books
change all that in the medical medium
books have changed all that
the thing is is if nobody ever healed
or got improvements or got out of their
wheelchairs for medical medium books and
information if nobody ever heals all
these years
and I and I didn't have all this
information from above to put into these
books and put out there no one ever
healed then I I should probably shut up
I should just shut up and not and not
and just be like okay what zeolites
enter the brain sure let me go get that
see like product
I should just be quiet
but the truth is medical meaning of
information has saved so many people
and has protected so many people
and and so it's all about looking out
for that person so they don't
accidentally do something like this okay
let's talk about diatomaceous earth
particles which I didn't cover
so I'm going to go into diatomaceous
earth particles in here so I'm in
problematic and damaging
supplements so let's go there now
so many people have tried diatomaceous
earth so it's not that I'm just picking
on zeolite let's let's hit diatomaceous
earth for a minute
agitates and clings to the intestinal
Linings and does not leave the
intestinal tract quickly so if somebody
eats diatomaceous earth
it clings to the intestinal tract but
doesn't leave
that's a big problem for people that are
struggling abrasive
to sensitive nerves
throughout the stomach so check this out
so there's a question what about fulvic
zeolite I used it with chlorella and my
tests were good
get rid of all medical medium tools
all of them and just go ahead and use
fall vacant zeolite
and then after a year or whatever
let me know how your tests are
that you'll be going back on all the
medical medium tools chlorella is a
problem all on its own so let's talk
about Chlorella
and we'll do that after diatomaceous
earth I actually will go straight to
chlorella now
and it's in the book so you can learn
right here it's in the books
leafy greens weren't in the health
movement that's a medical medium tool I
know that irritates some people because
they remember leafy greens in the last
five years or six years or something or
they heard it from somebody else but you
weren't even allowed to eat a leafy
green go back 25 years ago it was
iceberg lettuce in the health movement
it was romaine lettuce in the health
movement and so basically you know leafy
greens is a tool on its own you get rid
of your leafy greens you get rid of all
the other things in your berries and
your apples get rid of the lemon lemon
waters this is how it works with all
Trends not enough considerations being
given to who can have fun dabbling with
the trend and who doesn't have room to
play medical medium
information there here we go let's talk
about Chlorella
chlorella does not bind on to toxic
heavy metals properly this is important
to know
chlorella spreads toxic heavy metals
into adjacent tissue so if you're using
Chlorella
you're spreading metal potentially into
tissue
that's next to the metal
chlorella doesn't does not have the
ability to remove toxic heavy metals
from the body so when you actually
consume chlorelli you can't remove a
toxic heavy metal out of the body
it's not going to happen
chlorella is not antibacterial and it's
not antiviral either
one of the big reasons why so many
people are sick rather it often contains
bad bacteria resulting in foodborne or
illness so here's here's the story of
Chlorella
probably one of the most negligent
supplements that have been in the trendy
world for a long time it's caused
tremendous pain and suffering for a lot
of people
because it often carries a bacteria
within it
that bacteria doesn't get
found
and it gets out in the market and people
get very very sick I've seen people
vomiting for days and days hospitalized
because of Chlorella I've seen people
suffer great great disadvantages and
their healing process
because of Chlorella
I've seen people gut sick on and off for
years because of chlorella because of
the foodborne pathogens
bacteria that's in chlorella over the
years I would not even put that stuff on
my
table top
I just don't trust it to that degree
okay so the so back to that what's wrong
with diatomaceous earth particles
everyone
let's go we're in the brain saver
protocols
you guys are on sale right now
amazon.com I want you to know and these
are two incredible books released at
once getting both of them is critical
not just one of them
they're big textbooks filled with
information they're packed if you just
got on here
and they're 40 off let's talk about
diatomaceous earth particles here
agitates and clings to the intestinal
Linings and does not leave the
intestinal tract quickly if you have
vagus nerve issues
if you have anything going on with
anxiety any kind of things like that
anything happening with your intestinal
tract Crohn's colitis IBS not even that
just digestive trouble
diatomaceous earth particles is the
worst thing you can put in your system
another terrible mistake that's been
thrown on the chronically ill the
chronically ill
they're the guinea pigs
okay
and they're the ones that have to like
feed the system out there the corrupt
system of supplements and the corrupt
system of whatever out there
Pharmaceuticals whatever they have to
feed the system
the chronicle are always taken advantage
of
and the medical medium books you'll find
consistency not contradict no
contradictions you won't find
contradictions in the work I've done
going all the way back for decades
and so there's a reason lots of reasons
for that and the problem is like when
you take an example like diatomaceous
earth particles I can't tell you how
many people their immune systems tanked
because of Diatomaceous Earth
it drops the immune system
abrasive to sensitive nerves
throughout the stomach duodenum
intestinal tract triggering symptoms of
sensitive vagus nerves people do all
these Health Trends and supplements and
they do okay sometimes if they aren't
really sick if they're not that sick yet
but these trendy supplements are doing
their damage and it shows up later no
one understands what's really happening
and they pay the price later
okay so diatomaceous earth particles
cause problems throughout the stomach
duodenum and intestinal tract triggering
symptoms of sensitive vagus nerves so
here you are you're somebody with a
sensitive vagus nerve issue
and you're trying to heal
you got all kinds of ticks and spasms
you got tightness in the chest you got a
little bit of panic every now and then
you got anxiety you're struggling
emotionally you're struggling physically
you have some vertigo you have some
dizziness maybe you have something else
going on and you're dealing with a vagus
nerve sensitivity maybe digestive
trouble and problems because of your
vagus nerves and someone says oh here's
an ad right here take a look at this
diatomaceous earth or you should be on
diatomaceous earth and you take it
here's another thing about Diatomaceous
Earth get this one
also be cautious not to inhale
diatomaceous earth not to inhale it
I've seen terrible things happen to
people when they inhale diatomaceous
earth
due to its ability to lower the immune
system
when caught in the lungs
if you breathe in diatomaceous earth
particles
they get caught in the lungs and they
lower the immune system of the person so
that means if you have something like
Epstein-Barr if you have something like
streptococcus if you have Simplex herpes
one if you have a cold sores if you have
anything going on in your life
if you have cancer if you're breathing
in diatomaceous earth particles
and they get in your lungs it lowers
your immune system
you guys got to check out the brain
saver books they just came out now
they're miracles for the chronically ill
because they they protect
I can say this because it's true also be
cautious not to inhale diatomaceous
earth due to its ability to lower the
immune system when caught in the lungs
so you guys there's a list of 55 brain
betrayer supplements in these books with
in-depth information on why it's a good
idea to stay away from these supplements
I'm letting you know
and by the way it's an honor to be here
again you guys are going to look forward
to actually connecting with you guys and
showing you the books it's really it's
just been so wonderful
white blood cells whoa gotta hear this
about Diatomaceous Earths I forgot about
this I forgot about this
this is mind-blowing right here
white blood cells see diatomaceous earth
particles
as foreign Invaders and have to consume
them how do you like that they have to
consume them
I got a white blood cell right here
okay
so let's just pretend this sponge
is a diatomaceous earth particle okay
so you breathe in the diatomaceous earth
particles or you swallow them
and your white blood cells have to come
along
and they have to devour
the diatomaceous earth particle
and that's how it's lowering the immune
system
so when white blood cells see a
diatomaceous earth particle as a foreign
Invader it has to consume them which can
lead to an over burdened lymphatic
immune system so an overburdict
lymphatic immune system you know lymph
nodes so your lymphatic system through
your body so that's your white blood
count right there so it's it's devouring
those Earth particles
allowing pathogens such as viruses to
take advantage and create a flare-up on
a chronic condition so let's go back to
this a chronic flare-up so say someone
is trying to get into Health they're
getting rid of processed foods they've
found their way a little bit through the
health world
maybe they pick up celery juice
medical medium tool or something
but at the same time
they're also doing things like they got
stuff in here like they're like well
let's see I got my diatomaceous earth
particles here I got my zeolites over
here I got my full McDonald's what else
do I have and I got a whole bunch of
stuff and here they are they're trying
to move themselves forward
they're trying to get themselves better
and then there's this battle happening
that they don't know this war happening
the good things they're doing get
outweighed by the bad there's a constant
tug and pull so if you're not if you're
not that sick you won't notice so the
point goes like this if you're not a
sick person like really sick and really
chronically sick you're not going to
notice while you do all the bad things
but if you're really sick you'll notice
it or it'll just tank you and you don't
won't know what it was
that's important to know
and here's another thing too It's tricky
because you'll see somebody out there
say oh diatomaceous earth particles
helped me
and then it destroys a whole bunch of
lives
like diatomaceous earth particles it
helped me
and then you got 56 people that hear
that they go take it and now they're on
mattress Island and they're stuck on
mattress Island but who cares
who cares right
like who cares that's how it works it
doesn't matter if like 50 people
ended up like taking the wrong zeolite
or too much zeolite or whatever it is or
you got you got 50 people doing
diatomaceous earth particles and
chlorella you got people doing charcoal
who cares if they get too sick and
they're just battling chronic illness
for the next 20 years in their life or
they're injured by it who cares and
that's how it works out there
it was my experience my experience was
diatomaceous earth made me feel better
50 people hear that and they go down in
tank
thank you
all right so you know and that's just
the way it works
and it's sad there's a lot of yeah melt
them you said so many pitfalls out there
so true
so
let's go into
mildly problematic supplements I have so
many in here to talk about
and the thing is you guys
when that person tanks down the road and
they get sick or sicker
they took kind of a
bunch of people went down there before
that it's like it's like this it's
when someone is actually
like saying hey I diatomaceous earth
particles worked with me chlorella
worked with me no one knows about that
person that took the chlorella or their
child to chlorella and now they're so
sick for years because they got the
foodborne particles in their Chlorella
or nobody knows about the diatomaceous
earth particles that gave them such a
flare that they were now bedridden for
two years
nobody knows about that person who took
the charcoal and their intestinal lining
suffocated and they couldn't get
nutrients and they became so nutrient
deficient that they lost their lives
practically down the road but no one
cares or sees any of that they don't see
that history or anything but that one
sales rep or that one person's like our
charcoal's the greatest take it
internally it gets out metals and all
this crap they say
and
you know oh it does get Metals well
didn't get charcoal wasn't used for
getting Metals out years ago when it
came out on the scene until medical
medium talked about metals and then all
of a sudden the sales reps are like oh
yeah no it takes care of metals too
the scams are just abundant
so I'm in a section here of mildly
problematic supplements if you guys just
got here the brand saver books isn't
just this this is one tiny little micro
section out of the brain saver books I
want you to know this is just a tiny bit
okay mildly mildly problematic
supplements
all right
let's go into
herbal combination powders I'd like to
go into that a little bit
so herbal combination powders herbal
combinations that are low quality often
containing toxic heavy metals and what
people don't realize is powders in the
health Movement Like herbal powder
combinations really loaded with Metals
but really off the chart
often containing toxic heavy metals
often these herbal combination powders
contain non-verbal additives such as
Clays and probiotics that can either
irritate the gastrointestinal Linings or
just not be beneficial to the brain and
body so herbal combination powders that
have a little bit of this in it a little
bit of that and a little bit of
Bentonite a little bit of another clay
and a little bit of probiotic
they're really irritants
but they don't offer anything
the herbs that are chosen are not for
specific conditions and symptoms so
remember that every time there's an
herbal powder out there
it's never chosen as a blend for really
any specific symptoms or conditions or
really why or what it's thrown together
as a business
a business kind of
direction or intention always thrown
together of like what's easiest to find
the cheapest to find throw it all
together
and just put it out there
the herbs chosen are hit and miss so the
herbs in these herbal powders that
people actually consume and mix and
consume out there are all hit and miss
including in the capsules
it's not in enough quantity it was
someone stole this and poached this from
medical medium recently I couldn't
believe it like some I guess doctor dude
or somebody
um on social media
the only place you heard this one line
was from mm info published first talked
about first and here it is
the in these supplements they take only
specs and they put all the specs
together and then they lump it all into
one supplement but you have like 20 30
40 things in there
so even if there is an herb that can be
helpful for a condition so you've read
your supplement you read your your
herbal powders combination powders and
you say oh that herb is said to be
pretty good
it's not in enough quantity because it's
merely a smidgen of the herb mixed with
a dozen or more other herbs or additives
that was literally poached from Doctor
without citing it back to me
some dude on social media the poaching's
real it's Non-Stop
a supplement brand took it
and it had some health Guru doctor guy
on a podcast talking about it but they
took that so it's amazing how supplement
Brands out there will take medical meme
information and use it against the
people when they're the ones doing
exactly what the medical meme
information is saying is bad
and then they put it on an ad
all right let's find another one too see
pine needle tea I'm not gonna read that
one on here
not going to read about pine needle t on
here cold like spring I hear pieces of
your info everywhere is it driving you
crazy yet May right because it's pretty
much yeah
I hear pieces of your info everywhere
now they even say mystery weight gain
can be connected to the liver they never
knew the liver had anything to do with
weight gain published first by medical
medium and now used on ads too by
doctors and they don't even have a study
to be published around it they only have
the medical medium books but they
they're all doing it illegally by the
way mate it's all illegal it's just that
I have a choice to make do I go after
everybody out there that's doing the
most hideous things like that corrupted
things
or do which will take all my time or do
I still do I spend all my time putting
out answers and free information day in
and day out I can choose one or the
other you can't do both so I choose
making sure I keep on giving you guys
information whenever you hear stagnant
sluggish overburdened liver it's medical
medium terms and now doctors are using
it it's everywhere stagnant overburdened
whoever knew a stagnant overburden what
liver all mm terms
yeah
so
I mean my mildly problematic supplements
right here here's neem oil neem oil is a
big one right how many people took neem
oil how about that one so I got it in
here
it's I don't have a lot written on it
it's just avoid taking neem oil
internally it's too astringent
it's too astringent if you're even
sensitive you're going to be struggling
from that one
its chemical compounds are aggressive on
the stomach and intestinal lining so in
neem oil
it's a stringent chemical compounds are
not fit for being internal for the human
body and a lot of people get in trouble
because of that when they take their
neem oil but they don't even know it and
then they'll blame something else like
the Apple they ate and someone will say
well you're not allowed to eat fruit
you're fruit sensitive meanwhile it's
the neem oil that's just ruining their
gut
because of this neem is also an irritant
to the vagus nerve so here's what I
don't like about neem oil and I never
did you'll hear me never talk about or
promote neem oil neem oil is a massive
irritant to the vagus nerves
Vegas nerves were tightness of the
throat kinds of the chest anxiety Panic
all these different issues but it's a
big big irritant to the vagus nerves and
now you'll see out there because of mm
info again you'll see a lot of people
they're now Vegas they're experts even
though there's no science behind any of
it so where do they get their info that
they're talking about
um
did they talk to Spirit of compassion
too because I'm confused about that one
so all these decades I put vagus nerve
information out there and the Vegas
nurse react to real astringent
properties like the kind that aren't
like I'm not talking about like food
like like some blueberries or something
like that I'm not talking about
um a grape okay and even grapes grapes
some grapes can be so tart that they're
too intense right if you eat too many of
them but the point is is that the vagus
nerves are hypersensitive to astringent
astringent properties
and neem oil lights up the Vegas nerves
not to heal it it doesn't light up the
vagus nerves to heal the vagus nerves
neem oil creates a situation where it
increases anxiety it increases ticks and
spasms it increases digestive system
discomfort and all that and how many of
you guys have tried the whole neem oil
cold white spring many are wondering
about CBD oil I talk about it in the
brain saver book
I just don't want I just don't want
um
the pitchforks and the Torches and the
uh shovels and the bats with nails on
the end of them I just don't want to get
too bad of a beating or slashing today
so I'm not going to talk about the CBD
oil but it's in the books it's in the
book
so the vagus nerve is definitely
okay I will say this about CBD oil
you'll notice something it's not CBD oil
anymore
it's CBD oil mixed with all this medical
medium stuff why is that happening
uh for years uh you know like
everybody's had CBD oil to be a miracle
I'm not judging anybody
but then because CBD oil wasn't fixing
everybody they started putting like the
lemon balm and all the medical medium
tools in the CBD oil so now the CBD oils
have all the medical medium stuff in it
how weird is that why
because I haven't been promoting CBD oil
all these years because when
I had somebody come to me and they'd be
like well the CB oil is not working
uh I would have to say well we got to
get you on lemon balm a friend or
whatever or a loved one you have to get
you out of the lemon bottle oh my God
the lemon balm's working and so but the
point is is I get it a lot of you guys
love your CBD oil I'm not harping on
that I'm just saying that it's changing
in about a couple of years you're not
going to be able to get straight CBD oil
it's going to be CBD CBD oil with all
the medical medium tools mixed in it
you're not going to have straight CBD
oil in a few years I'm letting you know
it's all going to have lemon balm in it
and all the other stuff that's in the
brain saver books in the other books
original medical medium information it's
really Advanced about the vagus nerves
too what I'm talking about so just so
you know in these books
I go into advanced information about the
vagus nerves stuff I've never talked
about before are in here
original mm info is Vegas nerve
inflammation nobody knew Vegas nerves
got inflamed nobody knew you got mystery
nausea from vagus nerves that's mm info
nobody knew you vomited because of a
vagus nerve inflammation nobody knew you
had anxiety because of your
gastroparesis
they didn't know why someone had
um so Matt neem talked about the vagus
nerves creating all these different
symptoms and now once again they poached
them
it gets old man gets old but you just do
one thing you know one thing in time so
CBD I talk about it in here
so get ready
let's talk a little bit about CBD for a
second here most chronic illnesses are
caused by pathogens and toxins
this is in the CBD section
most chronic illnesses are caused by
pathogens and toxins
science and research
and doctors did not know this
it's originally mm info and published
going all the way back
chronic illnesses are caused by
pathogens and toxins
CBD is neither antiviral
nor detoxifying so I just want to say
this
not trying to cause any riffs you guys I
don't want you to dislike me more than
you might already or whatever
CBD oil
is not antiviral nor is it detoxifying
but get this
everybody's taking CBD oil
because they're sick
it's not something you want you go out
and take when you're not sick
when you don't have a single symptom or
a problem you just don't rush
to somebody and grab some CBD oil if
you're not sick with any symptoms you're
getting your CBD oil because you have a
symptom of some kind that's why you're
going to buy your CBD oil hey try CBD
oil worked for me okay good I'll go get
it I have anxiety I got this I got that
that's why you're taking CBD oil right
you have a symptom
but but your symptoms are caused by
pathogens and toxins unless it's some
serious emotional struggle which still
could have toxins like Metals involved
so your symptoms are caused by pathogens
and toxins get ready
CBD oil is neither antiviral
anti-pathogen
or detoxifying of the toxins and poisons
I'm giving you just a little bit of a
precursor
and we're going to talk about the brain
shot therapy cleanse challenge that's
coming up too
so
so get get ready for this one
in the past CBD oil was commonly sold as
a treatment on its own
you can only buy CBD oil
that's CBD oil
okay
the lack of results with CBD oil
Jackie V says I took it for anxiety I
stopped using it after I found MN that's
amazing that's incredible a lot of
people have have gone through that
get this the lack of results with CBD
then spurred on a change with its usage
by the way you guys bait and switch
the chronically ill
Get Fooled by the bait and switch
the system out there are all think
tanking about you guys anyone who's sick
with a chronic symptom condition because
you guys are the money makers for the
system
right because when you get sick you got
to pay for everything right you're sick
you got to look for answers whatever so
the system is set up like this
and if you say well you're selling a
book well I'm not selling a course
for five thousand dollars and I'm not
withholding the information and
wait until they come out in the library
go ask your library when you get a
chance I'm trying to get it in some
libraries and get it take it out for
free don't pay for it go to the library
but the system set up
because the system's rigged
and here's how it works the bait and
switch is happening with CBD oil right
now as we speak
the lack of results from CBD oil spurred
on a change with its usage
right now CBD oil is changing
the strategy for CBD has evolved
and CBD is now being sold mixed with
other medicinals such as herbs vitamins
and nutrients
that offer better results medical medium
info
hasea says lemon balm has changed my
life I used to have panic attacks every
single night I used to use CBD as well
never did anything lemon balm heals yay
well that's what I heard my whole life
that CBD CBD never did anything
I never recommended it once to anyone
CBD oil I still won't till today because
there's better things out there
I'm not anti-cbd if someone wants to
partake in it it's like that's up to
them that's their life you do what you
want
but get ready they have to add things
that actually work in CBD now it's a
bait and switch like lemon balm they're
taking lemon balm which really does help
people in their problems and they're
adding it to the CBD oil right now
it's a bait and switch once again but
they're taking lemon balm because of
medical medium
also CBD oil is really expensive
the strategy for CBD has evolved and CBD
is now being sold mixed in with other
medicinals such as herbs vitamins and
nutrients that offer better results for
individuals living with various symptoms
this can be misleading for CBD users
because CBD gets the spotlight so here's
how it works here's how they really
screw everybody over
they sell you expensive CBD
it doesn't work they found that out for
years now so now they're looking to
Medical medium
like like lemon balm exploded in the
world because of medical medium books
and information exploded right now
and if you eat best lemon balm ever is
is on my directory by the way
medicalme.com so lemon balm exploded
and now
they're like okay well we're seeing that
medical median people are getting better
with lemon balm let's take lemon balm
and mix it with their CBD
but they don't ever come clean and say
we're gonna make an announcement and
we're sorry that we totally screwed you
over for the last two generations
and we were really just confused and
didn't know it didn't work
so now we have to put things in that are
medical mediums and actually put it in
make it work nobody comes clean and Fest
us up
this can be misleading for CBD users
because CBD gets the spotlight
and then they'll say once you start
feeling better by having your lemon balm
in your CBD oil they'll say oh it was
the CBD
while it's the other constituents in the
combinations that are providing more
benefits you guys check this out I'm
letting you know now next week
brain shot therapy challenge
so the medical medium brain shot therapy
challenge is next week
you don't have to pay
some kind of like paywall it's not a
course
it's not some type of program that you
have to pay thousands of dollars for
it's free I'm doing it next week
medicalmedium.com sign up to my
newsletter so you know what day when
what how where
and brain shot therapy is in the books
so let's get into it right now
so I'm in the medical medium protocols
book both of them are equally important
if you're going to get the books get
both they're discounted right now on
amazon.com us
okay so here we are I'm taking us right
to the beginning here I'm going to run
through these it's going to be fun
because which in this medical medium
brain shot therapy challenge which ones
is SOC going to choose
that's exciting
which ones
are going to be chosen for it so medical
medium brain shot therapy I'm in the
protocols book let me just read a little
bit about if you're brand new to all of
this
medical mean and brain shot therapy
offers instant relief while you're
working to fix problems on a deeper
level with your brain and nervous system
now instant relief I have to give you
forewarning it's going to catch you off
guard because people don't get instant
relief in the alternative movement of
healing instant relief this is going to
hit you
I'm just so you're not caught off guard
I'm trying to give you that little
disclaimer like just be prepared I feel
like I have to do that
your brain and body have a quick
response to medicinals delivered in
liquid form what I call a shot designed
to be highly absorbable in the mouth
these brain shots there's a lot of words
at once these brain shots valuable
healing components can reach the brain
fast so here's how it works
these brain shots reach the brain quick
these specially formulated shots have
the ability to reset and rewire the
brain and that's why they're so powerful
because they have that ability to reset
and rewire the brain to shock it out of
patterns while at the same time reducing
triggers reducing triggers
that's what's incredible about it so
let's give you the list of shots here
and kind of showing you what they kind
of look like right
that's the toxic fragrances shot right
there
that's a negative energy exposure shot
right there has a bunch of information
about it about when best to use it all
of that so
let's see Trisha Rose says correction
you have a huge autism Community
following because you've healed and
recovered kids on the Spectrum with your
cleanses incredible
incredible
and I'm honored I'm honored
because here's the thing I'm showing you
guys the shots but I want to just say
this I'm just a little heart to heart
for a second
it
the medical medium Community when you're
like invested into your healing process
into the information you don't have it
easy because
aw here has the kick me sign on my back
so what happens is that people out there
the trolls the haters and naysators
Sayers are just going to be always like
mad and angry that you're healing
they're going to be mad and angry that
you've recovered they're going to be
jealous they're going to be
all of the above Because You're Breaking
All the Rules like truly Breaking All
the Rules if you ever have ever seen any
other health communities
people say they're they they get a
little better sometimes but then they
just disappear and they're far worse
than they ever were and you'll notice
that the rate of people getting better
at all the other communities doesn't
happen they just all stay sick
completely like all of them stay sick
for the most part
and they stay all sick and they stay all
Angry like if you go into some of the
different communities out there
and some of the different socials out
there with the different kind of things
like the like Hashimoto's or autoimmune
and some of the different socials out
there they're all angry they're so angry
they're sick they're angry they're
scammed
it's just they're just done wrong it's
just terrible and
people fight
they fight you on thinking you know they
fight you on thinking you can just
manage your conditions and symptoms but
you actually can heal they're just all
about managing out there and you
actually can heal
so they'll just like fight you on things
and tools to manage your condition
medical meme info is done about managing
it's about moving forward and getting
better so we're in the brain shots right
here instead of just cutting through
some of them that's the mold exposure
shot
SOC is going to pick out a bunch of
shots
for next week
so we're going to be doing the brain
shot
therapy challenge
next week
it's gonna be fun
I'm really excited about this make sure
you sign up to my email that's the mold
exposure shot that's the EMF and 5G
exposure shot love that shot I love that
shot
just love it
radiation exposure shot every time I
travel
every time I travel boom I'm doing that
shot boom boom boom every time I travel
every time I fly and I'm glowing in the
dark after I fly
it doesn't go away when you fly you got
the radiation and you still from 10
years ago it doesn't go away maybe if
you're doing like active medical medium
tools to get it to go away but if you
don't do that radiation just sits in you
you glow in the dark until you die down
the road it's like you just glow in the
dark every plane flight you just get
more radiation and more rain then they
make you go through those scanners
go with the pat down
I would never go through the scanner
Janet Rose I agree with most of what you
said about CBD oils on the market I've
tried one from the from the flower in an
alcohol base for delivery via drops on
the tongue and it works fine expensive
though you're getting the alcohol hit
it's sorry
sorry
you're just getting the alcohol hit if I
walked around with grain alcohol and
dropped it on my tongue all day long I
feel pretty damn fine too
that's how sad that is
it's like you know
it's like
I got this new CBD oil right here and
I'm just gonna take a little bit of a
hit now
the grain alcohol getting into my system
is just making me feel better
that was nice it was a nice alcohol hit
so once again you were doing like
without realizing it I'm not I'm not
being harsher look it's not about making
fun or anything I want you to know this
like thank you for being here I'm sorry
if I'm irritating for real like if I'm
irritating or snarky or sarcastic I'm
really I apologize and I want you to
know that like it's a true apology from
my heart
um but what happens is there's alcohol
in that CBD that one
and it's potent alcohol it's grain
alcohol you're gonna get the grain
alcohol hit and you're gonna think the
CBD is working for you but it's the
grain alcohol that you're getting a hit
from it's calming you down but that's
not good because that's a different
thing that's something you don't want
calming you down because it's been tried
for hundreds of years and hundreds of
years that's what men and women have
done is drank themselves to death to
calm themselves down and but you're not
drinking yourself to death I get it
you're just using a little bit of grain
alcohol from your CBD but that's what's
giving you the hit please know how it
works so you understand
foreign
you gotta read the books about it
alcohol is a whole other trick
where am I
here we are oh I am here
Jen coffin says CBD did nothing for me
toxic heavy metal exposure shot if you
think you were exposed by
Pharmaceuticals or anything else
pesticide herbicide and fungicide
exposure well why how would you have a
fungicide exposure please tell me
someone
let me read to see
this shot is an excellent tool when you
inhale an unfamiliar or strange odor
uh-huh
you're exposed to recently delivered
packages believe it or not recently
delivered packages
you gotta kind of like keep your nose
away from them a little bit because the
outside is usually contaminated with a
lot of stuff until you get inside
a neighbor sprays or treats their lawn
with insecticide or chemical fertilizer
treatment so if the neighbors spraying
something which they always do or
chemical treatments that are applied
around an apartment building okay
now I talk about okay here's another one
right
you're exposed to a town or city
treatment that's occurring on the side
of the street because the town and the
cities are always spraying the most
dangerous stuff they want to kill their
people apparently not purposely entirely
but there's a bigger industry that does
want to kill people with all these
chemicals above them
you spot somebody with a tank on their
back and a hose in their hand
and they're spraying for weeds
that's another one right there this is
when you use the shot
I mean no one's trying to kill anybody
I'm just saying that the industries that
create a lot of these chemicals
definitely
make people sick that's what I was
saying
you see a small to medium-sized truck
with a large tank on the back and
business signs on the side of that truck
that say Lawn Care bug control or
anything similar driving through your
neighborhood meaning that chances are
they just recently sprayed a bunch of
different houses in your neighborhood
and the wind's blowing it and you're
exposed so then you get out your
pesticide herbicide fungicide exposure
shot check this out
you're driving behind a truck that has a
tank on the back with mysterious liquid
leaking out of the tank I can't tell you
how many times I've seen that over and
over again and SOC told me when I was
driving or in the car driving someone's
driving that SSC told me that that tank
is leaking deadly pesticides and it was
just coming right out while you're
driving behind it
you spend time sitting in a park or
visiting Parks or you spend time on a
golf course right
wish I had time to play golf
insecticide treatments are sprayed in
classrooms classrooms they spray the
crap out of classrooms I know teachers
say well that's not true aw some say it
is true because they know a lot of
teachers will say aw you know you're
pushing it too far there's no pesticide
sprays in my classroom uh there is over
the summer time
because I know I have a family member
who works in maintenance at one of the
schools and tells me that here's how it
works that when summertime comes and all
the teachers are gone students are out
and it's summertime they gas bomb with
pesticides insecticides the entire
schools and the classrooms
heavily
insecticide treatments are sprayed in
classrooms from preschools preschool
to elementary schools to universities
and in dorm rooms especially common at
the beginning of the school year so
before the kids come in they spray for
all the roaches and spray for all the
bed bugs and they spray the dorm rooms
so when the kids come in they get so
much toxic heavy metal exposure from
pesticides inside of them and other
things too like the pesticide exposure
and funguside exposure it's crazy let's
go to another one here you live within
25 miles of a conventional fruit or
vegetable farm during its growing season
so you could be living near a tomato
Farm or something it's conventional and
they'll spray
you know that's that's a problem on its
own
okay
hope I'm not boring you guys
all right see what else we got
pharmaceutical exposure
sea Trails exposure if you see a whole
bunch of them out there lately sea
trails
can't say the word
obsessive thoughts shifter that's one on
its own if you got the excessive
thoughts and all that stuff I mean this
is just packed with information so
you guys
um check it out be there next week if
you can listen out from my emails on my
email list
gonna be doing
the medical medium brain shot challenge
I'll see you again later today I'm
coming back on later on
I'm excited Trisha Marie says yes I've
had so many antibiotics
so there's so many Tools in here and
these are just some
and Jackie B says yes sea Trails
everywhere you gotta say see
and not use the whole word on here
okay
you guys over 300 symptoms conditions if
you don't have the brain saver books
they're on sale right now get get get
some for family members and friends and
holidays and presents
I have purchased a lot of these books
for presents for the holidays for family
and friends
so that's what I did
May says yeah see crap
um anxiety eating disorder chapter okay
let's go into that there's an anxiety
chapter eating disorder chapter OCD
chapter bipolar chapter but that's just
some of what's in here
the eating disorder chapter is insane it
is so comprehensive and so packed with
information
you guys I don't even know what to say
I'm just really excited
Susan Susan says I left you a five-star
review on your books they're so
wonderful Susan thank you I really
appreciate it I was reading the reviews
so I'm pretty sure I read yours then
amazing you guys also look out for
imposters that say they're Anthony
William or Anthony Williams or whatever
and they're trying to get a consultation
with you and then they either take your
money or they have a consultation and
they hurt your feelings or trigger you
or God knows what they do because
they're crazy so look out for those
crazy imposters
Lorena says I'm reading the anxiety
chapter now
I don't do consultations they're
imposters
Cantu consultations I'm too busy making
sure I can get as much information to
you guys in free material 24 7.
there's over 300 symptoms and conditions
check them out also if you can leave a
review
Amazon.com or wherever you got the books
or whatever please leave a review and
how do you clean the books right you can
take a hand towel this is a sponge
sponge is probably not going to work
unless it's just damp but you take a
hand towel with a little bit of dish
soap on it and you just clean it off you
don't make it too wet because you don't
want to soak your book and you clean off
the grease from the conveyor belts that
come from Amazon
so here's how it works the books are
minted they're pristine and clean and
fresh and new and then they go to the
warehouse at Amazon and then Amazon has
conveyor belts that that there's grease
on because they have to grease the
conveyor belts and then the worker God
bless their soul takes the medical
medium book and they take it and they
throw it on the conveyor belt rightfully
so it's their job and the book is just
rolling down the conveyor belts and then
by the time it gets into the box it's
got a grease much another smudge another
smudge some dirt here and even some food
on here for some you know person eating
or whatever it is or drinking something
and then ask for a new book if you don't
like how it came ask Amazon for a new
book or just clean it and the reason why
I'm I'm saying this is because people
then get mad at me and think I gave them
a used book which is think that's think
that's not true no they've done it and
they've given me one stars because of it
people also ask because I saw that
before which book to do
so which book
which book
ready I'm gonna land on the book to get
I'm definitely gonna land right on the
book that you have to get okay I want
you to get the book that it lands on get
ready which book is it gonna be first
which But first you get both books is
what you get first that's where we land
because it's one book one gigantic book
that the publisher could not publish and
the printer could not print it's too big
it's over 1200 Pages they're over 600
Pages a piece and it's very heavy and
the problem is the publisher said we
can't sell a 12 pound book we can't sell
a 10 pound whatever book No One's Gonna
Be able to do anything so they had to
split it they're two books equally as
important tell everybody because
someone's gonna be like I got the brain
saver book and it's like no you didn't
you got the brain saver half book
Uma Kelly says I was mind blown how
Alloys affect our dreams oh my God
that's an incredible every line did you
see static brain chapter the acid brain
chapter the alloy brain chapter the
emotional brain chapter the meditations
in the other book here the recipes the
burnt out and deficient brain chapter
the eating disorder chapter which is
insane
there's even like a whole section on all
kinds of different conditions symptoms
with our brain
it is packed I don't think I slept last
night I'm too excited I was trying to
allow myself to get three hours of sleep
and I didn't sleep probably those three
hours because I'm working so hard and I
was so excited I was so excited oh yeah
podcast oh oh my God
if you guys are even still hanging in
there during this hour-long talk
I'm coming out with a podcast episode
next week
it's a meditation from the books
get ready for it
because it will change your life some of
you have already just experienced it in
the brain saver challenge you were just
in
it's a light infusion meditation
get ready when you experience that light
infusion meditation on my podcast
you're gonna feel it
tell everybody
if you can
listen to this week's episode 2 that I
just released
please listen to that when you get a
chance I just released it it was talking
about how our brain works
taking a hike
it was really powerful
yep Jenny Maxes keep going
I wish I could
fornella says I love your podcast I'm
honored truly
anyway get ready for the brain shot
therapy challenge next week
so that's coming
all right you guys The Germ Theory aw
why cell walls are made of fats
why are you told they're made of fats
that's the other problem
I saw that on the YouTube
yeah
all right you guys
I love you dear