hardcovers are here brain saver books
right there you guys and for the first
time I'm gonna be reading a section out
of these books coming this Sunday so
sign up to the newsletter because it's
going to be for the newsletter crowd and
I'm going to crack into these books
we're going to read a little I'm blown
away right here both these books were
really one big one right here but the
publisher could not
on the last two weeks this could not
happen so the each book is bigger than
any medical medium book right and uh
yeah these are really big anyway but
they're packed
and check out the link right there so
you can sign up the newsletter so you
don't miss out