If you happen to be by an air, grab a
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie. After all these years, all the
people it has helped, all the lives it
has changed. The smoothie is literally
changing lives. I had dealt with anxiety
and depression my whole life. Problems
with my eyes, so I getting blind. I
didn't realize how unhappy I was. It's
not just a smoothie in a bottle. This
isn't a protein smoothie. This isn't a
whatever smoothie. Those are great. It's
a functional smoothie. I think that it's
a really well balanced recipe.
Personally, it's five ingredients. Wild
blueberries, Atlantic Dolls, spirulina,
cilantro, barley grass cheese powder.
It's by the way really delicious. It's
just delicious. And I get other people
on it because it's so good. So when mom
used to make, I used to bring the whole
blender to work and then I'll blend it
at work. But when it's at Arowan, all
you have to do is just go there and pick
it up. Fresh pressed juice section, easy
to grab. A lot of people live by the
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie. They make it every single
morning. I've done it every morning for
over six years. Every morning. I do it
fresh every day. I drink about 32 ounces
of it. I drink the heavy metal detox
smoothie every day. Get the things
inside your body that your body's
craving. I felt lighter. Like I
literally felt lighter. I felt like I
had more energy. My skin was clearer. My
skin gets better. I'm shining from
inside and I feel it. my vision. It's
It's much better. I feel happier and I
felt more calm and less stressed out.
Lighter, brighter, mentally clear. I
think that that's a magic potion. This
is functional. This has a real purpose,
a purpose that moves people forward.
This is the Medical Medium Heavy Metal
Detox Smoothie at Arowan.
[Music]