This is the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie right here at Arowan. But
the HMDS has made it into the store's
fresh pressed juice section. Easy to
grab each day. What's incredible about
it is just the story behind this heavy
metal detox after all these years. All
the people it has helped, all the lives
it has changed. I think the heavy metal
detox is just a key part of my healing
journey. I do the heavy metal detox
every single day. It's my breakfast. I
need it. I enjoy having it every day.
It's just energizing. Oh, I feel
invincible. I was skeptical at first,
but um I started in with the heavy metal
morning cleanse and boy, right away I
noticed improvement in my digestion. I
just felt like I had more energy. My
digestive system improved. For me,
especially for my anxiety,
it has been a godsend. It's funny cuz I
actually resisted the heavy metal detox
smoothie for a while because I was like,
who puts seaweed and cilantro in a
smoothie? And then finally one day I was
like, "Okay, it's time." And I did it
and it was so delicious that I did it
every day for months and I was like,
"This is amazing. Why did I ever resist
it?" Your brain starts to breathe again
and you you come out of that little
bubble. I've noticed many improvements.
It's how to pinpoint them. It boils down
to just general life improvements in
every regard as well as spiritually, not
just for the body. I feel really
invincible. I feel empowered. I'm a tool
by which I can help other people. It's
just all in one little container and I
can just sip it or chug it or whatever
I'm in the mood for. I will literally
tell anybody who will listen.
I'm so excited and honored. I can't even
believe it. I'm holding this bottle in
my hand right now. This is the Medical
Medium HMDS right here. So, you can come
on into any of their stores. It's on the
shelf. Incredible, you guys. Incredible.