that's all you hear RSV that's all you
hear everybody's coughing everybody's
got mucus
everybody's got fevers that's what's
going on out there okay what's
incredible is the medical medium brain
saver books are packed with information
for keeping the immune system strong
which is amazing because what I'm doing
guess what I'm doing right now I'm doing
pathogen exposure shot every day that's
what I'm doing that's what I'm doing
I don't have a cough I don't have a cold
I'm just kidding around but I'm doing
the pathogen exposure shot I want to
read about it for a second too but I'm
also doing the time T shock therapy
which is a medical medium shock therapy
you guys the time P1 gonna do that one
two with you guys
I'm also taking the vimorgy propolis
vimergy micro C I'm taking the vimorgy
zinc I'm doing that too by the way these
three work together incredible tell a
friend whatever tell your doctor tell
your practitioner whatever but this
these three work together amazingly
right that's the beveraging stuff I'll
talk about that later because I want to
do maybe some vitamin C shock therapy so
we'll take a look
so you guys
let's just get going on a little bit let
me read this for a second so I'm going
to bring saver protocols by the way I'm
just going to tell you and I can't
believe the sale is still there and I
think it's still there I think so right
now 50 off brain saver protocols
amazon.com us right now it's 22
that's sick I mean that's insane 22
dollars
600 page book twenty two dollars
and it's got the protocols it's got
supplementation it's got the shock
Therapies in it it's got the brain shot
Therapies in it it's got so much in
there it's unbelievable and it's 22
freaking dollars I kind of even get it I
don't even get it it's really incredible
so okay pathogen exposure shot kind of
read a little bit it says viruses
bacteria
and viral bacterial byproduct right it's
mm info
shock can be useful
if you feel you've been around others
who could be contagious due to covet
the flu
mono
anything right flu RSV or whatever it is
I mean this is really incredible I like
those things really Corey
check this out right
you're concerned about having shared
bodily fluids with another person
through shared glasses like hey can I
have a sip of that sure boom wait a
minute you got you came down with the
flu you came out with RSV oh crap uh
that was a couple days ago that I was
sipping off your glass at the party
during the holidays but I'm not sick yet
and then three days later it's like sore
throat what's going on I feel kind of
funny I feel kind of a little congestion
here am I getting sick am I getting sick
or something
so I love the pathogen exposure shot for
this think about that so you're
concerned about having sheared bodily
fluids with another person through
shared glasses plates anything during
the holidays right or how about if
you're with a bunch of people during the
holidays and one person there's coughing
they're like oh it's allergies don't
worry it's allergies
and they're blowing their nose it's like
dude that's not allergies you got RSV
you got the flu you got a cold you got
something that's what you have right
someone's asking what the book's called
it's called brain saver medical medium
brand saver brain saver protocols
cleanses right and recipes but check
this out 22. amazon.com us
and make sure you get brain saver which
is
almost 50 off so this one's like 28
which is insane too so incredible both
these books are amazing so you guys if
you just came on here
I'm making the pathogen exposure shot
and reading straight out of the
protocols book right which is an
Incredible Book You'll see a bunch of
things here see this time I'm going to
make some medical medium time t-shock
therapy there it is I got the time see I
got the Rosemary I got the asparagus and
other stuff too right I also have the
Bemidji products right the propolis I
got the vitamin C which is the micro C
and I got the zinc these work really
good together an incredible thing that
I'm doing for myself I'm gonna make the
uh
a vitamin C shock therapy you guys know
I work with Bemidji I'll talk about that
later too about why their stuff is
mind-blowing like for real like when I
think about it like
like
how is it possible you can have like
such clean pure things in the world and
then you think other stuff is clean and
pure but it's not and I'll talk about
like that for a second too all right
pathogen exposure shot like I said
because I see a bunch of people coming
on right now you feel you've been around
others who've been contagious they have
something they're saying it's their
allergies oh my god I've heard that for
years listen I don't know if you've
heard that for years and maybe you're
somebody that says it you got the
allergies like allergies every three
months but yet you're catching a flu
every three months I know people out
there I've seen it for years they're
catching the flu every two to three
months but they think it's allergies
then they got the bronchitis then they
got the coughing then they're coughing
up the green phlegm then they're blowing
out the green phlegm right and they
think it's allergies that's not
allergies
okay that's not what allergies is
Stephen sin says since he says this book
is a lifesaver seven months seven months
of long covet finally going away thanks
to following the medical medium
information for the last two months
can't thank you enough Anthony Stephen
thank you for being here incredible I'm
glad you liked the books
so proud of you too because you're you
see the incredible Advance information
and you're using it I'm proud of you I
really am okay
so during the holidays when people get
together there's always somebody that's
coughing or sneezing and then forget it
five days later
everybody who is there most everybody
comes down with something that's usually
how it works okay so what I like about
the pathogen exposure shot I'm taking it
when I'm around people during the
holidays right so that's what I'm doing
I'm making that shot and I'm taking it
that's the whole point I'm also doing
I'm also doing the micro C I'm also
doing the propolis pure I'm also doing
the zinc right so I'm doing that too
which is incredible all on its own but
but I I just love having these tools it
just makes you feel good when these
tools are here
okay
so you're concerned about having shared
bodily fluids through public restrooms
during the holidays
you're in a public restroom how many
people went into that public restroom
that have RSV they have the flu they
have a cold that have something right
going around how many people are using
those toilets and so forth and
everything else at public restrooms
um you're concerned about shared bodily
fluids with sexual activity or something
and you're concerned or something and
I've always talked to doctors about that
and said get them get them doing stuff
for their immune system so they don't
have to be so scared and stuff you
believe you might have been exposed to
foodborne pathogens and you can you're
concerned about getting food poisoning
and that's what I love about the
pathogen exposure shot it has all these
options right here built into it which
is incredible right there right
but right now
really
everybody's coughing everybody's sick
everybody's got the bronchitis everybody
has the sniffles the fevers and all that
and it's just rampant right now and
there's a cold and flu protocol even for
children in this book right here so
there's protocols for cold and flu
it's in the book so we're doing a few
things we're gonna do pathogen exposure
shot let's get started on it let's get
working
all right let's make the shot so I'll
just grab if you got a juicer you just
make the shot with the juicer that's
the best way to do it I'm gonna put this
here I'm gonna put this here
so all right
I got my celery I got everything here
that I need so I'm going to start out
with six sprigs of thyme so let me get
some sprigs of thyme right here
so
I love thyme we're gonna do time T shock
therapy which I'm excited about let me
get some nice sprigs I can I can choose
the sprigs I want because I have a big
pile of time right here
from the garden which is really cool
right Garden time so I can choose all
these nice little sprigs here
amazing
all right so that's the first ingredient
I have right there sprigs of Rosemary is
the next one so let me throw this down
the chute
I'm doing the pathogen exposure shot
every day right now
I'm also doing the propolis every day I
don't have the flu
I don't have a cold
but I'm still doing
the zinc and the propolis right I'm
still doing that
so I put a little time in there let me
put a little bit of Rosemary now too two
sprigs of fresh Rosemary
news flash
forewarning
this shot has got a bite to it
okay I put I put roughly around six
sprigs of thyme in there there we go
that that pretty much gives us about six
one small quote a clove of garlic right
here boom so here's the thing with this
if you use a really big clove of garlic
in the pathogen exposure shot
it's gonna be really bitey
okay so that's a medium clove so small
to medium is what's really
directed for that too raw
medium asparagus
stocks
and you go
there you go
to Rob brussels sprouts
I'm looking for a Brussels sprout is
what I'm looking for and I have them I'm
also gonna find a knife really quick
so I'm going to cut them in half if you
guys just got on here we're dealing with
cold and flu tools is what we're working
with right here
mm info we're doing the pathogen
exposure shot we're also going to be
doing time T shock therapy
we're also going to be doing
a little bit of zinc some propolis
propolis
I don't know what
what
the world
is missing out when they don't have
propolis is so important all right
two stalks of celery now
got one
I gave this a really thorough rinse you
guys
so if you're like wait a minute he
didn't wash it what is he doing
there you go
so it's all washed
picking up messages
all right
there we go
so I have the pathogen exposure shot
right here I'm very excited about this
actually
there we go
so I'm doing this every single day right
now
worried about any exposures around
anybody it's an important one to do so
I'm going to take a shot now
just keep in mind it's got a little bit
of a bite to it
but we're talking about antibacterial
we're talking about antiviral
talking about anti-pathogen that's what
this is right here so when you have this
going through the bloodstream now
medical medium information talks about
time staying longer in the bloodstream
so that's really a powerful aspect of
time but when the time is mixed with
these ingredients it UPS the game so
this is information from above
this isn't concocted by me saying hey I
feel like putting some time in Rosemary
together and a little bit asparagus and
everything else let me just make a drink
it might be supportive for my immune
system this was explicit directions
details that came from above for this
pathogen exposure shot
it just feels really good too going down
I feel like I'm arming my immune system
what I like to do is I like to focus on
that too and focus on my immune cells
eating this up because this is fuel for
the for your immune system right and
then I'm thinking about phytochemical
compounds that are in the time and
everything else
in this shot in this phytochemical
compounds are injuring and damaging not
you but the pathogen
so what's in this pathogen exposure shot
or weaponized phytochemical compounds
through nature that are going towards
those bugs so
boom
feels so good it really does so you guys
I don't know if you're doing the
pathogen exposure shot but
you might want to consider it if you
haven't done it
all right so
do you know anybody who said anybody
who's got the flu anybody who's coughing
it's running through a lot of households
right now it's all I hear about out
there it's all is that what you're
hearing about too
all right so let's keep it going here's
the question right can you talk about
how we are taught that the more
exposures we have the stronger immune
system gets and why that this is false
it's very false
okay so what you'll hear out there
is you'll hear
germs make your make you stronger
and that's what you'll hear out there
right but that's information that comes
from
authorities in health
that don't know why people are sick to
begin with so you have to keep that in
mind most important part of that
question
the most important part of the answer to
that question is this
that's information coming from the
health world that doesn't know why
someone has fibro MS
any kind of neurological condition or
symptom neurological fatigue tingles
numbness burning aches and pains skin
problems all the different things that
people are suffering with migraines that
are mysterious all the mysterious
symptoms trigeminal neuralgia burning
skin burning mouth burning tongue
oh that's a mystery to medical research
and science alternative medical research
and science too
all of that is a mystery unless they
have the books right unless they have
brain saver brain saving protocols so
your question already
kind of falls into the place where okay
so whoever's saying that in the health
world that that what you get exposed to
makes you stronger
how are we even able to trust that
when they don't even know why someone's
in a wheelchair with MS someone doesn't
feel good and they got fibro lupus
someone has pots someone has decided to
know me so how come how come they don't
know any answers to anything about why
people are sick they don't know why
people have aches and pains and tingles
and numbness and vertigo and dizziness
and balance issues so
it's like oh I'm Authority in health
and what doesn't kill you makes you
stronger
I'm an authority in health and what what
what doesn't kill you makes you stronger
the more you get exposed to
the healthier and stronger you are okay
well then tell me why everybody's sick
with chronic illness we don't know why
everybody's sick we have no idea is it
the genes is it everybody's genes think
about how ridiculous it is
so the health authorities in Alternative
Health or whatever conventional Health
that are saying that you get stronger
from getting exposed when they don't
even know why anyone is sick why moms
can't get out of bed why people are
struggling with severe crippling anxiety
and depression
if you don't know why people go into
fitsamania and they're living with
bipolar syndrome and they're not and
they're suffering and struggling or they
can't even walk they're so inflamed
throughout their whole body they have no
idea why but they have the answer that
more exposure helps you
think about that
okay
our immune system is already Under Siege
so if we get more problems with their
immune system more challenges with their
immune system it can tank it
so it's not it doesn't make you stronger
it can finally finish somebody off
that's how it works our bone marrow has
to go into overdrive to produce immune
cells to try to protect you so exposing
you more is good for your bone marrow to
produce all those immune cells explosion
someone with lupus is already so exposed
already their immune system is
struggling left and right every day so
okay let's expose that person to more
stuff because some health authority
alternatively or conventionally says
that it's good for it it's good for your
immune system when they don't know why
you have Lupus okay so if I was somebody
then check this out because if you like
it give me a second if I had lupus
and I've been to all the different
doctors functional medicine doctors
don't know why people have Lupus they
don't unless they use mm info we know
that
but if no one if I had lupus and I went
to 10 Specialists and they didn't know
why I had lupus and then they told me
but more exposure is good for you how do
you even trust or believe that when they
don't even know why I have lupus
if more exposures
help someone then how come when an
elderly person whose immune system is
lowered
because they're elderly they're already
struggling how come they're worried
about
exposing them you get ammonia you die as
an elderly person
an older person is more the morbidity
rate
it's more exposure is the scarier part
about older people that's why people
when they're all in the nursing homes
during the whole covid blow up
lost their lives
did it make them stronger they were
already sensitive they're already
bedridden some of them they were already
struggling how is it possible on any
level that more exposure of anything is
good for someone who's already sick and
struggling
so if I have Lupus if I had fibro and I
asked my doctor why do I have fibro and
lupus and they said well we don't really
know studies suggest what we don't know
anything it could be autoimmune okay so
is it better that I should get lots of
exposures doctor and the doctor could be
like oh yes but exposures are really
good I'm a functional medicine MD and
I'm telling you that
that thought more can really make you
stronger and it's good for you I'd be
like you're insane
you're telling me you don't know why I'm
sick and then all of a sudden you're
saying it's good for me to get exposures
okay let me keep on drinking out of
everybody's glass because that will make
me stronger oh what herpes simplex one
oh so you're you have a herpes simplex
one breakout okay let me have your share
your glass too oh okay great oh there's
herpes on the edge of the glass it's
gonna make me stronger so let me just do
it it's going to make me more stronger
having this so oh oh oh a year later and
now I'm breaking out all my lips with
herpes simplex one it sure as hell
didn't make me stronger how about
chlamydia
how about chlamydia how about that one
let me just get exposed and catch
Chlamydia somewhere because it's gonna
make me stronger meanwhile the UTIs are
giving me the worst UTI on the planet
and then another UTI and then I have to
take all these antibiotics and another
UTI let me go let me go and jump into
some like crazy stuff and pick up a
whole bunch of chlamydia
and then okay uh doctor give me a bunch
of antibiotics because that chlamydia is
sure making me stronger
next thing you know you're getting UTI
after UTI after UTI after UTI and now
you're getting streptococcus all the
time immune system's breaking down oh it
makes you stronger though
foreign
it doesn't make you stronger
you don't want more exposure you want
less exposure but what's happening out
there is the reason why I'm talking
about this a little more I was gonna do
cold and flu tips but the reason why I'm
talking about this a little bit is
because oh my God I have seen so many
like idiot professionals and I'm not
trying to judge them or anything but
there's so many professionals now health
coaches uh naturopaths chiropractors
Do's functional medicine doctors mvs
right saying more exposures better for
you now are you freaking kidding me
you don't even know why anybody's sick
you think more exposure is a good thing
for them oh let me just get exposed to
five more simplexes how about that and
maybe herpes simplex too too get getting
exposure to that is real great or how
about the flu I don't want the flu
and I'm not judging anybody you guys I'm
just saying that more exposure weakens
the immune system there's enough
problems already with people suffering
and struggling right now you guys have
to know this like people are sick with
neurological problems for real their
vagus nerves are all chewed up they get
all kinds of problems their immune
systems are damaged and weakened they
got lupus they got fibro they got ra
they got neurological fatigue they got
mecfs right they have everything plus
all the symptoms going on
people have a hundred symptoms out there
they have 50 symptoms out there so let's
expose them to more does that make any
sense to you let's expose them to more
it's absurd it's insane it's ridic it's
completely ridiculous
all right we got to keep on moving we
gotta keep on moving forward we got we
gotta show to deal with a lot of good
cool tips and and stuff and all that
okay because I want to help you guys but
listen thank you for that question
because it's been meaning to talk about
it I wanted to do a podcast episode
about it eventually oh my God the
podcast episode list is like this and
I'm trying to chip away at it to release
some podcast episodes but
but what happens is it weakens us and
and it exposures weaken us so that bugs
that we have inside of us rise up and
that's mm info by the way a bunch of
doctors put put some kind of article
about that like oh yeah you have these
dormant viruses that are coming up
when you get the flu Oh I talked about
that years ago
I published it years ago what am I
saying too so what happens is that some
of you guys that have been with medical
medium information for now years know
I've talked about that how many times
and we get broken down and then our
immune systems get broken down and then
bugs rise up right they rise up and so
exposures knock are already weakened
immune system down and then the bugs
rise up and so what happens is when you
hear a doctor practitioner and listen do
what your doctor says and tells you to
do do what your doctor recommends in all
of that right I want you to do whatever
your actors are recommending you your
doctor what you feel good about whatever
with your what you're doing your doctor
but when I hear health professionals say
exposure is good it'll build up your
immune system that germs are your immune
system
I'm like you don't know anything I'm
sorry you might have a degree but that
degree is no better than a piece of
cheese sitting on a countertop because
honestly
if you don't know if you don't know why
people are sick and you're telling
people they need germs and germs are
their immune system
I'm sorry but take that degree and throw
it in the trash can just take it off the
wall and put it in the trash can like
that
all right
but do what your doctor says though if
you know whatever feels good whatever
your doctor recommends okay you guys I
am Gonna Keep On Moving on let's go into
it so I'm talking about zinc for a
little bit
so I take zinc all the time now you guys
know if you know the medical medium info
if you know what I've talked about
quality matters
the quality is not all the same the
reason why I actually endorsed Bemidji
and I said you know what you guys need
you guys need my official endorsement
official endorsement I need this stuff
to stay around for people I don't want
it to disappear I need it for myself I
take this stuff for myself and my family
I don't want it going anywhere so I
fully endorse them right
but why would I even do that why would I
fully endorse them
because
they actually don't hide anything in
their products because the law requires
that you can hide a certain percentage
in supplements so supplement companies
out there they're allowed to actually
hide a certain percentage of undisclosed
stuff inside their products femergy said
no I'm not we're not doing it and I'm
like okay then that's the best it gets
I'm sorry that's the best it gets that's
incredible so that's the first thing the
other thing qualities here is they
choose the highest quality stuff there
is they don't choose the lower quality
stuff like all the companies do for
Price Point advantage to try to make
more money on a product right so if you
want to start a supplement company
tomorrow
and you want to do it you'll go chances
are you'll get talked in to the lowest
quality of the quality stuff so you have
a bigger price point Advantage so you
can make more money remember she says no
we won't do that we want the highest we
can find and I've never seen that before
the other thing third party third party
independently test it boom
and the other thing no alcohol no citric
acid no soy no gluten no
maltodextrin no natural flavors no
artificial flavors the titanium dioxide
no caffeine no alcohol ever they know
better no natural flavors they know
better no citric acid they know better I
don't even know what to say about that
besides that's mind-blowing to me
and supplement companies have their own
free will and they change what they're
doing they're like oh this this time
we're gonna change it up you know we
sold that line of product let's redesign
you know no one even knows what they do
they don't disclose things like the
hidden little percentage in there that
they're illegal that they're legally
allowed to not disclose remember she
says no anyway
that's why I endorse them
and I'll endorse them 100 times over
I I don't even know what to say okay so
you guys we're doing cold and flu tips
the whole bit today I just made the
exposure shot if you just got here if
you you should watch this from the
beginning too if you just rolled in
because we're doing some good stuff and
what I love about these three is they
work good together
so to ask your doctor what's right for
you right you know because you might be
doing something entirely different
whatever it is so to use the stuff ask
your doc what you feel is right what
they feel but for immune system helping
this is what I do for myself I need my
immune system strong it has to be Rock
Solid I am up against levels of insanity
stress I'm up against all kinds of stuff
I'm battling stuff out there in the
world like I got all kinds of I don't
have time to be down I can't just say
I'm gonna be sick for three weeks with
the flu and cough in my guts out and I'm
just gonna have to be just I'm gonna
have to check out no more podcast
episodes no more free information no
more reconstructing the website to give
people more free stuff it all shuts down
and no more writing the next book with
Spirit of compassion I can't have down
time like I can't
like I gotta be on and I see people
they're like they're out there like boom
boom this person's got this boom coffin
sneezing this person's got this and I'm
like oh
immune system man
but I can't I can't go down and then be
in bed for a week and then slow recovery
where you're like you're you're slow as
a snail recovery it's hell you know and
you're like oh I just had the flu beat
the crap out of me I've been in bed for
a week I can't really function I could
just barely just get into my kitchen and
take care of myself I'm dizzy I don't
feel good I had a fever for three days I
can't do that
I gotta be like and I'm not gonna take
no no like health professional coach's
advice and say that germs will make me
stronger and I should get exposure well
that's the last thing I want I don't
want to get exposure right now unless I
have no choice and I'm with family or
I'm with friends and they all they're
sneezing or something or somebody's
coughing and then then it's like ooh
yeah I'm doing this I'm doing this you
know so anyway this is the liquid zinc
sulfate and you'll notice out there
that
you'll see it out there influencers be
like yeah it's the liquid zinc sulfate
and I'm like oh yeah but you don't know
the right one the one that you can trust
that isn't gonna have anything hidden in
there anyway
Erica says without beverages supplements
I wouldn't have been able to heal the
way I have I completely understand
without memory supplements I couldn't
keep myself as strong as I've been to to
fight the battles for the chronically
ill to be a voice for The Chronic Leo to
help The Chronic Leo like I do Monica
says memory amazing products
but I I share the same same feeling
without a doubt you know so all that
matters it's like everything like all
these little details matter if we're
trying to take care of ourselves Tara
Appleman good to see you remember she
has the highest Integrity they really do
it doesn't exist out there otherwise I
haven't seen it I'm not just saying that
I know this as a fact
I really do the progress I like it's
consistently contains over 50 percent of
the polyphenols which is incredible so
that's one of the differences right
there that like they can hang their hat
on
like the propolis literally contains
over 50 of active polytheanols they can
hang their hat on that with that because
that's incredible
and it it matters which is amazing right
and I don't personally like taking Dead
quercetin Like Me personally I don't
like taking course within that's a dead
course at him right the polytheon of
course did I like knowing it's active in
like the propolis right here and I got
to show you the stuff it's like it's
like just
Liquid Gold insane
so why am I even doing this today
because all I see out there is everybody
coughing and sneezing and coughing and
sneezing and that's why and it's just
like
and I and I feel bad it's like I feel
bad for people that are getting knocked
down by the flu and they're sick for two
weeks a week three weeks six months
because it just it it lowered their
immune system then the Ebbs and
everything came up and then they're
having it really hard like that breaks
my heart
because I know that so many people have
it so hard already
you know so I just feel bad that's
that's the bottom line check this out
though
I want to show you how incredible this
is
The Taste the difference is unreal with
the propolis
from very G it doesn't have alcohol in
it even non-alcohol provolift is out
there I can't trust because they have
some form of alcohol they have some type
of poly you know uh some different type
of ethanol or alcohol of some kind and
you can you that's what it tastes like
this doesn't
there's a big difference right here you
don't have this this Bernie alcohol
thing that goes down feels like it burns
a hole in the stomach feels like it
burns a hole in your liver you don't get
that like and that's incredible right
the stuff is just like liquid gold check
this out right here I mean this is just
insane look look at this right
look at that right there
kellen's saying that is
the the color is just unmatched too it's
not just this brown crab you can see how
amazing it is so let me just get another
dropper full right here okay right you
can see how amazing it is look at this
is that is that sick or what
I mean when you and the Purity over 50
percent
of active polyphenols over 50 percent of
active polyphenols right no alcohol
I mean boom can you see that at the
bottom look at that right there I don't
know if you guys might not be able to
see this but it's on another feed right
here we got the camera footage so let me
just bring it up to here like this is
just
unbelievable this gold
golden goodness right here this propolis
golden goodness
it's just it's like
and it's
when people say I want to do something
good in the world right I want to offer
the best blankets for people where you
know organic and the you know the cotton
in the blanket is so nice it makes me
feel good to know I'm offering that out
there in this world right or someone's
like and look at even coffee heads right
like coffee caffeine fiends right
they'll be like I want to start a coffee
you know company and I want to use the
best fair trade the Best Organic roasted
we roast our beans in a way no one's
ever roasted ever it's like you know
this coffee right here it's the we do a
roasting process that no one's ever seen
before right people want to make a
difference in the world the caffeine
thing though I'm of a little kind of
like I'm imagining where I don't think
that makes a difference in the world it
gets everybody addicted whatever but the
point is
is that sure if you're going to be on
caffeine anyway be on the best one right
if you're going to be on it and no one
can tell you different then be on the
best one but either way you know how
there's people out there the guy run
into and people reach out to me and
they're like aw I want to I want to make
the best baby strollers ever were the
wheels on the baby strollers
they don't do this thing because there's
bearings so you see moms of their baby
strollers right well there's wheels on
those strollers obviously and moms like
they like to push their babies along
with jog or or you know exercise
and so companies out there be like I
want to do something good in the world I
want to make sure the wheels on the baby
strollers give the baby the best ride
ever so the baby's not bouncing around
as the mom's pushing the stroller
there's so many people out there that
just that just they want to do good
things right
well
I want the best propolis that's ever
been out there anywhere here so when
someone actually needs that best
propolis that doesn't exist out there in
the world and vimergy can create it I
want that and that feels good to me
to me that feels good to me you know
it's it's those kinds of things I want
the best zinc there ever was and I want
the best vitamin C there ever was and
these are the things right there that
matter to me you know it's like you know
because everybody wants to do something
good you know
anyway so all right look
so I just put the the propolis in here
so I showed you it's got the golden
color and everything so now I'm going to
do the zinc right here too and I can put
the zinc
I'm gonna put a little water in this
shot with another shot that I have so I
got some water in here with the propolis
okay and I'm going to put some zinc in
there too
so
things with zinc is when you when you
hear the word zinc think immune system
right so I talk to people and it's like
you hear the word zinc you you think of
Yoon system
that's what I tell people they're like
zinc what do you do with zinc on my
immune system like whoa and you just you
you have that the reason why I'm saying
that is because every time your mind
your consciousness
sees z-i-n-c
okay every time your Consciousness sees
that z-i-n-c that's zinc
okay something starts Computing in here
right in the neurons in your brain
so I like to do this
because zinc is good for the immune
system that means your immune cells what
I do is I Envision my immune cells
gobbling up all that zinc
and then every time I even see zinc I
want my immune cells already getting
hungry
to receive it
I want that correlation I want that
connection right there and you guys know
I do the continuity thing right I'll do
a whole thing on that eventually too I
got other stuff I just got to talk about
so much
but I want that register right there
because you get your immune cells hungry
right
it's like you're getting hungry for your
meal so say you're eating three meals a
day two meals a day whatever you do
maybe you're in your mid fast and you're
doing one meal a day whatever it is your
juices your gastric juices they start to
get hungry if someone says food you're
just like yeah I'm hungry someone says
food your mouth starts drooling someone
shows you a slice of pizza and your
mouth is starting to drool right
someone says zinc
and you really put that connection and
you're taking the highest quality zinc I
feel my opinion is the highest quality
zinc there is and you're taking that
high quality zinc your immune cells are
gobbling up and eating that high quality
zinc think about that
so all someone has to do is say zinc or
you see zinc and your immune cells they
want to do good things your immune cells
want you gobble up that zinc your immune
cells want to do good things right
so I like making that connection
because that matters that matters to me
Spirit of compassion always told me that
when you're giving yourself something
like a high quality zinc
and your immune cells are using that
high quality zinc
to battle
exposures
what happens is there's this connection
that actually is made between your
central nervous system your brain your
neurons to your immune cells your immune
system your bones everything in your
body and so it's like whoa I'm getting
my zinc out I see the label I see
z-i-n-c I'm taking it out right here I
just put it in here and already my
immune system is saying give me that
zinc
because I'm ready for it
it's really cool
it's actually really powerful Cool's not
the word for it it's actually really
really powerful all right
so I just made myself a propolis shot
and a sync shot I put them both together
that's what I like to do ask your doctor
what's fine you know what you can do
but that's what I do
okay I'm gonna put my brain away over
here you guys
all right so I want to talk about a
couple of things I want to talk about
medical medium
shock Therapies
I'm very proud of what the medical meme
shock therapies have done for people
like if you've heard some of the stories
or read some of the stories and I've
watched it all through the years anybody
that I've helped personally that when
you see what the medical medium shock
therapies have done it's a very very
special special thing
foreign
saver books
quick news flash news flash real quick
22.50 off amazon.com us incredible right
so we're in the medical medium
shock therapies right here so can I show
you guys really quick here
let me get back to it
these books are tanks they're like tanks
they're just like really heavy they're
really big books
and they could have been split up in 12
12 separate books between the both of
them because that's really what's in
here overall when you when you actually
do the math
medical medium shock therapies right
here
so this is an important medical medium
tool that I've seen help a lot of people
ask your doctor about it bring the book
to your doctor ask them
such an incredible amazing set of tools
right here can I read a little bit if
you guys are okay with that
so I'm in chapter three medical medium
shock therapies you'll find that some of
the supplement protocols
in this chapter right are optional and
these are all optional that's the whole
point you can take your time and look at
it and find out what you want to do you
can customize your life into the
information here there's no
one-size-fits all with medical medium
that's what's incredible this isn't an
eat better book and it's just about
getting rid of processed foods and and
eating grass-fed beef cows that's not
what this is or eating you know organic
vegan and that's it this is literally
comprehensive detailed information of
illness
symptoms conditions
Therapies
all kinds of things in here
all right medical mediums zinc shock
therapy that's one of the shock
therapies medical medium vitamin C shock
therapy that's another one right there
medical medium lemon balm therapy
lemon balms for nerves
right helps to it's a comedy for the
nerves beverages has an incredible lemon
balm
all right medical medium Goldenseal
shock therapy
medical medium time T shock therapy
that's what we're going to make it a
little bit let's just essentially you
know what let me just start to get a
little bit of a time tea ready here so
I'm going to put like 12 Sprigs
so what I'm doing is there we go I'm I'm
treating this like three you know what I
mean so you can do that so once once
break like there is by itself right look
at this beautiful timer here you guys
so I'm doing is I'm doing right around
that's good right around 12 right so
here's the thing every three waking
hours
you do
the medical medium time shock t therapy
every three waking hours
so I really really love this one let's
go into a little bit about like first of
all let's get some hot water in here
so I'm going to do that
you guys don't mind it just had a
disappear for a second so I am making
this nice tea
we can get a good
there we go
okay
you guys relaxing we got some tea
all right you can put a little honey in
there I'm gonna put a little lemon in
here I got this nice lemon right here
I'm gonna cut this lemon open
I'm gonna put a little bit of that
[Music]
now I am going to put a little bit of
honey in there if you guys don't mind
all right
grab a little spoon
medical medium time T shock therapy
you know what's crazy
because time existed before medical
medium
talked about
to time shock therapy
it discounts it as if it's not a tool or
something right it's like oh no no time
existed before him
but did medical medium time shock
therapy T exist before
because I want to know
truth is it didn't
the reason why I say this it's an
incredible powerful tool don't get
thrown off when someone says oh he knows
nothing about time T time has been
around for years the Romans used time
so he doesn't he's not bringing anything
new right uh really
because this is an incredible therapy
right here so this shock therapy is
amazing every three waking hours
right
12 Sprigs
no one knew how to use time like this
for cold and flu cold flu RSV
nobody knew how to use time like this so
it's okay I get it you know that time
exists you see it in the grocery store
so then you discredit medical medium
really quick and say oh yeah I saw a
post from an influencer out there that
said medical medium doesn't know
anything because he didn't invent for
invent fruits and vegetables and herbs
and stuff
meanwhile
sort of compassion and a messaging the
information has invented or created
incredible combinations and tools and
information
that is unique and original
it doesn't matter if time has been
growing in Italy for 2000 years
it doesn't mean they used
the time T shock therapy for cold and
fluent to what we're dealing with now
and it's how you're applying them and
for what if that's all unique and so
this is an incredible tool is what I'm
saying and I'm talking about this right
now because I noticed that some
influencers they're trying to they're
trying to be like oh no
he's got all this original information
so but how do I live with myself now
because I want to package up and sell my
own information so wait a minute he
didn't create time
yeah I didn't create celery sticks
but nobody knew about 32 ounces 16
ounces on an empty stomach every morning
how it rebuilds the gastric glands and
all that stuff all that information
about how it kills pathogens everything
else how to use it nobody knew that was
SOC from above I'm telling you this in
case you've been hearing some of the
influencers throw you off path where
you're like oh well he didn't create
celery he didn't grow celery for the
first time on this planet yeah no I
didn't grow celery for the first time in
the planet but nobody knew how to use it
until now and so that's important to
know in case you're like oh time okay
that's been around no this is an
incredible tool
an amazing tool the medical medium time
t-shock therapy every three waking hours
as you're so you're doing this all day
and then you go to sleep and when I tell
like when when a family member I hear
out there reaches out they're like hey
cousin or something like I got the flu
what do I do I'm like time t-shock
therapy and what you do is if you wake
up in the middle of the night to pee if
you wake up then have this sitting by
your bedside side during cold and flu
during your cold and actually sip it and
then go back to sleep
an incredible tool right there all right
so I want to read a little bit about the
medical medium shock therapies if you
guys
have a minute
these are powerful healing tools to
rebuild your immune system by fueling it
with what it needs to fight an infection
supports your brain and body through an
emotional challenge when we go through
an emotional challenge it takes a toll
on our immune system
so that's why I love this right here
it's an incredible tool it takes a toll
on our immune system
helps to support your nervous system
strengthen and heal your digestive
system
so check this out it helps to fortify
and Purge the lymphatic system
the one thing about medical medium
information it's always been Pro
cleaning and helping to heal the
lymphatic system
because it works on fixing something
that's critical if you can't fix this
right here your lymphatic system can
never get better
so mm info is all about restoring the
liver and bringing the liver back if you
don't restore a stagnous luggish liver
which is MM info stagness luggage liver
right you know the Liver Rescue book if
you don't restore it you can't restore
your lymphatic system your lymphatic
system is just The Dumping Ground for
what your liver can't handle anymore so
you have to take care of your liver
medical medium shock Therapies
wait I want to finish this last little
part it's really incredible right
whether you're dealing with a condition
that's occurring for the first time
like acute
or you're experiencing a relapse
medical medium shock Therapies
have a profound record of helping people
overcome Health obstacles
if you guys know where to want to know
where to find them you're looking at
brain saver protocols it's right here
I'm at page 20 right there ask your
doctor what's right for you so bring
this information to your health care
advisor
foreign
practitioner your health whoever's you
know working on your health
medical medium therapy shock therapies
have a profound record of helping people
overcome Health obstacles you guys these
supplement therapies can be useful for
almost anything you're alien with
medical medium shock therapies are
powerful whether you're up against
intense stress or need a shift from a
long-standing chronic illness roller
coaster ride
medical medium shock therapies are
critical to this day and age that's why
Spirit of compassion created these
protocols right there
someone might say oh vitamin C was
invented before you medical medium what
do you know you're just like everybody
else in the vegan world in the keto
world
Spirit of compassion
invented vitamin C shock therapy and how
to do it and why and everything else
that did not exist in the health world
foreign
tries to destroy all that's good we Rise
Against Darkness using light-created
health weapons to regain empowerment
Dr Fawn good to see you yeah like
petroleum has been around for millions
of years but it's only until recently we
can use it more efficiently the sun has
been around for millions of years too
solar panels not so long
spot on
very very spot on
okay as Darkness tries to destroy all
that's good because that's what Darkness
does out there
okay I'm reading just reading some
comments see you guys
nature heal says one of my clients
couldn't get rid of her cough I told her
about time medical medium information
and she went out that day and texted me
that her cough was gone in a day
and that information did not exist in
the health Realm
so I love what people are doing now
they're taking like an aloe leaf
and they're saying medical medium didn't
grow an aloe leaf for the first time on
this planet
it's ancient medicine well then how come
ancient medicine didn't know what to do
with it
how come ancient medicine doesn't know
what to do with time in the way that
Spirit of compassion has brought to us I
don't understand what people want from
me
it's Unique these are protocols that are
unique therapies that are unique and
they're helping people
nobody knew about them all in the last
20 30 years or whatever
whoops
as Darkness tries to destroy all that's
good we Rise Against Darkness using
light-created health weapons to regain
empowerment you put alcohol in this and
you just you just destroyed the light
you put all the tincture companies out
there you want to put alcohol in all
your supplements then you're destroying
the light
you want to put citric acid in all your
supplements you're destroying the light
you want to put natural flavors in all
your supplements you're destroying the
light
the greatest stuff on the planet right
now in my opinion by far is is the
Bemidji line
you don't think I can't create my own
line of supplements
and call it medical medium
I mean people are like it's unbelievable
I just want I want I want people to have
the greatest stuff there is that's out
there
and I just wanna
give free information
and message free information non-stop
wherever I can go to the library get the
book for free
okay as Darkness tries to destroy all
that's good we rise above the darkness
and I say that over and over again
because I'll tell you why because
there's good things that we have at our
fingertips and I see how it works out
there
you know like
you got the best vitamin C where it
doesn't burn a hole in your stomach but
you got all these other vitamin C
companies they're using all that
stratascorbic acid someone uses it and
they get a belly ache and it ruins it
for everybody
as The Changing Times bring additional
stress Upon Us humankind goes into a
deeper Health deficit than during
previous decades I can tell you this
that the health and wellness of people
right now regardless of all the organic
food and all the eat better books and
the technology that we have in
conventional medicine there's more sick
people now today than there ever was 10
years ago more sick people now today
than there ever was 20 years ago I can
definitely say that 100 true
and it's not my truth it's the truth
Lila Collins says unbelievable amount of
stolen information from mm I totally get
his frustration because they're
spreading half truths
they are stealing so much medical medium
info between influencers that don't care
about People's Health between other
health people between all that other
stuff out there and conventional
medicine it's just a poached their
basically rating it
they're taking they're poaching they're
raping the information and that's what
they do and then they mix it up with a
bunch of crap that doesn't work someone
can kind of hang in there because they
get one of the tools by accident it's
not cited back to mm and then they're
kind of hanging in there but it's not
good because it's really really sad
house of Liz says thank you for calling
out the my truth crap
I actually talked about that on telegram
last night so if you guys don't know
about my telegram medical medium on
telegram
um subscribe to it because I do telegram
audio messages on there
sickness now dominates the lives of
billions of people medical medium shock
therapies are here to help level the
playing field that's what it's about
where chemical and the medical
Industries are playing dirty against
humankind so here's what it is MM info
medical medium shock therapies are here
to level the playing field that is why
they were created by SOC that's why
they're down here
that's why they're available
for free
get the information
it's free
so anyway let me make some vitamin C
shock therapy
and some fun sorry about the
tangent about the germs build your build
you and make you stronger they don't we
have to get stronger to beat down and
Crush germs
that's how it works all right let's do
this now you guys
here we are
so I'm going to take this right here
okay I think my time T is coming along
quite well
so good
time T shock therapy right there's more
details in the book about it you can use
dry time if you really had to you can
use fresh thyme it's in the book I was
just reading from so there's more
information in brand saver protocols all
right
so let me get some water in here
some vitamin C shock therapy
okay so what I do is
take two capsules
this is the micro C
so what I recommend this to a family
member or a friend I'm not worried about
their stomach
and that's that's what I do ask your
doctor was right for you but when I
recommend this I'm not worried because
it's so buffered it's not straight
ascorbic acid
so it's not just straight ascorbic acid
that's important to know
and it makes it so it can be used as a
really good tool these Details Matter I
can't even say it enough right
but I get it you know people on the
internet though all you have to do is
shout out one thing and everybody's like
oh
vimergy never uses tablets because they
don't want all those fillers they want
they don't want the glazes they don't
use tablets they don't want titanium
dioxide they don't want colors they
don't want glazes they don't want
fillers and that's the difference so
what you're noticing is you're noticing
a capsule so that's what I took out of
here and that's what I opened right
so I have the two capsules in there now
and then I'm going to put a little bit
of honey in there too
like this
I'm gonna put a little bit more in there
if you want a little bit more you can
put a little bit less in there if you
want to now I'm going to cut an orange
right here
and I'm going to squeeze some orange in
there it's a nice orange too
now two teaspoons is what I did
two teaspoons of raw honey
if you go a little bit over two
teaspoons is what I was trying to say
that's okay if you go a little bit under
that's okay right so I did two teaspoons
of raw honey and then I did Squeeze I
squeezed juice from an orange in here so
you can see
there you go you can use this is a very
big orange I'm squeezing juice from a
half an orange right here there we go
amazing
now I'm going to mix this
you guys don't mind
maybe we can get a close-up on this one
too this is really cool
so we got a little close up there it is
right there
and I shall sip it
amazing
I love it
when I tell family and friends you feel
like you got a bug coming on you feel
like you got something coming on
make sure you got that going on
it's so great okay
so
I love the shock therapies I'm just
looking through them now
what you'll notice in the shock
therapies too
you'll see different ages in here but
bring it to your pediatrician
I'm going to read about time
T shock therapy if you guys don't mind
okay
amazing
yep
okay time contains a phytochemical
compound that is antiviral antibacterial
anti-mold
anti yeast
and anti-unproductive fungus
that stays circulating inside the
bloodstream long after nutrients from
other foods have either been utilized
dissipated or eliminated out of the body
so I want to show you this piece of
information it's critical
that's from above there is no science
research that knows what time does in
the body besides research doesn't know
what other things do in the body
this is information from above that time
stays circulating in the bloodstream
long after nutrients from other foods
have either been utilized or dissipated
that's an incredible piece of
information right there
to teach us in and arm us for our immune
system health
that's not known out there in the world
sure it'll be poached and someone will
talk about it any day now right
and not cite back where it comes from
but it's an important piece of
information
so this is a phytochemical compound
inside the time
[Music]
that actually stays in the bloodstream
fighting crime
time lingers
ready creating a Time released
protective barrier against pathogens
the time has an ability to release a
protective barrier
times phytochemical compounds enter
every organ inside the body not every
phytochemical compound you guys reaches
every organ inside our body
that's the difference right there all on
its own
ready times phytochemical compounds
enter every organ inside the body versus
other herbs that only enter certain
organs in the body so think about this
for a second
time enters every single part of your
body there's no place it doesn't enter
from the skin to every single organ you
name it
other incredible herbs
only reach certain organs depending on
what herbs they are
okay you ready suggested applications
for medical medium time shock therapy
bring this to your doctor please
flu covet colds lung infections
bronchitis pneumonia allergies sinus
congestion coughs sore throats strep
throat scratchy throat ear infections
UTIs bladder infections kidney
infections HPV shingles EBV caused
infections sibo and we would only know
what an EBV caused infection is anyway
for medical medium info because science
didn't know sibo H pylori E coli
streptococcus MRSA cedifly acute jaw
pain tongue pain mouth pain gum pain
remember acute remember what I was
saying acute
acute jaw pain tongue pain mouth pain
gum pain fever body aches cold sores
fever blisters herpes simplex 1 parasite
concerns parasite concerns it isn't
going to be the parasite that's
bothering you it's going to be something
else but the time is going to help that
something else
that's where the whole my truth thing
comes in all the time it's like oh no I
have a parasite well no that's your
truth the truth is you probably got
simplex one hhv6 you probably got
shingles you probably got Epstein-Barr
and something else happening or
streptococcus infection that's the truth
truth but you're a truth which is my
truth you think it's a parasite see how
it works my truth and then the truth
autoimmune flare-ups episodes of
neurological symptoms so
what I love about the time T shock
therapy is you have those options right
there so let's take a look at this it
says medical medium time T shock therapy
directions
this reading from brain saver protocols
just so you know
22. amazon.com us it's they're giving it
away they're giving this book away which
is great
I am grateful for that
okay because it costs more to print it
but I am grateful that the Amazon
actually is giving this book away right
now and the other one
because then I have hope someone will
have it in their hands
make a special Brew of time tea with 12
sprigs of fresh thyme per cup of hot
water like I did you guys if you only
have access to dry time use two
tablespoons of dried herb per cup of hot
water let's steep for at least 15
minutes remove the thyme sprigs or
strain the tea especially if you're
using dried thyme so if you're using dry
thyme strain it is what I would do fresh
thyme you can just literally sip out of
here like this
but if sprig of time might go up your
nostrils so
I think that one just did
okay this question on that one this shot
works so well prevented me from getting
sick a month and a half ago
over there on Instagram
amazing oh the pathogen exposure got you
actually that's incredible
see guys these are the things we're
talking about today I hope you hope you
got some really cool tools and tips cold
and flu tips and everything right well
blueberry dream says my MRI improves in
starting medical medium my lesion almost
disappeared that caused my double vision
last winter and I've heard that a lot
from people who have either optic nerve
lesions
or lesions on the brain different areas
of the brain and improving from certain
medical medium protocols that they've
that they've worked on them so
customizing themselves which is
incredible
so
medical medium Army says why do kids
always get sick it's all over the day
cares and Schools are they putting the
bugs
in people
well anyway so a lot of kids get sick
absolutely it's just an easy place to
spread germs but Office Buildings are
getting just as sick
if you're in an office building
everybody in the office building
eventually gets something if you're in a
classroom
it's just a lot of people together
sneezing and coughing on each other
touching things it's just life it's just
the way it works it doesn't matter if
you're in an office building doesn't
matter if you're in school doesn't
matter if you're in a house with your
whole family eventually we can you know
contract or spread cold flu
well blueberry dream says I have
multiple sclerosis and MRI has gotten
better the doctors told me the best I
could do was keep my Ms at Bay I'm
actually healing yes of course on my
third 369 right now day two so you chose
the 369. here's here's how it works
when you hear somebody say because the
trolls are doing this now also the
some influencers are doing this now too
to try to knock down medical medium
credibility they'll say
I did medical medium to the letter and
did not get better it's like what did
you do you did it to the letter really
like what because that person that that
incredible person right there who's
healing her multiple sclerosis is doing
the 369s
so you know which is incredible and and
probably doing supplementation maybe
maybe part of the medical medium
multiple sclerosis protocol but you it's
like what are you doing
you know people there's a lot of people
that dabble and they only do like a
little they do celery juice once in a
while
and then they're just like I did medical
medium but did you like fly on the wall
you know how many exposures are you
getting how much caffeine are you on how
many you know comfort food meals did you
have which I completely understand I'm
not shaming anybody but so many people
there they don't know about this this
comprehensive guide of information in
here where they can customize their
protocols it's over a thousand protocols
in here it's just it's endless to
customize to get yourself better then
there is a multiple sclerosis protocol
and there is a lot of protocols for
symptoms conditions and diseases the
point is is there's something in here
for everybody to actually help get them
to the point to where they need to go
it's a comprehensive book
and there's so many protocols in here
it's incredible right and then you have
eight volumes of protocols do you have
liver rescues you guys
it's an Incredible Book
if you want to learn about the liver
like really learn about your liver like
what's happening inside your liver that
is an Incredible Book right there to
have so you can learn about what's in
there right
there you go anyway
I don't know what else to do
all the books are packed there's eight
volumes packed with information right
if you think I talked to a ghost
read medical medium
book one revised and expanded so you can
read where I don't talk to a ghost thank
you so get this book when you can right
it's got some Origins about medical
medium
foreign
okay oh Aubry Audrey says be happy with
the people who are following you dot dot
you have thousands and thousands not
everyone is going to listen to you dot
dot dot but when someone is someone new
finding you they get kind of turned off
with the whining about who's not giving
you credit I love what I've learned from
you but when I try to turn others onto
you that's the feedback I get of why
they don't want to follow like I do just
passing that on I appreciate you passing
that on but
but here's the point that I think you're
missing okay
if no one knows where the info comes
from
then how are they going to heal
do you know how many people that are
bedridden that are on mattress Island
they can't even function
and they get lost they'll end up putting
charcoal they'll dump charcoal in their
system or tons of sodium bicarbonate and
now they're in the hospital for the 20th
time
do you know how many people like feel
like there's no hope and they're like
there's no hope to heal and they've been
to 10 neurologists and specialists
I mean do you know how many moms can't
get out of bed and feed their kids and
did you know that when they get derailed
it's another year that their kids are
not going to see a happy mommy
did you know that like when a mom gets
derailed and loses two more years their
child goes from four years old to six
years old and in those two years their
child is between four and six their mom
was freaking miserable because she was
sick and went to every doctor Under the
Sun and then she was tricked by Fork
tongue out there
derailing her because they didn't give
medical medium info credit and cited it
and cited the medical medium information
back
do you know how much Fork tongue out
there is totally tricking people think
about it I've seen moms out there where
their kids were were raised during the
the most vulnerable years between ages
like two and ten years old and it took
eight years for the mom to find medical
medium info and guess why she didn't
find it she was derailed over and over
again told that I was whining about
getting all the credit
I'm such a great guy and are told that
it's all a farce or told that whatever
but I appreciate that you that you know
the information and you follow it and
you listen to it I do Audrey and I
appreciate that but I'm just trying to
let you know that
that and listen I know that you're cute
I know that if we had a conversation you
could say a lot more and you can talk to
me about it and I know that in comments
just know I have respect for the fact
that you can only say so much in a
comments right and I'm reading that
comment so I respect that
right but if you can't listen to the
telegram messages I've been leaving
about this kind of thing I left two last
night
I think the hardest hardest part too is
like when a mom's driving home from the
doctor's office with her teenager their
teenage son
or teenage daughter and the doctor said
that you have autoimmune and the
teenager
is in the car with their phone
and they're looking up and they're
looking up autoimmune right so they got
their phone and they're looking up
autoimmune and they're in the car and
they're like mommy it says here that my
body is destroying itself it's attacking
itself
how am I going to heal I heard this so
much kids telling their moms moms have
told me this the moms are like I don't
know sweetie I don't know why your your
body is destroying itself and that's
what they lead the doctor's office is
hearing that their immune systems are
attacking itself that's one of the
reasons why it's critical to get people
to know where the information comes from
to help Free People of that
misinformation so it all counts
it just does
if I don't whine
and moan and groan about it how am I
going to protect the chronically ill and
the information at hand
so that people have a Fighting Chance
and I get it there's a few different
types of people that come to Medical
medium some people they're not sick
they're just partially
sick a little bit and they get annoyed
because they're still able to play those
reindeer games out there and try
different things everywhere but if
you're somebody that comes to medical
medium and you're literally
on mattress Island and you got nothing
left in you
and
every my whining counts
does it ever
anyway you guys
um but thank you Audrey I do appreciate
it there's so much Fork tongue out there
Audrey that's a problem and and there's
so many hate campaigns against medical
media and there's so much research
inside stealing medical media
information and never crediting and
still crapping on it where they get it
from which is me
you know so
I have to stay ahead of it all I have to
protect people as much as I can
if I don't
help people
steer clear from all the traps they can
lose years
in their healing process or sick process
sickening process or healing process
they can lose years like for real
I mean you could lose 10 20 years you
know what I used to say years ago in the
first book and even before that
published and also lectured about you
can lose 10 20 30 years of your life
before getting the answers so where are
you going to get the answers
anyway right here
all right I love you guys this is a
great cold and flu talk
quite honored to have you guys here I'm
always at your service you guys know
that
always
I appreciate everything I appreciate
what you're doing working on yourselves
and everything but let me give you just
a little more tidbit here
keep keep a lookout for medical meme
podcast at Apple podcast because I'm
going to be releasing new ones
eventually I am working on them hang in
there
some pretty cool topics I might even do
a flat or a third topic
about the Earth being flat
might do an episode on that and I got
some others but actually I got a really
long a lot of incredible episodes coming
out that are going to be really helpful
sign up for my Telegram and check out
medicalmean.com
because be on the newsletter list
if you're subscribed to the newsletter
list and you're not getting newsletters
just resubscribe try to figure out how
to do it
yeah it's the episode like is the earth
round or is the earth flat
is the earth round or is there yo man
well this is really nice stuff I
actually know the Earth is flat man I do
yeah yeah I know you're at this flat
it's vaping
only vaping all right you guys love you