hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show each week I talk about the most
advanced healing information and secrets
about health much of which is not found
anywhere else and is decades ahead of
what's out there now and we're going to
be covering some of those today this is
a big deal I love this show what we're
talking about as I've always said who
has 10 or 20 30 years to wait blah blah
blah right the 10 20 30 years to wait it
does matter someone said again to me
recently you always say that they said
they said you know Anthony you always
say that 10 20 heard it over and over
and I and you know let me tell you
something and then someone else said to
me that it means everything to know that
I understand someone's pain and
suffering and chronic illness that's
lasted so long I said to this other
person who who was being kind of
negative about that and I said said look
did you ever have anything go wrong at
all did you ever have a problem oh you
know I once Twisted an ankle and you
know it took a couple of weeks to heal I
go what about if that ankle took 6
months to heal but more than that you
couldn't walk around or get around what
do you like to do they said well I like
to play basketball and you know I like
with my friends and I like to do this
and I like to go skiing I go but what if
you couldn't do that for a full year
what if you couldn't then what would you
be saying and you know and he said
you're right you're right I've taken
this the wrong way who does have six
months or a year I go well think about
the people who've had chronic fatigue
for 10 years on and off and or a
migraine or chronic
migraines where hey you can't plan
anything that day forget planning going
out with the girls or planning to go to
dinner or because you don't know if that
migraine's going to be there you you
don't know if that's going to be the day
the migraine comes and you know your
whole life gets planned around that or
that you go get a job and you you you
want to start a career you want to get a
job or a position opens up somewhere or
you get a you know you or a job opens up
at a grocery store uh to be a manager or
to you know whatever and you can't take
the job because you don't know if you're
going to be able to hack it because you
got the fatigue and it's been going on
for a few years and your family you know
is is feeling it and everybody's feeling
it around around you it matters to get
answers it matters to get things done so
that's why I say that so thanks for
being patient why I say that everybody
out there life is precious we have no
time to waste let's get the healing
going now today's about cold and flu
colds and flu the flu this is exciting
people get it every year they get colds
they get sore throats they get head
colds they get sinus infections they get
bronchitis they get pneumonia they get
all of that right you guys probably
experienced that in fact fact this year
has been um a flu epidemic of great
proportion I mean seriously it's been
really that bad this year this winter
it's been
unbelievable so we're going to cover all
that in today's show so basically we're
covering germs germs germs germs is what
we're that's what we're covering today
check out the healing path I always
recommend the healing path because it's
free it's basically an 18 audio course
18 audios packed with
information it's a free download and I
put my heart my soul my guts into
it I put everything into that and you
know to make sure that that information
is there for everyone so hey if you're
if you haven't heard about it go to the
website medicalmedium.com and download
it I mean I'm not trying to sell you
something it's free for real there's no
like gimmick just download that it's
free and you have literally what someone
has told me recently a treasure Trove of
information and um and so it's really
important that's something look there's
stories on Instagram that we put in that
we put out every single day Facebook and
Instagram there's articles that we put
out put out we put out tremendous
amounts of
information like like tremendous amounts
the blog articles everything check them
out they're not just little cutesy
little sayings and and just like a
little paragraph they're in depth
they're they're detailed about all kinds
of different conditions symptoms
problems people face just check it all
out check out the stories check out the
Articles check out the blog just go and
look because it's there for you that's
the whole point it's actually there for
you so I'm just encouraging everybody
because because you know someone else
also said to me like well what do you
what do you have you know what do you
have to offer you do what the radio show
you got the book no I there's lots of
things that we're doing to help people
we're dedicated we're dedicated and and
just like you're dedicated to Healing
you know I mean I have to do that other
part because it wouldn't be fair
otherwise because you're dedicated in
healing right I mean you're dedicated to
take care of yourself even if you're
doing one thing even if you're doing two
things three things you're taking care
of yourself in some way eating better
that's a dedication that's a commitment
that you're doing and I honor that I
respect that I believe in that I stand
behind you
100% And I have faith faith in your body
faith in your body healing I have faith
in you and so what do I have to do I
have to just keep on producing keep on
producing keep on producing you better
believe it and I'm not going to stop and
I have to keep on producing I have to
handle my other half because you got
that half covered so I want to make sure
all that information's getting out there
the blog articles all that stuff is
getting out there you know all the
information we put out every day and and
then of course packing it in the books
lifechanging Foods is packed I I you
know I I don't feel like I let you guys
down I think because I've been told a
few times recently that I didn't that
the book is packed and I remember you
know last year saying look you'll see
you'll see and it it it well hey you
know just you know and then there's the
new book coming out now another one the
thyroid healing book check that out it's
not out yet you know it's you're going
to have to you know wait a little while
but but check that out check out the
thyroid book and that's really jammed
packed coming out that's really packed
and and you will be blown away I promise
but I have to do that other half because
you guys are doing the other half we're
working together it's you and me
it's it's you and me it's me and you
okay and we are working together that's
the whole point and I can't get I can't
get lazy I can't get lazy and say I
don't want to put out that article I
don't want to ask spirit for all this
information that's never before ever
heard in any circuit in any Alternative
Market or any inter alternative healing
or in any books or on the Internet
information that Spirit provides that's
never been heard before so you can heal
I can't get lazy on that I just have to
listen to Spirit and get you that
information and deliver that just like
when I delivered it as a child to so
many people andto my grandmother and to
everybody else and I delivered that
information growing up and then being
there for you guys so anyway we're doing
cold and
flu cold and flu that's what we're doing
today so germs germs and germs how do we
first of of all not catch the flu how do
we not catch it there's ways of
protecting ourselves I think I told you
this one story before where I was you
know I was
traveling and I was rundown and I was
traveling and uh I I think it's about
five or six years ago don't know what it
is now I can't remember now but you know
and and a lot was going on and there was
a flu ripping through everybody had it
they all had the sinuses the cough they
all had the fevers everybody was getting
it had it and I remember I felt a little
tickle in my throat and I said oh man
this is this is just not this is not
good I don't need this right now I'm
doing so much somebody must have coughed
in my
face someone someone must have you know
or whatever and I felt that tickle in my
throat and spirit said the zinc the Li
liquid zinc sulfate the liquid zinc
sulfate and I did zinc shock therapy
that's what I did well hey it sounds
like it's something out there no no it's
something that I created meaning through
spirit that Spirit helped me create it's
not something you look up and you look
up Zing shock therapy and if it is out
there now that's because of me for sure
okay but the point is is because it
sounds like something that's already
been going around and it's out it's out
it's been out forever no it's not and
what happened is spirit said zinc zinc
shock therapy
I said okay what do I do Spirit what do
I do and I just shot a whole bunch of
dropper FS right in the throat
immediately cuz I knew I knew I was
coming down with that
flu and I just boom boom and I wasn't
sleeping cuz I was traveling a lot I
wasn't sleeping I was catching an hour
here catching an hour there was so much
going on it was the height of the flu
season and I just squirted it on down
there one squirt two squirt three squirt
four squirt right in the throat let it
sit there 2 hours later 1 2 3 4 squirts
let it sit in there couple hours later 1
2 3 4 let it sit in there bam woke up
that morning the next morning gone gone
gone gone never even touched me I got it
early I got it early and if we can't get
it early we can't get it early that's
okay too we could do lots and lots of
things to protect ourselves from the flu
and we're going to cover all kinds of
information about the flu and everything
so you know today's going to be really
fun but so the deal is the deal is how
do we not catch it to begin with well
you know we got to try not to get rund
down we got to try to get some sleep
okay fine you know those are the
basics but the flu virus likes to eat it
likes to eat like other viruses viruses
love to eat now um you know there there
are people out there professionals out
there in the medical world that don't
know yet
that viruses feed that they consume they
believe that no these cells reproduce
they reproduce through a protein and and
um that's all they do they don't they
don't eat anything and so this is this
is information that's out there as far
as viruses don't eat anything that's
wrong and
misinformation viruses feed they eat
that's what they do they love certain
things like for instance I always talk
about the epscene bar virus I'm the
first one to bring into the world what
Epstein bar what symptoms Epstein bar
causes I'm the first person to do that
now it's being taken and the
information's just being scrambled it's
running around a muck out there uh
people aren't giving me credit about it
and they're just trying to rewrite it
and it's but it's not you know 100%
accurate and I always say try to go to
the main source the main source is
Spirit that's the main source so when it
comes down EP bar and stuff always come
back to Spirits information um the
thyroid book covers a lot of that that
I've never even covered in the first
book medical medium but anyway
viruses viruses feed and they're
hungry they multiply through food
sources that's what they do food can
enter into a virus so viruses have a
door a doorway that opens and shuts and
food enters into the virus that's how it
grows and
reproduces this is will be discovered it
will be and there's lots of things that
are discovered now that I knew 30 years
ago this one will be eventually but the
flu virus loves food now if you talk
about the Aven flu if you talk about the
bird flu bird flu the reason why the
birds catch a flu is the virus loves to
attack it has the ability to attack a
bird it has the ability to feed off of a
bird what's the bird of choice that flu
viruses love to feed off of the bird
choice is chicken chicken chickens okay
fowl chicken that's what bird flu likes
to actually eat and feed off of and bird
flu is a dangerous one because it causes
flesh deterioration because it feeds off
of Flesh internally inside the bird so
that flu bug feeds off the adrenal
glands inside of a bird meaning it eats
adrenal gland and it eats eats flesh so
it actually feeds off of um cells cells
in the body flesh cells in the body of a
bird so that's the kind of virus it is
but all flu viruses like to eat chicken
now I'm not trying to scare the crap out
of everybody purposely to get them to
stop eating chicken you like chicken and
that's what does you right you feel and
you're eating still your leafy greens
and you're still bringing some fruits in
that I want you to bring then hey if
that's what you want to do that's what
you want to do you know I I'm not anti
every single diet but I will say if you
want the least chance of catching a flu
or stomach flu especially that darn
stomach flu where you vomit and you're
sick and your stomach's a hot mess if
you want to get rid of all the you know
the different stomach flu then you don't
want to have chicken in your system and
I don't mean chicken that day or chicken
that night I mean Chicken in general now
what what you're thinking right now
maybe not all of you but what you're
probably thinking is hey wait a minute
what about chicken soup isn't that the
best cure for the flu no it's not the
best cure for the flu it's not it never
was a cure for the flu now I know I'm
controversial on this for a minute here
because I know there's a whole bunch of
chicken soup stuff going on out there
and there's all these people trying to
prove it and it's always it's been you
know it's been looked at and it's
folklore and it goes it's everything
from science to folkl or whatever but no
chicken soup is not what makes somebody
start getting better or feeling a little
better okay it's the it's whatever else
is in that chicken soup it's the garlic
it's the onions everybody does a chicken
soup differently they have the garlic in
there they have the onions in there they
have the carrots in there they have the
celery in there they have they have um
I've seen people put zucchini in their
chicken soup
you know old recipes just just chopping
up zucchini it goes in there I've seen
lots of different things in chicken
soups every Grandma has a different
chicken soup they're not all the same
but it's what's in that chicken soup
namely garlic namely an onion especially
an onion believe it or not that actually
helps improve and then it's the
hydration of the chicken soup and it's
the mineral salts in the chicken soup
the mineral salt there's nothing in the
chicken that help helps you with a
colder flu that's the part that's
fighting against you when you're using
chicken soup for a flu or a cold I'm not
trying to be negative about chicken soup
not I'm just trying to look if I don't
give it to you straight then I'm doing
you wrong bottom line I'm doing you're
wrong so if you're if you get upset
about me and you think I'm like might be
biased about chicken soup or anything
like that because people are really
their head strong about their chicken
soup like that's one area I was afraid
of even kind of jumping into today I
remember for the show I I Was preparing
a little bit I was talking to my
assistant and I said I'm afraid to talk
about the chicken soup I'm
afraid I'm afraid but then you know I
thought about it and then spirit said to
me spirit said what are you going to do
you going to do the people wrong I said
what do you mean spirit said well you
just don't be straight with them you're
going to do them wrong I go oh man so
here's the deal here's the deal what
happens is with that chicken soup you
got all the mineral salts in there from
the celery you got that you got the
carrots there's mineral salts and
carrots and there's also precious sugars
that feed your liver and feed your body
and feed your body's immune system to
fight the flu and then the onion the
onion is antiviral
antiviral garlic antiviral the flu is a
virus that's what makes chicken soup
chicken soup so what I like is I like
taking out the chicken because that
feeds the virus that feeds the flu virus
especially the flu virus out of all the
viruses especially the flu virus the
chicken is literally its number one food
number one food and people who eat
chicken on a daily basis every day when
the flu season comes around they get the
flu and they may get it twice three
times unless they take care of
themselves in other ways while they're
still eating the chicken unless they're
taking care of themselves so the person
who goes I never caught a flu and I eat
chicken every day it's cuz you're
probably doing other things for your
health and you're keeping yourself
steady with all these different ways so
when you do catch that colder flu it's
mild or you don't remember you had one
cuz it was 2 years ago and it was mild
mild there's a lot of people that got
get
slammed three four times a year with a
cold or flu or sinus infection or
stomach
flu and you want that chicken out of
there just telling you right now you
want it out of there you want the
healing broths I like the healing broth
reason why the healing broth doesn't
have chicken in it because I don't want
it to be a chicken soup because I know
that viruses will the viruses that are
chicken wanting will want it chicken
hungry will want it so so that's why the
healing broth is what it is because it
really is a healing broth when you
remove the viral
feeder really important to know so you
can still make your your still make your
chicken soup without the chicken and
still get better results with cold flu
you know sinus infections a whole bit in
fact why don't you put more onion in it
in fact why don't you put more garlic in
it and make it a real healing healing
soup a a savior a graceful savior soup
why don't you really do that and remove
that chicken fat chicken fat takes
oxygen out of the blood so you can't
fight the virus even faster so it even
the fat from the chicken on top of that
chicken sou make a big big pot of
chicken soup stick it in the
refrigerator and the next morning you
come to it and you got a half inch of
fat on top of that Frozen not frozen but
solidified gated right there on top
right there on top that fat right there
slows down your liver makes it sluggish
that fat right there stops your immune
system from beating down epine bar it
stops your immune system from beating
down a flu virus right there stops your
immune system from from beating down
bacteria like strep aaka strep Ackle to
strep throat it stops that a big fat
layer of fat stops oxygen to your immune
system oxygen to your liver oxygen to
your heart you don't want that on your
soup while you're trying to heal you
don't want that there okay this is
important really important to know wh
watch the flak I get from this show I
can already feel it coming on but look
look look I'm just saying if you want to
be flu free or fight it faster if you
don't want to be bog down these are some
tips that are so
important so let's go into some more fun
stuff about all this colds there there
are no colds anymore colds rhinovirus
there are none they've all been
dominated they've all been taken over
you're only going to hear it here only
going to hear it here another piece of
information you're only going to hear
here sound like a broken record that
record with that I half to though
because if there's anybody new that's
listening to the show for the first time
they need to know I'm not just taking
some information off the internet and
delivering it to you like everybody else
is but no I need you here to learn so
you can help people I need you to know
all these things so here's the deal
there aren't colds anymore news flash
it's all the flu and it's only the flu
even if it's a mild variety of flu
there's so many different strains now
that information's out there there's so
many different strains of the flu but
what's not out there is there's no cold
there's no colds no no no no I'm sorry
it's all flu and guess what the flu
isn't just the winter it's not just the
fall when everybody goes back to college
and everybody's got the flu and they're
coughing their butts off that's not not
when it is it's then it's 6 weeks after
that it's 6 weeks after that it's 6
weeks after that it's 6 weeks after that
then you get into then you get into
March it's six weeks after that then you
get your next wave of flu April six
weeks after that you get your next wave
of flu in May and just when you think no
one catches colds and flu in the
summertime bull they all catch colds and
flu in the summertime been helping
people for over 30 years I can't tell
you how many people both kids and adults
sinus infections all summer long from
getting the flu getting the sinus flu
stomach flu during the summer barfing
their brains out stomach flu viral flu
um chest flues bronchitis in the middle
of the summer going all the way to
August there's always an August flu
before you even get to late September
when everybody goes back to
school the flu never stops because it's
happening all across the country all
across the globe
when it's winter in Australia the flu's
ramp it you see and it's everybody's
hopping on planes and bringing it to the
US it doesn't matter where it is and in
the summertime in summertime in
Australia I'm just using Australia's
example everybody's bringing it over
there in the planes from our winter it
doesn't matter the flu is 247 it's all
year long everybody's catching it
different times of the season it doesn't
matter and it's always there and colds
have died they have been taking over see
cold bugs the little cold bugs that used
to be the bugs of the colds little tiny
sore throat some sniffles goes away in a
day um if you're lucky a temperature of
99 those are the past now if you do have
symptoms like that you could easily have
one of the mild flu or your body's
fighting that flu fantastically so it
doesn't turn into what feels like a flu
so you feel like you just had a cold so
if you're at work and someone's like oh
I just dealing with a cold I got sinuses
got a little thing no it's the flu it's
the flu bottom line and how you may
react to that flu is different than how
the other person reacts too everybody
reacts differently some people get a
pipe and fever of 104 pipe and fever of
102 they're
Delirious some people they just just run
a temperature of 100 they go to
work they go out and Bowl after work
and um and that's what happens and you
know it's it's it's it's not so not so
heavy duty it's kind of mild here's the
deal the flu always creates all this
mucus in many cases and what happens is
when it creates mucus like that so when
the mucus starts and starts to drain it
drains at night it drains you know the
whole postnasal trip but even more than
that drains into the chest you may not
feel it you may not have a cough at
first when you start with a flu and you
different levels of flues different mild
ones whatever but whether mild to
extreme and then the mucus builds up in
the lungs 3 days later you start to
cough or the mucus starts breaking up or
really starts in the sinus is heavier
and heavier then drains back down in the
chest that mucus in the chest that's
where bronchitis that's what bronchitis
is bronchitis is that mucus down in the
chest
pneumonia is is when bacteria starts to
proliferate starts to grow from that
mucus being down there too long so you
get you become
pneumatic so you know because people
have the pneumonia bacteria they have it
they both have different varieties of
pneumonia bacteria all in them they have
chamian pneumonia they have all
different kinds of pneumonia that's
inside of them so you have to you have
to understand how that works um so
that's in US automatically that bacteria
and that bacteria really is worthless it
doesn't cause any trouble unless you're
really beaten down run down eating
terribly wrong um catching cold and flu
and not even catching cold and flu if
you're just beaten down and run down not
taking care of yourself and you're
severely zinc deficient yeah you know
you can you can get that bacteria can
really you know start up you can get a
strep strep strep bacteria in the lungs
causing uh pneumonia too a strep
pneumonia IA you can get you know a
Pneumatic bacteria basically what that
means it's a bacteria that that's kind
of slightly unidentified to some degree
it's just they that's what they call it
pneumonia basically they don't know what
it is there's a couple of varieties of
pneumatic
bacteria and um you know really believe
it or not the strep has a lot to do with
a different varieties causing causing
that but the whole point is you got the
flu it's draining
down and it gets down to the
lung and then it sits in there the mucus
and then you got the cough and you got
the bronchitis so if you're not you know
doing expectance and taking care of
yourself and taking it easy you know
that that mucus you get the coughing
attacks in the morning coughing teexs at
night and you really can't you can't
function good and then what happens is
if the mucus is down there way too long
you can get the pneumonia possibilities
which is bacteria can get built up down
here whether it's a strep that you've
had in your system for years or um you
know a type of pneumatic bacteria that
you've happened to have in your system
like a caldia bacteria anything like
that yeah and and it could be down in
there and start creating some kind of
pneumonia if you're really run down if
your zinc reserves are low you're not
taking care of yourself it can go into
something like that but the mucus a lot
of people when they first come down with
their flu they're usually say they go to
work and they're not feeling that great
they get the sore throat and they're
like no no I just got a sore throat
everything's all good but then you know
that night comes sore throat gets a
little worse they get a fever in the
morning like okay they go back to work
again and now you know the the the
sinuses start to clog up and the mucus
starts to form a little later on it's
almost predictable you said well you're
going to have a cough in four days
you're going to have a cough in 3 days
you're going to have a cough in 5 days
they're like no no no no I'm not going
to have a cough how could I have a cough
I only have a sore throat I got a little
mild fever no you're going to have a
cough and then yeah four or 5 days later
person's coughing their brains out
because you know the flu is just running
the course but here's how it works it's
like an every six week cycle I was
talking about before there's a new flu
in the Horizon new flu in the Horizon
I've seen people catch him every 3
months I've seen people catch him every
six weeks I've seen people run down
where they catch them in all different
ways but there's a lot of different flu
they take different shapes different
sizes flues come in different varieties
some flu like to create more high fevers
some like to be sinus related only only
and some like to be stomach related some
like to be across between sinus and
stomach a lot of people get so much
mucus that they think they got a stomach
flu but it was really just all sinus
because the amount of mucus that they
swallowed lots of swallowing mucus down
in in the stomach letting it sit down in
there and then the stomach gets sick it
gets bloated as heck and no appetite
sometimes you might vomit mucus there's
a lot of people that cough and vomit
mucus when they got the flu because
their stomachs are filled with mucus
their lungs have it and they're just
coughing it out so these are all the
things hey maybe you you've been in this
position maybe you know someone but um
so knocking colds and flu out early is a
big deal so we're going to cover that I
talked about the zinc always have a
bottle of liquid sulfate zinc with you
nearby in your life just always have it
because if you think you're even
remotely getting the possibility of a of
a flu you want to shoot that zinc in
your throat and let it sit there if
you're zinc sensitive where you're just
too
sensitive just do a few tiny drops some
people that can't they're really
sensitive to certain vitamins and zinc
can be you know a sensitive thing to
some people um how do how else do we
prevent a flu keep your fingers and your
face keep your fingers in your hands
away from your face keep your fingers
and your hands away from your eyes you
know if it's flu season you're working
on keyboards and you're working and
you're doing this and wherever you are
or you're touching somebody that's got
the flu whatever you got to do just
don't take your hands and put your
fingers in your eyes don't rub your eyes
because it's an instant flu it's a
guaranteed catch I mean practically
guaranteed when you're out and about
going to restaurants whatever you know
take handy wipes with you during flu
season use a handy wipe before you start
your dinner at a
restaurant order your food hot order
your food hot at the restaurants so that
the person making it because during flu
season they're coughing they're sneezing
coughing all over your food sneezing all
over your food the weight is sneezing on
your food coughing on your
food and it goes on and on and on the
beat goes on and and you want to make
sure your food comes really hot so it
just basically kills the flu viruses
these little things matter every bit of
it so you want you know want to make
sure you got cooked food and you don't
want to be doing the raw salads and and
when you're in the middle of flu season
in restaurants and you want to make sure
that your food is piping hot you know
say hey look can you can you make the
plate hot can you make the food you know
can you just throw the food in the oven
get it nice and hot whatever it is it
all matters so see these are some of the
things to think about so let's go back
to um what foods feed the
flu what foods feed all viruses dairy
products that's a big feeder of viruses
I talk about it in the books you know
and I talk about it in different ways
like the first book I mentioned it
Medical medium and then I provided more
information in the second book but it's
important to know that what you're
eating can feed something else that's a
way that's a real true way of protecting
yourself right there it's it's really
imperative to know that and you might
say well I mean I feel fine once I've
eaten that piece of cheese I feel okay I
can eat cheese you know every day I
could have it on my salads I could have
it on my sandwiches but it is a recipe
for feeding something eventually whether
it's an Epstein bar whether it's cytoma
virus whether it's hhv6 whether it's
simplex one Simplex 2 whether it's you
know um something else it can feed it
including bacteria it can feed it eoli
loves eoli itself loves it merca loves
it loves dairy products just so many
things love it and if you're big into
parasites if you're someone who just you
know is is a parasite freak meaning like
you know you know there's people out
there that just everything's parasites
everything's parasites everything's
parasites it it then don't feed the
parasites cuz guess what parasites eat
they eat and worms eat dairy products
that's what they love milk cheese butter
milk cheese butter kefir yogurt ghee
yeah even ghee believe it or not so
always know this so cold flu season
don't eat any dairy products you have a
better chance of not catching cold not
catching a flu and if you catch the
flu okay it could be much more mild less
mucus I've seen people who catch the flu
every single year I mean out of the
Decades I've been helping people they
catch the flu every year couple of times
a year worst flues ever mucus everything
bronchitis you name it sinus infections
all of it with it misery and they
stopped dairy products and they stopped
getting the flu or the flu was cut down
to a manageable level where they caught
it once it was mild and they moved on
with their
life okay another one too eggs big one
really does feed the flu virus so cold
season you don't want to make two
scrambled eggs if you do make two
scrambled eggs for breakfast during cold
and flu season or whatever during that
time and I still say cold even though
they don't exist anymore it's all flu
but it's by habit just so many years but
the bottom line is you put put some
garlic on that toast then if you're
going to have egg and toast put some
garlic on it if you're going to have
butter you I mean I know you know people
like yeah but grass-fed butter is the
best and that's no yeah that's better
absolutely that's better because it's
going to lack it's going to lack all
that you know that GMO grain inside of
it it's going to lack you know all of
that um hormone and everything that's
added it's going to lack it's going to
be reduced in heavy metals I get it so
sure you have the grass-fed butter it's
still going to feed a flu so if you're
having a flu cold and you make some
scrambled eggs and you have some toast
with some butter put some garlic in
there you got to try to help defend also
put something in there that's going to
be killing off the flu
virus at the same time you're trying to
feed the flu virus by
accident so you know and that's that's
an option you can do you know and I
offer that option because some people
they just like they like their toast and
butter they they love it
and they catch a cold and flu and they
have tea and they have toast and butter
so we put some garlic in there're like
yuck no try it they put a little garlic
raw garlic on top of there and they have
it they actually get better and they get
better faster they feel a little bit
better and they notice a difference so
it's something you can do so stay away
from the eggs stay away from the dairy
products when it comes down to those flu
and being sick sinus infections sore
throats all of it no matter what cough
whatever is coming on stay away from
that stay away from the chicken pull the
chicken out of the soup like I talked
about that's right that's
right you should do it I'm not saying
you you can't eat chicken again if
that's what you love I'm just saying
it's even better without it is what's
going
on so what are some of the uh weapons
what are some of the weapons we can use
to keep ourselves
from getting really sick from flu and
stuff like that let's go over it olive
leaf I love olive leaf so if you know
olive leaf you could take every single
day if you have Epstein bar or you take
every single day if okay let's just move
the K you know move Epstein bar over
whether you have fibromyalgia multiple
sclerosis chronic fatigue syndrome by
the way which are all Epstein bar but
move Epstein bar over you know some
someone said to me you say well it's
Epstein bar with you that's all it is
okay okay move it over let's talk about
fibromyalgia let's talk about multiple
sclerosis let's talk about rheumatoid
arthritis let's talk about um connected
tissue diseases guess what they're all
Epstein bar yep that's right so anyway
you can use the olive
leaf with that is what you can do you
know and cystic fibrosis all that
Epstein bar breast cancer Epstein bar
Hashimoto thyroiditis Epstein bar I'm
the first person to bring that to the
table because you're going to be hearing
a lot about everybody's putting it in
putting it in their books right now and
they're put doing courses out there in
the world and they're saying about how
Epstein bar is involved that came for me
it's important to know because I'm going
to provide more and more firsttime
information and always going to be ahead
of everybody not because I'm smart but
because Spirit knows and that's the
point so stay tuned and because you want
you want you want the stuff you want the
gold you want the good stuff I can't let
you down I got to be with you stand
behind you you're doing the other half
of the work so I got to be I got to do
mine always provide so the deal is you
want that olive leaf in there anyway
take a couple of capsules every single
day I mean I would do that you can get
capsules you can get it in tincture
alcohol-free tincture olive leaf so but
when you start getting the flu or you
start feeling sick with something up
your olive leaf eonia golden seal
incredible for the flu golden seal you
could do by yourself you can get the
combination e can eonia golden seal I
love it I also love it battling strep
strep throat
tonsilitis um you know sinus infections
caused by strep I also like you know
because there's different sinus
infections that aren't just the flu you
can get the strep the chronic sinus
stuff where it's not a flu there's
people that have sinus infections that
are chronic from strep and then a flu
comes by and then their sinuses get much
worse for about two months and it
finally backs down to their normal Agony
where their sinuses are just partly bad
because they got the chronic lowgrade
strep and then another flu comes along
and boom and now their sinuses are just
totally ter terrible and they're back to
that again well eia golden seal
Elderberry Elderberry syrup get a good
Elderberry syrup incredible incredible
for the cold and flu colds and flu back
to that again the colds Lum root Lum l o
m a t i u m ladium some people call it
ladium I call it l ium lomatium root
incedible for the lungs bronchitis
pneumonia flu sinus problems fever
whatever lomatium root is fantastic I've
seen it save people's lives ibrite yep
your eye you know like your eyeball
ibrite beautiful herb you know I love
right around Midsummer walking in a
field I don't know if you ever get a
chance to walk in a field I try to do
that once in a while in the summertime I
try to get out to the you know to the
wild I try to get out there and I and I
like to ask Spirit to identify all the
herbs for me I've been doing that since
I was a child since I was a child I
would say what's this weed Spirit say
that's not a weed that's this what's
this spirit Spirit said that's not a
weed that's s sasparilla what's this
Spirit that's not a weed that's chaga
you know what's you know when I was
little and so I love still doing that at
the one thing that keeps me sane
throughout it all throughout all the
crap that's out there and all the bull
and everything else and stress in life
it's the one thing keeps me sane so I
love
Midsummer going out and being like whoa
Spirit told me taught me about ibrite
when I was younger showed me it you know
ibride is amazing it pops out of the
ground it's 3 in tall little cute little
flowers that Bing in the Sun and they
look at you I Bright's an incredible
herb so you can get that you can buy it
you know alcohol freeing a tincture so I
Bright's amazing for knocking down flu I
like ibrite too for strepa cacus I like
ibrite for other things um Cherry Bark
for the cough you can get Cherry Bark
syrup just like Elderberry syrup and for
the kids you can use any of these for
kids in smaller dosages as a mommy you
can totally prevent coold you know the
whole flu
thing okay and you know it's Mullen Leaf
Mullen Leaf m u l l e i n Mullen Leaf I
love that that's a great tincture for
the lungs incredible for the lungs I
like Mullen leaf for shingles shingles
related neuropathies shingles related
frozen shoulder um you know Bell's paly
shingles related you know I'm I was the
first to bring what shingles does causes
bells paly and everything else and now
recently I saw somewhere that someone
was talking about Bells paly being
Jingles related uh you know thank God
for Spirit bringing this information to
the world so
so Mullen Leaf's amazing for the
shingles but it's incredible for the flu
it's incredible for sinus infections
bronchitis lung issues so you want the
Mullen Leaf
propolis propolis is amazing for the
immune system really powerful incredible
for flu I love it you know I'll do if I
feel like something's coming on or
something boom just some propolis
nothing ever comes on when you do it
that's that's what happens just propolis
right down in the throat it's amazing so
you got that very powerful um you can do
you that anytime you want so these are
options right here vitamin C always do
vitamin C you should be doing vitamin C
anyway every day and so make sure that's
in your system so that's there but you
can do the ginger ginger turmeric shot
in life-changing Foods use that for a
flu Ginger turmeric shot yeah it's
pretty strong it's a pretty strong shot
no joke but use it if it's too strong
for you then just do Ginger turmeric tea
simmer it hunks of Ginger hunks of
turmeric syn s um simmer it go to the
store health food store get some
turmeric get some ginger hunks cut it up
put it in simmer it up and then you got
something you got something you could
have tea you could drink it all day long
and shorten your flu protect yourself
from a flu and bronchitis too see here's
the deal if you get the flu you're
already in it so the so now you want to
make sure you don't want the
bronchitis if you're someone who gets to
that point you want to now make sure you
you don't want it ever pneumatic if
you're someone who's ever worried about
that or gets to that point pneumonia so
so you want to do those t uh turmeric
ginger pieces simmer that tea and then
the healing broth the garlic the onions
and the celery and the healing broth and
you you can do you know little broccoli
in the healing broth if you really like
a little asparagus in the healing broth
because if you look at life-changing
Foods you'll see what's going on with
asparagus you'll see what's going on
with the little cauliflower you'll see
what's happening with garlic what it
really possesses the information that
Spirit put out there and when you make
that into your healing broth you can
have that without the flu you can use
that to keep yourself healthy but it's
amazing it's powerful it's it's really a
great thing for the body for the immune
system it boosts bolsters the immune
system charges it up you know you charge
your phone you charge your phone right
your cell phone oh wait the the cell
phone's dying down I got to charge it
here let me get the charger plug it in
you know the iPad you know needs a
charge you know these devices need
charging wait this flashlight that I
have the batter's going dead I got to
put new batteries in it you got to think
about that with your immune system you
got to think about that that way every
time your cell phone starts to die down
you got to plug it in again you got to
instantly think about your own immune
system like wait a minute what did I do
to boost up my immune system what did I
do to plug in my immune system like you
guys seriously that's how you should do
that's what I do so if I'm like oh crap
my my cell phone's dying down I got to
plug it in here I go wait what did I do
for my immune system to charge it up
just now you know that and so I have to
go now and I've go meaning I have to go
and some vitamin C I go let me do some
vitamin C keep the immune system strong
let me put some extra gar let me make a
healing broth put some extra garlic in
there so look you can do any kind of tea
when it comes down to flu you know you
can do any kind of tea and it'll give
you some benefits you can do chamomile
tea it can still give you some benefits
put lemon in your teas if you're doing
herbal teas here's the one I like I like
I like the rose hips I like getting the
rose hips in bulk you can get them in
tea bags too now but I like getting them
in bulk taking those rose hips really
steeping them making you know doing the
hot hot water French Press whatever
steeping them making that like red that
tea red and then I like squeezing lots
of lemon in there and that right there
is a
powerhouse it's incredible for for sore
throats okay now there's what happens
with sore throats there's a lot of
things that cause different sore throats
that aren't flu Rel needed but their
strep their lowgrade chronic strep now
just because someone has a sore throat
and a doctor they go see the doctor and
the doctor does a swab on the back of
the throat does a culture and strep
doesn't show up doesn't mean it's not
strep related the only time the strep
shows up from a culture is when it's at
its earlier times when someone has strep
throat it's like when when uh children
or young adults have a really bad case a
white pocket bubbles up on the tonsil or
the back of the throat to the sides of
the tonsils and that's swabble that's
swabble you could run a culture on that
but after that a lot of times people can
get sore throats and it not be you can't
do that you stick the swab down there
the the strep is in the lymphatic system
chronically underlying inside the
lymphatic system and it's causing sore
throats so that's something to
understand too strep is just that's how
works okay you can also have an Epstein
bar sore throat you can have a mono sore
throat a mono sore throat um that is a
virus meaning it's a mono virus abine
bar virus causing a red sore throat on
one side of the throat that hurts really
bad I'm giving you some different stuff
about sore throats that are separate
from
flues and so where you never develop uh
you never develop sinusitis you never
develop mucus you're not coughing ever
ever but you get this wicked sore throat
on the left side of your throat did
anybody ever get that and the wicked
sore throat on the right side of the
throat or sometimes both but yet it
doesn't turn into mucus it doesn't turn
into a fever that's an Epstein bar
related sore throat that people get all
the time believe it or not when Epstein
bar starts to go and surfaces up through
the lymphatic system and gets to the
throat when you get run down it's a
different level of chronic mono people
experienc in their life every now and
then so that's just a tidbit too that I
thought I'd cover as well um I hope this
Show's been helpful I hope it has these
are some of the things you can do to
protect yourself um when you go on
airplanes take handy wipes when you go
on airplanes airplanes are Petri dishes
they are Petri dishes it's like sitting
in a Petri dish it's like basking in a
Petri dish you know the funny thing is
when I'm on the airplane um Spirit
doesn't stop telling me what's wrong
with every single person on the airplane
so when I get on there okay when I get
on there it's it's um there's it's
really funny I got to tell you something
I used to think let me be the first one
on the plane to sit in the back the way
back the last seat in the back I'll try
to get I always think let me go sit in
the last seat so I don't have to watch
everybody walk down the aisle by me so I
could do readings but what happens then
is I can see everybody in front of me
ahead of me when you're sitting way in
the back you just see a a sea of people
and and then spirit's giving me readings
on every single person I'm looking at so
then I thought let me sit at the front
of the plane in any way I can capacity
and then but then everybody walking by
me as I'm sitting there you you know you
get the read on so it's really funny
I've tried to dodge it the best I can
but what happens is spirit will be like
that person's got a flu it's it's it's
in the middle of the stage of the flu
that person just is getting the flu that
person's cough they're getting over the
flu that person has pneumonia that
person has bronchitis so every three
people that person is going to get the
flu in three days that person is going
to get it a week from now so spirit's
telling me this as each person's walking
by down the aisle and then spirit says
that person has
tuberculosis that person has this and it
goes on that person person just came
from visiting a family member in a
hospital and has
Mera so this is how it works when I sit
on the plane and they walk but everybody
walks by so I like to bring handy
wipes and if you want you can be as bold
as bringing an n95 mask or some kind of
mask you know little little Hospital
mask but you know that's that's another
option too you have to prevent catching
something on planes I'm trying not to
make you you know phobic about it all
I'm just saying in the height of the
season even though the flu goes all year
like I talked about before in the height
of the season in the winter when you
don't want to catch it because it's you
know Zer degrees outside and you want to
function and battle the elements you
know you just got to look out if you can
bring the handy wipes wipe off your seat
in the side of your seat or something
that the arm rests and uh Keep Your
Hands Clean don't put your fingers in
your eyes you know when I sit on a plane
I watch people rubbing their eyes they
take off their glasses and they just
rubbing their eyes then they go to use
the bathroom they grab the bathroom
handle and they go in there and watch
them grab the bathroom handle and go in
and they use the bathroom don't wash
their hands come out cuz I know I asked
Spirit did they wash their hands spirit
said no they come back out and they know
touch the you know door come in they're
rubbing their eye they're taking off
their glasses rubbing their eyes I'm
like well that's great so the so look
out for those things take your handy
wipes same thing when you're in public
restrooms and everything you can catch
the flu by just not being you know
mindful about your hands while wash them
when you can use the handy wipes look
out and then keep the zinc on hand keep
all these other things I talked about on
hand you know these herbs red Roots
another herb that can be helpful so you
can look up red root try to find that
alcohol-free that one's also helpful too
so bring that on board so you know the
bottom line is this is
look if you've been suffering with a
chronic illness if you've if you got a
chronic illness whether you had a
diagnosis or not whether you have a
diagnosis of Lyme disease and we talk
about Lyme disease you know you know you
know the drill I put it in medical
medium the first book whether you have
whatever it is you don't want to also be
battling the elements of a flu you don't
want to battle that on top of it all and
some people they just battle their
chronic illness and they they do pretty
good they don't get a flu too often they
stay away from them they don't get sick
too often with the other outside you
know variable but the deal is you just
want we got enough to worry about and
take care of ourselves so do you know
all these things can help and move you
forward strengthen you so if you're
someone that's dealing with ra or you're
somebody that's dealing with lime are
somebody that's dealing with you know
something else you got some backup you
need some extra support and that's what
this is all about today listen I love
you guys I stand behind you you know
bless you bless your hearts for caring
thank you for listening to the show you
know I can't tell you how many times I
asked Spirit who's going to be listening
to the show and spirit gives me a window
a window into everybody I love you
dearly take care
bye-bye