when there's smoke in the air because of
the LA fires right now things really bad
for a lot of people I mean it's
devastating I'm sure you guys have seen
it out there people losing their homes
people losing their Farms their
businesses their family's homes their
apartment buildings they're losing their
places to live I just wanted to come on
here just uh for a couple of tips number
one one of the big things is because the
air is so dry the Ash and the air it
just cuts through it just gets into the
lungs really easily and I think that's
really hard for a lot of people one of
the things that you can do is you can
wear like an n95 mask it's going to help
a little bit I mean it's obviously not
going to protect you with flames and
heavy heavy smoke so if you're exposed
and you're out of your house and so
forth one thing you can do is you take a
towel like this and I've said this
before with other fires over the years
but you take a towel and you moisten it
so this is really important right here
you moisten it I'm squeezing out the
water and you breathe through the towel
a moist towel that's important you can
actually make it as thin as you want you
can double it up depending on how it
feels you can do this too you can hold
it just like this and you can put it
over your face and you can breathe
through it so what happens is the water
is what catches a lot of the toxins a
lot of that dust a lot of the ashes if
you're moving around you get a couple of
towels like that you keep them moist and
damp now there's this packet I don't
know if you've had this before it's a
medical medium tool book right here okay
environmental disaster a quality tools
including some air cleaners that are the
best ones other tools too
supplementation you know for after the
fact as well you get some place you're
able or things start coming down got to
build your immune system back up after
getting everything cuz when it goes into
the lungs and it goes into the
bloodstream what happens with chronic
illness when people have chronic illness
it could be a trigger all those toxins
all those poisons floating around Metals
prayers go out to anyone you know my
heart pours out to you you know I'm
proud of you for all you're doing