now we're live let's go
we're live right now it's the medical
meeting morning cleanse challenge we're
doing it okay i'm excited you guys this
is really great and i'll tell you why
it's great because everything everything
you do for your body
it pays off and it pays off in an
incredible way you know everybody's
worried about maxing out the credit card
i get it you run your credit card you
push your credit card you run your
credit card go into the gas pump you're
sticking your credit card in there well
your pancreas is your credit card your
adrenals are your credit card your liver
is your credit card right
you can burn those babies out and
eventually that liver
that spleen that pancreas right just
says okay i'm done i'm done you maxed me
out you maxed me out and that's it i'm
done and that's what happens all the
time so you have to understand that
so what we need to do is we need to now
figure out a way of getting savings into
your liver savings into your pancreas
savings into your kidney savings into
your adrenals this is how you do it
right here
because no matter what you do and how
you go through life no matter if you get
times of trouble and times are good and
times are trouble and times are good and
something happens here in the world you
know is about to blow up
volcanoes about to explode something's
gonna happen
you gotta be healthy you have to be
healthy your organs have to be strong
that's the key right there so no matter
what happens in the world no matter how
bad the world gets if it's screwed up
right now and it's just like okay the
world's all screwed up right now
are the all the angels come in here
because it's like was this the ending
times right now or what is this the
ending times no no it's not the ending
times so let's just keep on moving we're
going to keep on moving we're going to
keep on moving and guess what you want
to make sure your adrenals are
strong you want to make sure your liver
is strong you want to make sure your
brain is strong do you know how many
people have toxic brains
their brain that brains they have
for brains because their brains are
so toxic there's all these podcast
doctors acting like they know about
health there's all these podcast
influencers that act like they know
about health and literally the brain is
filled with
and
yeah they sound like they're smart for
five seconds but really when you scratch
the surface they don't know anything
about what's going on they're highly
toxic their brain is filled with msg
their brain is filled with caffeine
their brain is filled with fragrances
right perfumes colognes and and all
kinds of other different chemicals on
their detergents their fabric softeners
their scented channels are breathing in
all the time right they're incense
they're breathing all the time their
brain is just filled with all this crap
and people don't realize it right one
thing i can tell you right now
right no matter what happens in this
world
you
want your health to be good and if
you're struggling with your health now
that's okay because you can fix it you
can fix it the medical medium cleanses
are critical for healing critical for
fixing things you guys i'm gonna cook a
little millet real quick too right now
so i'm gonna pop some millet in here in
a little bit we're going to talk all
about this i just want to get it cooking
in the moment is what i want to get
doing
so
you guys
you'll see here i got a whole bunch of
cool stuff right i got a little pot
boiling up
you know we got that going i'm gonna pop
a little bit of millet in here
so let's do this now
nice nice you guys ever have millet it's
an option when you don't put fat in
there
okay
so
cleanse the heel
remarkable book it's a medical textbook
it's helping people all around the world
and it's a sanctuary for people
you had all your blood drained out of
you for years
right
you paid thousands and thousands of
dollars in doctor bills and functional
medicine doctor bills and naturopathic
doctor bills right okay
right you search far and wide you're
sick you think you found answers then
you're sick you think you found answers
and you're sick and then finally you
come across a book like this
and if only you had the medical medium
books a long time ago and i heard this
so many times
i wish i found that book five years ago
i wish i found you 20 years ago i wish
i've had the answers all these years i
can't believe i just sat there
struggling and struggling and struggling
with no answers medical medium cleanses
are part of what gets people better
and so right now
i'm just letting you know this is the
book we're doing the medical media
morning cleanse inside this book
so i'm excited we're avoiding radical
fats is what we're doing so keep that in
mind
we're avoiding radical fats till noon
till noon so what's a radical fat let's
go into that right now we got a lot to
cover i'm actually really pumped up
about this
so what's a radical fat
right here you see you guys
don't those sausages look really good
those sausages look really good
okay
radical fats right here so we're live on
tick tock 11 telegram you guys rumble
facebook youtube
so check this out okay
eggs are radical fat
they're high in fat people don't realize
that but they're high in fat
why do you think there was this fear
about eggs years ago where doctors
actually had it right
where if you eat too many eggs you're
basically going to have a heart stopping
effect and you're just going to die of a
heart disease or something like that
well they're still right about well they
don't believe that now because they
don't know what they believe
because you know propaganda just
switches gears every la every minute but
there was a one time where conventional
doctors
they were saying hey you got to worry
about eggs well guess what you still got
to worry about eggs that's a radical fat
and then that sausage right there
radical fat maybe you juice meatless
sausage you guys do meatless sausage
because those are filled with radical
fat too
yeah
they are and then you got the bacon
right you got the pork right there
that's a radical fat
and then you got that lump of butter
right there
till this day
anybody that thinks butter in their
coffee is a good thing
they're just misled
and
whoever propelled that butter in your
coffee thing out there in the world is a
complete and an idiot and has led
people astray in a bad way
a real idiot that did the butter in the
coffee thing
that guy
i think his name is
i think his name i can't remember his
name
anyway the point is is all that does is
lead people to heart surgeries artery
surgeries like with vein surgeries
getting getting valves replaced so you
got to be careful that's a radical fat
right there so then you've got your
pancakes
there could be oil in that batter or
there could be other things in that
batter too so this is just a radical
fat meal right here so i'm just letting
you know that guy uma kelly that guy
so we got
got another radical fat i just want to
give you guys now you're not going to be
eating these foods during this medical
meeting morning cleanse challenge right
let's pretend this is a vegan pizza
let's pretend it's a vegan pizza right
i mean how many people have vegan pizzas
like a lot of people i'm gonna treat
myself
i'm gonna treat myself
okay um
so and i'm gonna have i'm gonna have a
vegan pizza i'm vegan so i'm gonna have
a vegan pizza i'm treating myself right
now
radical fats
absolutely vegan cheese right there
vegan cheese so these are radical fats
i'm trying to let's show you a few more
radical fats and then we're going to
talk about dirty blood that's the next
part so we'll talk about dirty blood
right
so let's get into that a little bit in a
minute so what's a radical fat
that's a radical fat right there
so you guys aren't eating any of this in
the morning because this is the medical
medium warning cleanse challenge you're
keeping the radical fats out of the way
i get it you think a cow's healthy
chocolate right that's healthy chocolate
let's
see what else is going on here here's
some almond butter right there that's a
radical fat right and guess what almond
butter is a healthy fat yeah you got
some coconut oil right coconut butter
coconut oil that's a healthy fat right
there
okay
it is but it's a radical fat and i'm
gonna tell you why this is so important
if you guys are totally on this right
now if you're coming on right now you're
gonna have to watch us from the
beginning please do but just so you know
radical fats stop the body from
cleansing when you eat them before noon
when you eat a radical fat before noon
your body does not cleanse that's it no
cleansing cleansing doesn't happen
whatsoever
what's another healthy fat peanut butter
is a healthy fat i've always said that
i've said that since i was like six
years old
that it's a healthy fat
six years old it's a healthy fat it is
spirit of compassion was saying yeah
that's a healthy fat
it is and guess what when i was six year
old six years old peanut butter wasn't
considered a healthy fat it was
considered a terrible
horrible fat that can kill your heart
did you know that
mainstream medicine believed peanut
butter
would kill you
back
when i was six years old
and at six years old spirit of
compassion would say no tell people it's
healthy but it's a healthy fat but you
don't want the healthy fats before noon
is what i'm trying to say
you don't want to do that here's a
healthy fat right now
in my hand
avocados
avocado toast save it till noon and
after if that's what you're going to eat
is a healthy fat
okay that's important power of
compassion said i used to eat high-fat
breakfast it totally destroyed me
the high-fat breakfast
definitely does some damage to people
especially if they got autoimmune eczema
psoriasis especially if they have lupus
multiple sclerosis any kind of condition
whatsoever including acne anything
vitiligo it's dermatitis
so
what you get when you keep on having
radical fats in the morning
what you get is dirty blood thick dirty
blood that's a healthy fat right there
got some almonds right there i got some
cashews right there that's healthy fat
too
but you get thick dirty blood and your
liver stops cleansing is what happens
when our liver stop cleansing
right
we build up toxins over time more and
more toxins build up and more and more
toxins build up and then one day
you're going along
and now
you wake up one morning
and it's time to call the doctor
and now you're a new patient
a brand new patient
are you a new patient
oh yes ma'am i'm a new patient okay um
what's your information uh my
information is this and this and this
okay the doctor will see you on the 23rd
of this month
what a drag what a drag you get there
and they bleed you to death to begin
with
that's important to know right there
and
friggabor bear
i just saw that
all right well look yeah the liver stops
cleansing
and then we get in trouble and then we
get sick as time goes on rob said the
keto diet wrecked me
rob
the keto diet
killed the people years ago
they changed the keto diet now where it
still will wreck people the keto diet
will still wreck people
but they brought in fruits
they brought in vegetables
they brought in a few greens
they brought these things in right
and so
and and but the keto diet when you're
sick will still wreck and destroy but
people don't know that sure if you've
never been sick before and you go on a
keto diet a new keto diet of the day
which allows a green juice it allows
sugar it allows avocado right you go on
a new type of keto diet of the day right
now which isn't a keto diet but you go
on to the new keto diets you might get
some results you might get a little
weight loss because you got off of
processed foods but if you're really
sick it will just halt your healing and
eventually you go downhill as time goes
on yeah i've seen the keto diet just
wrecked people for years and years and
years your liver
wants a routine
it needs a routine
because your liver's routine is to do a
whole bunch of cleansing and clean up
and clean up the garbage and package up
the guards should be dumped out in the
morning your liver wants to dump out the
garbage in the morning do you guys got
the cleanse of heel book because we're
in the medical meeting morning cleanse
challenge you got to get a book someday
if you don't have it now get it for the
future so you can do the cleanse
yourself or be ready for our next
cleanse right this cleanse is free by
the way
go to library and get the book for free
so this is the cleanse the heel
challenge morning cleanse challenge so
we'll talk about the liver a little bit
here all through the night you guys
all through the night
right
it isn't santa claus that's just flying
around on his
on his sled
it's not just santa claus working in the
middle of the night
okay to deliver toys
and the reindeer it's your liver
it's working every single night not just
one night a year like santa claus right
it works every single night
that's what it does and it's packaging
up
instead of all kinds of toys and
presents it's packing packaging up
toxic heavy metals fragrances perfumes
colognes
fabric softeners right detergent
chemicals
um insecticides herbicides fungicides
fire retardant okay
formaldehyde ammonia
right it's packaging up and that's just
to name a few pharmaceuticals who is on
pharmaceuticals a lot of people are in
pharmaceuticals now they're on their
antidepressants they're on anti-anxiety
meds right they're on all these
different pharmaceuticals that they were
on antibiotics last month they caught
the you know thing going around
and then boom they're on an antibiotic
doctor says here's an antibiotic and all
that stuff builds up and said the liver
but if you're not doing something to
cleanse it out to get rid of it if
you're not doing something to move it
out of your system then what are you
doing
what are you doing right now we're live
you guys on tick tock we're live on
rumble we're we're live on youtube live
on facebook live on telegram you guys in
tik tok we're doing the medical media
morning clench challenge hang out and
watch just you can learn something to
really protect your health and get
yourself better what you see right here
is a whole bunch of cool stuff i got
cilantro right here i'm going to make
the heavy metal detox smoothie so
everybody keep in mind that's what i'm
going to do i'm going to do some lemon
water too which is really incredible so
i'm going to make some fresh lemon water
we're going to talk about what to do i
got celery too i might run some celery
through a machine i got a papaya the
whole bit so i'm giving everybody the
rundown and we're talking about the
liver
so we want to get rid of thick dirty
blood so the first part of the medical
medium warning cleanse right is you get
your lemon
don't do it in hot water you guys on
tick tock you guys on youtube
don't do it in hot water yes you can
have a cup of hot tea and put lemon in
it there's nothing wrong with that but
if you want to flush
if you want to liver flush
you guys can't
kill the lemon
you can't put the lemon in scalding hot
water
and kill it
so it doesn't flush your liver in the
morning
so keep this in mind this is a critical
piece of information right there because
you'll see it every day
i put my lemon in hot water in the
morning because my ayurvedic
doctor said so i put my lemon in hot
water in the morning because my
nutritionist said so
that's great that's cute that's that's
great but guess what you just stopped
flushing the liver
it has to be in lukewarm water room
temperature water or cold water
it can't be in hot water so that is so
important to know all on its own right
i'm gonna tell you guys right now so
what you do is you take your cup right
here and you get some water
you get your 16 to 32 ounces of water
right
you get your lemon
right here
and you squeeze your lemon into it just
like this
i want to show you guys on tick tock i
want to show you guys on youtube
facebook rumble
check this out
idolina says can i use limes if i don't
have lemons absolutely and i'm going to
get a lime right now it's right here
so
i got a lime i want to give you a lime
tip you guys very important
if the lime is green you can still use
it but it's not ripe but you can still
use it
you want the limes that have some color
to them the color changed so that's a
lime
you know tip right there okay
when you let the lime ripen or you find
that lime that's more ripe you'll get
more juice out of it so i'm going to
squeeze a little lime in here i know i
mixed it and if you want to mix it you
could too
but i'm just putting showing you with a
little bit of lime in there as well
so the first thing is 16 to 32 ounces of
lemon water or lime water first thing in
the morning
and you start out your day you start
flushing the liver
that's your credit card right there
there it is
so
what you can do is you can pay the bank
by flushing that liver out you're
building your liver reserves back up
right there that's what you're doing
you're building it back up
important to understand you want to be
able to flush your liver out every
morning
if you guys
take one thing from here from the
medical media and the medical media
morning cleanse challenge one thing
guys are busy you've got a lot going on
you just take one thing
do the lemon water but 16 to 32 ounces
not eight ounces
and not in hot water you do 16 to 32
ounces on an empty stomach first thing
in the morning before your coffee and
i'm not recommending you drink coffee
i wouldn't
but if you do and that's what you're
gonna do when i can't stop you if you're
gonna have your coffee
if you're gonna drink whatever
if you're gonna have your tea your black
tea if you're gonna have your caffeine
in the morning
do the lemon water
before you poison yourself and your
liver remember that
do the lemon water 16 to 32 ounces to
flush out your liver before you shut
your liver down with caffeine and
adrenaline
keep that in mind right there
okay
and you can
you know you can take the caffeine out
in the morning that's a troublemaker you
can take out which is really great
but keep that in mind
flush the liver
before you poison it
really important and i talk about that
in the medical medium cleanse the heel
book so i mean look i can't stop anybody
from drinking their caffeine and this
isn't an anti-caffeine
you know
talk today
but i'm saying the details are in here
if you are going to drink the coffee
which people do every single day
then do that coffee
after you've flushed out that liver
important tory sue says could i juice my
lemons and freeze the juice in ice trays
so as to store them up if you have to
absolutely then put a cube in a glass to
dissolve it in the am uh yes you can
is it ideal
no but it's still doable that's doable
that's better than putting that lemon in
the hot water so i want to answer more
questions to you guys i want to be
really helpful i want to tell you how to
do this cleanse
this free cleanse
free okay
john morris hey
i don't think coffee is bad as long as
you don't add a lot of sweetener but i
agree you should flush the liver first
because the first thing you consume is
what your body takes in the most of well
first of all thanks for agreeing with
that flushing the liver first is great
i'm glad you don't think coffee is not
bad you know that's that's that's fine
i'm glad the caffeine companies taught
you that and i'm glad the caffeine
propaganda and the caffeine industry
taught you that too the coffee's not bad
and but i'm just going to tell you right
now
okay sure john john morris right i
respect what you say of course right
you're a guy but women's health suffers
from caffeine
women's health suffers greatly from
caffeine
i'm just going to let you know right now
women have to
birth children
and it takes adrenal strength to do that
a difficult birth
can happen for women because they toast
out their adrenals from all that
caffeine
so that's one thing important another
thing too
women are being thrown on these
intermittent fasting diets
and they run on caffeine and adrenaline
all day and eventually by the time
they're 40 they're burnt out they're
fried they can't think they got brain
frog
their adrenals are totally toasted
and
and what happens is they've also gone
through maybe one or two really
difficult births
and maybe you've even had c-sections
because of it the adrenals get burnt and
fried out
pain tolerance goes you know down really
fast and caffeine causes a lot of this
another thing that happens with women
too is your skin gets all choppy they
get all the they get all of the brown
spots all over their face that happens
all over their skin that's from caffeine
so
john i get it you think caffeine's fine
and
as a guy sure can drink the caffeine but
for women's health it's actually
terrible the caffeine industry knows
this behind the scenes
and their mantra is get pregnant women
on caffeine
so that their babies will be caffeine
addicts when they're born
and get pregnant women on caffeine so
their breast milk is filled with
caffeine so their babies are caffeine
addicts when they're breastfeeding and
this what this does is it ensures the
caffeine industry banks and banks and
banks and banks
and never stops banking
all right
enough on the caffeine talk as we go
right here
wait 15 to 30 minutes you guys and then
we go into some celery juice so we get
that celery juice going after 15 or 30
minutes if you guys see here i got some
millet cooking i got some oatmeal if you
hang around we're gonna make some
oatmeal we're talking about staying away
from radical fats if you guys just came
into the party late watch this from the
beginning on one of the one of the
platforms right there we're doing the
medical medium morning cleanse challenge
right here it's right in cleanse the
heel
just so you know
it's writing cleanse to heal the medical
media morning cleanse challenge this is
a medical textbook it already has a
track record of saving lives around the
planet it's an incredible book it's
highly detailed over 200 symptoms
conditions you might want to get one if
you get a chance go to library get it
for free either way
someone said hey you sound like an
infomercial that's funny i don't
advertise on youtube if you guys notice
my youtube has no advertisements and you
guys notice either do my podcast
episodes
so here we are let's go into and the
book is for free
so go to the library and get the book
for free
so i know every now and people say well
he's trying to sell his book get the
book for free
and save a life save a friend's life let
somebody know about it tell your friend
the good library and get the book for
free and the cleanse is free that's
important because i know people come on
here and they're like whoa wait a minute
there's a cleanse where do we have to
pay you don't have to we're doing it
we're doing the medical medium cleanse
challenge let's get into it so after
your celery juice 16 to 32 ounces
okay we move into
our the lemon water we move into the
celery juice next so that's the next
phase of it so we run some celery
through here's what we do okay
so
if you guys don't have a juicer use a
blender that's okay if you don't have a
juicer use a blender and that's what you
do
there's ways of doing things that are
different if you need to
if you have an old blender take your
celery chop it up throw it into the
blender that's perfectly fine you can do
it
right
[Music]
so we're going to do
is i'm going to run some celery through
here
now if you're somebody that's sensitive
okay
somebody that's sensitive
you can do less four ounces two ounces
if you're somebody that's sensitive do
less celery juice
all right
and that's perfectly fine if you're
somebody that's sensitive in this
situation where your blood is thick and
dirty you've never cleansed before
you're eating radical fats all the time
you're highly toxic
you've got pathogens but don't even know
it you got streptococcus in your
intestinal tract you don't even know it
right
and you got symptoms conditions you have
no idea what they're from
they're from pathogens and toxins
so if you're somebody that's highly
toxic and you're doing the medical
medium morning cleanse you don't have to
do 16 to 32 ounces of celery juice you
can start out with four ounces you can
start out with eight ounces
keep in mind you haven't had radical
fats yet kathleen has a question can you
use powdered celery juice no you cannot
i can't tell you what to do you have
your own free well you can do whatever
you want right of course
my recommendation is don't do it it
won't fix you it doesn't have the
ability to fix anybody it doesn't have
that healing ability it's dehydrated
it's lost what it needs to help heal
someone and clean somebody up keep that
in mind if you guys just came on here
we're doing the medical medium morning
cleanse challenge we're heading into the
section of juicing celery you can do
four ounces six ounces 8 ounces whatever
you would like you don't have to do 16
to 32 ounces i prefer 32 ounces that
would be fantastic
okay
so
the reason why some people get benefits
from intermittent fasting is because
they remove fats in the morning but they
don't know that's why
they actually don't know why
they're getting some type of result
it's because they're moving fats out of
their morning regime they're keeping the
fats out
and that's why
okay so it's important to know
but the problem with intermittent
fasting is you will burn your adrenals
out
with intermittent fasting because you
have to get trace mineral salts and you
have to get sugar in your bloodstream
if anybody's anti-sugar like
anti-glucose
then you're they're illey misinformed
because
what happens is if you don't get glucose
to your brain in the morning
you're starving your brain of what it
needs glucose is why we function
so the critical aspect of intermittent
fasting the critical aspect of it
working to some degree is you keep fats
out but you have to have something in
there
that actually feeds your brain
to keep that in mind
so when you remove
sugar from your morning you don't need a
piece of fruit you don't have lemon
water okay when you remove sugar from
your breakfast in the morning and you
just
intermittent fast you're you're now
running on adrenaline and caffeine if
you're somebody that's intermittent
fasting on caffeine right these are ways
that age you faster and they don't help
you cleanse
so right now we're making some celery
juice
if you're somebody that's doing the
medical medium morning cleanse challenge
and you had your celery juice already in
the morning hang on we're still going to
do some other stuff so this is going to
be fun okay
so right now i'm running some juice i'm
already past 8 10 ounces easy i'm
probably going into like 16 ounces easy
i'm going to go a little bit more too so
we'll run some more
this is the omega for the people asking
about the juicer right now the juicer
sale ends i think tomorrow this is the
omega
mm
900 hds so one that saves money you see
this right here this is coming out dry
just so you know you guys
i'm just showing you guys on tick tock
can you see that right there on the
screen
so that's coming out dry right
the reason why this pulp is dryer it's
this machine
and so you're saving money so you're
you're getting a lot more juice right
there just so you know
i've endorsed this this this company and
machine
i've endorsed them because of what they
what they offer with this because this
is insane really is it just is
so i'm going to run one more stick
through here
susie newton says
can i do celery juice first then lemon
water yes
yes you can you can flip it
go backwards
go backwards in a good way
i'm actually fine with that are you
kidding if i can keep you off the fax
until noon and you just want to switch
you just want to switch that off like
boom silvery juice and
and lemon water definitely let's do it
[Laughter]
all right
we got some celery juice going right now
i'm excited about this okay
so just letting you know before i put
the machine away over here
i think it's another day with the sale
at omegajuicers.com it's the mm900 hds
just letting you guys know it's the one
that saves people money
is what it is
which is incredible
so you've got to strain your celery
juice you guys on tick tock if you're
ever going to do celery juice to get the
maximum benefits out of this herbal
extraction you have to strain it keep
that in mind
you want it pure liquid that's where the
gold is at
you guys on rumble that's where the gold
is at right there okay
there you go
somebody asked me on tick tock just now
what do adrenals do
what do they do
if you're talking that's because of
adrenaline
if you're walking that's from adrenaline
right
anything you do did you take a shower
this morning
that's from your adrenals your adrenals
gave you that
blessing that's why people that they
lose their adrenals they can't get up
they can't shower
okay
adrenals do all of that for you right
that's what they do okay they make it so
you can exercise
they make it so you can play
they make it so you can partake in
things that aren't good for you like
alcohol and caffeine and all kinds of
stuff which is terrible for you but your
adrenals allow you to survive through
all that and partake in anything okay so
adrenals do everything for you we have
to protect them we can't burn them out
the medical medium warning funds
challenge
protects your adrenals right there a big
protector of your adrenals these two
little things you see right here
okay
these are your adrenal glands they're on
top of your kidneys
celery juice is a big part of getting
them strong and bringing them back
so you got your celery juice right there
16 to 32 ounces
okay
is a big deal
right there
by the way that's the pulp in my hand
just so you know
i can put it into a tiny little pulp
ball
i don't know if your juicers do that
where it's dry like that you can put it
in a little but yeah that's that's why i
like the mm-900 hcs i could just like
talk look at that like just toss that
out
all right
what happens is your adrenals are there
for fight or flight they're there when
you have a broken relationship they're
there when
your boyfriend breaks up with you
they're there for when you go through
divorce they're there when your
girlfriend breaks up with you they're
there for when you're in a car accident
they're there when someone texts you and
they just start texting you like you
know some mad texts because you know
they're upset about something a family
member or a friend and it gets you
jazzed up and now you're shaking like
did they really say that did my friend
really say that my friend doesn't
understand me my family member doesn't
understand me that's your adrenals right
there and your body's shaking right
they're there for you when you're
running from a bad person they're there
for you before you when you're walking
down the street in a city and someone
pulls the side of you and says get in
the car you're like are you crazy no way
and your adrenals are there for you to
get you running and moving you know and
so your adrenals do everything right
but we have to protect them bottomland
and we abuse them that's the bottom line
we abuse our adrenals so there we go
we abuse them because we do a lot of
caffeine we don't eat that's one way
that's one way of use them but here's
the thing okay medical media morning
cleanse challenge you just did your
lemon water now we just did celery juice
i'll bring it out for now okay we'll do
that right you got your celery juice you
got your lemon water right here
here we are and now
you're free
to still eat if you want but don't have
the fats
a lot of new people came on already let
me give you the rundown
don't do your almond butter before noon
don't do your peanut butter before noon
you're not gonna cleanse
it's just not don't do your tahini
before noon okay
all right don't do
chocolate before noon i'd prefer you
didn't do chocolate at all but i know i
can't stop people from eating chocolate
don't do it before noon
that's important right there
don't do other things before noon too
don't have eggs before noon i prefer you
didn't have eggs at all but don't have
them before noon no eggs before noon
okay
keep that in mind that's important
don't have sausage bacon ham turkey
don't have chicken before noon
don't have fish before noon don't have
eggs before noon i already said that
don't have butter before noon
all right so keep that in mind all of
that matters right there
don't have pizza before noon you're
doing a cleanse you guys have to know
something it's really important your
liver won't cleanse
if you're doing radical fats
before noon
keep that in mind
you want to give your liver some
cleansing time it has a routine the
routine is it's packaging up the junk
and garbage in the early
morning hours
and it needs help to get rid of all the
poison
so you have to make sure you keep the
radical fats all the fats that i'm
showing you right here you got to keep
them out of your diet in the morning
before noon so your liver
can get rid of
all the junk and garbage
critical information you guys for
healing
power of compassion says don't have
scrambled eggs don't have scrambled eggs
before noon
very important very very important this
is information that's critical you guys
all right
so
you can see all the different options
there's so many recipes you could have
before noon
during cleanse the heel if you don't
have the book you guys on tik tok you
can go to the library get it for free
this is a free cleanse right now we're
doing medical meeting morning cleanse
challenge right now okay you can also
get it on amazon 51 off let's make the
heavy metal detox smoothie which is in
the book now we're going for the gold is
what we're doing
we're doing it now
okay so let me put these radical fats
away over here for a second if you guys
don't mind and we're about to make the
heavy metal detox smoothie a famous
smoothie actually that's famous around
the world now the medical medium one is
famous around the world for getting
metals out of people and bringing
people's lives back and that's what
we're doing next right here all right
so i got a blender with me right here
i'm gonna bring this over
so this way you guys on tick tock can
see this too
we're making
the heavy metal
detox smoothie
this smoothie has a history
of turning lives around
it already has a long standing history
so this is important to know for anybody
new here this is not like some cute
little smoothie idea that might help
somebody or not but nobody really knows
we're talking life-changing results
life-saving results that have happened
for so many people they swear by this
around the world it's even famous
because of it the whole bit okay
something to know if you don't know
anything about me you're wondering like
who is this guy is he a hack or whatever
my number one new york times
best-selling author but it's not just
that i'm the number one
health author best-selling health author
almost seven years running now in the
world globally medical medium protocols
medical medium tools all of it whether
anybody likes me or not or likes my face
or likes my personality or whatever it
is still number one forget saving lives
and turning people's lives around and
medical medium science
is always stolen by science so medical
medium science is always taken by
science
out there so just keep that in mind if
you want to know anything about me
let's make the smoothie let's see what
we need
let's get some bananas in here
two bananas right there so i got them
right here
okay here we are
two bananas so think about this you had
your lemon water you flushed out your
liver you're still flushing your liver
because you didn't drop in radical fats
so now we're putting some banana in here
yeah how incredible is that we're
putting some banana in here now amazing
okay we're gonna do two bananas is what
we're gonna do so that's the plan
two bananas okay so we're gonna do
another banana
you guys
exciting
now the banana is helpful
the banana is definitely helpful but
we're going to put a lot of things in
here that are really helpful this is
what we're going to do
we're going to put the magic
ingredients in here that make the heavy
metal detox movie that's the next part
so let's go into it
wild blueberries these are frozen wild
blueberries right here
wild blueberries
so that goes into the heavy metal detox
smoothie right here okay
two cups of frozen
wild blueberries watch those babies go
in right
okay
amazing
incredible
so that's that's that's already set up
there
one cup of cilantro
let's get one cup of cilantro in there
critical to go in here now the reason
why this works
is because
of the blend of what's going in here
keep that in mind
the blueberry doesn't remove toxic heavy
metals
but the wild blueberry does
that's
right there
the secret ingredient one of them now
we're gonna do the cilantro that's in
there another ingredient
incredible
now we're gonna do two other secret
ingredients right
we're gonna do the spirulina okay
that's the one i trust i'm not sponsored
okay and i don't own the company
but that's the spirulina okay so that's
the vimergy visa and victor i m as in
mary ergy dot com if you want to know
about that one right there and that's
the best one on the market
when you use a high quality product like
this it takes
the removal of metals to an entirely
different level and that's what i love
about it so you put a teaspoon of that
spirulina in there
remember
if you did your your lemon water
you did your celery juice
and now you're getting the heavy metal
detox smoothie in you
you have to realize how much you're
really cleansing and detoxing into what
degree into what level
it's it's actually incredible what's
happening
in your body
you're getting rid of what needs to go
okay
all right now here we go right here
barley grass juice powder so that's the
beverage barley grass juice powder right
there you don't want barley grass
you have to have barley grass juice
powder
okay
keep that in mind people who don't like
the taste of cilantro are high in metals
they're high in metals
the heavy metal detox smoothie doesn't
just get rid of metals it gets rid of
chemicals it gets rid of insecticides
pesticides fungicides it gets rid of
gasoline you're breathing in it gets rid
of a lot of things right
so we're going to get some dulse right
now and i got the liquid dulce i'm using
for this one so that's the memorgy
liquid dulce right there okay
kelp is not gonna get the metals out
important to know
iris seamoth cmos is not gonna get
the metals out
okay i still like it
i still like help i still like other
things too it's not going to get the
metals out so the dolls is the one that
gets the middle up carla henry says can
you do the metal detox if you have metal
in your mouth yes you can
people do it all the time absolutely
sets of energy dolls right there
visa victor i am ergy dot com i'm not
sponsored it's just incredible stuff we
got the dolls in there so we're building
these things up now i'm gonna put a
little bit of wild blueberry juice now i
do work with wyman's
okay
i do do work with them
i endorse this product 100
and i do work with them because what
they do
is they take the wild blueberry out of
the field
they harvest it out of the field right
which is a process all on its own that's
unbelievable because it's really hard to
do
and what they do is
they press it
okay so what this is right here is a
wild blueberry juice
okay that's pressed i never want this
stuff to disappear in the world
because
it it's an unbelievable process to even
make it happen and the antioxidant
levels off the chart so what i do is i
put a little bit of that too so i have
not only have the the blueberries in
there frozen wild blueberries in there
but i put that in there too so that's
something i do that's the wyman's right
there okay
shop.wymans.com can find it there so
what you see in here
is the cilantro the wild blueberries
you see the spirulina the barley grass
and the dolls now we're gonna cut an
orange okay
we're gonna do that we're gonna cut this
orange and we're gonna squeeze it into a
smoothie now if you want you can put a
little coconut water in there if you
really want you can put a little bit of
water in there too i like to squeeze
orange because that's part of the recipe
of getting orange in there which is
important right
be open-hearted good to see you i know
you leave comments on youtube
every now and then you're going to make
the heavy metal detox movie right now
incredible
so i'm going to squeeze some orange in
here and we're about to rev this baby up
and then we're gonna go into some other
options and talk about some other stuff
with cleansing
today which i'm excited about right
now
you can put one orange in there i like
to throw two oranges in there i love
oranges so let's do that
i'm gonna squeeze two oranges in my
smoothie right here
if you guys just got on here it's the
medical medium morning cleanse challenge
please watch it from the beginning we're
live right now but watch it from the
beginning when you get a chance so many
good important pieces of information for
your body your health
critical pieces of information
for real you know heavy metal detox
movie is one option for breakfast you
don't have to have this one in the
medical medium morning cleanse you don't
have to do this
you can do
oatmeal which i'm going to make in a
minute you can do millet which i'm going
to make in the end and the details are
in the book right here
so check out cleanse the heel when you
can get it free at the library or
amazon.com us 51 off let's blend it up
i think i got everything in there
so we're going to turn this baby on
and we're gonna start it
[Music]
all right you guys i'm blending up the
heavy metal detox movie as we are
we're live on rumble live on youtube
live on facebook live on tick tock live
on telegram probably live on something
else
yeah
plus you've got the angels watching you
right you guys know the answers are
always watching you
all right blending it up
[Music]
all right
we did it
okay you guys
we got the smoothie right here let's get
it into a jar
so we're going to pour it right here if
you guys can see
you don't have to have the heavy metal
detox smoothie in the morning
you can do the you can do the medical
medium morning cleanse challenge without
it you can have oatmeal for god's sake
if you're still hungry after your celery
juice and your lemon water you can have
other things too you can have an orange
you can have fruit you could have a
banana you can have melon you can have
apples
you can just have apples how about that
you just do that if you want
if you're somebody that's used to some
big old breakfast
if you're somebody used to some big old
breakfast okay like big time
then let's do some steamed potatoes
right here
let's do steamed potatoes these are nice
and warm right out of the steamer right
here okay
so we can do steamed potatoes in the
morning
how about that
how incredible is that
steamed potatoes so listen we're making
millet right now i got the pot on let's
take a look and see what we have that's
a heavy metal detox smoothie right there
that's your celery juice right there
just think
about what you're doing for your body
think about
cleansing toxins that have been inside
of you from years past
think about
being
disease
symptom condition free down the road
envision your future
of being free from your fibro
free from your sibo
free from your celiac
free from your colitis free from your
ibs free from your eczema free from your
psoriasis free from your lupus free from
your neurological line free from your
r.a envision yourself free
from your anxiety
from your depression
envision yourself free from it down the
road
because you're accessing the tools
to get to that point
think about that
right
every single day you guys should see
that
what's the future
doesn't matter what is on your plate
right now what is the future your future
you're gonna get rid of these conditions
you're going to get rid of the eye
floaters you're going to get rid of the
tingles numbness so you're going to get
rid of the tinnitus you're going to get
rid of the vertigo you're going to get
rid of it all
you got to think about that because
that's your future
and it's not just going to happen
because you're thinking about it
you're accessing that future it's going
to happen because you're going to apply
the tools and you're going to make it
happen you're going to make it happen
let's talk about millet right here
okay
so we're making some different recipes
by the way for everybody right now we're
doing this again tomorrow but we're
making different recipes tomorrow so
we're doing this free medical meeting
morning cleanse challenge the same time
we're doing it tomorrow and we're going
to do it all over but we're actually
going to do different recipes
so i'm really pumped up about that big
time letting you know right there so
what i have right here and what i just
cooked
why you guys were here with me is millet
how exciting is that
i just cooked some millet
so
this is an incredible
warm
fluffy food right here
okay so let's get a bowl and we'll get
it in there
there's a nice bowl right here look at
this
so i'm gonna get this warm hot fluffy
look at that millet in here
millet is a better option than oatmeal
it really is
what you don't do is you don't put the
butter in here
don't put avocado in here
you can put avocado in here just don't
do it till afternoon
till afternoon
keep it
fat free in the morning let me show you
what you can put in here and it won't
break your cleanse
how crazy is this this isn't going to
break your cleanse right here by having
millet and
let's just put a little bit more millet
in here
put the rest of it in here this is great
there we go
so delicious
this is uh steaming hot right now you
guys
piping hot okay
so i got this gorgeous millet right here
so we're gonna put
some wild blueberries on your millet in
the morning you can do that to your
oatmeal too
right look at this
if you want to put more you can put more
you want to put less you can be you just
do you with this okay
check this out
ready now i'm going to put either one or
two options you could do this i could
put maple syrup on it i can put honey on
this
right
we got maple syrup right here
put a little maple syrup on here guess
what
you're still cleansing
i just put maple syrup on here you can
put honey on here too if you want
but i just put maple syrup on there
wild blueberries they're frozen wild
blueberries
i have them on top of that hot steamy
millet
gluten free
i put a little bit of maple syrup on top
and that's allowed in the medical medium
morning cleanse challenge
fats are what stops you
from cleansing in the morning keep that
in mind fats also block
the sugar from entering your cells and
you get insulin resistance in the
morning everybody gets insulin
resistance in the morning
because they're on so many fats
and they end up getting sugar in them at
the same time mixing it so let's get
some oatmeal going so here we go we got
the pan ready
the pot ready right here let's get a
little bit of oatmeal in here
so this is exciting okay
can you add oil free oat milk i wouldn't
because i don't think it's fat free oat
milk oat milk gets pretty high in fat so
you're pushing it on that one it's so
concentrated that oatmeal so that
oatmeal gets pretty high in fat keep
that in mind right so i'm gonna pop some
oatmeal in here that oh milk
does
oatmeal doesn't
oatmeal is not high in fat okay
it's not high in fat it's not an overt
fat but when you concentrate that oat
milk it almost crosses it does it
crosses the line kind of into overt fat
world is what it does
and then over fat is it the radical fat
world right and that's going to stop you
from doing what you need to do so let's
get some water in here
right
and i'll put a little bit more water in
there we're cooking this right now
you guys if you just got on here this is
the medical medium morning cleanse
challenge
there we go
i got some oatmeal on right here if you
guys want to see i don't know if you can
see this right there see this on tick
tock you get a better view or so you
guys get a better view on telegram too
why does oak meal hurt my stomach makes
me bloated i get dizzy eating it too
here's how it works oatmeal is not a
healing food
so
stephanie doyle oatmeal is not a healing
food
but it's not a food that feeds viruses
and pathogens but if you've got other
stuff going on other sensitivities and
other things going on it might not be
the best option for you something else
could be the best option for you see
it whether it's millet becomes a better
option whether it's steamed potatoes
becomes a better option for you you see
so steamed potatoes could actually be a
good option right there for you keep
that in mind it could be just bananas
too also what do you put in your oatmeal
that could be actually making you
bloated getting you dizzy and hurting
your stomach so keep in mind be your own
detective
what are you putting in your oatmeal
it's like hey what am i putting in the
oatmeal here um well
am i putting uh i'm putting things in my
oatmeal here
like am i putting this in my oatmeal
right here
so let me see i just got to find a teeth
really quick hold on you guys
hold on i just gotta find it's heat
right here and i'm just getting some in
the in the oatmeal so if you're getting
dairy in your oatmeal
or butter and your oatmeal
that actually i think i got enough right
there i think that was good i think i
got to put
you guys
it depends on what you're putting in
there you're putting peanut butter in
there you're putting dairy in there
dairy can be a problem right there in
your oatmeal right
and i got the oatmeal cooking right here
that could be a problem
and so keep in mind it's what are you
putting in there peanut butter
that could be a problem that could be
giving you a bellyache the peanut butter
and the oatmeal what else is going in
there is it just oatmeal by itself only
maria says mushka says can you show the
book again please
i will gladly show the book get it free
at the library if you want or amazon.com
us 51 off it costs more to print it for
the price you're selling on amazon
that's incredible for this book they got
a crazy sale on this book right here
and so it's 16.99 200 symptoms
conditions protocols supplements dosages
it's got multiple cleanses in here but
it's it's more than that
it's got a track record of saving lives
turning people's lives around
getting them out of the fire
like literally people rising out of the
ashes because of this book around the
world
millions of copies sold
that book
is one of the big books out there that's
saving lives so actually it's the only
book that's saving lives out of books
where people
boom they do the mono cleanse and they
get out of their colitis
they don't have to get their colon
removed like we're talking about that
kind of life-saving stuff incredible
right there go to medicalmedium.com sign
up to the newsletter so you actually
learn about what's happening what we're
doing okay
please share your stories on your
morning cleanse too
uh if you can get a chance hashtag
medical medium right tag at medical
medium when you get a chance so i can
see you you have to hashtag and text so
you have to hashtag and tag
medicalmedium both so i can see your
story so i can post them on instagram
post the stories on instagram so just so
you guys know
so which is really cool and i can share
your post as well so just letting you
know there right so i got some oatmeal
cooking oatmeal cooks fast if it's not
like just steel cut or something so it
cooks really quick this is an instant
oatmeal right here so it's instantly
done
but i'm just letting it kind of
get nice it's kind of absorb and get
nice and good
so lana says what can you put on a
steamed potato
right
you can put spices on a steamed potato
you can do that that's one thing you can
put lemon on a steamed potato which
really makes it pop
that's alright too okay
so you can do cayenne if you're into
cayenne right i'll put cayenne pepper on
a steamed potato
right you can make a potato veggie
skillet you can take all these
vegetables chop them up asparagus
whatever you want right
asparagus broccoli cauliflower and you
can just like stir fry those steamed
potatoes in with that make yourself a
potato skillet you can make your you can
marinara sauce
you can do you can do a sauce
like a tomato sauce or a salsa and have
it with your potato
oh god
it's endless actually
it's endless so i got the oatmeal
cooking right here we're just about done
it's getting nice and good
if you guys just got on here we're
working through the medical medium
morning cleanse challenge
right
you can make a medical medium nacho
cheese sauce that's gluten and dairy
free which is incredible for your health
so why are we doing the medical medium
warning cleanse
what's the point
what's the purpose
so that's something to keep in mind like
why do we need to be doing it what's the
point why do we have to do it
and you can do so much with steamed
potato you can make potato waffles you
can put maple syrup on it you can do it
all right if you if you follow medical
medium information and recipes you can
see we can do everything with a potato
so the goal you guys
is not to bombard
your
liver and organs with fat in the morning
you want to be
fat free is what you want i got the
oatmeal just heating up and cooking
right there you want to be fat free in
the morning keep that in mind that's a
big way to cleanse
if you have fats in the morning you
can't cleanse so nothing cleanses just
keep that in mind you want to stay
hydrated in the morning so what happens
is when you do your lemon water first
thing in the morning 16 to 32 ounces and
then you wait 15 to 30 minutes you do
your celery juice 16 to 32 ounces of
celery juice right and then you have
your heavy metal detox smoothie
if you want if that's one option or you
don't need anything and you just want
you know an orange or something right
that's something whatever it is
you're allowing yourself to cleanse
is what's happening you can drink
coconut water sometime in the morning
which would be really smart 16 extra
ounces of coconut water 16x extra ounces
of water
those are important too you want to make
sure you're hydrated all morning so
you're finishing your cleanse
the morning cleanse is about taking out
the trash that was built up and and if
you do the morning cleanse more than two
days because we're doing it for two days
right now
on this free cleanse if you do it more
than two days
you're taking trash out
is what you're doing
from previous months
previous years
now we're going into a deeper cleanse
that's what you do okay the oatmeal's
done
let's get moving
i'm gonna put the oatmeal in this nice
bowl right here
what about quinoa is that okay quinoa
is okay but you'll there's a reason why
you don't see quinoa here and i'll tell
you right now just give me a second here
we're gonna
put this oatmeal this hot steamy oatmeal
right here
there we go
nice
got the oatmeal right there you can put
the wild blueberries right on this
oatmeal too
so you got your steamed oatmeal right
there it's really hot
let's put some wild blueberries on there
so frozen wild blueberries
you can put a lot of them on there you
can put a few of them on there that's
okay
this is so good right here
wow
incredible
can you imagine and you're cleansing
right there you can put maple syrup on
there you can put honey on there
so i'm gonna put a little bit of honey
on this one if you guys are okay with
that
okay so we'll pop a little honey on here
you can put banana in here too
so i'm gonna do that i'm gonna chop up a
little banana put a little honey
drizzled over there okay how good is
that
seriously
let's get a banana
that would be awesome too chop up a
little bit of banana in there too
right
so
some nice banana slices in here too
you guys
look at that right there
incredible
so what you have right there
is a radical fat free meal allowing your
liver intestinal tract other organs to
cleanse
it even allows your brain to cleanse
people get all that brain fog they have
so many toxins built up in there and
when you do the medical meeting morning
cleanse because we're doing the
challenge
that's something you can have you guys
there's no nut butters in here
that stops your cleanse
there's no oat milk in here there's no
almond milk in here that stops your
cleanse there's no peanut butter in here
that stops your cleanse
so right there boom you can have that
late morning if you want or some time
after you had your celery juice your
lemon water your celery juice and your
smoothie or no smoothie just celery
juice and lemon water and that's what
you decide to have right there
incredible
you got your millet too that's an option
with maple syrup on it
you guys it doesn't stop here you can
have sweet potato if that's something
you really like it's freezing cold on
half the planet right now
you know so it's freezing cold right
so if you're somebody that's like you
need something warm that's what this is
the oatmeal the millet steamed potato
steamed sweet potato winter squash is an
option right there too
so you can do butternut squash
right you can do even spaghetti squash
if you want but butternut squash they're
in the stores right now that's a kabocha
squash
these are all helpful so let's talk
about quinoa the question was can i do
quinoa
the reason why quinoa is not a highly
recommended medical medium food
is because it's scratchy
it's scratchy
so many people come to medical medium
information
[Music]
to be
taken away from pain to come out and
rise above their illness and symptom and
condition
quinoa is not a guarantee
that's going to happen for somebody with
intestinal tract disorders
it's scratchy
people have diverticulitis
diverticulosis right
it's a different scratchy it's not like
when you have some lettuce and you have
diverticulitis that's good for
diverticulitis right
it's not like that it's a different kind
of abrasive scratch quinoa causes so
when you have crohn's colitis ibs other
intestinal tract disorders gastroparesis
other problems in the intestinal tract
inflammation in the intestinal tract
quinoa is not the best bet
yeah i like quinoa it's not the best bet
though for somebody with all kinds of
other conditions
that's why it's not recommended very
important to know cold white spring good
to see you may good to see you yeah it's
because it's scratchy
so
so and people don't realize this so you
have somebody and they got all these
kinds of issues they got celiac they got
sibo they got all these other conditions
and they're still having problems and
they don't know what the problem is
they're just like oh my god i just went
to the bathroom i don't know what's
going on here and they don't realize it
but the quinoa is causing an aggravated
issue inside it's not it's not that
quinoa feeds bugs it doesn't quinoa
doesn't feed pathogens it doesn't feed
epstein-barr it doesn't feed it doesn't
feed streptococcus all the medical
medium information about epsine bar and
all those other different pathogens
right it doesn't feed those
right oatmeal doesn't feed pathogens
millet doesn't feed pathogens but what
you have to understand is the quinoa has
a scratch to it then that scratchiness
because quinoa doesn't break down
and it goes through you like sandpaper
and that's why it's not recommended but
but but yet
i've said you can eat it sure and it's
something that's still
okay
but it's not top dog
it's not top dog really important though
okay
you can read the books for details like
cleanse the heal this is day one of the
medical medium morning cleanse challenge
we're doing day two of the medical media
morning cleanse challenge tomorrow just
letting you guys know there's there's we
have autoimmune right here in this book
of how to overcome it anxiety depression
eczema psoriasis
reproductive system problems fibroids
endometriosis right acne okay all kinds
over 200 symptoms conditions protocols
check out the book when you get a chance
if you can't afford the 16 because it's
on sale on amazon right now go to the
library and get it for free i don't care
i just want you to have it i want you to
be able to heal all right
what does the medical medium warning
cleanse do
it rids
toxins that feed
pathogens
keep that in mind people are sick
because they're loaded with bugs and
they're loaded with toxins getting rid
of one of those
pushes people to the finish line
getting the chance to cleanse your liver
to get those poisons out that keep you
sick by feeding bugs
it gives the liver a chance to do its
job
to fight for you and it gives your
immune system a chance to do its job
you're rebuilding your stomach glands
you're building up your hcl you're
cleansing your liver building up your
bile reserves out of your liver all this
is happening from the medical media
morning cleanse
you guys
we're going to go on ig we're going to
turn tik tok back on in a little while
we're going to turn telegram back on a
little while
and we're going to do another round
coming up just want to straighten up a
little bit
and i'm excited so
and just you let you know
because what's going to happen is the
juicer sale is over tomorrow and we're
going to get a million dm saying uh do
you know what juicer you use aw which
user do you use michael meadow wants
juicer to use and i'm going to scream
i'm going to take a car ride and drive
my car off cliff
and while the car's going off the cliff
i'm gonna roll down my window and say
the sale is over
i'm not gonna do that
that's a cartoon all right you guys
mm-900
the celery juicer
all right
and
just know if you're suffering or
struggling
there's hope if you're somebody that's
suffering someone who's struggling got a
neurological symptom or a condition of
any kind
okay
millions have healed around the world
doing mm info
just know
that you have the ability to heal it's
inside of you
we're just customizing what we need to
customize for you to get yourself out of
whatever you're in and move you out of
the woods
into the light okay i love you guys