had symptoms that nobody seemed to know
anything about could not find help after
seeing 15 doctors they kept telling me I
just I needed to be on anti-depressants
for the rest of my life it just didn't
make sense getting off them I had a lot
of uh withdrawal symptoms and some of
the supplements that Anthony recommends
stopped them stopped the withdraw
symptoms in their tracks it was
incredible but then also the heavy metal
detox smoothie you know that's what has
really turned things around for me uh
the depression is just it's a thing of
the past but the fatigue was still
around and so as soon as I do the celery
juice I feel the fatigue lift so I think
uh the things that Anthony talks about
make more sense than anything I've ever
heard in my life it's profound
information
[Music]