and helping people
all the decades one of my most favorite
things which I call a tool is propolis
hands down because I get asked a lot of
questions people will be like Aw what
about this what about this what about
this product
what about this company what about this
thing here
and propolis by far
is one of my favorite if you stick
around I'll do the continuity test too
and which is incredible because when you
do the continuity continuity test with
the vemergy propolis it's an entirely
different frequency entirely different
I'll talk about why in a little bit
by the way you guys memory is on sale
right now they have a killer sale going
on themergy.com check it out Vias and
Victor I am as in Mary e r g y.com don't
miss out on their sale okay we got some
bees flowing around because we're
talking about
propolis so I got my B friends here okay
so I got my little bees
and they're here with us just don't
sting me don't stink me
so we're talking about propolis which is
really exciting it's one of my favorite
tools of all hands down
and you guys know I work with emerging
you know that I I've endorsed them like
Full Throttle endorsement because I need
the stuff to stay around because you
can't find the Purity it doesn't exist
out there it doesn't you can't find the
Purity out there
it's not possible I've been through all
of it out there I've checked everything
out tried everything all of it and the
Purity is just unmatched and I'll talk
about that a little bit too but we're
we're talking about propolis and what I
call is like the power of nature when it
comes down to propolis it's an entirely
different beast and
all the years the bad propolises that
I've had to contend with because it's
like this you know that it's like it's
like the kind of like love hate thing
right like propolis is incredible but
all there was out there were crappy bad
low quality propolises with alcohol in
them that's all there was so it's like
here you got this incredible tool like
incredible tool but you can't really use
the tool so much because it's so
contaminated
and has so much junk in it and hidden
things in it and hit ingredients it's
got alcohol and you know propylene
glycol it's got all these bad things in
it and it's so it's always been that way
it's like
you know you want to use something
and you know though that you can use it
but you're not going to get really what
you need out of it because it's not good
but yeah you need it there's that whole
thing and the thing is the vermic
propolis it's not like that that's
what's incredible it's alcohol-free
that's just one little thing about it
all together so you guys are coming on
so we're talking about Pro Bliss that's
a good time to talk about it too because
propolis immune system
it's like an easy thing to kind of line
up in the mind too it's like immune
system
what time you know what what's going on
in the season right now all of these
things it's like immune system propolis
that's how I look at it too you know I
had a doctor ask me the other day like
what's the best thing things happening
going around you don't know what's going
all this stuff and what's the best thing
what's the best thing and I'm like
problems immune system the doctor was
like okay oh yeah I got it immune system
propolis because
you know that's just easy it's easy to
remember easy to think about the whole
bit
but I want to talk to you guys because a
couple of cool things right now beverage
has a sale which is a big deal that's a
big deal so that alone is incredible so
check it out vimorichi.com these
invictor I Amazon Mary e r g y.com so
that's one thing automatically I want
you to know about so they have a sale
and that is awesome okay it's the first
thing right there so let's talk about a
couple different things before we go
into propolis right
the four things that I love about the
vemergy company the four incredible
things and you guys probably remember
them maybe label requirements allow a
company to have a certain percentage of
ingredients they don't have to disclose
on the bottle
okay so that's what it's like out there
so label label requirements allow
companies to have hit ingredients in
their supplements that they don't have
to disclose if it's under a certain
percentage Bemidji says no we aren't
going to do that so that means like for
instance they're propolis it's not going
to have that hidden undisclosed
percentage of ingredients inside of it
it's not going to exist and I can't find
a company that will stand by that so
that's one like drop the mic one
incredible like thing all on its own so
that's one point
another incredible point right no
alcohol no caffeine no vinegar these
things are in supplements out there no
maltodextrin no natural flavors that's a
big one all on its own if you guys ever
heard the medical Bean podcast right I
have like a podcast episode talking
about natural flavors and how bad it is
so they have no natural flavors which is
incredible no soy no gluten right none
of that I mean we're talking Colleen
because there's a lot of supplement
companies out there and I see it all the
time where people will ask me and
they'll be like what about this one what
about that one I go did you read the
back of it do you read the back of the
label and that's not even the hidden
stuff
and you read the back label and you see
it you see natural flavors this flavor
that flavor flavoring you see all of it
there vanilla flavor whatever it is you
just see all the different flavors in
there
and those flavors are bad news and I
talk about that all the time
since the other like Point that's
incredible about the beveraging company
the other one is
a third party independently tested so
Bemidji does third party independently
tested so the reason why I'm going into
this to begin with you guys just got on
here like why is he talking about this
I'll tell you because we're talking
about propolis and it's important to
know what you're dealing with when
you're looking at something pure when
you're looking at Purity right and
that's important especially when it
comes down to immune system and
everything about the immune system so
and then there's the fourth thing that I
love is they choose the highest quality
now I think there's a game out there I'm
going to tell you right now okay you can
call a less quality ingredient quality
so some supplement companies can be like
yeah quality tested quality that's what
they can say and all that but it doesn't
mean they pick the highest level there
was it doesn't mean they went for the
highest level available because price
point it doesn't work out for all the
companies memory G doesn't care they go
to the highest quality level the highest
tier and that's where they head so when
I look at the four different things
it blows my mind right there that
automatically I can't find that anywhere
if there's a company out there I'd love
to talk to them because I guarantee they
won't have those four things because
I've done that I've talked to companies
I've talked to people out there and they
won't go near that so what vimergy holds
and what they Harbor and what they do no
one else will go near or touch and
that's what I call Unbelievable so we're
talking about propolis so when it comes
down to propolis
quality matters for sure because of
things like alcohol that's in propolis
and hidden ingredients and all of that
and so that's a big thing all on its own
by the way if you just guys just got on
here bemidji's having a sale so just
letting you know check it out when you
get a chance
and you guys know I work with emerging
because of those four points I talked
about I endorse them 100 just endorse
them across the the top there so you
guys incredible I'm just waiting for
some of you guys getting on you know
getting on here we're talking about
propolis
so when it comes down to problems it's
about immune system always keep that in
mind that's what I love about it and
then antioxidants and the polyphenols
that's another one too so we're going to
go into that a little bit
uh all right so let's hit it so people
are just like quercetin quercetin corset
hit like quercetin is good that's what
you'll hear out there like you you know
I I even today I'll hear like doctors
will just call me up they'd be like hey
I want to ask you about quercetin and so
a lot of people are into that but then
there's
bioactive living forms of it and that's
propolis and that's what's incredible
and the vimergy one so the Bemidji one
has the bioactive forms of polyphenols
in here over 50 percent are in the
propolis and that's what's incredible
all in its own so a lot of people will
just talk about things like quercetin
but yeah
there's dead quercetin
and it's not bioactive and it's dead and
then there's the ones that aren't and
that's the whole point about propolis it
Harbors these incredible polyphenols so
I wanted to talk about that for a little
bit too
so
um look you guys this is this is I'll
show you how this even looks and how
incredible it is too
you'll see how golden
it is
and clean and that's what I love about
it right there but I put a little bit in
this
shot glass right here
she's dropping in there it's just the
color is just extraordinary really
Maria says if you sign up for their
email list they will send you
notifications when they have sales
incredible
amazing definitely
so if you look at the color of it too
on its own it's different than anything
I've seen out there
so all the years of the propolis that
I've used have tried I've seen this is
an entirely different form in my opinion
from anything I've ever seen so you can
see the color of it the golden color
right so what the B does the B picks up
the resin
from tree buds
so that's how it starts off
and then the B uses that resin from the
tree Buds and produces propolis which is
like a lacquer it's it's basically a
bond and so then the bee takes it into
the nest I got my little bees right here
that are swinging around the bees take
it into the nest and use it to put the
nest together
and so but there's different qualities
of propolis out there
and so what I love about the beverages
one is the quality and that's what's
incredible about it so I got it right
here and what I usually do is I'll do it
this way right in a shot glass but I
just wanted to show you I also put it
directly in my mouth as well
so what I always recommend like doctors
would be like well what's the best way
to take propolis I'll say well look
you're the you're the doctor you can
tell your patient what to do but you can
put it right in your mouth and that's
fine too
so that's a that's another way to take
it but I have it in a little bit of
water right here in the shot glass I put
a little there just like this and
the thing is is that if you see other
propolis
out there
you'll see it's like Brown real dark
brown yucky sometimes a black color too
it won't be this gold
and you'll see the difference
and that's impurities is what you're
looking at when you see the different
colors that like you're looking at
alcohol reacting too as well to propolis
so you're so when you see other
companies and other brands out there and
I've seen this for years the alcohol can
turn it
a color
and so they they're really dark brown it
could be black it could be an entirely
different color and that's something you
won't see here you see the Purity
difference which is incredible all on
its own so
I'm gonna actually have one right now
all right
and what happens is that
I do the continuity test that I talked
about with you guys at one point and I
want to talk more about that another
time too of like what that is and how it
works so what I do
I saw hold this in my hand now this
isn't Kinesiology this is using your own
free will and no one else's free will
so nobody else's energy is intercepting
and so the other thing is your Korean
continuity to your brain
which is your central nervous system to
the product
and that's how it works like it's brain
to product and then the intention
right so the intention of your brain
knowing that you're going to be sending
energy
down to what's in your hand and what's
in your hand you're going to send energy
back up the nervous system straight to
the brain so it's the knowing it's the
Free Will you're using to create that
continuity test so it's both the Free
Will and using your brain
as the channel to send it down the
signal to go back and forth so what I do
with supplements and I've held so many
different propolis and I've held them
and done the continuity test right
and you feel like there's a block you
feel blocked
and I've had that so many times
especially if there's alcohol in there
especially if it's a poor quality form
then you feel that like blockage when
you hold it
and over the years I've had so many
propolises
to do that test with and I remember when
vimergy put theirs out and I grabbed it
and I said well see you know it
everything is above board everything's
great let's see what it feels like
and it's an entirely different sensation
and you could do that you can go like
you could be in a quiet space you can do
that in a quiet space relax you can sit
down you don't have to stand up and you
take it and you hold it in hand
and then you make that connection do
that like affirmation you say I'm
holding the propolis in my hand
and then you take your hand your other
hand and you put it right on top of your
head
Lily Collins says is continuity test
like muscle testing no because it's not
muscle testing you're actually not
muscle testing
that's not what you're doing
you're making a continuity frequency
between your brain
and your hand
so it's not muscle tested
muscle testing is somebody else's free
will
actually
being thrown upon you I'm not saying
it's good bad it's whatever anybody
wants to do out there it's fine whatever
they like
but that's different so Kinesiology and
muscle testing which is the same thing
is entirely different than this so this
is continuity test
and there's a big difference so with
this test okay and when you do it with
the probe less
it's on another level which is
incredible like when you do it with
products that are amazing it's an
entirely different level when you do it
with like garbage products or products
that have all kinds of bad things in it
and all that like the bad propolis is
out there and you do the continuity test
and you can feel the block
it's crazy how you could feel the Block
it's just actually amazing so
how to do a good continuity test and
we're going to do we're going to talk
more about this and go through because
there's so many details about how it's
done but holding it knowing you're
holding it
first and foremost
right so it's not like a trick with
muscle testing where
you're and I'm not saying this is a
trick or anything like the muscle
testing is a trick but it's like if your
practitioner is doing muscle testing
with you and they put a vial in your
hand beat or even know what it is
right that Consciousness is not your
subconsciousness Consciousness your soul
and the Brain itself to physically brand
physical brain is not connected to
really the vile
because there isn't even a knowing
so when you make that subconscious
conscious soul and physical brain
connection that you know what's in your
hand that's the first and foremost you
know what's in there that's got to be
key all on its own so you're holding on
to that
and you know what's in there okay and
then the second thing you have to do is
you're actually creating a connection to
the central nervous system so it's not
muscle testing it's the central nervous
system it's your main group of neurons
and nerves and you're making that
connection
to what's in your hand but to make that
connection you're actually sending a
frequency
right from your brain
through your arm down to the other arm
to what's in your hand and at the same
time sending it back and so what happens
is that if it's
not Pure or not pure enough or not
strong enough or it has
hidden ingredients in it
or it has undisclosed stuff in it or
it's weak or it's a real low quality or
it's got something like alcohol just
cheap junky alcohol in it Whatever It Is
you won't feel
that sensation
you won't feel it at all it'll just get
blocked and just like what is this and
sometimes you'll get even a short
circuit so
what's incredible about this is when I
was like okay well I can't wait to feel
this one
and what you do is you sit down
somewhere in a quiet room
you just relax
and then
you give it a few seconds and you know
what the intentions are you know what
your free will is going to be involved
with doing you're not using somebody
else's Free Will somebody else's Soul
isn't getting in your way somebody
else's intentions or free will is not
getting in your way
so it's not going to get in your way uh
it's not going to get in the way of your
subconscious and consciousness
so you're actually it's only you
and you alone your intentions your free
will your subconsciousness your
consciousness
your physical brain your soul and what
you are holding
and that completely is different than
any muscle testing any Kinesiology any
kind of testing on that level completely
opposite
it's far from it because that is
somebody else's Free Will being used and
I'm not saying anything good or bad
about that I'm just saying it's somebody
else's free will
and a lot of people do it differently
rise of Melton says I did the continuity
test last time you talked about it with
Bemidji products and it felt like a flow
of energy that opened up in my head so I
guess it worked that's what it feels
like it feels like a flow of energy
that's opened up
Claire Dunn says love you Anthony I'm
healing every day in every way credible
so it's a feeling of having an open
Channel and it could even be just it's
just like a crazy feeling with that like
it's it's incredible and I want to talk
more about it too when I get the chance
like go into details on how to do it so
when I do the continuity test
with like the propolis
I also like it what it does is it
connects me to where it came from it
connects me to the bees it connects me
to all of it and that's the other
incredible part right there so then you
get all of that energy going through and
you feel it it's really powerful like I
feel it now just by holding this now and
doing this and that's not me sitting in
a quiet room I'm sitting here
uh just trying to like talk about all
this Nicholas says try the continuity
testing on Bemidji and I felt a clean
uplifting Vibe that's the feeling I
tried it on a different brand and was
feeling nothing good that's how it works
like when I take a propolis that's
filled with the alcohol because they all
have alcohol in them even the ones that
say they don't or whatever this
you know there's there's still something
in there that
kind of nobody knows about right
and the the feeling is so much different
it's just it's unbelievable
Miranda says propolis shock therapy
helped me kick my fever with like
incredible you're over there on YouTube
amazing
that's so wonderful so you guys so we're
talking about if you just got on here
we're just chilling out
I got some lemon balm tea but guess how
I've been doing it I've been doing my
lemon balm tea like this
I've been doing my lemon balm tea like
that and I used to do it that way so I
ran out of tea bags because I also like
the lemon balm tea bags right and stuff
but I ran out of them like a while ago
and and then I'm remembering well this
is how I also like to do it which is
incredible
so what I do is I take water I put a
little honey
in there and then I take
and that continuity test on their lemon
balm is actually insane too actually
because lemon balm is like a commentive
right calms and nerves and so when you
hold lemon balm and you do the
continuity test
and there it is right there
it's really incredible
if you guys if you guys are really
intuitive and know many of you are and
some of you guys are working on your
intuitive abilities right
if you're really intuitive
and or if you're working on your psychic
abilities tell packing abilities right
all of that Clairvoyant abilities and
then you actually focus on that when you
have a pure product like this because I
can't any the products out there they're
not pure like this so but when you have
a pure product like this and you do this
and use your psychic ability
use your intuitive skills right
tutability
use your Clairvoyant ability everybody
has it whether it's developed or not
telepathic ability rate
and then you try to visualize
the incredible lemon balm that was used
for this
amazing resource
and you connect and you also do the
continuity test with it
it's actually a meditation so
and you'll feel that if you do the
continuity test
laying down because that's what I'll do
too is I'll take the propolis
and
I'll actually lay down
I'll relax I'll hold it in my hand I'll
put my arms out like this
and I'll just totally chill out
I'll lay on the floor
and then I'll put my hand here
you feel it right when you put your hand
here though all of a sudden boom you got
the continuity right going right through
but you do it as a meditation
and you can do it for like
30 seconds a minute take your hand off
and you're laying down
and then you do it again
you do for another 30 seconds for a
minute
it's an incredible meditation I'm
actually smiling because I could feel it
and it just reminds me of when I do it
every other day because I do that a lot
and the feeling you get
when you're not being blocked by
contaminants and other things and you're
actually getting the continuity go
through like right through rushing back
and forth so what happens is that
it goes from the brain to the hand
to the the pure product and from
the hand to the brain
and then it goes back and forth
and it's that
as vacillating back and forth and that's
how it really happens and the feeling
you get
cold white spring you're gonna try it
try it and do it as a meditation which
is incredible
and you know and I've had a lot of dead
products in my hand
that I've tried it with and you feel the
block
you even feel like whoa and you feel
like you gotta let go you feel like you
have to let go a friend of mine brought
some other like company and said well
what about this try this do the
continuity test on this I said all right
well let me lay down and I'll do it that
way and
I purposely didn't look at what was in
the ingredient list
that my friend actually brought the
supplement it wasn't very G was another
company and I purposely didn't look at
what was in the ingredient list I didn't
want to be biased
I want it to just be completely ignorant
to what was in the list of the
supplement brand
and I basically said I'm going to go by
your word I said to my friend my friend
said it's supposed to be the best
quality and the best Fury I said I'll go
by your word
I grabbed it I laid down I did the
continuity test I felt it he says what's
wrong with you I said what do you mean
what's wrong with me
I
feel that this is just totally blocked
and then I looked at it and it had all
this garbage in it on top of it people
wouldn't think it's garbage but it was
garbage Natasha says we did all this for
my eldest who just had the same eye
infection and the eye infection only
lasted three days
I love as a mom I don't need to worry
about anything hidden in Bemidji
products Natasha that's the incredible
thing it's like it's why I endorse them
because it's like
I don't want them to ever stop I worry
about that right because it's like it's
like you worry about that with them I
don't have to worry but I also want them
not to not to like create it
they're creating it for people but if
people don't know how and how pure it is
I don't want it to disappear is what I'm
trying to say I don't want it to
disappear I want them to get the support
they need and that's what I want
you know it means it means so much
so um but that's what the whole point
I'm trying to say is they don't have any
of the undisclosed hidden ingredients
you could have a certain percent of
undisclosed hidden ingredients label
requirements let the companies do that
where they they have a certain amount of
percentage of ingredients that you will
never know about ever and then the
quality tier they chose from is the
lower quality so it's price point you
guys know about that like if you guys
know about business right a lot of you
guys know about business right
that the the price point thing
so if you started a supplement company
tomorrow
and you went to go re like find
resources
and be like okay I'm gonna Source a good
whatever
you're gonna see where
they give you like they Source out the
cheapest of everything
and that's what you just automatically
go to you're like okay price point you
go with the cheapest you go with the
lowest quality even if you're allowed to
say it's quality
vermergy doesn't do that they don't care
about the price point they just say you
know what it's about people and it's
about their bodies
and so they go for the highest the
highest it's like that they can find
that they can find and if there's a
higher they'll find it and that's it the
highest and that's they go for and
that's the whole thing you guys saw how
I did the lemon balm right
I love it that way like seriously
so I've been doing this instead of the
the tea
so I'll do the vermergy Limbaugh if you
guys don't know the company it's Visa
Victor i m is Mary e r g y.com code of
energy.com we have a sale on too I just
thought I'd let you guys know about the
sale as well
so
now you can do another continuity test
now the brain to hand one
is like a really really powerful one the
other one is
hand to hand so you take a bottle of the
same product right
so
I got two bottles of propolis right here
so you take the bottle of the same
product
and you hold them in both hands
and you get continuity from one hand to
the other hand right
that's another one you can do too but
the only difference with that one
okay the only difference with that one
is you want to start out by having both
hands
on top of the place where your
subconscious your consciousness
your physical brain and your soul is so
you want to have both hands on top
and you can relax you can lay down and
then the after you have it on top for a
little while and I'll go into details
more on this in the future but you go
then you grab on to the products and you
do a continuity test between both
and that's another one you can do
and that one might be that might one
might be more you might like that one
better my favorite that Spirit of
compassion taught me and and I didn't
get these from anywhere it's not like
anybody ever you know doing the
continuity test and how it works and how
everything that's actually Spirit of
compassion it's for years and years that
I've that have used
but my favorite is
oh and if you're whatever hand you want
to do
and they'll bring a smile to your face
too because
you feel it
it's a sensation and it's like a
relaxing sensation but yet it's charged
at the same time because you feel like
it's like you're floating it's like a
floaty feeling too
it's just incredible so that's a
continuity test and that's something
that I've lived by for most of my life
and that I love and there's so many
tools that I've gotten from Spirit of
compassion that it there's only so many
I mean I I try to give you guys so many
tools all I can and as much as I can you
guys know I do that so this is one of
the tools that I love
so anyway when it comes to out of
propolis like I always teach people that
that ask me and stuff it's like immune
system it's one of the things I love
antioxidants is another one now
antioxidants are different in different
things
so something like
one antioxidant from something like if
if someone says well coffee has an
antioxidant right well
the bad outweighs the good in that
situation
right all the caffeine
stresses out the adrenals
adrenaline is like gasoline corrosive
so whatever little antioxidant that they
discover in a coffee bean
really can't compete with how much is
going wrong when you're on a lot of
caffeine
it's not something you'd like to know
and so you know when it comes down to it
there's but their antioxidants that are
in Pro that are in propolis are
different which is a whole other thing
that I was talking about before you guys
just want to give you a rundown
on what's happening with the propolis
and remember she's on sale right now
I'm just reading your comments too
um
I'm gonna have some more lemon balm tea
without the tea bag which is incredible
on its own
so try the continuity test when you
actually get a chance and see how it
feels
it's really
a powerful way to connect
and if you're somebody that's like using
your intuition
you're building up all your different
internal skills that you have it's a
whole nother thing to all of them so
anyway guys
I will see you again