system people should be thinking about
right now and
i know some people do but how far are
they thinking about it like
what are they really thinking about when
it comes down to the immune system
because
what i'm seeing out there is a whole
bunch of sick people in the world
and getting sicker sicker sick or sick
or sicker glad you guys are here
live on facebook live on youtube live on
tick tock live on clubhouse
i'm excited about this live we're
talking about 12
immune system boosters but we're going
to even talk about it even a little bit
more than that maybe a 13th maybe
some different foods and stuff so i'm
excited glad you guys are coming on good
to see you guys
this is really an important one i know
that i always say that but
information is powerful information is
knowledge we needed
we need it to heal and dr faun md good
to see you guys come on good to see you
coming on
thank you for being here today all you
guys
so i'm excited about this because what
i'm seeing out there is people
getting sick and it's it's bad enough
we've got chronic illness we've got lots
of chronic illness out there right
but all the different autoimmune people
are getting it left and right all the
different neurological symptoms people
are dealing with
people are suffering with brain related
conditions every single day they're
suffering with the cranial nerve
problems the vagus nerve the phrenic
nerve
all the different nerves okay cranial
nerves and people are dealing with that
left and right out there
and we're already having these problems
okay and
then there's the skin conditions right
eczema psoriasis the dermatitis all the
different skin conditions
okay and rosacea too all that acne right
but then
we got the flus we got the flues
the flues are out they're out there
i hear it all the time all the time you
know
i got a fever i got some kind of cough i
got congestion
i've got mucus in my sinuses i'm so sick
i'm in bed
and and i i can't even function it's
been like this for nine days
hearing it every single day out there
right
and so i'm always like immune system
you've got to have
a strong immune system it's critical
because we're already up against so much
you guys are already up against
all the different stuff the thyroid
conditions everybody
is going to have a thyroid condition
eventually
everybody is going to have a thyroid
condition hashimoto's thyroiditis
hypothyroidism hyperthyroidism graves
thyroid
nodules cysts tumors everybody's going
to have a thyroid condition
everybody's going to also have a cranial
nerve problem one way or another tingles
numbness
aches and pains ticks spasms blurry
vision
uh you know floaters in the eyes
tinnitus ringing the ears dizziness all
of it
and and we're also coming up on bad
flues
bad plagues bad flus right
and i've always been ahead of the curve
and something if you're new to medical
media information medical medium
information is so advanced
it leads the way in natural medicine
alternative medicine conventional
medicine when it comes down to chronic
illness so it leads the way
it's the most advanced information it's
always ahead of everybody else
like the blood draw information the
blood testing information that
that i delivered and
so many other things about how
epstein-barr causes all the different
conditions out there how it's one of the
viruses
how there's more than one variety of
epstein-barr and how it reactivates and
causes all these symptoms
no one knew this so medical medium
information if you're brand new here
is leading the way it's leading the way
for all the naturopathic doctors
functional medicine doctors
chiropractors who play natural medicine
all of it it's leading the way for all
of them
and they use pieces of it they're all
using pieces of it now
and that's what's happening so i want to
make sure still leading the way
and it's important that we have
that information so we can protect
ourselves
so we're talking about flu protocols
we're talking about immune system
building
we're gonna use zinc shock therapy
vitamin c shock therapy we need
time t do a couple of other things too
so i'm looking forward to it um
gianna i just made the banana garlic
honey nori rolls
that you posted on tick tock so so good
aren't they
that's an incredible immune system
builder right there you've got the raw
honey in there and i'm gonna make that a
little bit so right on tick tock
incredible
you got the raw honey you got the
garlic in there you got the banana and
you've got the glucose and i'm going to
talk about why that works
so you guys we're in the immune system
we're in there now we're talking about
it here we are so we got some
supplements in front of us
these are the ones i use my friends
family me
for immune system protection immune
system buildings so let's hit the zinc
right off the running
sinks something everybody's deficient in
i talk about it all the time
so stuff falling out of the sky and i
say stuff
falling out of the sky like the
chemtrail stuff right
all that different pollution everything
that's falling out of the sky
ddt is still floating around in the
atmosphere all the time
it blows around from continent to
continent right we got all the stuff
just blowing around and when it lands in
your soil
when it lands in the soil we grow our
food in
it depletes it so toxic heavy metals and
other
chemicals coming out of the sky land in
the soil
every single day every single night and
they then the rain
brings them into the soil into the earth
and it depletes the earth of zinc it's
one of the reasons why we don't have
zinc anymore in our soils our foods
don't have
zinc and if i hear one more time one
more time
just eat some oysters or do some oyster
do some an oyster supplement i mean i
mean
honestly it it's it's like i can do
everything i can
but i don't know what more i can do i
mean i just
don't you know so let's try that now
right don't you don't want to try that
it's terrible
so when you're doing oyster products
you're just getting more mercury
one of the very things that's depleting
the soils of zinc
so let's just try let's try to eat some
oysters and just so you know
oysters aren't high in zinc they just
show zinc they show it as one of its
trace minerals but they're not high in
zinc it's just that everything is so
depleted in zinc
and this is important to know because
this is where everybody fools everybody
everything is so depleted in zinc
that the tiny tiny bit of zinc in a
pumpkin seed
that shows up or in an oyster that shows
up make us go hey
no let's sink oh my god we just found
zinc just found zinc hey there's zinc
and oysters
eat a bunch of oysters if you want your
zinc
meanwhile every single fruit and
vegetable is supposed to show even more
zinc than an oyster does but it doesn't
because the earth is depleted right
the earth is depleted the soils and
pumpkin seeds happen to have a little
bit of zinc in it but you can eat yours
you can eat pumpkin seeds until you
can't eat them anymore and you're not
going to get enough zinc for the immune
system but that's the illusion
that's happening out there pumpkin seeds
are good for you i'm not saying pumpkin
seeds aren't good for you
but it's not going to be enough it's
like okay i'm coming down with the worst
flu of my life let me eat a bag of
pumpkin seeds
i mean is that stupid i mean really you
know like
it's like it it really is like that it's
like that
it's you know
oh my god yeah i
gotta get towards flu i think it's the
plague
yeah i get a fever and i notice that my
head is so stubby
wait eat a bag of pumpkin seeds no no
oysters
oh my god i think i'm gonna die yeah
yeah i know i called the doctor yeah
they they
yeah i i'm talking to what
you're eata eat a oyster
what should i get some oysters if you
get a really bad
i flew where i got the i got the play
gets going around
who should i should i send should i go
to should i get to the store and buy
some oysters
how many oysters should i eat
how many oysters should i eat should i
eat a
box of oysters would should i get a bag
of pumpkin seeds
is that gonna help me right now because
this thing is killing me
a box of pumpkin seeds all right i gotta
go
does that make a lot of sense to you
guys i just want to know does that make
a lot of sense
chris good to see you pumpkin seeds
never got anyone better and chris
it's so true it's so true mary said i
also wonder where does the zinc and the
supplements then come from trace mineral
zinc liquid zinc sulfate
from the earth but you can't it's not in
your soil
where your crops are growing it's not in
the soil your crops only have a little
root
system a little root system in the dirt
so you got your little top soil right
and you got something growing out of
your topsoil
okay you've got a little root system
down in here and all that soil there
the little root system is in okay that's
your turnip is in or anything is in that
root system
the zinc's not there it's not
but but that's this is how ridiculous
alternative medicine is
or conventional medicine too is okay
let me eat a box of oysters i better
call my oyster guy
let me do that right let me quit like my
oyster connection
how stupid or a supplement now that's
got oyster in it i mean can we be
any crazier
so why are you announcing amazon f4
tick-tock won't notify me when you're
live
so then tick-tock okay you guys so let's
get into it on supplements that are
critical zinc is one of those critical
supplements right there
okay that's the one that isn't hard
on the stomach like other zincs doesn't
have the citric acid
the alcohol the preservatives it's not a
hard
zinc and that's that's the difference
there's so many people are like why i
had sink it made me so sick
well yeah i tried all the zinc out there
i
i tried one it was so toxic out there it
was from a
reputable company out there and i
grabbed it it was the liquid stuff i
looked
at i said yeah i do see garbage in here
but let me just everybody says this is
the best one
let me take a look i took the cap off
boom sent it down and i
literally thought i was gonna vomit my
guts out on the ground
i said this is poison poison and so
that's the thing out there there's bad
zincs out there and bad
supplements give supplements a bad name
that's how it works anyway you don't
need to take a lot you can take a drop
you
can take a little bit each day you can
take one
drop one drop
and you can you can eat boxes and boxes
of oysters
trays of oysters plates of oysters and
you're not gonna get what
one drop can do that's by available like
that
one drop it's not gonna happen you can
eat bags and bags of pumpkin seeds
how stupid is that okay let me just eat
bags of pumpkin seeds if i get sick
right all important information
off the running these things matter
details matter
they do so good to see you guys coming
on we're talking about a building the
immune system why it's important so
let's go into the immune system
basophils monocytes neutrophils
lymphocytes
killer cells white blood count cbc
right your white your whites blood cells
your large white blood cells
okay neutrophils all part of the
right basophils neutrophils monocytes
lymphocytes
all these different aspects of our
immune system
we need things to support it because
those those parts of our immune system
are
under attack when we get invaders enter
our lives
so zinc shock therapy is is really a
great
is really a great way to stave off
something people feel like they're
coming
down with now you can do zing shock
therapy
ask your doctor what's right for you but
i'm just saying that's what i do as a
zinc shock therapy and i have my
family and friends using shock therapy
zinc shock therapy is in cleanse field
you guys just came on here you don't
have this i know somebody's going to ask
a question like
what do i do about my fibromyalgia it's
like oh my god
do you have the book what am i going to
do in my eczema
you got any it's in the book like
what do i take for my gout
it's in the book anyway you guys 51
off amazon.com us check it out when you
can it's a medical textbook
it's an angelic price i call it because
i don't know why amazon has this book so
low
it's cost more to print it it's i i
really believe
the forces are are working you know for
the chronically ill
and for for the good of humankind when
they lower this price like that because
16 for a book that's 500 plus
pages it's a big book anyway
zing shot therapies in the book
slingshot therapy is two dropper fulls
of zinc
every three hours you know every waking
three hours
you can do it one day you can do it two
days it's two dropper fulls of zinc
every three hours now you can do six
tiny drops every three hours and i talk
about in the book
you know you do what whatever your
doctor tells you to do but
you do six tiny drops if you want every
three hours you can do one drop or full
there every three hours
but it's a great technique to shut
the crap down it's a great technique
to shut that down it is got sore
throat coming on
i got i don't feel good i got a sore
throat coming on um
i think i'm coming down with something
and
it's like shut that down
boom it's like every three hours
a little bit zinc and
good dude of water shot glass right here
you could put it in the water you know
shot glass add a little water to it
so let's keep on going that's the zinc
zinc is is the one of the founding
fathers one of the foundation pieces of
our immune system right there
important to know so this is the
vimrajee if you guys just came on here
need to know the company's the company i
use i'm not sponsored
this isn't a sponsorship this isn't a
sponsorship
important to know dr sherry green good
to see you
incredible let's move on
a little bit going to something else
that's really important what i love is
goldenseal
that's a powerhouse all on its own for
the immune system
okay so pathogens don't like goldenseal
bugs don't like goldenseal even mrsa
doesn't like goldenseal right
sharptococcus doesn't like goldenseal
chronic sinusitis bacterial vaginosis
utis bladder issues bladder infections
kidney infections
lung infections throat infection sore
throat
strep throat or any kind of sore throat
the sore throat in the corner of your
throat you guys ever get the sore throat
in the corner
i go oh i got a sore throat coming on
it's in the corner but yet i don't have
a cold
but yet i don't have a flu there are no
colds by the way
cold's just colds don't exist on the
planet
any time someone starts coming down with
something it's the flu
or flu family virus is like the plague
but the cold has been the cold is gone
when someone just gets a mild rendition
of a cold
that was just a mild rendition of the
flu the cold just
died off that whole you know i caught a
cold
you didn't catch a cold you caught a flu
you just had a mild version of it or
you were able to get through it fast
someone else caught the same cold
they're coughing their guts out they now
got bronchitis they're on antibiotics
they're seeing the doctor
they caught the same cold you caught
you just your immune system handled it a
little better
yeah you might not have been at that
place where your cycle wasn't coming on
and it might have been in between your
cycle coming on and ovulation coming on
and then
it didn't turn into a bad flu it turned
into a real mild flu
right important enough that's how it
works
but someone else caught it's cold too in
the group of people so the group of
friends someone else caught that cold
well that wasn't no cold because someone
else is literally bedridden with 103
temperature
they're on the couch to coughing their
guts out
and they caught the same cold there's no
colds
anywhere anymore cold the cold
virus the little rhinoviruses and the
little cold viruses
those have come and gone in our history
gone
gone they're not around no more
you get a little something well i got a
little sinus congestion i'm starting to
come down with something that's the flu
you might have a mild one
but that's the flu it's important to
know how things work
the goldenseal is critical for all that
if you guys want to know what this is
of emergency stuff via the victor i am
mary ergy
dot com important to know so it's
memorgy.com
that's the stuff that i use if i want a
golden seal it's got to be one with the
quality it's got to be the one i know i
can trust it's gonna be the one i know
that can knock something out in my
system and not something else it has to
be a product that doesn't have that
hidden that hidden five six seven eight
percent of
hidden mystery ingredients that the
manufacturers all put in everybody's
supplements
vimergy doesn't allow that
so yeah so so goldenseal is important so
i love covering the cold
information but i hear people like i
think i got a cold now
no and another thing too is allergies
get confused
i love when that happens someone's
coughing
they got the runny nose they got the
sinuses and it's like
you know it's like it's my allergies
it's not your allergies
you know yeah well it's allergy time i
think i'm dealing with an allergy
you got the flu you've got you're
coughing
you're coughing your lungs out you've
got the sinuses running you've got the
you've got the low-grade fever you got
the flu you don't have you
don't have allergies that's with that
maybe you do have allergies but that's
not an allergy
you can get the flu every month people
get it every month their immune system's
so low you guys they get the flu every
month they get the flu every seven weeks
eight weeks and then and then it comes
down to
it comes down to yeah getting the flu
every because the flu is out every six
weeks
there's a new flu every six weeks if it
isn't just the plague that's cycling
in the new flu is cycling in every six
weeks you can get the stomach flu now
right now i'm hearing about it all over
the place everybody's like i just got
over the stomach flu i just had the
stomach flu
what's the brand on tic it's vimergy v
is in victor
i am as in mary e rgy.com i'm not
sponsored it's the stuff that works
it's the stuff that works that's all
plain simple
just stuff that works it works for my
friends works for my family
some of the most powerful people in the
world that reach out to me what should i
be taking a w
should be on the vimorgy stuff people
don't realize if you guys p
if you guys knew who i spoke to your
minds would go
like they're the people the most
powerful people the world
are calling calling me reaching out
that's how it's been for 30 plus years
and they're reaching out and they can go
to 50 doctors but they're reaching out
because they want to be like aw what do
you say
works i'm like well you should be on
this
should be on this and
it matters anyway so back to golden seal
talking about cold talking about flu
talking about all that stuff
okay so
kathy caitlin my hypothyroid issue
has been cured due to following your
information
no more floater no more
menopausal symptoms no more sciatica no
more chronic allergies so much more
incredible
kathy i'm glad you're here awesome
so isn't this information interesting
though so when you hear somebody
you know it's like it one thing about
medical medium information it has no
it has nothing to do with me being smart
because i'm not smart i told you guys
over and over again it's where i get my
information it's the source right
how am i gonna put together seven large
medical textbooks
that are ahead of science and research
and pave the way for all alternative
medicine conventional medicine
how am i gonna do that i didn't even go
to college
right it's from the source and i love
when everything is clarified there are
no colds anymore
there are none it's either mild or
serious flues
or the plague now or mild and serious
flues
and there's going to be a lot of them a
lot of the flus there's one now there's
a stomach flu going around
there's also another flu going around
and then the plagues going around
three things going around right now
so anyway gold and seal is critical how
do i know
two things are going around i get the
calls from
powerful people in the world and family
members what do i do
what do i do so get on your vimorji get
on your vimorji
what what i picked this stuff up at the
health food store
it's got alcohol in it
it's got citric acid in it doesn't even
have the right amount of
gold seal the quality goldenseal is
terrible all this important so
goldenseal what i love about goldenseal
is there's something inside of you
that tells you your healing
when you start taking gold the right
kind of goldenseal you can
feel it kathy i wish more people would
listen to me when i tell them about your
protocols i have
healed so much because of you it's just
it's spiritual
discrimination is all it is kathy the
reason why i don't listen to spiritual
discrimination
it's a lot of people
don't realize that first of all science
and research
the ball it just dropped the ball they
think that it's going to be there to
catch you
they do they think it's going to be
there to catch you
science science of research are you
there
because when i get sick someday yale
universe yale and harvard
and all the dartmouth all of them are
gay and all the scientists are going to
catch me
when i get sick with my cranial nerve
problems and my migraines and my fatigue
and my aches and pains my trigeminal
neuralgia and my sciatic pain
they're all going to fix me catch me
okay you ready
okay okay catch me you're there
they're not gonna catch you cold and flu
protocol inclines the heal by the way
check it out all right i got to take
things serious here
uh and it is serious in a sophie i
didn't have a flu
even once since i started following mm
so really amazing you know it's it's
i've heard that a lot
and yeah there's a lot of them going
around and you could be you know
at a little point where you could get
something absolutely there's that many
things going around and you know that
at least you'll have better chances with
mm stuff
for sure so there's something about gold
and seal the right kind like when i take
the vimergy golden seal right
something just hits you
that your body's kicking in the gear to
heal
you've got to remember that too right
always ask your doctor what's right for
you take what your doctor wants you to
take i'm just saying that when i have a
family member
take this i always ask them you feel it
you feel it kicking in you feel that
right
that's your body registering to this
right here
because this is so potent and strong
and so right and and the quality is so
good
that the right kind of golden seal
because golden seal in itself
is magical magical herb
magical root magical herb and
and when you when it starts entering the
body
so angela says isn't golden seal one of
the supplements like licorice you
shouldn't
take longer than two weeks yeah i mean
here's the thing right
with goldenseal it's like an antibiotic
you said it's a natural antibiotic okay
and
if you have to be on it longer than two
weeks it's still gonna do what it's
gonna do for you
but i talk about it in cleansing heal
that it's good to take a break sometimes
two weeks on two weeks off
but i've taken goldenseal just long term
to keep my immune system strong
i've recommended family members be on
gold gold and seal
six weeks solid without taking a break
i've recommended
people i've known friends to be on gold
seal for a three-month stint
and then take a break and then go back
on it for three months but yes
it's a little rule of thumb take little
breaks i do the two week
on two week off and cleanse the heel
so goldenseal is just something really
special
it's one of those herbs roots herb root
that talks
communicates to the immune system to the
body
and you can feel it when you're taking
it when that sore throat's coming on
and you're like i got to do something
and you take that golden seal you know
you take that golden seal got a little
shot glass here
i just put three dropper holes of that
golden seal in this this little shot
glass right
and you feel something coming on or you
got a uti
got bladder infection it won't give out
you've been to the doctor that won't
give in
you got i just saw dr nesbitt no no one
wants to no one likes dr
nesbitt someone left a comment i think
was on ig or somewhere and they said i
hate dr nesbit
i just felt i felt so bad for dr nez but
is dr des been in today in surgery today
dr nesbit's in surgery but we can get
him out of surgery
i'm pretty sure we might be able to get
him out in the middle of the operation
while the patient's on the table still
we might be able to get them out for a
while while the patient's on the table
they'll just keep the patient under it's
okay
the nurses will be be around the patient
when dr nesbit comes in
with the golden seal you feel the golden
seal kick it
no one likes dr nesbitt
truth is everybody loves dr nesbitt they
just don't like me
they love dr desmond jennifer i'm taking
goldenseal right now
i feel so much better when i am on it i
just took it
what happens is golden seal has a
communication
ability like it's an herb root ancient
herb root that's connected to our immune
system in our body
emma swann how can you possibly hate dr
nez but i don't know but people do
there's a couple of people just hate him
haters gotta hate you he says
all right you guys let's let's move
along move along
licorice root about licorice root
get ready you ready you guys ready
ready hhv-6 hhv-7 hhva
cancer cancer hhva cancer virus right
hhp6 in its mutations causing all kinds
of problems hh37 people have out there
hhb9 through
undiscovered 10 through 16 simplex one
simplex two
all the different versions cold sore
fever blister
cold sore they call it cold sore not
simplex is what it is
no it's just a cold sore don't worry
about it just give me a
don't worry about it i gotta i got a
date tonight
we going out tonight yeah
well what you saw me earlier today yeah
i know i saw you earlier today
you saw what you saw this really
it's it's nothing to worry that's just a
call it's just a it's cold sore
yeah it's just a cold sore
we going out yeah
this is a fever blister
huh it's simplex
what do you mean it's simplex i thought
it was a fever blister
a simplex one what do i do
all right all right i'm hanging up
what i love about the licorice root it's
so great for that simplex one simplex
two
ebv epstein bar over 60 varieties of
epsom bar
chronic fatigue syndrome fibromyalgia
r.a neurological lime that's all fc and
bar
lupus epstein-barr list goes on right
epstein-barr epstein barr
okay well licorice root
so important if you guys just came on
april
you guys just came on here um talking
about vimergy supplements bees and
victor i
m e r dot themorgy.com that's where you
go
for the best stuff i am not sponsored
i'm talking about the best quickest ways
to do some healing understanding the
body understanding our immune system
rebuilding the immune system
i've seen bar in all its varieties
shingles virus and all its varieties
cytomegalovirus hpv darlene
darlene wong hpv
licorice is good with hpv it is
i saw wild lizzie flower
okay so anyway we're talking about
licorice root right here you guys we're
live on tick tock we're live on facebook
youtube we're live in clubhouse
we're doing the immune system building
talk this is an important one
licorice roots critical right there okay
do what your doctor
tells you right ask your doctor if
licorice is okay ask your doctor if
licorice is right for you
i'm just telling you that i use licorice
for my immune system i use it for my
adrenals
i use it for my adrenals i have to
you know when some you know when someone
else when someone comes onto our live
and says what is he talking about
blood tests what you don't want to do
the big blood draw thing
trying to get everybody to learn about
the blood draw on a blood test
and how that works what and then all of
a sudden my adrenals start going
next full moon okay guys so
licorice is really good i use licorice
all the time i'm putting in two dropper
fulls of licorice right here
licorice is anti-viral antiviral
very important to know anti-viral
i got chronic fatigue syndrome i got
fibromyalgia i got
hashimoto's thyroiditis i got
hyperthyroidism
i got cysts i got nodules i don't feel
good i got fatigue i got tingles and
numbness that can't be explained i got
ringing in the ears i got vertigo
where my vagus nerve is obviously
inflamed it's not obvious until medical
medium
taught people that's what causes very
good then you got the vertigo you got
the dizziness
viral anti-viral immune system
low-grade viruses everybody's got the
ebv's
everybody has those it's important to
know
two dropper fulls of licorice
going down lemon balm talk about that
lemon balm is incredible for the immune
system
people got the gas the bloating their
their hydrochloric acid
died inside of them where their stomach
lands weakened and just
fell apart right
grab a little stomach over here
let's do this real quick
guys i'm honored you're here we
are talking about the immune system
hello
so we got a stomach right here
one of the reasons why everybody has
digestive problems and they also have
bad bacteria in their gut is because
their stomach glands have been burnt out
their low their hydrochloric acid is low
to nil to none
okay virtually none non-existent and
that's what happens when that happens
bad bacteria can prosper especially for
feeding that bad bacteria bad
foods right so then the bad bacteria
prospers inside the gut each pylori
rises
e coli arises rises and streptococcus
right there apple then good to see you
everything everything rises that's bad
bad and it rises okay
what i love about even goldenseal
is good for that too but what i love
about like the lemon balm
that's the nettle
what i love about the lemon balm is
it's antibacterial antibacterial
love it but it does something else
because the gut gets inflamed from all
the bad bacteria the inflammation
bothers the nerves
and so all the nerves going into the gut
gets sensitive
and then everybody has all these
neurological issues in their gut
and they feel it and they're having
problems in their gut intestinal tract
different digestive issues and
everything else michelle l good to see
you
they have all these problems and that's
what i love about lemon balm
it's an anti-spasmodic for those nerves
it calms down the nerves inside the gut
but it's antibacterial too
it's a great gentle immune builder
something can be taken every day every
single day
you can take the lemon balm every day
helping to keep your immune system
strong so even stuff that's inside of
you that's growing that shouldn't be
there
starts to grow starts to grow
elizabeth elizabeth edwards says yep me
i get stabbing pains you get the
stabbing gut pains right
little gas bubble moving through and it
hurts like heck
because it's inflamed in there and
so lemon balm is something that i use
for
my friends and family when they have any
kind of issues like this so that's
important
guys anybody coming on that's the
vimorgy if you don't want to know the
brand
using victor i am ergy.com i'm not
sponsored gotta say it over and over
again i saw someone left a comment
saying he's just a marketing machine
like you know what that's crazy because
because that same person is probably
watching a whole bunch of people that
put a million dollars a month in
marketing
for all their ads on youtube and
everything else like all the doc
the podcast doctors and all those guys
and they're selling
they actually own all the supplement
companies they own all the products
that's ridiculous marketing machines so
me trying to help you take a high
quality product makes me a marketing
machine
stupid it's like what am i supposed to
say i better not have you guys
you know what i won't give you guys any
advice anymore don't take care of
yourselves don't do anything for
yourselves
right don't do nothing don't do nothing
don't even do celery juice
quit the celery juice just don't do
anything
yeah i i've been pushing bananas forever
stop the bananas yeah marketing bananas
yeah marketing bananas that's right
where's the bananas
i'm marketing them uh-huh yup what a
marketing machine i
am yeah what else am i marketing melons
quit the melons huh watermelon yeah i've
been behind watermelon for years i'm
marketing watermelon
yeah okay oh wait i got some time for
the time t i'm gonna make for everybody
i'm marketing time
i'm such a marketer yeah
real marketer what else am i marketing
honey
yeah i better stop telling people to use
it for their immune system i'm making
billions of dollars in honey did you
know that
all right you gotta stop fooling around
all right let's go on the immune system
so what i'm trying to say you guys is
that it's a misconception right i'm not
sponsored by vimergy
and i told you guys i'm working with
lyman's to make sure their blueberry
juice sticks around because i don't want
that stuff
that's a treasure and i don't want that
stuff to actually disappear because what
it can do for people is just
it's it's it's hard to make wild
blueberry juice to get it out of a field
and press it
and i don't want them to stop so i said
you know what just if you want me on
board to let everybody know then i'll
work with you guys
absolutely
i don't sell honey i don't sell bananas
don't sell melons
i don't sell cellar let's go talk about
a little bit more
and i'm working with a mega under juicer
i told you that guys you guys know that
but
it's not mine and i don't own it
kimberly so grateful for bemidji
products they have transferred my health
transformed my health nice
all right guys let's keep on moving
let's talk about we talked about the
lemon balm how important that is what i
do with lemon bums lemon balm
straight in a lot of times i'll do it
straight in
i do before bed calms me down
carmen name of blueberry juice please
that's the wymans so it's shop
shop.wymans.com
shop shop.lyman's
w-y-m-a-n s-com
okay and that's the wild blueberry juice
and i do a shot
for my immune system every single day
he wants to do a shot
i needed that today thought i need it
all right we'll keep on moving along
guys do you think i fall around too much
i got it yeah so let's keep on moving
around
moving on cat's claw okay let's talk
about cat's call get ready
neurological lime if anyone's got
neurological lyme
ask your doctor if you can take cat's
claw
ask your doctor doctor can i take cat's
cloth
so make sure you ask your practitioner
your doctor your health care provide
provider
you've got neurological lyme if i had
chronic fatigue syndrome with no
neurological lyme diagnosis
i'd be doing cat's claw if i had
um if i had any kind of condition that
was listed in
autoimmune i would do cat's claw
so if i went to the doctor with a whole
bunch of symptoms and they went to
another doctor and they went to another
doctor and then i'm not a neurologist
and then i met somebody else and then
i'm all over the place i'm getting scans
i'm getting mris i'm getting all that
stuff
i would be on cat's cloth that's what i
would be
on cats call i've seen people over the
years go see 10 doctors
whole bunch of different specialists you
guys a whole bunch of different
specialists
and i put them on cat's claw and
everything went away over time
we could put them on cat's claw had them
on the celery juice and a few things
and then things just started going away
and they went to 10 doctors
this one has no alcohol it's high
quality no citric acid
it's the real deal it's why i stand
behind this product because it's that
good so cat squat is antiviral
antibacterial i love it for pathogens i
love it for pathogens
there's people out there sick they're
just sick you guys know some of them
many of you guys have struggled and been
through right there's people sick they
got they just
they got the brain fog they can't even
think they got the fatigue they can't
even function
they they have so many issues and when
you start taking the cat's call and you
start bringing that in
things start changing it's part of
protocols in here
right here that's part of protocols and
cleanse the heal
if anybody just came on if you don't
have cleanse to heal
it's sad because 51 off amazon.com or go
to the library try to get it free at the
library if you want
i always tell people i don't care if
everybody goes to the library
and they get it for free as long as i
know you have it
that's what matters okay my publisher
sells the book
i don't sell the book so details matter
right here i actually i'm not
self-published
there's a lot of people that are
self-published they're selling their
book right
i'm not the publisher owns the book
they sell it it's to get it out there in
the wider world
and it matters so people can actually
you know find it okay it's a it's a book
that you can reference from it's a
reference book tech medical textbook
okay
51 off amazon amazon.com us you should
have the book tick tock you guys
so cat's claw i like cat's claw for
anything bacterial i love cat's ball
with when someone has
mrsa or they got a staph infection
anything like that it's like cat's claw
someone's got a uti
cat's claw someone's got something
that's plaguing them like
some kind of long-term infection or
something in the lungs
cat's claw elky love all your
recommendations i have all your books
and learned so much i'm honored i'm
working on a book right now i can't wait
to finish
i'm actually like i was working on that
book all night
all day okay let's keep on moving
what did i miss here i got the golden
seal i got the zinc i talked about the
licorice root the lemon balm the cat's
cloth
nettle leaf aha metal leaf
something something you can take every
single day
every day you can take metal leap right
ask your doctor if you can
but every single day i take it all right
now here's the thing all right people
all about the collagen
the collagen the collagen right
proof medical medium information leads
the way is for years i've been telling
everybody
that you can't grow collagen from eating
collagen
and now since medical medium was so
advanced
everybody laughed they're like he's
wrong medical means wrong you take
collagen powder in order to build
collagen right
well they were wrong and i told
everybody they were wrong you'll find
that medical media information is never
proven wrong ever
never has it's consistent and it's never
proven wrong it's only proven right
now all the supplement companies have
taken medical medium info
and they're saying you can't build
collagen by eating collagen anymore
so you need all these other things and
they're taking little pieces of medical
medium information and they're putting
it in a product and they're saying this
is how you build collagen
mm info if you're new here leads the way
in natural medicine
for years and years and years actually
for decades now fact
so important to know why am i even
talking about any of this
metal leaf is a great supporter of that
collagen
how come they don't put multiple herbs
in one
bottle only ah
very important question right there how
come they don't
because that's how they rip you off out
there
well very important question i talk
about that and cleanse the heal
that's how they rip you off
they put lots of different herbs in one
bottle
so you can't get better if you buy
an immune system builder herbal formula
you just got ripped off seven ways to
sunday
fact because every one of those bottles
they use a spidgeon of a little smidgen
a little spickle a little tiny smidgen
of each herb and a poor quality one
because that's how they make their money
that's how they make their money
okay
yeah uh herbal world
yeah herbal world manufacturers of all
the herbal supplements that we all
that we that we sell to all the small
independent companies
yep we're putting in a little tiny bit
of each herb
we're going to put adrenal formula on
there and then we're going to put
immune formula on another one and then
we're going to put
a brain formula in another one and we're
going to throw
a little tiny speck of each herb in that
formula
so that they can't get better but yet it
costs us nothing to do it that way
and we're gonna make sure there's
alcohol in there or citric acid and
everything else in there and natural
flavors
perfect yup that's what we do at herbal
world
and that's how it's done another reason
why
vimergy doesn't do that now here's the
thing
the reason why medical medium protocols
get people better so when they really
understand the protocol they're seeing
that they're not getting an
herbal remedy that has 20 herbs in it
because you won't get better if there's
20 herbs in there
if licorice is an antiviral you need a
good amount of it in a good quality
amount of it
the right quality to make something
happen
you can't get better with a speck of
cat's claw
a speck in a supplement that's either a
dried herb supplement
or a bad liquid liquid one that has a
whole bunch of different herbs
you can't get better you guys this is
priceless information
this is information i taught for decades
so people had to
wait in line to talk to me so they
because they were sick and they're like
well i took
uh this well you know but you're not
getting better
because knowing the right herb to take
in the right quantity is how people
get better that's how it's done you guys
seriously chris chris you seem fine to
me
it is priceless you're right i mean
seriously think about that
and i do it for free i can charge for
three thousand dollars for my immune
system uh building
course i can do an immune system
building course you guys in charge
three thousand dollars
imposters are actually saying their
medical medium and they're out there all
through europe in the united states and
they're charging people a thousand
dollars to three thousand dollars just
to talk to them for five minutes
i can get a million people to to
actually buy into an immune system
building course a million people at
three thousand dollars a piece
and i do it for free and then someone's
gonna shame me for
showing my book which i don't even sell
my publisher does so i make this much
off of it
to keep the lights on
so why wasting why wasting your hard
earned money question mark
just for your info a w's job is to empty
your wallets
meanwhile filling in his own
he doesn't care about your health love
you
oh love you who's that strike 77 strike
i think did you get your did you get our
invite
did you get her invite
i think you said that i think that was
towards me right shark77
so why wasting your hard earned money
question mark
just for your info aw's job is to empty
your wallets
really meanwhile filling in his own all
right
strike did you get my invite we invited
you here
to the house uh-huh are you gonna be are
you are you
you are you're already on your way
you're gonna be here in a minute is that
a mistake strike 77 or not i'm just
curious i don't know
if it's not a mistake wait love you
anthony i think that's a mistake i think
that's just written different
all right that's right i don't know
[Music]
i think that was an accident
[Laughter]
all right
all right listen strike i think you're
knocking on the door yeah
strike i think you're knocking on the
door do you got my invite okay
wait i hear you knocking at the door i
hear you knocking at the door
i'm late striking
[Music]
strike stop strike stop it
strike stop
whew all right strikes here you guys i
got strike with me
strike decided to come yeah
strike what do you think do you think
i'm trying to just take everybody's
money
really is that something you want to do
is that the problem
strike uh-huh strike don't do that
crackling again
strike stop it
strike stop
strike 77 we invited you
here as a friendly gesture
all right strike you gotta go
all right i'm making some tea on that
note i gotta make some tea
i got the kettle going on a little bit
you guys see that
envy doom take one money aw
works himself too much to even enjoy any
money
correct
oh my god
i need to light a scented candle
you guys i gotta light a scented candle
right now
and get on the phone with my friends i
got a phone call coming in right now
i'm just getting some tea i got a phone
call coming in
i got a phone call coming in
oh my god hello oh
my god i am gonna relax and write in my
journal
and i'm going to huh
i'm going to light a candle a scented
candle that i picked up
oh my god it smells so good
mm-hmm ah yeah
i think i'm stirred journaling i just
gotta
fill out my journal for the day i had my
facial
mm-hmm oh my god that sunday candle
smells so good it's just what i needed
right now
i'm having a really bad day
totally oh my god kimberly miller did
you see that
yeah i just had a massage
and i also had a facial oh my god i'm so
into the self-care thing i could do
self-care all day long and all night
long
i had this scented candle so i just
bought a whole bunch of them
yeah are you coming over i just finished
my journal
okay all right
i need to light a scented candle right
now because
okay so um i think that was a mistake
strike 77 right
okay i gotta blow this out oh my god
oh my god oh my god that stuff is just
poisonous
that just lowered my immune system so i
need to go back into immune system stuff
right now
all right we're talking about nettle
nettle is nettle supports the immune
system
it has phytochemical compounds that your
white count
feeds off of so let's get some white cow
now
so it's a white blood cell you guys
right there
it's a white blood cell yeah
and white blood cells love phytochemical
compounds from
herbs certain herbs and
nettle leaf actually nourishes and feeds
your white count it doesn't make it go
berserk strong right
like after infections but it keeps it
strong
so it helps to keep it strong that's why
i love metal leaf i also love natalie
because it is the building blocks
it's one of the building blocks to not
have wrinkled skin and
not age so fast it's one of those
building blocks
i love it the white count right here
all right i'm gonna make some tea let's
do that so i'm gonna do some
mushroom tea i got some chaga
you guys don't mind if i micro dose
well yeah i'm micro dosing here
yeah dude micro dosing
uh-huh got some mushroom
powder some shrooms yeah
doing some shrooms i got some reishi
and some chaga mushroom
okay let me get some water
so i'm making some chaga and reishi tea
which i do occasionally
which you're not going to find in this
reishi mushroom
you're not going to find caffeine in
here
so that's the chaga mushroom which
you're not going to find in the rishi
we're live i don't know what else to say
we're not going to find
caffeine in here you're not going to
find
caffeine mixed in here why
because caffeine destroys your immune
system i know i'm gonna get a whole
bunch of crap from a lot of you guys
right now like
what about decaf coffee what about
what about my green tea what about my
matcha tea
you're not your caffeine lowers your
immune system
it can set you up for a bad flu
it could set you up if people are around
people that actually
have the flu or or something that looks
like it
or anything like it or a plague or
anything it's not even just that if
you've got
immune system problems you got
autoimmune you don't want caffeine mixed
in your mushroom
powder so you don't want caffeine mixed
in your rishi
your chocolate yorishi
so important to know you don't put
coffee
in rishi mushroom you don't put coffee
in chaga
and then pretend that gave you energy
that the rishi gave you energy
rishi is not known to give you energy
change is not known to give you give you
energy but they're good for the immune
system but if you mix them with coffee
you just destroyed it
you destroy you're destroying your
immune system
caffeine destroys the immune system so
if you mix caffeine with
mushroom you don't even get the good out
of the mushrooms because you're
weakening your immune system when the
mushroom's supposed to
actually help your immune system because
caffeine stimulates
your adrenals right
your adrenals caffeine blows them out
blows them out boom blows them out
that's what caffeine does
blows them out important to know
so i'm making some
i'm making some mushroom tea
so i got some rishi and some chaga
okay that's a great immune system
builder right there can have that once
long i don't have it every day
i just have it like a couple times a
week a little bit
here and there you can put raw honey in
here
i got some raw honey
it's important to know though that
literally people are out there
and they just want to destroy people
people love to destroy people they just
love to destroy people that's what they
do out there
wild lizzie flower death by a thousand
cuts out there
people love to kill people
you don't think so you don't think so
okay
then why take something so pure
something so pure and then contaminate
it with something that actually ages
women
ages women gets them addicted and ages
right makes their hair fall out
because caffeine is a psychoactive drug
so let's take a psychoactive drug
stick it in something pure and good
because people out there want to hurt
people i don't know what else to say
it is that i don't give me that there's
no bad people out there don't give me
that
okay let's do some vitamin shock vitamin
c shock therapy now
let's do that vitamin c shock therapy is
something that i really love
i still have to talk about lysine i
still have to talk about b12 for a
couple of minutes
so what i love about but first of all i
take six capsules three times a day
that's what i do six capsules three
times a day that's what i do every day
you do what your doctor does do i'm just
saying that's what i do right
but if you feel something coming on
spirit of compassion put together this
vitamin c
shock therapy right
and it really works so
pouring some water in here
i really i really appreciate your
patience you guys
why i play around in here with
everything
truly i'm truly honored for real
so i'm doing two capsules of vitamin c
every two hours i am going to add some
orange
got some orange in there i am going to
put some honey in there
this is an immune builder drink immune
builder tonic
right here
right so i got two capsules of vitamin c
not just any seed it's the microc you
guys don't have this type of if you guys
are
are using a vitamin c you'll when you
experience this someday
if you ever like branch on to using say
the microc
you'll notice the difference it won't
burn a hole in your stomach
it's not like battery acid so i just put
honey in here
squeeze of orange two capsules of microc
every two hours every two waking hours
awake every two hours there's rose hips
in this microc by the way i know a lot
of people like well i'm not gonna
i'm not gonna venture on to unless it's
got rose hips
there's rose hips in there
so every two hours
waking two hours because if you're
sleeping you don't want to wake yourself
up
to try to actually take this you want to
sleep
right so yeah
there we go that's it mixed it up that's
the vitamin c shock therapy
it's really good too every two hours
that's a great technique for the immune
system you think you're coming down with
something you think something's up
okay let's talk about lysine
it's the inhibitor of viruses the
herpetic family viruses
it's all the different herpes families
the shingles viruses the ebv
viruses the sedimentary virus all the
viruses that actually plague everybody i
like it for any virus
any virus any virus but but lysine is a
helpful way to heal you got the vertigo
that's that's viral you got the ringing
in the ears
you got the tinnitus that's fire you got
the floaters in the eyes that's viral
you see you guys got the blurry eyes
that are unexplained that's viral right
you guys got the pain that you know is
not a tooth but you got the jaw pain and
you got the neck pain you got all kinds
of different pain in the migraines
viral shingles epstein-barr right
simplex one
all these things cause all these
problems even if you don't have a
shingles rash or a fever blister in the
moment the viruses are still in us they
go into our brain stem
they just they just the neurotoxins go
into the brain stuff
they cause vagus nerve problems they
cause phrenic nerve problems all that
stuff
and what i love about lysine it's a
great way to recover it should be in
somebody's protocol
robinson k says definitely works well
the vitamin c
shock therapy and zinc shock therapy
works incredible it's
here did i tell you guys that
medical medium information right leads
the way advanced information
and then there's a whole bunch of closet
doers
they're closet mm people meaning all the
podcast doctors that take the
information are all doing the celery
juice in the closet
they're all doing the protocols the same
shock therapy for their own calls and
flu's in the closet
they just can't talk about it because
then medical mean gets credit
i've actually heard this many times i've
know i've known doctors over the years
including recently
that no doctors that closet mm
they do all it's all mm closet stuff
big time the podcast people the youtube
doctors
this youtube doctor recently stole all
the shingles information from medical
medium and acted like it came from a
study and then when you look at the
study it's not in there
it's it the closet medical meet is all
about doing you know
doing medical medium in the closet
you can take a lot less of supplements
than what i take or recommend
in the books too you can read the book
and learn how you can take less
right ashley kevin good to see you you
can read how you can take less so let's
keep on moving forward b12
is the next one b12
closet mm robinson case is closet mm yes
podcast doctors are doing medical medium
information
secretly secretly
podcast doctors do they use the
information they use it they drink
celery juice
it's been reported to me over and over
again by the other doctors
thousands of doctors thousands of
naturopaths take medical medium info
that's why they're doing the zinc the
licorice root now and all this protocol
stuff
and they're they're secretly doing
medical medium in their practices or
meaning in their own life yeah
it's good to know let's try to move on a
little bit b12 every single cell in your
body needs b12 so yes it's part of our
immune system because every single cell
in your body every single immune cell
relies on b12 every single killer cell
immune cell basophils
monocytes lymphocytes neutrophils uh
white blood cells
just everything needs b12
diana case meyer says i've heard celery
juice and a lot of similar from before
you were out of diapers laugh out loud
and i know you're lying
because you're lying for sure i know
that
for a fact yeah
medical mediums my celery juice is here
because i
wasn't here before sorry yes
someone might have juiced it once by
itself in a juicer because they juiced
every single fruit and vegetable
as a little experiment let me juice
carrots
let me juice beets let me juice celery
but nobody knew 16 ounces on an empty
stomach 32 ounces for recovery and
health nobody knew what it did nobody
knew about seven clusters of
shots uh salt nobody knew about anything
about it
how to use a therapy all that stuff and
the details matter
yes i did not grow so i'm the first
person on the planet that grew a celery
stick
yeah i'm not claiming i did did celery
ever run through a juicer at one time
yes it did but nobody knew how to use it
as a therapeutic tool to bring
somebody's life back
and if that information isn't there it's
dead in the water and nobody uses it and
no one heals
so yeah and you didn't hear about using
16 ounces of celery juice on an empty
stomach
ever before medical medium you are a
liar
and i might even call you actually dr
nesbit just
hold on huh what
dr nezovitz coming out of surgery really
oh good good good dr nesman's coming out
of surgery
you guys dr nesbitt is coming out of
surgery
we'll find out what dr nesbitt's doing
okay dr nesmet just came out of surgery
you guys
dr nesbitt i was just talking to a diana
yeah dr nesbit nectar nesmet is not only
a board-certified surgeon
but a board-certified psychiatrist yeah
i was just talking to diana who sat
there lying on
yeah on the feed she said that she's
known about celery juice
before i was in diapers first of all
diana doesn't even know how old i am
because i ain't no kid uh
what do you recommend for diana
really now diana dr nesbitt is a board
certified
psychiatrist and is wondering if you
forgot your medication
today he recommends you going to your
doctor immediately
and making sure that all your pills
are correct what else
dr nesbit says that diana
he says make sure you check with your
your physician that your psychiatric
meds
are in order
dr nesbitt said that if your psychiatric
meds aren't in water then
what if they are in order he says dr
nesbit said that if your psychiatric
meds are in perfect order
then you might be ready for a straight
jacket really
it's terrible to say that that's
actually horrible
dr desmond says that for you to sit here
and lie
to try to discredit
me means you're
psycho dr nesbitt is not
really being nice today um dr nesbitt is
always right gia 24 gt
yeah dr nesbit what what do you
recommend for diana
dr nesbit says he recommends diana seek
psychiatric help and care and she might
even be certifiable
that's that's that's terrible
the only thing that's the only problem
with dr nesbitt and i i don't mean to
disrespect you on any level
like dr nesbit i don't mean to
disrespect i just don't know if i like
everything you say and i'm not
supportive
of everything you're saying so uh
i just need that known and i'm not
supportive of everything
dr nesbitt's saying yeah did that i i'm
not supportive
i i yeah dr nesbit that's dr nesbitt's
opinion
okay that gives me back to surgery okay
yep okay all right we
we gotta get going okay dr nesmet's
going back to surgery you guys
talk about the b12 every single cell in
the body relies on it it's critical
every
pepper seed good to see you every single
every single cell in the body relies on
b12
very important to know you guys so i ran
across a lot of the
and then the curcumin great for the
immune system
it's got antibiotic antibacterial
properties
not real real strong ones but it has
them
and i love all that like when mixing it
up because different viruses respond
differently to different things and your
immune system responds differently
so like i like uh curcumin because it's
a natural aspirin
you know if you're working out and you
pull something out
if you like you push yourself too hard
if you're
chronically ill and you don't work out
but yet you push yourself really hard
just trying to get like from one room to
another
curcumin's really great either way you
know it's
it's a major workout for somebody who
has chronic illness to even get into a
shower
sometimes the water can almost knock
people over who have been through hell
and back and they got severe
neurological fatigue
i've seen this for years and and they
can
strain something just literally going to
bathroom or getting up and doing
something or working in the kitchen
lifting something i always love curcumin
as someone's recovering from chronic
illness and coming back from it and they
don't have the muscles yet they don't
have that strength yet
they're still really fatigued and going
through so much but yet they're healing
and on their way to healings they love
human for all these reasons and
for someone who's already healed and
they're exercising again and they got
their life back and they're exercising
right
i thought that dr nesbit really said
some just harsh things sometimes and
that's why you know i told you guys
okay anyway i ran across a whole bunch
of different supplements let's just
talk about some time water i'm gonna put
some thyme in here and let it sit
sit for a while you guys don't mind it's
a great immune system one right there
i'm gonna make a time water
i'm putting time in here in a big
picture of water that's
medical medium informational tools right
there
[Music]
okay gonna have that going as well got
my chaga rishi
tea remember if they want to stick
caffeine into rishi mushroom in your
chaga mushroom they're
totally just
trying to get you hooked and addicted so
you always buy the product
and stay high in caffeine it's just it's
dark
it's dark stuff caffeine knocks down
your immune system so
if you're gonna knock down your immune
system because you're addicted to
caffeine
do it separately for from your chaga and
your rishi do that separately not at the
same
time as your caffeine natural flavors
are in protein powders natural flavors
are in all these different products now
you guys because it's msg and it's
addictive so it does something to the
receptors of the neurons
right here so msg is natural flavoring
it's in supplements so you stay addicted
to your supplements if you see natural
flavorings in your supplements
that's to keep you addicted to the
supplement because msg
uh sets off a signal
francesco is there a complete list of
supplements to have somewhere
make sure you have the medical medium
cleanse the heal check out my posts
on ig just keep on looking for the posts
there's a lot of information in those on
ig
and facebook and so forth right and um
i didn't make the banana roll i got to
do that really quick
so okay
moving things over a little bit you guys
oh my god that scented candle
oh it's terrible i'm not gonna light
those scented candles anymore to fool
around in here like that i can't even
do that anymore as a demonstration
because oh my god
yeah and the time t i didn't do yet but
what i'm gonna do is i'm gonna do
a quick nori roll right here
do the banana nori roll so you guys with
me right now
i'm still here you guys not going
anywhere
okay
got a nori sheet right here i'm gonna
take a lemon
gonna moisten the nori sheet a little
bit
there lemon's incredible for the immune
system
it's my medical mean protocol it's got
the this part of the lemon is a big part
of it too
so let's get a banana going here
all right
mary fox what's best for bloating check
out cleanse the heel i got a bloating
section in there all right we've got a
banana
okay putting it in the middle uh the
noise not in the middle of the noise
sheet right right on the edge of the
nora sheet you see that you guys
okay now i need some garlic
this is a great one too i'll tell you
why this is i didn't tell you guys why
this is so important why it's so
important
okay
this is a medical medium great medical
medium tool right here
i'll tell you why one is
one is because there's no fat in this
meal what people do when they start
getting sick or they're chronically ill
they eat too much fat they fat
themselves to sickness
that's what happens so when someone's
catching a flu or they're getting the
plague i can't tell you how many people
who are getting the plague where their
taste buds were starting to go
mary ann says in your email you're going
to talk about what's coming so we're
going to talk about that
i am at your service
i'm here to please all for free
okay so what you got on here is a banana
you got some garlic clove chopped up
boom thrown on there you got honey right
and
little lemon to moisten the sheet you
got yourself
the immune system nori roll right there
okay why is it the immune system normal
for one it doesn't have fat in there
when people start getting sick they
start coming down with something the
first thing they do
is they eat they eat they're like i need
something i'm getting sick i'm feeling
sick i need to eat and they end up
eating fat oil
they end up having olive oil on
something they need to be nuts and seeds
nut butters i've seen people eat a half
a jar of peanut butter as they were
getting sick
their taste buds get funny they feel
like they have to eat their throat's
getting a little funny so they start
eating and they end up eating a heavy
meal whether it's animal protein or it's
plant-based
fat you know like avocados and nuts and
seeds and oils or
chicken or fish or something they end up
eating and the minute they
throw all that fat in their system they
just explode at the virus and now the
vibe meaning the virus just proliferates
like crazy because you don't
have oxygen anymore in your bloodstream
because it's filled with fat
this is a fat free option that's an
immune
buster because it's a bug buster
you got the garlic and the honey the
honey is anti-viral
so you got the raw honey sitting right
in here you've got iodine in the noria
sheet
iodine is an antiseptic against
pathogens
bananas are antiviral did you guys know
that bananas have antiviral properties
and then you got the garlic which is
antiviral right
great for you know great bugs for any
kind of bugs viruses
bugs and viruses and pathogens explode
they explode they proliferate when you
start downing fat when you're sick
you instead of having them explode by
proliferating them
you want to explode them by killing them
so you want
foods that actually help so you can you
can your immune system
can go and destroy that virus or
anything you're taking can go destroy
the virus the minute you're starting to
get sick you've got that golden seal
going down but you don't need a steak
dinner with your golden seal
because you're going to be doing all
this fat you don't need a chicken dinner
when you're starting to get
sick as you're taking your golden seal
yeah you still should take your golden
seal
but the problem is if everybody's
fatting themselves to death as they're
getting sick or anything's happening
then it defeats the purpose
all right so let's talk about what's
coming
i've already mentioned this months ago
and right now we're
up against a flu now and a plague flu
we're up against two
we're up against a stomach flu right now
that's out there and starting to swish
around out there
it's all kept into the wire no one's
talking about it but everybody's getting
it
there's a reason they don't talk about
it and then you got the plague
up and amp and up cranking up right
so you got that going down too so that's
on the up and up
and we're going to head to a place where
after the summer after because everybody
is like in this this place where they're
just well i'm so sick of the whole thing
i'm so sick of everything going on
and everybody's out and about and doing
their thing but people are passing
around a lot of bugs right now
passed around a lot of epstein bars
because they haven't been around people
so they're passing around a lot of
epstein bars people are
doing a lot of stuff out there and
passing around a lot of simplexes epson
bar and shingles
and then we got the flus going around
and the plague going around and it's
going to take us to the fall
and it's going to take us into early
winter and
it's going to be pretty bad not to
mention what's coming along with this
which is the uptick a massive uptick of
chronic illness
which is going to be hushed hushed for a
while it's not going to be talked about
no one's going to know about it but
people are going to be like
chronically sick fatigue like never
before autoimmune disease is being
diagnosed left and right chronic
neurological problems that are cranial
nerve-based vagus nerve-based right
all the vagus nerve problems all the
cranial nerve problems are going to be
exploding come by this fall
it's already happening now by this fall
and winter
and it's coming to a place where
it's going to be a lot more sicker than
we've ever seen in our history we're
already getting there now we've already
been there but now we're going to
a quick jump heading right now on to the
fall and the winter
anyway you guys i didn't have a chance
to do the time t
i'll do that on ig i'm gonna put tick
tock back on in a little while
and i'm gonna put instagram on in a
little while i'm gonna put clubhouse
back on
you guys on facebook you guys on youtube
youtube i hope you join us somewhere on
joint spirit of compassion in me
somewhere on
tick tock or on ig you can do clubhouse
but you can't see anything on clubhouse
but it's still great all right you guys
i love you much
and member of energy that's the company
not sponsored but that's the good stuff
bees and victor i am is the mary e r g y
dot com not sponsored but that's the
good stuff right there
so i love you guys i'm heading over to
ig pretty soon give me like 10 minutes
clean up set