we're live right now and we're talking
about the top four
supplements a baseline what does that
mean it means a foundation a baseline it
means
the top four with all the different
autoimmune conditions
all the different issues people have all
the different symptoms the mystery
symptoms the eczema psoriasis which is a
mystery
to medical research and science right to
the ms and
als and tingles numbness aches and pains
jaw pain nerve pain neck pain back pain
restless leg syndrome
migraines whatever right all of it all
of it what
is the top four what is the best and
then we'll go after the top four we'll
hit the top
eight right so we'll hit the top eight
as well a lot of people say
what am i going to take or what can i
take well starting at the top four is a
great place to be it's the foundation
it's the baseline that's what we're
talking about
i'm also going to do a couple of things
i forgot to show you guys the other day
like
one thing that i do for myself
personally
how i consume spirulina i didn't talk
about how i consumed spirulina and
barley grass juice powder with this
other technique i use that i've used
since i was younger
and it's a great technique so i'm
excited to show you guys that good to
see you guys coming on
i missed you guys i'm glad everybody's
coming on here tick tock we're live
facebook we're live
youtube we're live clubhouse we're live
and you'll be starting with the top four
i just saw that just now
okay it's great and i'm also going to
answer questions about fulvic acid
people are talking about that lately
okay we'll cover that in a couple of
minutes too and
we'll cover uh cyan cobalamin
to b12 you know psychobalan people are
they're always saying well what about
cyan cambodian what about that one how
come you always talk about
methylcobalamin how can you always talk
about adenosine cabal women
and i'll cover that good to see you guys
coming on austin good to see you brother
glad you're coming on hey uh everybody's
just giving everybody a couple of
seconds before we get moving and
we'll go into you'll see melons right
here in front of me
what's going on with these melons right
some of the crackling open
show you how i do spirulina house with
liz good to see you
i got some different melons right here
and
when melon season's happening i crack
the melon open
i scoop out the seeds and then i'm gonna
try to show you guys how
i do spirulina and borrow the grass
juice powder
using melon so that's gonna be fun
michelle l good to see you
so glad you guys are coming on now so
let's go into it a little bit
all right top four right here zinc is
one of them one of the top four really
important right there
so what now here's the thing not every
zinc works
and that's what people don't understand
so i wasn't clear
perfectly clear as to why i'm so
about vimergy so it wasn't perfectly
clear
like how come i'm so about them like
what makes them
so different like something mind-blowing
i'll give you this example right here
okay
they're the only company that's
has a stabilizer for zinc and
stabilizers is the only way to keep your
zinc
working active and functional so if
vimergy's inc disappeared
and was gone we would have all the other
zincs on the market
they would not be stabilized very
important to know that means their
their their ability to work
and do what needs to be done for zinc
lessens
and it could lessen greatly that
includes
it surviving or even staying stable
and that's how zinc works zinc has to be
stabilized
and so when people say oh no i can order
some other zinc
let me look here oh here's a company
that that's that's got all about
quality and let me check them out and i
can order that zinc
and what people don't realize those
aren't stabilized
and that's a critical part right there
so
if if vimergy zinc disappeared
i would be like well i don't know what i
would do to be honest i know that all
the other zincs would be
destabilized and that's a difference
right there
that means that it may not last more
than a month on the shelf it may not
last more than a week after
manufacturing like no one knows
because when it's not stabilized
anything goes wrong and so this is just
one reason right there that's so
important you guys
we're live on tick tock facebook youtube
clubhouse good to see you guys talk
about the top four
supplements now if you guys don't know
about vimergy it's v and victor i
am as mary e rgy.com go to vimergy.com
that's the best place to go
and i'm not sponsored by these guys okay
this is just the best stuff out there
it's what i give family friends
it's what i take myself so you you might
be somebody that's like wow i know this
company that's really good
they put out a zinc they put out a
liquid sink sulfate
just like vimergy but they did not
learn about stabilizing it
and vimergy did and vimergi's only
company learned about stabilizing
so there's there's that alone is just
unbelievable
lisa says i finally decided to throw out
all the crap in my cupboard
and only go with what you currently
recommend such a difference such a
difference at least it's an unbelievable
difference
and that brings me back to the whole
like the whole game that's happening in
marketing right now
fulvic acid didn't work you guys don't
know the history
and i'll go into that and i'll go into
the rest of the stuff for a second but i
wanna
i wanna cut the head off the snake okay
i wanna cut the head off the snake right
now
the reason why medical medium doesn't
recommend fulvic acid
or humic acid is because they already
tried it on everybody
and it died they tried it on everybody
and it died out
they sold all their expensive marketing
a fulvic and humic acid
20 years ago and then it died out
because it did nothing for anybody
makers of fulvic acid don't know why
anybody is even sick
but the mar here's what they do a new
generation of suckers comes along
over and over again and they re ignited
it
with marketing and money and that's why
you see everybody talking about fulvic
acid fulvic acid
it's really an epic example of how
nobody knows history
you guys don't know the history it never
worked for anyone
it doesn't get somebody out of lupus
fibromyalgia mass aches and pains
chronic fatigue
all these things that medical medium
gets people out of that medical medium
information is known to get
people out of the first time in our
history to get us out of these
conditions to get rid of ra
to get rid of kidney conditions to get
rid of utis forever to get rid of
excellent psoriasis to do all these
things that's medical medium
that's what that is only medical medium
has done that i hate to break it to
anybody who's a
either a doubter or a naysayer or a
critic i hate to break it to you
but everybody stayed sick in the last 20
30 years
unless they learn the tools to heal and
then
all the different scams were tried they
tried the fulvic acid scam
20 years ago 18 years ago and it burned
out because it didn't work and then they
wait
they wait to reignite something when
when everybody forgets
i just i can't even i can go on and on
and i don't want to waste your time on
that stuff
so let's let's uh let's
i mean honestly and they know that we
can become robots and just be like
and not know history because we get
reprogrammed too
you know we get reprogrammed and we just
forget history and then we're just like
folding asset oh my gossip give me the
full vacuumic acid
yeah i give me that okay i'll take this
i'll take that
i you don't think i could put out a
fulvic acid tomorrow
i could put out a medical medium fulvic
acid you don't think
uh you don't think like i think about it
everybody's like fulvic asphalt they
have fluffic acid
so i could put one out tomorrow medical
medium fulvic acid tomorrow
if it was good for somebody you know i
don't own any supplement companies
i don't own any but if i could literally
just start
a supplement company tomorrow call it
medical medium
start with fulvic acid and everybody
would buy it
but then everybody would get ripped off
everybody would get screwed over
because nobody knows it doesn't do
anything
anyway let's keep on moving along i
don't want to waste your time but it's
important these are important questions
that keep on coming up too because
people are like why isn't he talking
about it what do you mean why am i not
talking about
because they didn't been there done that
fulvic acid makers don't know why people
are sick that's the whole point
but that's how it works anyway
good to see you guys coming on let's go
into so i was talking about the zinc
like
so what okay what he has a favorite
company he has a couple of favorite
companies
uh you know a few favorite companies why
is vimrgy such a favorite company
it's the only stabilized zinc and that
makes a difference it really does
so luis vic uh victoria says
um you're wrong fulvic acid takes my
pain away stop all your medical medium
tools
uh louise uh victoria stop all your
medical need tools
stop them all stop your celery juice
stop all the different stuff stop your
spirulina
stop uh put put put all your put all the
bad foods back in
um stop all the medical medium tools
stop all of them and see what your
fulvic acid does
you know stop your celery juice stop
heavy metal detox stuff everything
stop everything right and then see what
fulvic acid does for you
because i'll tell you what happened
before medical medium everybody took it
by the truckloads and stayed sick and
got sicker and then his medical medium
tools siphoned in
and started saving lives it changed
everything
it changed everything so that means that
when you take other things
anyway i'm proud of you i'm glad i'm
glad you feel better no matter what and
i'm proud of you
glad and i'm glad you're here louise
seriously i'm honored you're here
but i'm actually just trying to look out
for everyone
and that's the key like i you know what
i've i've said this before
everybody stop everything medical medium
you know all everything just boom no
medical medium anything
in the whole system everybody stopped
the lemon water that that medical medium
brought back brought in
everybody stopped the celery use that
medical medium brought in everybody stop
everything right you know and just
forget the barley grass cheese powder
out there forget the frozen wild
blueberries
get all that just remove all the tools
get rid of the cilantro because nobody
ate cilantro they chopped up a little
tiny piece and threw it on guacamole
so let's get rid of all the different
leafy greens because nobody ate leafy
greens that's medical medium information
let's get rid of that
let's get rid of all of it and then what
we're gonna have
is a keto diet an old keto diet
not even a new keto diet that has mm
info in it you'll have an old keto diet
and you'll have folic acid you'll have
your zeolite
you'll have your bentonite clay you'll
have your apple cider vinegar
you'll have your you'll have your olive
oil
you'll have all these things right and
then and then see where we are we will
be back to where we were
20 years ago oh my god
marianne said i did fulvic in humic acid
it didn't work
it doesn't work what people do is
they're on so many medical medium tools
now even if they don't know it
indirectly
that it's keeping them afloat so they
can
they can mess they we can afford to mess
up now did you guys know that
like that wasn't like that years ago
michelle l says
did it all she said did it all you can
afford to mess up now
because your wild blueberries are saving
you your celery juice is saving you
you know your low fat is saving you all
these things are saving you
and and that's how it works so let's
move on a little bit don't want to waste
your time on this but it's it's in you
know it comes up
so let's talk about the zinc a little
bit more so
the reason why this zinc helps
and it works for the zinc shock therapy
and it makes a difference and i'm not
sponsored by this company
but they're the only ones that figured
out how to stabilize zinc
and those other companies says i notice
that the bots come
in right the minute medical medium tries
to get people better
with information the bots come in they
come in and they start pushing their
zinc
liquid sulfate they start pushing their
stuff
but it's destabilized it's not
stabilized
but nobody knows this and here's the
other thing
here's the clincher of why here's
another clincher of why vimergy is the
best
here's another clincher you ready for
this
vimergy knows about something in the
supplement company
supplement company world that'll blow
your mind
get ready for this okay all the
supplement companies
are allowed to put stuff in their
products and not listed on the label
if it's a small amount
a small amount the reason why
i am deadly cautious now
about so many companies is because
there's four percent something in there
that's not listed on the ingredient list
that nobody knows about
there's six percent something listed if
that's in there that's not listed on the
ingredient list
demergie knows this and they know
to stay away from that game that game is
real
all the supplement companies have things
in there
you'll never know they're not listed on
the ingredients
so when you say your favorite stuff i
love this
i love that that's going on out there
there is portions of things that they
don't have to list in the ingredient
list
and that right there is a mind blower so
when people say oh he's just
he just likes to take what he takes so
he's gonna of course back it up and
stand behind it no
it's more than that and i don't go into
this nitty-gritty
i don't but it's time to go into this
neighborhood helpful is it's awful
you couldn't believe you couldn't
believe they don't have to list it
there's a there's a law in
supplementation land when everybody
gets their supplements made out there
there's a law
the supplement company the blenders that
make it all for all these people like
hey i woke up this morning i want to get
an investor i'm going to start my own
supplement
it's going to be high quality let me go
do it they go do it
there's there's a portion of
something in there no one lists on the
ingredient list
that's not good for you and it's in all
the supplement companies out there
and nobody knows it's actually evil
okay i'm going into the nitty-gritty
today because you know what happened the
bots came
out i'm trying to like help people you
know compassion
caring you try to help people i want
people to heal
right and then the bots come out that
are paid and all the admin come
out and the mlm people come back try
this v12 try this b12 oh
try this thing try this thing oh no
better do fulvic acid don't listen to
him fulvic acid let me do this let me do
this
and no one realizes you know what so i'm
like okay all right
okay then let's get into the
nitty-gritty let's expose
the crap out there and that's one reason
why i back
them orgy because they're like they tell
they're the worst
nightmare for suppliers they're like you
ain't sticking
you ain't sticking small amounts of
something in our product
you can do that to every other company
like you do you're not doing it here so
that's one thing right there
really important okay so let's
you know it's just like fragrances they
don't list the ingredients of a
fragrance
well supplement companies do something
similar to this all of them do
the manufacturers all do this so that's
one thing right there so
anything you guys take that for
like some info that's really important
just go to another thing that's critical
all right vimergy knows medical medium
standards
so when you go to another liquid zinc
sulfate
when you go to another b12 they don't
care about
mm standards the owners of
those companies don't care about medical
medium standards
you guys care about medical medium
standards because you know it's the best
it's what got people better
all these years right you guys care
about medical medium
standards they don't let me go oh whoa
the bots are out
tried sb12 try this b12 that b12 company
doesn't care about medical medium
standards but you think they
they're all you think they're all
plugged into medical medium standards
like some weird some angel fairy
some magical spell was cast upon all the
other supplements
for them to care about medical medium
standards no
no it's just they don't care
they don't care and these are
differences
for someone who's really sick and they
don't care
you can sell not you can sell
supplements to people all day long to
not so sick people
but when people are really sick it's
make or break a stabilized zinc is make
or break
right the right kind of b12 is make or
break
right these things are make or break
okay
a spirulina that's not from the pacific
ocean
is make or break right
a spirulina that doesn't have a random
piece of mysterious plastic in it
from the pacific spirulinas companies
is make or break all these things matter
when you're really sick
and these are just something so let's
move along there's more stuff too
um you guys if you just got here top
four supplements we'll even go to top
eight okay
and you know especially if you're like
you got a budget if you got a budget
if you're somebody that's like hey you
know i can't afford much right now or i
can't afford
something what do i do well i look at
the top four so if i was in that
situation right and i couldn't afford a
supplement
i would be like well you know i would go
with one of the top four
that's what i would do and here it takes
me to the next place too
what happens is they also get you out
there
where it's like let me go and buy this
really
really cheap junkie product out there
or two products out there that won't
help me heal when i can actually get a
high quality product can make a
difference so that thing happens all the
time
you know and and that's something to
think about
so then we'll talk about like other
stuff so what i love about
you know what i love about vimergy too
is they don't use
palm glycerin key let's go there
okay so i got a lemon balm right here
right here's a cat's claw right here
okay glycerin glycerin in here right
they don't use the palm glycerin now i'm
in the top
four okay you guys i'm in the top four
right palm glycerin isn't the worst
thing in the world
it's not i'm not sitting here
hating on it like it's the worst thing
okay
because because there are there are some
products out there that are decent that
have palm glycerin in it
and sometimes you got to take the good
you take the bad that's what you do
right
but then she went to a different level
and they don't use the palm glycerin
and they use organic when they can on
top of it with their glycerin they use a
flax glycerin
they took it to a level no one has so
they took it to the flax glycerin right
and that alone is mind-blowing because
they insist
on making sure they're not going to do
the status quo
just regular crap that's out there
and so that alone is mind-blowing
somebody's like well i like this other
company i'll go get there's
i'll get use their lemon bomb or
whatever it's like oh you just got palm
glycerin
and vimergy doesn't use palm glycerin
and i didn't go into this nitty gritty
the last time i did a live you guys and
i didn't go into this nitty gritty of
all this
incredible information about the energy
or whatever and
because there's so much to talk about
but these things matter
here's the next one from vimergy right
that blows
blows my mind it might blow your mind
they independently test everything for
bacteria
and the other companies don't think
about that
that right there independently
test for bacteria they independently
test for bacteria
when the other companies with their
spirulinas
and their supplement products are not
independently testing for bacteria never
mind testing for bacteria
most of them think about that one
okay so lisa angle said their lemon balm
really helped me
it helps me i'm under a lot of stress i
do take it i showed you guys how i take
it
and lorraine elle says thanks for going
through the nitty gritty
i know it doesn't make everybody happy
but thanks lorraine
robinson the details do matter they do
and i'm giving you guys the details
right here
um so yeah
so what one supplement would i suggest
on tick tock i just saw that right there
right
so if someone's not going to someone's
not going to get any supplements
fine right they're not going to be able
to get any or they're not interested or
however it is but they're interested in
one supplement right
i'd go i would go with one from the top
four
and then i would think about what's
going on in your life
do you think you're really viral do you
think you're really viral okay
so did you look up your symptom did you
look up your condition did you
see what's wrong with you because makers
of the other supplements out there in
the world like makers of the trendy
stuff
of colostrum and collagen and fulvic
acid or whatever that's out there right
makers they don't know why you're sick
but you can find out why you're sick so
what's wrong with you that matters right
there
okay so are you viral
do you think you got neurological
fatigue did you did you suffer from
neurological lyme did you suffer from
any kind of do you have aches and pains
you have tingles and numbness that's
mysterious vertigo anything
tinnitus ringing in the ears dizziness
right whatever it is
because a great one to start with is
zinc
that's a great one do you have
tendonitis do you have restless leg
syndrome do you have all that kind of
stuff then you're going into nerves
neurological so
you're using zinc to actually help
with what's causing the nerve problems
and then if you venture on to a second
supplement
it would be like the b12 so the b12
would be
the next one because now you're on the
b12 the b12 is to bring back
nerves that have been damaged hindered
by low-grade viruses or anything else
going on or toxins
so b12 is another important one you
could either pick
either or if like if that was me i'd be
like okay maybe i'll go with b12 when
that's over with i'll move to the zinc
meaning you
you empty the bottle you used it now hey
i'll go with the zinc
and that's an option too by the way it's
off amazon.com us it's a medical
textbook it's packed
take advantage of it so
so we're going into the top four i got
them right here just letting you know
i got the micro c i got the lemon balm i
got the zinc
i got the b12 so we're covering
this information so one of the very
important tidbits or pieces of
information that's critical
okay is that
vimergy independently tests for bacteria
that right there wins me over because
chlorella
which doesn't remove toxic heavy metals
but yet the chlorella machines going out
there right the marketing the mlm
and everything else they do for
chlorella so everybody's on chlorella
right
that not only doesn't get metals out to
take somebody to the finish line
because that's been out there it never
got anybody better see they repeat
history over and over again for the new
set of suckers
well chlorella has had bacteria in it
dangerous bacteria that's really mauled
a lot of people over the years
one of the reasons why i never
recommended it and i stayed
crazy far away from chlorella
is i've watched it rip people's guts
apart
and set them back for years and
sometimes never recover
they've never recovered from the damage
chlorella did
and that stuff isn't independently
tested for bacteria
so not only is chlorella not the option
but spirulina is better but then there's
a question of what spirulina is best
out there and then it falls onto vimergy
for the reasons of
of what they do and the quality of the
product
oh my god i'm throwing my chlorella out
anybody that's a friend or a family
member or something like a cousin that
reaches out to me that's like hey can
you kind of go over my subs with me
i'm like all right all right let's take
a look like i'm on chlorella
are you kidding me my god throw it out
it scares me actually
it scares me so um
let's uh move a little bit more
let's go back and let's back into the
top four we're in the top four right now
why is the top four important let's head
there now so if you're somebody that can
get the top four
you got the vitamin c the micro c
you got the lemon balm you got the zinc
you got the b12 so let's cover why why
would this be in the top four
it's important enough so if you look
here in medical medium climbs to heal
right you'll see what you need to know
about supplements in here
and it's a top four for a reason okay
and because most
everybody's suffering with symptoms
that are viral viral related
toxin related from viruses
okay so and their nerves
are giving them symptoms let's go back
over that
why is this the best top four most
people are suffering from
nerve problems usually caused
by viral issues aches pains tingles and
numbness ringing the ears tick spasms
floaters in the eyes uh dizziness
vertigo restless leg syndrome
back pain body pain neck pain and i'm
gonna explain
why each one is important and cranial
nerve problems
cranial nerve problems right there
okay there's a method
to this a method that's
extremely beneficial and helpful for
people
because most people with their migraines
their aches and pains their dizziness
they're ringing the ears that's right
okay
the floaters in the eyes are dealing
with problems
they're dealing with optic nerve issues
optic neuritis even though it's not
diagnosed
people have all these symptoms they're
dealing with cochlear nerve problems
their ears they're dealing with all
migraines trigeminal nerve problems
pain all on the side of their head the
side of their face their temple the back
of their neck the forehead
all that right they're dealing with
vagus nerve problems you guys nausea
tingles and numbness on their arms their
torso okay
um tightness of chest high anxiety
panic right they're dealing with all
that cranial nervous issue
issues you guys and by the way makers of
all the trendy stuff out there don't
even know about any of this stuff unless
they pull little
tidbits from medical medium this is all
original
unique information that saved lives
around the world about cranial nerves
about the trigeminal nerve and all these
other issues and viruses causing it
and metals it's where it originates
and so what people are dealing with
so if i walk down the street and spirit
of compassion is with me
like always and people are around and be
like
trigeminal neuralgia right here they got
the shingles virus this person has a
simplex one virus right here
causing problems with them this person's
got two epstein bars
this person's got an hhv6 they're all
releasing neurotoxins
this person's got restless legs because
of it this person's got
jaw pain because of it teeth pain in the
back here this person has pain in the
back of the neck
because of it and it's all cranial nerve
stuff
so the top four there's a reason for the
top four
and how important it is baseline i call
it
baseline okay the baseline is here
because of that reason and when you
learn what's wrong with you it even
comes more clear right
so okay let's go a little bit
let's go a little bit more so let's go
into why with these let's hit b12
cranial nerves they get injured they get
frayed
they fray like a piece of yarn
just so you know the migraines the
trigeminal nerve issues
all the problems with the nerves okay
the back pain
that's that's meaning like the back of
the neck pain right
the all the other issues tingles and
numbness from vegas nerves tightness of
the chest the panic tightness of the
throat
heart palpitations heart palpitations
all these things from the cranial nerves
your vagus nerve
trigeminal nerve right your facial nerve
facial sensitivities your hair hurts so
when you pull your hair
it hurts your scalp right all that
is those cranial nerves okay
fatigue neurological fatigue where it's
unexplainable
i'm tired every day i can't really push
through my energy is not there
cranial nerves that's why the b12 is so
important it's in the top four
that's november gb12 if you guys just
got on here watch this live from the
beginning again
on youtube if you want okay and tick
tock if you guys just got on there watch
it live on youtube if you want
and that's why the b12 is important why
this b12
and not another b12 okay
i'm gonna give you the rundown about
that too it's a combination of
methylcobalamin and adenosine cobalamin
the combination that makes a difference
it doesn't have hydroxycobalamin in it
because that one messes up the other
two and people don't realize it doesn't
have a cya cobalamin in it because that
one
doesn't absorb so
when it comes down to the right b12 it
matters to healing nerves now what does
b12 do for the nerves
it helps repair them nerve cells
need b12 or they can't repair
they can't repair they can't repair you
can't repair those cranial nerves
without b12 being able to be there to
repair
okay let's move on a little bit let's
hit zinc
zinc stops the cytokine storms from the
flu
stops the storms from the plague
zinc stops the cytokine storms but it
also
stops your immune system from getting
overreactive
and under reactive and everybody's
immune system
is either overreactive or underreactive
overreactive or unreactive overreactive
or underactive then that's what
everybody's immune system is
and that's why the zinc matters
we're all deficient in zinc one way or
another we're all deficient because the
crops don't have it
and if you think pumpkin seeds is going
to give you enough zinc and an oyster is
going to give you a zinc you're mistaken
there's very little zinc in that to
begin with which leads me to the other
trend that's happening now is like
oyster related
products now it's real smart let's take
the most polluted thing out of the ocean
fill the dioxins and toxic heavy metals
and let's make it into a supplement
that's what i mean though there's no
sensibility
it's almost like it's anybody and
everybody has lost their mind when it
comes down to stuff out there
and it's sad you know you were chugging
oysters laugh out loud chris were you
chugging oysters because of just you
liked oysters at the time
or was it because you wanted the zinc
okay anyway this is the most gentle
thing
the liquid sulfate but stabilized
and that's the difference right there so
that
so why is the zinc important and why do
you want to keep your immune system
level because it's up against pathogens
in our immune systems is up against
pathogens that's why
we're up against the epstein bars the
simplex one
right people have to understand some
you've ever had fever blister
and it went away the virus didn't go
away
the virus sits in the cranial nerves
virus sits in the liver that's where the
virus sits
and it creates other symptoms along the
way and then you're starting to get all
these other symptoms and you're like
well wait a minute what is going on here
and zinc's critical
for stopping that from happening so the
little bugs that create the simplex one
and
all the different bugs it actually helps
you know there's people out there that
get the worst debilitating set of
shingles
they could ever even imagine making them
almost want to commit suicide
shingles being so so harsh so bad
right a version of it so bad like
ripping through their neck their mouth
their face
some really bad shingles out there and
if they only had enough zinc in them or
the right kind of zinc along the way if
they only knew how to take care of
themselves what foods not to eat having
the right sink
it's so sad i've seen a lot of sad sad
sad situations
all right let's move on to lemon balm
why would lemon balm be in the top four
guys if she just came on i'm talking
about vemma g2 them rgbs and victor
imergy.com
if you watch the beginning of this video
you'll see the reasons why vimergy is
far surpassed
supreme over anything else out there and
i'm not sponsored by vimergy
very important no and i'm not a
shareholder of energy
it's critical to know this stuff so why
would
lemon balm be in the top for everybody
because of stress
because everybody's nerves are frazzled
because
everybody's nerves are inflamed
that's why they're sick
their nerves are inflamed all your
mystery symptoms that you get
throughout the body many of them are
because your nerves are
inflamed the cranial nerves are inflamed
that's why
pertinent information beyond and
lemon bomb right
it does two things one thing is
antiviral
it's an antiviral very important when
used as an
antiviral the other thing is because of
the nerves it's an antibacterial too
what i love about is a lot of people
though have the strep bacteria causing
utis causing conjunctivitis causing
styes
causing chronic sinusitis causing
chronic ear infections causing lung
infections they'll have
strep bacterial vaginosis bv they'll
have
shrek what i like about it being in the
top
four what i love about that
is people are walking around with strep
bacteria all through them
and limb bombs a great antibacterial for
the strap
but it's also an incredible nervine
it's an incredible nerve calmer
it's what i love about it soothes the
vagus nerve
the vagus nerve think behind so many
people's suffering
that's why it's in the top four that's
why it's part of the baseline
and let's move on to and here's the
thing
okay here's the thing people would be
like oh i'll go look for a lemon bomb
then
i don't want to get the vimerage you
want because all because all the
marketers are coming out now use our
lemon balm use our lemon balm because
aw is talking about lemon balm we know
that we can do a with the sharks can
come in and do a feeding frenzy
just go on to his his platform and just
be like pushing there's
another b12 push another liquid zinc on
somebody
and get people enticed the bots will
come out the paid bots will come out
left and right
right and but they don't realize yeah
guess what and you get that other lemon
balm
and they'll be a small percentage of an
ingredient that you don't know about
that's not good for you that's inside
that lemon balm
because the supplement companies all
have to
abide by some evil rule
that you can that that the suppliers
that the manufacturers
put things in there nobody knows about
and members just say
uh-uh not gonna happen not gonna happen
with vimergy
there's no way we're letting anything in
here that can hide
and not have to be recognized and that's
why and that's one reason plus the lemon
balm they source is
the best through the roof move on
deanna says i watch so many of these
lives and they are invaluable with info
but this is what so many need so they
can just start i know
i don't know i'm honored to hear deanna
seriously
so vitamin c all right here we are
vitamin c is in the top four because
it's still that important
it's still that important without
vitamin c
we die but that brings me back to
without b12 we died
without b12 or vitamin c we die did you
know that
scurvy was a real thing okay
without any fruit or a squeeze of lemon
or squeeze of lime or an orange too many
years going by
without any kind of fruit without a
berry without an
apple too many years too many months
going by
without fresh vegetables that also have
some vitamin c in there right
vitamin c if you take out any vegetable
whatsoever and you take out ever if you
just lived off of only
canned meat and only canned meat and
this isn't an anti-meat campaign because
i'm pro-animal protein and i'm
pro-plant-based if you're plant-based
steak plant-based
if your animal protein that's what you
like to stay for animal protein
but just learn the tools so you can heal
because i'm not on one side of the aisle
or another because it ain't about that
you can be sick when you're vegan
you can be sick as a dog when you're
plant-based and you could be sick as a
dog as a keto dude
maybe sick as a dog as an animal protein
person
that's why animal protein diets have
incorporated so much medical medium
information by now it's unbelievable and
it's sickening too watch because they
won't say anything back to medical
medium we'll just
oh oh we better bring in that now
because medical medium has a record of
getting more people better than we've
ever seen we better bring this into our
new diet
the vitamin c is critical right without
it if you lived off of canned meat
and only canned meat it would be
devastating
if you lived okay let's just say
something else let's say something else
that has no vitamin c in it
what if you lived off of canned
mushrooms or can you lived off of
canned uh something that doesn't know
vitamin c just canned beans
it's okay say you're not an animal
protein person and you're not gonna do
canned meat
a little of canned beans just canned
beans only but only
be devastating because you
you would lose all your vitamin c to the
point where you would just go down with
the ship just like they did in the old
days
so question mark emma says why can't we
use supplements on the mono cleanse
you can you can use supplements on the
mono cleanse you can
um emma do you have the book read the
mono cleanse section
read the monocle section i know we want
to jump like
head into things and stuff but i always
say have
read the supplement chapter 2 in here i
always say
have the have the book have the textbook
it's on sale 51 off amazon.com us right
now take advantage of that angelic price
so they call it now angelic where can i
get those
so panchayats vimorgy.com v is in victor
i
am as mary e rgy.com so vimergy.com
that's where you get these all right so
vitamin c is that important so
what makes this vitamin c better than
you why do i hold
this vitamin c because i can hold
anybody's vitamin c
if there's an incredible vitamin c out
there i'll hold it and i'll show you
guys
but there isn't one that matches this
the others are like battery acid
that's the problem that's the problem
like battery acid you got sensitive
tummy that stuff will just burn your
stomach
it's hard on the system vitamin c's the
heart on the system and i know a lot of
you guys know
this i bet you a lot of you guys have
tried vitamin c's and they're hard
they're hard and this is the one that's
gentle the microc
is a whole different combination
different make and model
one that's it it it the others are
antiquated compared to so that's why i
love that
i could take more of it so when i take
vitamin c you know i take six capsules
three times a day right that's what i'll
do
six capsules three times and i saw
somebody in the comment section
say if aw is so healthy why would he
take that much sup
i saw that i don't know if you guys saw
that right if anthony william is so darn
healthy
why wouldn't he need no supplements
uh i'm up against all the same thing you
guys are up against
chemtrails falling out of the sky
fragrances i'm breathing in left and
right wherever i go
that are highly toxic and dangerous
people scented candles coming off of
their clothes
air fresheners i'm up against flu
viruses i'm up against the plague
if i'm out and about right i'm up
against all that stuff but the
differences between me and you maybe are
actually i could be wrong you guys might
not sleep that much differences between
me
i don't sleep that much and so you
better believe
i get jacked up on vitamins because
i i you know the other night i had three
hours i think i when i did that live the
other day i had two and a half hours of
sleep or something i forgot what it was
ridiculous it was three hours
so i'm writing the book and and that
book has a deadline
it has a deadline and i got to get it in
in the book
and i can't cut corners on the book i
can't say
my crowd will be happy with whatever i
wrote down here
they'll be they'll be fine no it has to
be the best book ever written
out of medical medium right it has to be
like a book upon all books and i feel
that
know that i can't let you guys down
that's the medical mean book series
the last thing i need you guys is
reading a medical medium book and be
like
huh like i thought my mind was going to
get blown
and and i gotta blow your minds because
i want you guys to have the healing
information to save lives but also want
i want your minds blown because medical
meme information blows my mind
comes from spirit of compassion anyway i
got a deadline so i'm on less sleep
working really hard right now so i'll
work 18 hours and days
19 hours in a day sometimes 20 hours a
day i'll end up on my office floor
right i'll end up my uh i'll be on my
office floor dressed up like this
like curled up on the office floor with
my phone over here
to the side right all these papers on me
and i wake up and be like huh huh where
am i
if you're if you're on a tight budget
it's worth
thinking about the top four
okay if you're on a tight budget you're
gonna buy just one supplements worth
picking one out of the top four
so why is vitamin c important let's go
into it because it is a great antiviral
viruses hate vitamin c and if you have
enough vitamin c floating through your
bloodstream
floating through your bloodstream but
not vitamin c floating through there
then you're gonna protect yourself it's
great protection
also cells need vitamin c to thrive
so all the different cells throughout
our body brain cells everything
need vitamin c to thrive
important now selena we so are my life
has changed forever and i don't know
where it'd be without
mm i'm selena manager here thank you for
being here today
guys are incredible so anyway i got some
shot glasses here
now i got a couple other things to talk
about so i was talking about
i'm also going to crack open a melon and
show you guys what i do so if you guys
are thinking about running off because i
know some of you are so busy i know all
of you guys are busy but if you're going
to run off or something you think you
caught the show you didn't catch the
show
because i'm going to show you something
i didn't show you with melons how i eat
spirulina and barley grass juice powder
it's simple really but you know so i
want you guys
also to know we got more to cover today
so hang in there i also
i want you to read what you need to know
about supplements if you don't have the
medical medium book
cleanse the heal please consider getting
it try to get it free at the library if
you can't buy it
but it's 51 off at amazon.com it's a
price that can't be beat right now
it's insane really that price it costs
more to print out the book
details matter and they're in there so
let's go a little bit we'll go a little
bit further so
there's a question out there one
question is
how come psychobala mean you're not
talking about that type of coenzyme that
b12 how come you're not talking about
that b12 one is it doesn't absorb that's
the bad b12
that's the b12 that's in b12 shots
that doesn't work that's the b12
that's in crappy b12 supplements
and just because you might find the
adenosine kabbalah man and the
methicobalamin
the good b12 and another supplement
doesn't mean there's not that hidden
junk i told you about plus fillers plus
alcohol and everything else
and natural flavors and msg
so and this one doesn't have that and
that's the bemrg one
okay that's the vimergy b12 that i was
just talking about right
but
bad supplements give supplements a bad
name
that's how it works bad cleanses
give cleanse cleanses a bad name all
right
couple questions so why don't you talk
about cyocobalamin first of all that
stuff was
the conventional b12 the really bad
stuff that was in the b12
patches 20 years ago so if you wanted to
go to a store and you wanted to buy a
b12 supplement they had b12 patches so
you would buy the b12 patches they had
silocobalamin in it
and it didn't work it doesn't work and
it's toxic
so if anybody is like no sila
cobalamin's the best because i saw that
in the comments too
so i think that the youtube comment is
like solid kabbalah is there like oh my
god what planet are we on
like who's telling people this stuff
that it's the best
this stuff was not only toxic that was
conventional medicine's bad b12 that was
the one that doesn't even absorb that's
the one in the b12
shot that poisons people that's
sayakabalamin is the bad one
and once again it's people who don't
know why anybody's sick that talks about
it and once again it's like these
this history comes back to haunt us
because we don't know about the history
so it comes back and we get involved in
it and then we become that person that's
like whoa cytobalam and that's the one
to use and you're like whoa you just did
everybody a disservice even mentioning
that
okay so let's get into the next thing
here's the question right here
methylfolate so vimergy's got a
methylfolate right
they got a methylfolate and people are
like well don't you take folate with
b12 don't you take folate with
methylcobalamin
yeah it's great to take together it's
great to not you don't have to take them
together
it's great to take them together
methylfolate is important
it is but you can also get benefits from
b12 without methyl folate
they don't have to be together dr fahn
yeah
psychobalan is the bad stuff
so that's the answer that question
that's out there right
for more free information you should
sign up to medical medium newsletter go
to medicalmedium.com get all the free
info
check out the directory
medicalmedium.com as well so let's move
on to the
other four supplements here so i just
showed you the baseline i showed you the
top four
supplements the b12 the the micro c the
lemon balm the zinc
right now
i got these next top four right here
spirulina lysine cat's claw
curcumin okay so why are these the next
top four the top eight why are we going
into the top eight now
okay people are sick because
of pathogens cat's claw
is an incredible anti-pathogen
supplement cat's claw very important to
know
neurological lyme lyme doctors now play
with cat's claw
they use cat's claw now because medical
medium
brought that to the world nobody knew to
use cat's claw for a lime
neurological lines cat squat right
another thing too people have all kinds
of different issues
that are viral related they got the
chronic fatigue syndrome they got the
fibromyalgia they got all the ra they
get all their problems
multiple sclerosis whatever cat scale is
a great one
well brand uh victorious the energy v is
in victor
i am as in mary e r g y dot com
themorgy.com go straight to their
website
okay and so cat squad is fantastic for a
lot of reasons one is antibacterial
really good one if you were diagnosed
with candida
you want cat's claw and the irony is
cat's claw's not gonna kill off your
candida because candida is not why
you're sick
if you're diagnosed with candida you've
got sibo which is streptococcus
cat's clock kills off the strep and then
your candida
problem goes away check with your doctor
what's right for you
i'm just saying this is what i offer a
friend and family or me myself would do
castle is great for sibo it's great for
intestinal bacteria that's out of
control
it's great for viral issues that's what
i love about cats that's why it's part
of the eight
the top eight give you the top four
moving into the top eight
right
so julie's saying my hair is falling out
and i have bald spots what should i do
and my
skin is very thin and bleeds under
under skin what should i be taking check
out the book right here when you get a
chance
sounds like you don't have cleanse to
heal the information's in there to start
getting your life together
ask your doctor if the book's right for
you amazon.com 51
off okay lysine why is lysine in the top
eight
because everybody's dealing with hepatic
viruses
people are all sick because of hhv-6
hhv-7 sedimental virus shingles viruses
epstein-barr viruses simplex one viruses
simplex two viruses and all their
mutations
that's why people are sick lysine's
great for the herpetic family
that's why it's part of the topic people
can get better they can
they can and they don't have to try to
experiment with a zeolite or a fulvic
acid or a
collagen to do so or a bentonite clay or
a charcoal powder or a fish oil oh my
god or a probiotic oh my god
okay
you know people get flu
people get flus all year long
they get flus all year long and they're
they're they're beaten down by viruses
well people are sick with chronic
illness speak like autoimmune because of
all these other viruses herpetic viruses
cytomegalovirus the h86hv7 hhv9
10 through 16 undiscovered over 60
varieties of epstein bar over 30
varieties of shingles mm information but
all these different viruses and that's
why people are sick just like when
people get the flu virus they're sick
from the flu virus when they're sick
from the flu virus
so lysine's a good part of that one so
let's go into the next one
curcumin right first of all dimmer zeke
curcumin
far surpasses the others i won't bore us
with like details about that already
given
so many reasons why the quality is off
the chart right
but what i love about curcumin because
it acts like a natural aspirin
people are inflamed and it's like a
natural aspirin
jennifer smith says i can't get my son
to do heavy metal detox so i was hoping
zeolite
might be a doable compromise jennifer if
that was my son i wouldn't be playing
with zeolite
i wouldn't the zeolite train came into
town
many years ago and died out and
disappeared for a reason
and now it's back in town to hitch a
ride onto the heavy metal detox movie
and and you can do what you want do what
your doctor tells you right
for your son if it was my son i wouldn't
be doing zeolite and i'll tell you one
of the reasons is because there's a
whole bunch of zeolites
that are not edible and they get mixed
and dusted
do you guys know about this i want you i
want to ask you guys a question this
will tell me how much you guys also know
what seasoned or not right
do you guys know this ready
if you're eating a gluten-free product
right that's made in a factory
that they also make products that have
gluten they have to forewarn you right
because the gluten-free product gets
dusted
by the not by the by the gluten product
you guys know that right so glute like
gluten-free breads
are made right or they're made in
factories a lot of times with gluten
breads
so even though the gluten-free breads is
gluten-free it's
also it's the same thing with like nuts
if people have nut allergies they have
to list
nut allergies because it's processed in
a plant where they're also doing nuts
right
and then the nut dust is going on top of
the other product
that you think there's no nuts in you
guys know this right
anybody know this it's important you got
it
zabo you got it cross contamination
well that's the zeolite world and
there's a bunch of zeolites that are
like asbestos you cannot actually
swallow it or eat it it's not diges
it's not it's it's actually a hindrance
to the colon intestinal tract
so there's zeolites you cannot ingest on
any level but they're also
dusted on top of zeolites you can ingest
and nobody knows the difference because
it's not monitored
it's why one of the reasons why i'm done
with zoi
done done done but guess what
the admin paid by the zeolite company
zeolites back in town zeolite trains
back town
and they see that the heavy metal detox
movie has saved a lot of lives the mlm
world has come back into town with their
zeolites and they see that the medical
medium
heavy metal detox smoothie is famous now
it's in all the juice bars around the
world
everybody talks about it it's worldwide
famous
and it gets metals out and then the
zeolite world said hey you got to take
the zeolite with the heavy metal detox
smoothie
but your benefits are coming from our
zeolite that's where it's coming from
do you know do you do you know anything
any more disgusting than that
no and that's how it works
there's no regulatory regulations
on mixing the zeolite clays
there's zeolites in the earth that are
mined out of the earth that are used for
industries
and they're getting cross-contaminated
with zeolite that's ingestible
and nobody knows it so when we take your
zeolite products
it's dusted from bad stuff
is dr nesbit coming on aw
yeah dr nesbitt will come on for you
april
we'll i'll ask dr desmond to come on
maybe when yeah we'll bring dr nesbit on
yeah michelle miller says nor is all the
ingredients listed
exactly michelle so when you get your
zeolite
all the ingredients aren't listed
there's
almost 10 of that bottle has something
you don't even know that's in there
and that's how it goes boom
this is what it is all right talked
about what i love about the curcumin
it acts as a natural aspirin so many
people are hurting
they're hurting okay and curcumin
cumin is anti-bug too
it's anti-bug for like basic bugs and
stuff
right basic one staff and things like
that and all that curcumin's actually
it's great but it but i like it because
it has
a calming effect it is phytochemical
compounds that soothe
nerves and muscles and i like that this
one doesn't have additives fillers
doesn't have alcohol doesn't have all
that other junk in it
everything else citric acid that's in
all the other supplements so let's go
into
this is incredible quality it's not just
any curcumin let's go into one more
you guys are we having fun i'm trying to
have fun here april i'll try to bring
dr nesbit on dr nesbitt is a very busy
doctor
extremely busy surgeon and i'll see if i
can get him on here
i know he's doing something right now
but we'll get him on don't worry
so anyway spirulina is in the top eight
it's important gets out the toxic hectic
metals
but it's so nutrient dense
irma says vimergy curcumin has helped me
greatly with my restless leg syndrome
incredible incredible
michelle l says my husband does well on
curcumin amazing
yup lemon balm love human is great for
pain
amazing yeah
it's it's incredible so anyway i'm gonna
crack open a melon i'm going to talk
about spirulina
maybe in the barley grasses but let's
before we go right to there because i
know we're
we've got still a couple minutes i
talked about celery force the other day
and someone left a comment and said
he's got to be kidding i wasn't kidding
when i first took the product it happens
every day when i take the product
in like eight minutes i was cleaning out
my freezer i wanted to clean up my
freezer
and clarity came like i've never it was
like almost
it was bizarre this clarity that came
and because it's got the inositol the
right kind of blend of inositol in there
and it woke me up i had something like a
couple hours of sleep that night i was
working all night and everything and
then i was up in the morning
and i was cranky right and i took the
celery force
and it was like someone played a joke on
me it was almost like not only was i
alive and awake but i had
clarity in the in the most strangest
sense ever and
and it was like also i had to clean the
freezer cleaned out i had you know in a
whole bit
and that's something that's just
mind-blowing i don't know if anybody
else is hooked on
celery force but i've been hooked on it
ever since from
from it's incredible for the adhd all
that stuff that people have
i'm hearing about it all the time
anybody that has adhd when they're on
celery for like
why is it clearing up adhd there's no
celery in it by the way
katie says between my celery juice and
the morning and celery force i can think
and focus again in work that's
priceless it's precious yeah
lori says absolutely not kidding celery
force is the bomb is it not
it's it's it's unbelievable what it does
amy tang says i have felt that celery
i sorry i have felt that clarity with
celery force also isn't that
unbelievable
sometimes it hits me in 12 minutes
sometimes it's 15 minutes but sometimes
it's eight minutes
he showed us the celery forest has
helped me so much with my brain
fog i love it for brain fog for people i
love that
i know it's it's just it's crazy so
anyway
um quick run down in spirulina why is it
in the top eight
let's hit that right now you guys okay
because getting out of toxic heavy
metals getting the toxic heavy metals
out of her body is critical
critical get the mercury out critical to
get the aluminum out
critical to get all those poisons and
toxins out i don't
like the pacific spirulinas anymore
the ocean got too dirty okay karen says
how much
curcumin to take daily have lots of
inflammation
you should read the book and take a look
at the supplement section and the
illnesses and conditions look for your
condition
bring it to your doctor ask your doctor
what he thinks she thinks
so this is the purest form of spirulina
out there breaks my heart when i see all
the other bad spirulinas out there
because i know people aren't getting
what they need
not to mention they're not independently
bacterial
tested independent bacteria
tested from bemidji that difference
changes everything it breaks all the
rules
and it changes everything people think
this stuff's a joke like you know like
the supplement quality difference are
you kidding there's a huge
difference huge difference you guys
we're live on tick tock live on youtube
live on facebook
live on clubhouse and so anyway
we're on that right there let's let's
crack open a melon so here's something i
do and i just want to give you guys a
quick rundown on this
is so i love these honeydew melons
when i can get them a lot of times you
can't get them a lot of times you have
to wait until they ripen that's another
thing too
so you got to learn how to ripen them
robinson says don't they test for heavy
metals too though yes of course they do
i'm saying of course they do
independently they independently test
for toxic heavy metals
there's a difference when you
independently test the test for toxic
heavy metals huge difference
it's everything it means everything and
that and that's what's incredible
absolutely all right let me get a spoon
now
a couple different spoons i didn't show
you guys this
the other day because i forgot i got a
lot going on
so i'm scooping up the seeds just bear
with me here
right and you can do mil in a couple
different ways you can cut it up in
cubes you can throw it inside a bowl
right you can do that you guys i'm glad
you guys are here today
um amazing so what i
like to do is i like to cut open a half
a honeydew
and i like to take the honey honeydew to
my desk
and this is a canary i think oh this is
like a crenshaw
uh and then there's different kind this
is a cantaloupe right here i got a
couple different melons right here right
cat yes put your money into the vimergy
products you will be amazed over time
it really makes a difference and and all
these things make a difference about it
let me
let me get this guy over here for a
second
all right
so i like to do with my spirulina
is i like to put it on my honeydew melon
so
this is a favorite thing of mine for a
long long time so i take
some spirulina and i sprinkle it on
i sprinkle it in the hole right
right in there sprinkle it in there is
what i do
okay so i got my spirulina in the melon
and then i take barley grass juice
powder
i'm gonna grab some of that i'll
sprinkle that in there too
so
that's how that's how i consume it a lot
it's not barley grass this is barley
grass juice powder that detail matters
right there
people that know that for so long they
just saw i'll go get
barley grass well then that did nothing
barley grass doesn't do anything it has
speaker barley grass juice powder
okay and there's no gluten in it very
important to know
and if you get a crappy barley grass
cheese powder it's so sad because
you know you try to you try to make sure
in any way in your capacity people have
information so they can heal and then
someone will be like
i use this barley grass juice powder i'm
like okay good luck
because under 10 of that is going to be
products people don't even know that's
in there it could be
msg it could be anything in there and
they don't have to put it on the label
and you know why is it that good because
a company said so or is there actual
data and facts of why they actually you
know have it that good
it's just it's actually crazy really so
this is what i do and what i do is i
scoop out the melon like that so that's
one way i have it
you can cube up the melon you can put it
in a bowl
and i'll take this to my desk and i'll
just eat it like that while you know a
ripe melon and i'll actually put the
spoon in and i'll have a little bit of
that like that i've done that so many
times
elizabeth edwards i saw barley grass
juice powder on amazon
that people are buying for heavy metal
detox that they
clearly say they grow with aluminum in
the soil
you can give me all the information i
won't use it
you can give me all the answers so i can
get better but i can't get better
self-destruct i will do the wrong thing
self-destruct that's what we do as
robots
self-destruct self-destruct we're robots
we're sheepless people
give us the answers and we'll still do
it wrong give us the answers and we'll
still do it wrong
we're paddle moo we're sheeple
robot robots self-destruct self-destruct
we'll do it wrong we'll do it wrong
we're sheeple
we're paddle we're steeple we're paddle
we'll do it wrong we'll do it wrong
he said the right thing but doesn't
matter we'll do it wrong we'll do it
wrong
self-destruct pull the pin out of the
grenade pull the pin in the braid
all right not fooling around but wait a
minute
dr nesbitt has to come you gotta see if
i get doctor that's been
gotta call him up
all right i
swear i'm gonna need some celery for
some lemon balm
i'm gonna need some lemon balm actually
because exactly
and you're ready it's like yeah i tried
the barley grass juice powder
and i'm not getting better um doing the
heavy metal detox
and emm is just wrong he's must be wrong
no you're using the wrong stuff
yeah is dr nesbitt is he busy
is he in surgery no he just got out of
surgery
oh great great can he talk can he come
can he come over
um yeah well i'm not going to take much
of his time
somebody at april asked for dr nesbitt
yeah april
gee i think she's on youtube or on
facebook
yeah we're live right now can you get
can you ask dr nesbit to get here as
quick as possible
please if that's okay all right good
doctor nesmet's on his way
and here's dr nesbitt sue says how i
seek dr nesbitt sorry about this
asus just asking a question now i see
why you're stressed
so i'm sorry people are nuts dr nesbitt
are people really nuts
dr nesbitt is a board-certified
psychiatrist but also a board-certified
surgeon
he's a cardiologist he's a pulmonologist
and he's got a thriving practice he just
came out of surgery what did you just
who did you just work on dr nesmet works
on famous people
did you dr nesbitt says he just removed
what did you just remove
dr nesmet just removed somebody's spleen
dr nesbitt do you think we could have
done something though
like maybe we could have dr nesbitt do
you know medical medium protocols
you do well did you was the spleen
inflamed
it was inflamed well you know that's
epstein-barr virus that inflames the
spleen right
you know it enlarges the spleen it's
epstein-barr virus
you know that he says he knows that but
he's a board-certified surgeon and he
said he had to remove the spleen and
do you think he could have spared that
one
he said maybe dr nesbit dr nesmet though
i do not
i do not be open heart it says dr nesbit
quacks meow
i do not doubt dr nesbitt because dr
nesbitt
understands trolls really well and
understands naysayers really well out
there do you
um he says yeah dr nesbitt
i'm just reading comments as we go you
guys on tick tock do you see dr nesbitt
well i better let dr nesbitt get back
into surgery
dr nesbitt doesn't like the you some of
the youtube doctors
um what about the youtube doctor some of
them
dr nesbitt said some of the youtube
doctors are not only just frauds but
they're not real doctors and what else
some of the podcast doctors are frauds
too and they they steal medical medium
information
really what about the these youtube
doctors
do you want me to do an imitation
the doctor husband wants me to imitate a
youtube doctor hi i'm dr
ninaburg and i'm i'm going to tell you
the five
top tips uh omega-3s from eggs are very
good for you good for your brain
hi i'm dr hoon and here's my ad
what else uh okay i better let dr
nesbitt go to work you guys
yeah i i think we i think we got to go
to work
okay dr nisman i'll let you go all right
okay dr desmond said he's got to go back
to surgery
he's going to remove a brain from a
podcast doctor
the only work dr nesbitt only removes
body parts out of
bad doctors on podcasts and on youtubes
anyway okay guys so
let's just let's get moving on we are
heading off to ig instagram
and we're gonna turn tik tok back on
we're gonna put tick tock back
on we're gonna be back on we're gonna go
on ig
and then we're gonna put clubhouse back
on i feel bad for the clubhousers
i mean that's a great app but man you
can't see jack
anyway you guys heading off to ig you
guys tic tac i'm gonna turn you back
on keep your notifications on not that
that matters
they're not notifying practically
anybody all right you guys
i'll be on there in about 15 minutes
just got to clean up and
a couple of minutes right so grateful to
you too ashley
kevin and