we're live all right you guys I'm just
making some dinner right here thought I
would go on um June 15th are you guys
going to be there how many of you guys
are actually going to be there because
it's coming up it's actually coming up
Culver City I'm going to be there in
person in Culver City I'm going to sign
some books bring a book and there's
going to be some speakers there too
that's going to be really cool so I'm
actually excited about that surprise
speakers um how cool and you guys know
the collaboration between airwan and
medical medium the heavy metal detox
smoothie is going to be on the menu and
this is like our big
celebration uh proceeds going to me will
go to a 501c directly back into the
medical medium Community I will not be
making a penny but I spent a Katon of
money on free merchandise for anybody
that's going free
merchandise and not Joker stuff either I
mean high quality stuff that's only
being issued at
this uh book signing it's only going to
be issued at this uh heavy metal detox
launch party it's not going to be issued
anywhere else or sold anywhere else it's
not going to be sold it's going to be
given away
free and I got a lot of it
because I think we have some people
coming are you guys coming I'm trying to
take a look at the comments right now
I'm just trying to make my lentil you
love
lentils I'm trying to make my lentil
soup right now it's not a lentil soup
it's actually a lentil stew which is
incredible okay I'll be there Sanja said
I'll be there coming from Melbourne
Australia okay well I better have my
best outfit on because that's a big deal
to me that you're coming from Australia
so I better have my best outfit on I
better have my crap together and who
knows I'm going to be speaking too by
the way I'm going to be speaking when
have I done that just signed up last
minute how do we travel while
maintaining the medical medium lifestyle
I'm doing the same doing the same I'm
I'm dropping some fresh tomatoes in the
lentil soup are you guys okay with
this there's a lot of tomato juice on
this cutting board it's spilling
everywhere but that's life that's life
boom let's get this sucker
cooking let's get some of this tomato
juice cleaned up real quick let's get a
red bell pepper going all right all
right all right come on pull it together
Allison says coming from Northern
California which isn't really that far
amazing guys this is going to be in C
City LA anelia coming from Bulgaria
I mean seriously Maro so excited to be
there thank you over there in YouTube
incredible you guys I'm really pumped up
about this I'm not
kidding I may I'm going to talk about
some heavy metal stuff if you want
Little Q&A about that I got the lentil
stew going we're talking about the event
right now June 15th just so you know
June 15th Culver
City aan collaboration medical medium
the heavy metal detox they are going to
be making a lot of heavy metal detox
smoothies proceeds that go to me are
going to a 501c back into the community
how crazy is that I'm not making any
money on any of this meanwhile
everybody's like make money selling
programs selling this selling that
selling product selling that the whole
like everybody's like buy this buy that
buy this everybody's banking right not
making anything on this instead in what
happened was I was like hey come into
Awan and I'll sign some books and then
all of a sudden Awan started see getting
a whole bunch of phone calls people are
rolling in and boom it's actually insane
now so this has turned into an in insane
event Victoria rising from the ashes
love that handle um does irwan make
celery juice yes it does get them to
make it they'll they'll order it they're
going to make it of course and they're
going to have extra celery because of
this they're going to have extra food
Iran's going to have extra food extra
celery of extra everything for the heavy
metal detox smoothies they're going to
be rigged they're going to be rigged I'm
telling you because people are calling
from all over the world people are
coming and we're making sure everybody's
going to have a great time free
merchandise and I got friends coming
speakers people that are going to be
speaking and I'm going to be speaking
too I might even have a surprise because
I'm speaking so honestly you guys do you
want to miss this are you going to be
there I mean come on S said over there
on YouTube yeah looking forward to
meeting in person dreamt about you last
night incredible and I'm honored by the
way M says over there stubs on YouTube
coming from Atlanta that's really cool
suggestions
amazing incredible someone said please
come to Taiwan I wish I could but I
can't not right now but I'm going to be
in Culver City this is going to be crazy
irwan is the best Market on the planet
hence why the medical medium heavy metal
detox movie uh Alexandra amazing hence
why the heavy metal detox is going to be
on their
menu okay M says will be will there be
bathrooms in media
Park yes there will indeed there will
this this is going to be incredible you
guys this is going to be an incredible
thing that happens on the 15th of June
I'm serious real Chelsea Field
wow Chelsea Field I hope they have extra
staff too yes they do Chelsea dear dear
dear friend of mine who I call Family
Chelsea is going to be there uh-huh I'm
excited Chelsea Fields is going to be
there you guys are you going to be there
or what I mean it's coming up it's June
15th it's June 15th I'm making a lentil
stew if you guys are chilling out with
me this is my dinner tonight are you
guys okay if I eat this or is there some
reason I shouldn't have lentils
too let's
see reiken vegan says what company is
this and where is it you're won in
Culver City okay it's an
incredible health food store incredible
health food store right medical medium
heavy metal detox is going on the menu
there proceeds that go to me go to a
501c back into the community register at
Medical me
just so you know if you're wondering
what this is and what's happening go to
medical.com and register if you plan on
coming register to this event if you
plan on
coming so let me tell you guys a little
story about this are you okay if I talk
about different things while I'm
shopping all right so initially right it
was about getting the heavy metal detox
smoothie right on a1's menu okay they
were like let's get get the medical
mediums heavy metal detox smoothie on
here I'm like great right
but okay you guys are with me right here
and then all my proceeds from this we
going to go to the 501c back into the
community that's why I'm doing it I'm
not doing it to make a penny I'm not
doing it to make money which going to go
back to the community okay I just want
to fill you guys in a little bit about
the backstory here so
then I was going to say hey I was saying
everybody just bring your book in I'll
sign it there but a lot of people are
coming which is great A lot of people
are coming so then I was like well we're
going to need some
room so cuz a lot of people are coming
and then it's like well there's going to
be speakers there we're going to have
some fun I'm going to be speaking and
I'm hoping I can do a few things that
are going to be really cool for
everybody and then initially I was going
to do all this free merch which I which
I did right which is great
but then I had to get more free merch
and more free merch and more free Merch
this is going to be a freaking blast
this is going to be an insane time in a
freaking blast like this is not a joke
what's happening for June 15th in Culver
City at aan okay this is a party this is
literally a party and it's free you
don't have to buy a $100 ticket $200
ticket no you don't it is free baby free
okay but sign up so we kind of got a
heads up of how many merchandise free
merchandise gifts that I need to hand
out the reason why it's important to
register at Medical medium.com and sign
up I need to know because I'm handing
out a ton of stuff and I need to know
like come on who's coming what's going
on so yeah
I'm pumped up fresh oregano right here
from the garden you guys fresh oregano
that was red bell peppers that was
tomatoes that went in here there's
lentils down in here I'm going to chop
up an onion look at this incredible
cilantro right here how insane is that I
got some colored greens fresh out of the
garden and I got some cayenne peppers
fresh out of the garden right here okay
all right let me get some of this
oregano in here now a lot of times what
I do is I just throw it all in I care
about stems and all of that but since
you guys are watching me make this I
want to make it differently a little
differently cuz um because what's going
to happen you guys might be like hey he
throws in all those thick stems and then
you're going to make your stew and
you're going to be fishing those stems
out and then you're going to be maybe
mad at me and so what I'm doing is I'm
showing you right here if you make this
lentil stew just kind of like get the
leaves off of this oregano you want to
talk about medicine talking about fresh
oregano fresh lantro collard greens
you're talking about garlic I got some
th right here oh fresh thme let's get
that in here okay little fresh time are
you all right with that not fresh dry
Time come on come on dry time there it
is I put a decent amount in there did
you see that you
guys all right great put that those big
stems over there let's chop up this
regano real
quick right heavy metal detox smoothie
the heavy metal detox in the medical
medium original book The Heavy Metal
detox has helped so many people around
the world save lives gotten Metals out
of people's brains excited flying in
from oh my God Hawaii I can't even
believe it that is
incredible that is
incredible all right fresh oregano from
the garden going right in
here right there into my lentil stew
youy guys I got the lentil stew going
are you guys okay with that I'm going to
show you here if I can a little bit I'm
just leaning It Forward Tik Tok you guys
see this YouTube you guys see this all
right all right let's see what else we
got in here let's get an onion going oh
no no I'm going to be crying with this
onion darn it ATM over there and IG
there are going to be a lot of
us I got a feeling I got a feeling
there's going to be a lot of you guys
I got a feeling okay there's going to be
a lot of you guys you know and aan and
medical medium team we're talking and
we're like holy
sh what do we do Gina over there on
YouTube my daughter and I are flying in
from Massachusetts love it she wants to
know if Dr Nesbit is going to be there
and it's very possible I have not ruled
that out yet at all I have not ruled
that out oh man I don't like chopping
onions cuz I'm going to have like the
crybaby face super Trish 1999 Good Year
by the way I'll be crying when I see you
and you're going to make me cry that's
what's going to happen you're going to
make me cry I have a feeling that that's
what's going to
happen and then I'm going to be crying
there but I got to tell you guys right
so check this out right irwan and the
medical medium team we were all talking
together about this initially it was
like get the smoothie in there right
let's let's help people let's donate to
the 501c back to the community right and
then all of a sudden ir1 was getting a
lot of calls a lot of calls a lot of
calls so aan and us were
like yep and I'm like while I was
getting hand out free merchandise and
yeah going to have to be a lot of free
merchandise okay and then uh um and I'm
going to be signing some books I'm
pumped up about that but then we
realize we need a little room so Awan
and I'm going to be an
irwan I'm going to be an aan I'm going
to roll in earlier right the events from
9:00 to 3 I'm probably going to pop in a
little earlier get into aan sign a few
books right it's going to be crazy and
then we're going to be at the park media
park because
you can't put a stage inside
aan because a lot of people are coming
so you can't put a stage inside of aan
there's no room to put a stage and and
have all these speakers
speak okay soy over there in IG I'll be
crying
too you'll be crying all day cuz we'll
all be crying I'm going to be crying all
day yep that is true
that is very
true we'll see how much the snow
blindness kicks in if you guys are
familiar with that we will
see um but it'll all be good and all be
I got faith I got faith right I do I got
faith but don't worry it's going to be
great hummingbird over there on YouTube
I'm so excited to see you in
person
nice all right I'm getting onion in here
let me get some garlic in here I might
throw a collard green in here let me get
a collard green boom yo yeah boom couple
collar greens let's get that in the stew
let's um dice this up are you guys okay
if I do this right
here I don't know if you can see this
over Tik Tok are you guys seeing this
okay making the lentil stew talking
about the event going to talk about some
metals and other things
too getting Metals out of the brain is
critical I'm going to tell you right now
bipolar right even Ms chronic fatigue
Alzheimer Alzheimer's dementia Lyme
disease Metals need to come out there's
pathogens along with some of those
illnesses that I'm mentioning there but
metals have to come
out Mercury is in people's brains it has
to come out I'm telling you right now
over there IG Coach Amanda says coming
from North Carolina
boom North
Carolina
um coming from Australia
Alison
what that's a trip that's a
trip be
[Music]
there bad singing I think today I don't
think my Tunes are right I don't think
I'm on key
today all
right w one two three
four be
there um I'm pumped up seriously about
it Palm Springs you coming from Palm
Springs
seriously if the medical medium heavy
metal detox has helped you please
comment has the heavy metal detox helped
you at all has it you guys because I
know it's helped a lot of people turn
their lives around Jennifer NC here
first time seeing you incredible let me
get some garlic going in here I forgot
to put Garlic in here and let me crank
up the heat I got onions in there you
guys I'm making a lentil stew are you
okay with this I got got collard greens
around I have I don't know if you can
see that I got cilantro right here um I
got some hot peppers right here I'll put
that right on top of the cilantro so you
guys can see that a little bit trying to
get it into the camera I got a soup
going right here let me get the lid I
think this is the lid and it is that's
the lid let's get that going a little
bit a little garlic
too share how the heavy metal detox has
helped you I would love to see how it
has helped you you guys share how it has
helped you I would love to yes
tremendously yes tremendously I've seen
it get people out of wheelchairs I've
seen it turn people around oh my God the
hmd saved you saved you I had
Alzheimer's disease back in 2017
here's you you know what's really hard
on me let me tell Alison heavy metal
detox has been a game changer for me
took a couple of years but my brain got
quiet so quiet now so smooth I forgot
what anxiety was like that's incredible
too all of that is incredible I got to
tell you
something there's nothing more
disturbing when you see things in the
mainstream Alzheimer's scientists have
now studied what causes Alzheimer's you
mean like what you did last for the last
30 years what you thought it was
proteins in the brain and some other
stuff right right and now they're like
you know they're like Alzheimer's um you
know there is hope for people with
Alzheimer's it's like yeah how because
the heavy metal detox is what reverses
Alzheimer's and has it's what helps
reverse and Stave off and shut it down
and stop it if someone's really bad with
their Alzheimer's it has the ability to
shut that down at least to stop getting
it worse and even backtrack it a little
bit if somebody has you know a moderate
version of Alzheimer's has the ability
to shut that down and backtrack it
somebody has a moderate version of
dementia has the ability to backtrack it
and shut that down if the brain is
damaged too much by metals and dementia
is off the chart so bad someone doesn't
even know where they are they're they're
on feeding tubes then you know I can't
say it's going to then get them out of
bed and they'll be dancing but I will
tell you this so many people with
dementia and Alzheimer's have reversed
it recovered staved it off because of
the heavy metal
detox it's crazy it's crazy and you see
this stuff constantly out there and all
these podcast people now in the health
realm that are running a billion ads and
they got millions of dollars because
they started out rich and they're taking
over and dominating the health scene
they're like talking about Alzheimer's
somebody gets on there and they're
giving their tips and I'm like dude that
ain't getting anybody better I'm sorry
it's a wild west out there Elena right
there over on IG I was trying to lose
weight for the longest time even eating
clean for a long time once I got started
with the heavy metal detox smoothie boom
it started falling off whoa whoa whoa
whoa
amazing all right so what else here it
helped reverse my Hashimoto actually
that's incredible Dr
Karen Ken amazing thank you for being
here doc incredible
incredible can't underestimate the heavy
metal detox MS symptoms
reversed whoa Roby girl over there on IG
MS symptoms reversed that's what I'm
talking about Cheryl on IG brain fog got
so much better oh that's incredible
chopping up some garlic
incredible whoa life changing I could
read and write after talking about after
taking the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie after 30 days you can
read and write that's incredible spirit
filled kitchen over there in IG hey
that's a really cool handle all right
let me get some garlic in here you guys
don't mind
right making uh
some some stew there we go everything's
in there that needs to be in there cook
cook cook all right Aurora Aurora's
morning hey good to see you over there
on IG I stopped doing the heavy metal
detox for a while and I got suicidal
that is terrible that's so hard I have
massive brain issues and mold issues in
my home however wow but you stop taking
the heavy metal
detox my God depression gone ATM says
anxiety
gone over there J no more migraines for
my husband from doing the heavy metal
detox that is incredible think about the
power of that kind word over there in IG
emotional
regulation whoa keeps the emotions
regulated so we're just riding night the
Motions are regulated they're doing good
okay Janet Brown over there I'm detoxing
from chemo yes it
helps I love the heavy metal detox for
people for anything like radiation like
all kinds of stuff love it for that
cranes over there it has an IG has given
me resilience amazing I love it John
Luke over there heavy metal detox took
me out of depersonalization over there
and I G incredible you guys too on Tik
Tok heavy metal detox you know are doing
good over there you guys doing the heavy
metal detox I'm cooking this up nice
it's going great so Soldier medic over
there in IG that's a cool handle H hmds
is my happy pill happy pill depression
anxiety right depression anxiety OCD to
personalization heavy metal detox
baby all right gozy boss says my energy
levels are all off the chart when I'm
drinking them in the morning guys if I
butcher your handle just don't mind me
okay I'm trying my best I think I'm
getting the handles
right okay Breezy Brie over there heavy
metal detox smoothie brought Clarity to
my mind
cleanses I never thought existed oh
sorry no no no no no I'm trying to see
there's something in the way but I'm
looking okay oh clearness clearness
incredible so Breezy Brie heavy metal
detox brought Clarity to my mind
clearness I've never thought existed
peace of mind is the best for some
reason my collar green is like changing
the words it's you can see it reflecting
into the IG sometimes all right maybe
I'll move them reverse chronic migraine
severe chronic fatigue all mental health
issues pretty much gone over there
knowledge on
IG knowledge cool handle on IG you
guys seriously
unbelievable Pam over there in IG heavy
metal detox smoothie healed my fatigue
fibroids and Endo floaters and
more drop the knife don't drop it on
your
foot Do not drop the knife a bad idea I
got a lentil stew stew cook it right
here I got my this cilantro is going on
fresh fresh on top I'm going to get a
bowl going that's going on
Fresh Victoria rising from the ashes the
heavy metal detox has changed my life
Wow liy lissy heavy metal detox smoothie
helped me so much I hope to see you at
the event so powerful guys who's coming
to the event right Alexis the heavy
metal detox has helped immensely with my
depression incredible all this is
mindblowing and that's what matters it's
this it's people healing getting better
because of s so's
information because of s so's
information it's incredible I'm the
messenger my job was to deliver it in
this crazy world right deliver that
information no matter how much Flack no
matter how much I get no matter how
much spiritual discrimination I get no
matter how much you know like whatever I
get jealous people or whatever it is
causing problems no matter how much crap
is made up and stories my job
is the messenger to bring this to people
and for people to take that information
and heal Lizzy over there and YouTube
hmds helped me no more brain fog no more
salami
arms Denise over there on Facebook the
heavy metal detox movie saved me I had
Alzheimer's disease back in 2017
my God my
god seriously oh man I am so happy to
hear that you have no idea and you do
have an idea how happy I am because it
matters it's so good um I'm taking a
look at the stew right here so here is
some of the stew on here incredible
lentil stew is cooking it's almost done
it's not going to take long how do you
like that how do you like them apples
all right quick quick just run down
really quick you guys are you going to
be in cover City June 15th I'm going to
be there I'm going to be speaking I'm
going to be doing it there's going to be
a stage there boom we're building it
we're building everything more people
are coming it's going to be incredible
Awan and medical medium are joining
forces together is what's happening
they're putting the hmds on the menu
they're going to have stuff rigged for
for that day I'm very honored to be
working with them and um I'm going to be
in Iran a little earlier for a little
bit and then I think when things get
kind of
like intense I'm going to be boom right
across the street and then probably back
in air onean probably running back and
forth it's going to be nuts it's going
to be nuts okay Ram there heavy metal
Smoothie has helped so much with brain
fog on IG G
incredible so yeah you guys proceeds
that are supposed to go to me that's
what everybody would probably do um not
everybody I guess in the world but
pretty much I'm making sure the proceeds
don't go to me and they go to a 501c
back into the community how great is
that um anyway what do we have
here um Dorian okay heavy metal detox
healed my severe eczema that I had since
childhood God
incredible incredible this is cooking
like crazy right now all right um Jordy
three months so far detox my mom would
beg me to start it and I so glad I did
no
anxiety
incredible I'm telling you now you guys
heavy metal detox has helped so many
people and you guys know for so many
years and it's incredible it's
incredible the hmds the original book
that's start at the hmds
here
okay let's see Earth healthy my
essential
tremors I'm looking at the U oh eat
healthy wow be healthy incredible handle
I love it my essential
tremors are so much calmer the advanced
369 has played a huge part in in calming
my Tremors they're not completely gone
but so so much better that's
incredible Metals cause ticks and spasms
aches and pains Metals cause all kinds
of stuff anxiety depression even eczema
psoriasis okay Thrive with orisa coming
with my husband from Naples
Florida the hmd Smoothie has helped us
so much you're coming from you're going
from Naples
Florida to Culver City La
I'm excited I can't wait to see you
there that's an
incredible incredible you know Cross
Country flight and you're going to be
there I'm going to be there
listen just going to tell you guys
something right now okay it's going to
be cool I'm giving away all this free
merch I'm going to be signing books I
got some friends popping by to do some
speaking it's going to be really cool
I'm going to do some speaking
[Laughter]
yep I'm going to throw hot pepper in
here all right renzy Lulu hmds has
helped with my severe neurological
symptoms neurological symptoms are
brutal they're brutal you guys don't
mind if I put a cayenne pepper in here
really quick can I just put some of it
in here Cayenne gets real hot um inside
of a stew so I'm not going to like
overdo it
okay s to um to has over there on
YouTube hi Anthony the heavy metal detox
help me with my depression anxiety and
brain fog love drinking it every
day think about that right now isn't
that kind of interesting right I've
never seen and I've seen this like like
people telling me all the time aw you
know out in this community in this group
no one heals like they do at the medical
medium like Community nobody heals allhe
and all these different conditions if
one person heals out there because
they've removed a few processed foods
and they're feeling a little better they
Herald that is God the herald is God out
there we finally healed somebody out
there we got somebody better with type
two diabetes you hear this right and
then but that's like a grain of rice
compared to a silo of rice in the
medical M community of people their
lives being saved with the information
it's incredible celery juice the heavy
metal detox the morning Clans I go on on
and on and on JW Jones it's helped me
and my wife over there on Twitter which
is X now now my 24 year-old son is doing
it every day he needed it as he has been
racing dirt cars whoa dirt cars since he
was 7 years old he has witnessed the
benefits whoa he's racing dirt cars whoa
that's actually it just sounds really
cool it does so he's he's like racing is
that where dirt bikes he's racing dirt
bikes he's racing ATVs he's racing
four-wheelers he's Racing monster trucks
he's racing all kinds of you know cars
and they're just on the dirt it's really
cool BMX biking I mean you know like
it's just all
great all right you guys okay what do we
got this is coming along
nice yes we are making food tonight I am
making my dinner if you guys don't mind
it's a lentil stew I will show you
really quick Linda Hill over there on
YouTube hmds helped my daily evening
headaches and me with six months sorry
and
whoa an me with in six months whoa
that's
incredible you guys amazing I'm just
showing you this right here really quick
here we
go um I'm really pumped up about this
whole thing I'm just letting you
know
yep incredible so so Linda I'm really
excited that heavy metal detox helped
your help like you're doing it daily
daily evening headaches that's
incredible a lot of people get headaches
at the end of the day so they have daily
headaches or you know evening headaches
in whole bit I know a lot of people get
that and that's that's you know um so
yeah so and it's helped you with uh in
within 6 months that's incredible Linda
amazing all
right yeah
yeah all
right you guys I'm really pumped up
about this I really am I got a stew let
me see if I can get it going and get it
into a bowl if that's
[Music]
possible so many people multiple
sclerosis so many people with Lyme
disease so many diff different different
conditions CFS
um so many different people with
digestive trouble you know Metals get
into the lining of the intestinal tract
they burrow themselves in there and in
the liver and it's so important to
actually have the heavy metal detox to
pull that out so intestinal tracts get
healthier Denise thank you so much for
saving my life I don't know where I
would be without you I went to so many
different doctors for 20 years begging
them to save me from the Alzheimer's
disease not one doctor had ever been
able to help me I was literally on my
knees begging them Denise I'm so happy
over there on Facebook that you have
found this information found the heavy
metal
detox heavy metals get into the brain
and they
rust let's see grab that and they rust
okay heavy metals get into the brain and
they rust that's how it works
they outp poet they out gas they
explode okay uh Megan Miller quit weed
and chocolate and finally moving the
needle been doing medical meeting for
years thank you Anthony and S so that's
incredible I'm so proud of you by the
way I really
am what happens is Metals get in here
and when they get in here okay they
saturate adjacent tissue that's tissue
next to the metals Metals burrow when
they find their home in the midline
canal and other areas the left
hemisphere the right hemisphere frontal
lobe when metals get buried in there
around the pituitary and so forth what
happens is they outgas they rust they
disintegrate they out poock it okay and
oxidize and when those Metals oxidize
I'll tell you right now what goes wrong
as the metals oxidize they travel and
they travel to other tissue and as they
travel to other tissue you forget who
you are as they travel to other tisue
tissue you get anxiety and depression
and bipolar and OCD as they travel to
other tissue you start getting you know
a possible diagnosis of Alzheimer's
dementia and so forth or memory loss and
any kind of other depersonalization
anything when they
travel you can get insomnia you can get
restless legs when they travel to
adjacent tissue you can get all kinds of
different problems that's what I'm
trying to tell you sonon over there on
Facebook what is the heavy metal
smoothie where do I find it new here
amazing so glad to see you I'm making
lentil stew by the way I'm here so where
is it what is it you can check out
medicalmedium.com you can look at it
look at it there go to medical
medium.com and you can type in anything
it'll come up the heavy metal detox is
in these books right here okay medical
medium heavy metal detox is in here and
there's a heavy metal detox cleanse in
the brain books right here so medical
medium book series you can go to Amazon
right you can go check it out there
Amazon us go to Barnes & nobl pick up a
brains saer protocols book pick up a
medical medium revised in New Edition
right
here and learn about the heavy metal
detox and what it's done for people and
everything else it's
incredible thank you for being here by
the way
RoR RoR says onig i' be gone your
information
has brought my life back without your
information so you'd be gone without
that you know what you got your life
back you're here I'm so happy you're
here thank God it's the best thing ever
to know you're here because of that
information I'm a
messenger I like bringing the
information whatever cost it costs me as
far as energy time money and also severe
beatings along way because people don't
like Cutting Edge information that saves
lives out there Linda Hill coming from
behind the orange curtain Orange County
whoa you're coming from Orange County
you're going to be there in Culver City
I have a
vision that vision is I'm going to be in
Culver
City I'm going to be in
Aran I'm going to be signing books I'm
going to be in the park across the
street we got got speakers coming
there's going to be free
merch some really badass stuff too and
it's going to be a blast I am
pumped I want you guys to know I'm going
to be drinking smoothies while I'm there
so if I have blue all over my face
please don't punish me for it anelia the
information from telegram message about
Mars is mind-blowing please speak more
about this just a little note here okay
check out my telegram when you guys get
a chance please I leave personal
messages over there on telegram
exclusive to telegram audio messages I
just left one about Mars you guys should
go over there and check it out okay and
listen I'm going to be talking about
Mars more much more so what do I know
about Mars I know stuff from Spirit of
compassion about Mars that's the whole
point Roya I was an addict heavy with
drugs and alcohol I had have been clean
almost a year I don't think I would have
been able to do it without you over
there
Roya on YouTube like you're going to get
me crying okay you're going to get me
crying
incredible rehea way King amazing thank
you for being here Jennifer pza I'm new
here may I ask how I'm eager to try the
heavy metal detox so would like to know
heavy metal detox that it consists of
five incredible ingredients I talk about
in the books Right medical medium
medical medium right here I don't know
if you see it on IG it's probably
flipped backwards this is the medical
medium Secrets book New Edition go to
Amazon go to the bookstore go to Barnes
& Noble go to the library if you want to
get it for free go to the library if you
want to get it for free I don't care and
you'll learn about it right now check
this out this is interesting right
here brains saver protocol book heavy
metal detox cleanses in here okay as
well so please check it out when you get
a chance but I'm going to be in Culver
City the heavy metal detox is going on
the the menu in irwan and Culver City
and all the irans I'm excited cold white
spring where you been why are you not at
2 in the morning why am I up at two in
the morning time huh Rena Robinson heavy
metal detox smoothie is helped my
depression brain fog trigeminal
neuralgia that's a big deal migraines
Etc the 369 are the
best
incredible
incredible Cold Light spring I don't
think it's 2: in the morning is it is it
could be 2: in the morning I need to go
to bed I do Sandy I gave your video a
thumbs up so more people find this
information incredible thank you for
doing that that really helps seaweed
hero where have you been man build my
world nice of dream I love all your
lyrics I read your lyrics I do I read
your lyrics all the time and then when
you're not around I'm like where I got
no lyrics to read so fun Gina
brandwell over on YouTube lifechanging
once I started having two or three heavy
metal detox smoothies a day anxiety
reduced by 80% thank you doesn't seem
like enough hearts hearts back heart's
back okay heart's back
incredible I think my stew I'm going to
drop the temperature in my Stew cuz my
stew is done I don't want it so boiling
hot where I burn my mouth so I am
bringing the temp down on the stew I am
woo
yep that baby's hot it's
cooking you guys I am so excited about
this Janette says I will be there thank
you Janette I'm really happy you are if
you're going to be at the event in
Culver City on June 15th comment now
where are you coming
from where are you coming from comment
now where are you coming from you guys
if you're going to be at the event June
15th in Culver City with me I will be
there from
Taiwan okay mind blown boom CN TOA says
thank you for the Mars information on
telegram looking forward to hearing more
there's going to be a lot more Mars
information I'm going to blow people
away with SS's
information I'm excited it's fun stuff
Jen coffin coming from Florida too nice
coming across from Florida amazing Vicky
Russell I want to come so badly amazing
I hope you can get there if you can that
would be so incredible Toby 777 by the
way ask for a pat down at the
airport but boom can I please get a pat
down at the airport please I would like
a pat down yes I don't want to go into
that x-ray
machine don't worry sir that x-ray
machine isn't bad it doesn't give you
anything it's like it's like getting a
dental x-ray nothing more than that go
right in okay I will let me go into it
I'm standing in there now thank you glad
this doesn't hurt me
[Music]
thank you go Ahad I'm all
set miam over there um
Miriam Miriam over there on Facebook
Crohn's disease is healed I will be
forever
thankful my God Miriam Crohn's disease
is healed I will be ever thankful and I
will be ever okay forever ever ever ever
thankful too that you did that for
yourself because that's why I exist
that's why I'm here it's so you can do
that I want that to be there for you
that's the whole point that's what it's
about that's what it's about okay can I
get a pat down
sir um why you can just hop right into
our x-ray machine here at the airport
thank you I'll go in
there okay coming from Connecticut
incredible limited edition amazing
limited audition that's really cool
Courtney W
Indiana that's actually really
cool Andrea Santos coming from
Atlanta
nice Lana coming from Florida you are
amazing you guys I'm getting
nervous I'm getting nervous now I am
because speaking at this aan
event I'm speaking so I'm getting
nervous now I'm speaking
okay Victoria rising out of the ash is
coming from Canada whoa jeso coming from
um your your comment disappeared I
wonder where it went Cleveland Ohio
Scott Robertson amazing EO fruit
sandwiches is Northern
California no sorry Salt Lake City
Utah healing with Ana Northern
California amazing
Ivon coming from Orange County
California Love It Reno Nevada and
Brandford Leia
Massachusetts they're going up so fast
the comments you got to catch them while
you can man or you can't see or Oregon
darc Lee great Sarah coming from
Kentucky USA Lizzy coming from Northern
California whoa Allison Saunders coming
from
Sacramento Alexandra Sophia you're
coming from Palm
Springs
wo
amazing amazing 75 dubs coming from
Santa Monica dude you're right there
Margie Matthew Dean coming from Maryland
incredible Santa Monica Santa Monica
Culver City you're just right there oh
I'd be so upset if you didn't
come you're you're in you're living in
Santa Monica if you didn't come I'd be
like why aren't you coming man so glad
you are all
right Muma I'm coming from LA Los
Angeles super Trish 1999 coming from
Boston wow whoa summer
summer over there on Twitch coming from
you and your daughter are coming from
British Columbia Canada
amazing Reena Nevada I see that Michelle
Switzerland
whoa Switzerland okay
yep now I've seen everything coming from
Switzerland incredible
coming from cool Stephanie says coming
from Cool California Alexandria coming
from Marin County San Francisco above
San Francisco
amazing you guys I am so pumped up all
right so I have this incredible lentil
stew right
here nice I'm going to chop up some
fresh cilantro I'd like to throw that on
top I might even have some a nice Bowl
somewhere
Angelique Angelic light Studio flying
from
Guatemala
whoa okay um Sheree
posa Summerfield
Florida
whoa um incredible Sant tamy coming from
Connecticut amazing Toronto here with
Hanna coming from Toronto that's
mind-blowing my God I'm going going to
you guys
whoa maroi
California I can't see that one for some
reason it's going quick got to get it
back down Sienna coming from Monrovia
California did I get that right I am
pumped up you guys I'm gonna see you
there that's what's blowing my mind AKA
Sharice greater Toronto
area whoa Ecuador
whoa estd Ecuador Erica Tucson
Arizona on my way to
Arizona Philadelphia Atlanta La Sophie
over there norstrom Sweden
Sweden it's
incredible all right is it
late Noah's plate on IG coming from CLA
Del
re incredible CLA Del re all
right Chris coming from Joshua Tree
California whoa Bohemian is coming from
Santa Ana Southern Cal man Southern Cal
Santa Ana wins they come blowing through
whoa get ready somewhere around January
the San winds are slamming you go
outside at night and it's pounding J New
York City nothing wrong with New York
City come on
over I love New York come on over
amazing you guys Boston see that
too incredible yeah you guys uh Rema
where is everyone going okay the
question is where's everybody going June
15th Culver City California Los Angeles
okay aan and medical medium doing a
collaboration the heavy metal detox
smoothie is going on the menu there and
we are pulling it together check it out
register at Medical
medium.com and are you coming to the
event register ATM medicalmedium.com are
you coming to the event proceeds for the
heavy metal detox every penny you buy
every heavy metal detox smoothie you buy
that day and from there on I hope you
guys buy them every day I hope if you
guys are around I know that there's so
many people coming from far away but if
you live in that area in California I'm
hoping you go in there every day please
please please buy the heavy metal detox
smoothie in any of the airan stores
because guess what those proceeds my
proceeds they go back to a 501c back to
the Community Medical meme Community to
help people out so please do that if you
can I am going to be purchasing them too
so just know that so when I'm there on
June 15th you're going to see me wait
when's June 15th when is that is that
like around the
corner that's in what 12 days what is
that 13 days what day is it today is it
June 3rd June
2nd I better get my bags packed I better
get I better get my stuff together
that's all I can
say and um if you guys see like heavy
metal detox smothie all over my
face you know on my hands on my pen when
I'm signing books please don't punish me
don't give me too much of a Beatdown um
because I'm going to be guzzling those
babies while I'm out there while I'm
signing books and speaking on the stage
I'm going to be guzzling those babies if
you would like to share your healing
story you can learn more at the link in
the profile you
guys at this June 15th Culver City Event
if you would like share your story there
okay share your story there okay when
you're there share your story about how
you healed anything like that because so
many people have asked me where can I
share my story I want to talk talk about
it I want to talk about what happened to
me Anthony I want to talk about what's
went down with me you know and what what
happened my suffering my struggles what
I've been through and I want I want to
be able to tell that story um going to
make sure you have that ability that
chance to do that on June 15th with
every every opportunity we can you know
Andy says can you heal seizures check
out the medical medium information learn
about seizures
but you will need to sign up in order to
tell your story and everything so go to
Medical me.com figure it out go there
you know you'll need to sign up also
I'll send stuff out on the newsletter
and stuff like that too make sure you're
on my
newsletter okay you'll need to sign up
so link is in the profile check out the
link in the profile so you can sign up
to tell your story on June 15th there in
person in person where I'm going to be
if you want to tell your story sign up
to the link in the profile incredible
you guys let me put a let me put this in
a
bowl can I move you over I can let me
out
here all right so what I'm going to do
here I'm going to get a nice bowl of the
stew going sounds like a full house
Beverly says I hope it's big for all the
adubs
fans making it
making it happen yep Lana I still can't
believe it that we will be able to be in
your and so's
vicinity definitely going to be in my
vicinity I'm going to be speaking I'm
going to be signing books I got some
speakers coming some friends I'm handing
out free merchandise
yeah g t Tanja 22 hours flight from
Singapore amazing it' be great to meet
everybody I'm I'm so excited so let me
just chop up some cilantro you guys okay
with that I'm going move this over
okay all right tick tock you see that
this is the lentil stew you guys see it
right here all right and I going to chop
up some fresh cilantro really quick
right here you guys don't mind okay all
right can I do this fresh cilantro it's
going to go right on on top of this toew
it's the way I like to do
it all
right you guys okay with this check this
out right right on top I like to do this
boom put all this right on top here
fresh cilantro on this lentle stew
excuse me okay all right and I like to
I like to chop up a little fresh tomato
right on top of this stew as well so
check this out a little bit of fresh
tomato right there okay okay right there
in the Middle look at
that
boom got a nice spoon here that is the
lentil stew for tonight that's my dinner
right there there all kinds of good
stuff I put red bell pepper in here
there's oregano from the Garden wo
you're hot you're definitely hot whoa I
feel that coming through my hand pretty
healthy Jenny says so excited you are
coming to iroan I am I
am and it's soon June 15th can you
believe it arriving June 11th from
Wisconsin whoa Dell's Wisconsin to
celebrate my birthday with you all whoa
K
LOVE okay I am
game I am I'm with you guys I am excited
actually Connie over there in IG you
seriously saved my life with celery
juice after being sick a year after food
poisoning we should never ever ever ever
underestimate the power of celery juice
the power of celery juice how many
people are drinking celery juice every
day what it's doing for people that is
one of those sure shots man there's so
much musical chairs and so much BS in
the Health realm it's wild west filled
with it everybody's trying to do this
and do that and do this but you know
what celery juice is key it's key hmd
key the heavy metal detox key all these
things matter wow Jessica says wow you
put like three cups of cilantro on your
soup I am keeping it smaller
tonight because of you guys I'm going to
put all of that on there as I'm eating
this bowl all of that cilantro you see
there but I'm trying not to go too crazy
in front of you guys don't want to look
a little weird but that's how much I
love cilantro mm information treat
cilantro like a leafy green treat your
cilantro like a leafy green yes treat it
like any leafy green please you guys I
love you I love you I'm
excited I can't wait to see you all
right give me a thumbs up if you like
this
video okay share the video if you can
send it around all right you guys but
seriously you're going to be psyched
about the free merchandise that I I am
issuing just for this airwan
collaboration with medical medium June
15th in Culver City California La I'm
just being straight up on this I am
you're going to like the
merchandise that I'm giving away I spent
a lot of money on it and it's free and I
am pumped would love to see your posts
on how the heavy metal detox has helped
you tag at medal medium so I can see
them hashtag and you know medical medium
so I can see them do both you guys
amazing see you soon I'm going to enjoy
some
dinner yeah it's like Tom Lana it's
coming up it's coming up like
soon I'll see you guys soon I'm pumped
up Soul Garden looking forward to
tasting Wyman's blue juice when I come
over from New Zealand woohoo it's going
to be in the hmds over there in
Iran bumped I'm going to need a bunch of
those that day because the the whole
thing is from 9 to 3 right I'm going to
get there a little earlier I'm going to
be drinking them right off the running
I'm going to be drinking so many of them
hopefully I don't have to run off the
stage because that I've drink too many
of them like 10 of them 15 of them might
have to go to the bathroom heid M my
lips and teeth are often Blue from the
hmds and my lips and teeth are going to
be blue too on June 15th and I don't
care there's nothing I can do about it I
can't be like o I'm worried about I'm
worried about my face here I don't want
the blue all over it I don't care it's
so good it tastes so good I need to
drink them I'm excited all right love
you guys all right
hello