heavy metals are the
rulers of Life on planet Earth toxic
heavy metals get into people's brains
and then Metals speak for the person I
know I've said that before right you
maybe may have heard that Metals talk
for the
person metals can make us highly
emotional highly sensitive metals can
make us so
depressed suicidal that's what metals
can do no one would ever no no one would
ever know you're living your life you're
going through life and you're suicidal
you're going through life and you're
depressed you're going through life and
you got high anxiety and panic and Chaos
you feel like it's happening internally
and you've been to every doctor and
every psychiatrist and every therapist
and you've been here you've been there
years are going by and you're just
somebody told you you're up and down
you're bipolar so now you're up you're
down you're all over the place another
person said you got depersonalization
that's what those symptoms are is
depersonalization another person is like
oh you got OCD another person like you
got Tourette's Metals run the gamut in
our brain they take over our brain and
then they change things in our brain
metals can do this they are the rulers
here on planet Earth they truly are
people don't realize this and hopefully
someday they do a lot of people have
mercury lead
cadmium arsenic aluminum nickel
copper the list goes on what you'll find
out there is there's a trendy thing
where copper is good for you they say
it's not me saying that but copper is
good for you we're missing copper we
don't have enough copper you can drink
out of copper you know things and
thermoses and mugs and all these
different stuff and people think that
that's a good thing they think well in
Ancient Ancient times they had copper
and copper held the water and people
used it as an
antimicrobial but they also got copper
poisoning which created Madness you know
that's a thing that people don't realize
so the exposure to Copper is so great so
I want to hit that right away cuz I know
some so many people are like you need
copper you need
copper zinc gets rid of your copper you
need copper this guy over here says zinc
gets rid of Co you know you hear it all
the time out there have you guys heard
that what people don't realize is we're
inundated with copper first of all
copper is high in all the fruit fruits
and vegetables and herbs and
spices copper is in everything it's in
meat it's in chicken copper is in every
vegetable copper is in avocados avocados
are high in copper copper is in
everything and there's two forms of
copper that are in everything there's
the natural Trace mineral
copper that's in the earth and then
there's the industrialized copper that's
in the earth two kind of copper is in
food we have so much access to Copper we
are not copper deficient we are far from
it we are over inundated with copper we
have too much copper and it WS havoc in
us it's one of the toxic heavy metals
copper so many people have mercury in
them but it's passed on through
generation to generation to generation
we get our Mercury from our parents
parents get our Mercury from their
parents their parents get the Mercury
from their parents it goes on and on and
on back back back back you can go a
th000 years you can go 2,000 years you
can go 3,000 years and that mercury
trans it just basically transforms
itself back into our own body it becomes
something in our own body passed along
from Generations ago and generations ago
and we end up with
Mercury lots of toxic heavy metals we
can pass on generation Generation
generation but Mercury's a big one
Mercury we really pass that one on gener
generation after generation and that
mercury can sit inside our brain and it
can be thousands of years old you can
have mercury inside your brain that is a
thousand years old like where did it
come from what's going on passed from
generation to
generation that's the kind of metals
that are stored inside of us but I don't
have any Metals what the heck metals are
not my problem I got a little depression
I got a little anxiety I got a little
OCD I got a little dep personalization I
got a little ups and down got sadness
that's mystery mystery sadness I can't
find peace in my mind I can't sleep I
can't stop these thoughts I got OCD
that's driving me crazy I got all these
different things going on metal metal
metal metal and metals and metals we're
going to go into little detail on Metals
I'm also making the heavy metal detox
today so
hmds medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie what you see in front of me
really quick I'll give you an
introduction if you guys are interested
you see the the wild blueberry right
here yes the wild blueberry here it is
that's it we'll talk about that a little
bit later as well you see some cilantro
right here really fresh green cilantro
you see some oranges see some dolls you
see some spirulina Bly grass you see
some bananas and so forth a little
coconut water too in the glass I might
do something with that and we got the
blender so we're making the heavy metal
detox smoothie how many of you guys are
on the
hmds I know a lot of you guys
are a lot of you guys are so let's get
into it a little bit okay all
right Alloys so what happens in our
brain is we get metals and they mix they
mix we get a little bit of copper
aluminum Mercury in our brain and then
they blend together how do they do that
they Forge into an alloy through brain
heat if you're upset your brain heats up
you get emotional your brain heats up if
you're exercising and you're exercising
and exercising and you're working out
you're working out your brain heats up
if you're experiencing immense Joy your
brain heats up if you're experiencing
immense pain and suffering your brain
heats up if you're actually challenged
emotionally and you are under stress and
you are struggling emotionally your
brain heats up and when our brain heats
up the metals inside our brain can get
hot they can get hot and they do the
electricity inside of our brain
electrical impulses that are going round
and around and around and around right
in our brain those electrical impulses
swimming around that electrical grid as
that electrical grid is going going
going going getting hotter and hotter
and hotter any little bit of metal
that's sitting anywhere in in any neuron
any gal cell anywhere in the brain gets
hot and Mercury will snuggle next to
aluminum aluminum will snuggle next to
copper copper will snuggle next to lead
and so forth and these Metals sit inside
of our brain and then we have emotional
experiences stress relationship breakup
something happen somebody betrays you
maybe somebody cheated on you maybe a
friend did something maybe a coworker
did something maybe life is just unfair
maybe somebody else did something
whatever happened we H gone under some
kind of emotional struggle in some kind
of emotional situation our brain heats
up and then any kind of metal inside of
our brain forges and binds into each
other and becomes an alloy I call it the
alloy
brain normally the viruses that are in
our body that are responsible for
autoimmune love Metals I always say to
people all these years we can get rid of
our viruses work on that but we can also
get rid of our metals and work on that
the sicker people and the sickest people
got the viruses the pathogens right and
they got the
metals the sickest people have the viral
pathogens and the
metals people with ALS multiple
sclerosis neurological problems chronic
fatigue syndrome me or just CFS
bad
fibromyalgia lime disease all of it
pathogens and
metals people who actually have more
metal suffer more people who have more
pathogens suffer more you have but the
combination is really hard so many
people live a miserable life they
struggle and they suffer because they
have both pathogens and metals they have
the combination so what I like to to do
is I'd like to get the medals out so
let's talk about that a little bit why
are so many people healing in the
medical medium Community the largest
community in health worldwide by far and
the largest community in health that
actually has the most people healing
worldwide that came to this community
devast devastatingly sick chronically
sick terrifyingly sick the sickest
people come to the medical medium
information the sickest people out there
in the world come to medical medium
information so you have to think about
this okay I mean we have some people
that didn't come here that sick we do
have that but if you look out there and
you see what's going on out there you'll
see this person this trainer has this
this person has that out there this this
you know doctor has this out there this
practitioner has this out there but they
don't have the sickest people on the
planet coming to them and the medical me
information is there for the sickest
people and the sickest people are high
in metal and they're high in pathogens
and that's just how it
works and a host of other things that
medical medum information talks about
right a whole bunch of that
stuff why does the hmds why does the
heavy metal detox smoothie work why does
the heavy metal detox
work
why what I mean by work meaning you
start getting rid of the depression you
start getting rid of the OCD you start
getting rid of anxiety you start feeling
better your CFS starts to come calm down
your fibro starts to drop your
neurological lime starts to improve your
Ms starts to improve and heal why and
many other symptoms too including ezema
psoriasis severe dermatitis all these
different things rosacea why does it get
better because when you're removing the
metals you're taking one of the most
potent Foods there are for the bugs away
you're taking the most potent foods for
the bugs you're removing those Foods
away from the bugs think about
that so as you remove Metals you're
removing the very food from the Epstein
bar the hh6 the hh7 the hh10 through 16
the hsv1 hsv2 C cyto virus right ceglar
virus you're removing all of the food
from that bug from those bugs the
shingles
viruses and then once you remove that
food the metal then that virus and that
pathogen becomes less less aggressive it
becomes more docile it
weakens and you start to
heal someone comes to me and they say w
what should I start with first what
should I do I'm sick I've had this this
this this this I've been to this many
doctors what do I do
I'll be like did you start with the
heavy metal
detox did you work on getting the metals
out did you start with some of the
antiviral protocols what are you doing
and then if they do the heavy metal
detox what happens is you start getting
those Metals out of your body they come
out of your liver and your brain and
then something changes all of a sudden
you're starving the pathogens that are
keeping you down because this is how it
works okay a pathogen will feed on
metal and when a pathogen feeds on
metal
right so you got the pathogens in you
everybody's got the pathogens in them
that's right you better believe they do
fever blister anybody cold sores anybody
oh yeah oh no I get cold SES all the
time and uh my sister gets cold sores
all the time and my mom got cold sores
for a year this we got a family of cold
sores that's what we have fever blisters
hsv1 right so you got the cold sore
virus okay yeah I had Mono I had Mono
before yeah that's Epstein bar you've
had Mono before exactly and then you got
all these pathogens right here right
could put happy faces on them because
these pathogens are really happy because
they're eating metal and then all of a
sudden we get exposed to toxic heavy
metals in so many different various ways
just the simplest ways every time to
this day I hear about somebody using an
alkaline ionizer water machine and I
don't care which brand it is every time
I see that I'm like oh yeah you give it
10 years you give it 10 years drinking
that water cuz those plates will just
blow up in there and they'll just
corrode and the metal that will be going
into your body from those
machines is just
unbelievable or if you're somebody
that's drinking the copper thermoses and
the copper mugs and the whole bit
because you think that's
healthy or you're somebody that's
exposed to aluminum foil or you have
Metals in you already that are
percolating we're going to go into that
a little bit so Metals Metals enter into
our body so many different various ways
they come on in and when the metals come
on
in guess
what they don't come out Metals go in
and never come out Metals go in and
never come out
Metals arrive and they never leave they
never leave they go in and they enter
the organs is what they do but we got
pathogens in us and when we have
pathogens in us the pathogens love to
eat and Gobble up the metal copper
Mercury pathogens eat and when they eat
they that's what happens why are we
sick mm info right
here mind-blowing information from so
mind-blowing pathogens feed off of the
metals that come
in and when pathogens feed off the
metals
right they then
here you go they
poop
excrement right out of them there you go
okay pathogens feed off of the metal and
then release the metal and then the
metal becomes a a
neurotoxin it becomes a
neurotoxin and uh someone on there saw a
comment saying are you grumpy ew am I
grumpy it's hard to stay super happy
when somebody people do things that just
aren't good for them out there you
should see it out there you guys know a
lot of people do a lot of things that
aren't good for them all right so I just
wanted to run that by you a little bit
so what we do is we have these epscene
bars we have these jles viruses we have
these hhv 6s yeah yeah we have the
simplexes in us and what happens and
then we collect more we go out and
collect more it's like sure I will
gladly collect another virus from you
definitely okay let me go here and
collect another one they're easy to
collect these days it's very easy to get
viruses and pathogens very easy there we
go what people don't realize with Metals
okay is they
Forge okay so we got
Mercury we got
copper like my my handwriting it's not
so great well what are you going to do
and so Mercury and copper love to
snuggle they love to forge they find
their way to each other is what they do
they find a way to each other they're
attracted to each other inside the body
Mercury and copper do you ever have a
filling removed no you haven't right not
to worry then your family members might
have your parents and their parents
might have your grandparents might have
had a whole bunch of mercury fillings
put
in and then their grandparents had a
whole bunch of mercury fillings put in
and it could even go further back than
that with Mercury fillings put in and
those Mercury feeling I've seen people
like I never had a Mercury filling
because I'm a younger person and I never
had that they didn't offer it they
offered a different composite it's like
don't worry you got plenty in you from
your grandparents and their parents and
your plenty of mercury in you it goes a
long way a long
way copper and Merc Mercury combine and
when we get upset and we get
emotional and something Jacks us up and
we're just like we're
lit and we're on fire for some
reason brain heat occurs all this brain
heat occurs right when that brain heat
occurs that electricity starts to cook
Metals electricity in our
brain hits that metal like no other and
then the forging process happens you got
a little copper inside your brain you
got a little mercury inside your brain
now you're
upset something gets you
angry angry something gets you upset I'm
writing really sloppy tonight something
gets you
upset and really
a maybe somebody just pissed you off and
then brain heat occurred and then the
copper and the Mercury start to forge
together from that heat it takes time it
takes time but it happens and then it
becomes one and now what you have right
here after they Forge is an alloy now
the copper and the Mercury copper the
Mercury are now one that makes things
worse and
then a bug comes
along little
virus awakens your immune system is low
your old mono virus starts to come out
the old EBV Epstein bar starts to come
out and what does it do it stumbles
across an alloy a combination of copper
and mercury and it gobbles it up what a
mess on this
board and when it gobbles it up it goes
to the bathroom and when that epine bar
goes to the
bathroom that's neurotoxin right there
neurotoxin that
neurotoxin can create anything
anything Vagas nerve issues tightness of
the chest tightness of the throat
vibrations all kinds of different stuff
going on nerve
Sensations ticks and spasms and aches
and pains and everything else and
fatigue yeah fatigue brain
fog all that neurotoxin pouring out of
that epine virus that just had that
copper in Mercury it's releasing that
neurotoxin into your bloodstream and
when it releases it into your blood
stream it starts to circulate float
around gets to the brain gets to the
nervous system hits the Vegas nerve
start starts to weaken the Vegas nerve
hits the cranial nerves and gets us sick
and now we don't know what's wrong where
what how we have no idea we're going
everywhere we're looking for help we're
doing castor oil p P we're doing Cod
Liver Oil we're doing sodium bicarbonate
we're trying to drink alkaline water
we're just looking looking looking we're
doing keto we're doing blood we're doing
this we're doing you name it we're doing
dious Earth particles which I strongly
strongly advise to my family and my
friends never to
do because it lowers the immune system
and then we're looking we're looking for
answers and all kinds of stuff you guys
I just saw somebody ask I shall deliver
the brains saver book right here that's
the book I'm in right now check it out
get it free at the library if you can or
just go to
amazon.com so let's go into Metals a
little bit more I would love to talk a
little bit about it okay beyond the
damage that toxic metals themselves can
do there's the truth that they act as
viral fuel so you got to understand
something it's critical to get Metals
out critical somebody may not have a lot
of viral issues or viral load they might
not have a low- grade viral infection
they might not have a highgrade viral
infection they may not have a big viral
load but they got a lot of metals and
then all of a sudden one day happens
where they pick up a virus and it all
just explodes on them I was healthy I
was doing good I don't understand and
they're backtracking in their mind I
remember when I was healthy I was doing
fine I was doing fine and then they're
doing their affirmations and they're
talking to themselves and then they're
talking to their their practitioners and
their doctors and they're like you don't
understand I was just fine the other
week and now I'm sick I was just fine
months ago a year ago I was fine I was
doing good and now I'm sick why why why
nobody knows it they were loaded with
metals and then something happened
either they contracted a virus or they
just had a virus come out of dormy
because their immune system got lowered
for some reason or another and a virus
came out and it gobbled up the metals
and boom overnight they had the worst
Sensations and the
worst symptoms the brain fog and the
aches and pains and the tingles and
numbness and the neurological Sensations
and the trigeminal
neuralgia and so much more and they're
struggling because it was the perfect
perfect recipe The Perfect Storm it was
the bug eating the metals at just the
right time and that's it they went down
and now they're living a life where it's
all about their health and only about
their health and they just weren't there
before they don't know what that's like
and they never experienced that
before I want to read a little bit
something to you real quick if that's
okay if you guys will let me do
that okay melting down when our brains
get hot and there's metal involved
because that's what happens
we're loaded with all these metals and
it becomes an alloy right the toxic
heavy metal particles break down the
metals melt they actually melt inside
our brain toxic heavy metals in the
brain get wear and tear when electricity
currents are entering them they start to
change did you ever notice somebody
changing did you ever see somebody
change like you don't even know who they
are like I don't even know who you are
man like I've known for years but you're
something's just changing about you what
is it like I don't even like who are you
who are you now this you could see in
somebody that has Alzheimer's right this
you can see with somebody who has
dementia you could really see it then
because it's just so obvious and you're
just like whoa something's wrong and
that's from toxic heavy metals and
that's original medical medum
information but it's from toxic heavy
metals causing the Alzheimer's right and
dementia but what happens is if you're
not diagnosed with Al Alzheimer's and
it's not so apparent and it's not so
visible and it's not on that scale at
all it's not about losing your memory
it's not about going into some kind of
mania it's not about any of
that it's just about everyday living in
life and you're just like why is that
what that person's changing what is it
about
them a lot of times that's metals that
have melted and they have melted
together and they're forging and they're
changing and that's what that is metals
that forg together their shapes change
so metals that enter our body or have
been in our body since we were born end
up changing over time corrosion can
occur as well the metals corrode so I
want to show you that really quick we're
going to make the heavy metal detox
smoothie I love that and we're talking
about heavy metal detox I want to talk
about like blood testing for Metals I
want to talk about urine samples for
metals
[Music]
right all
right cuz that's important too the metal
goes
in the metal particles go in okay they
go in a certain shape and size
Industrial Metals that go into us all
the time in so many various way did you
have fast food metals were in
it that's just one thing but what
happens is metals tend to melt as we
have electricity running through our
brain and electrical impulses are
hitting the metal particles and they
tend to melt when they melt they they
change shape and all of a sudden they
have a different shape to them they're
not the same shape anymore they came in
kind
of off shape in a different way but now
they've changed all the shapes have
changed and when that
does happen we
change when the shape of the metal
changes that has entered our body
because it's melting we
change you can't really tell at first
with a lot of people but then you can
tell later or if someone hasn't seen
somebody in a long time and then they
see them and they see how different they
are in different various ways there's a
changing that
occurred all right
so I want to look a little more into
this another reason brain conditions
worsen with time is that more toxic
heavy metals continue to collect and
this is the next part I want to say
right here so you got these Metals right
there in you and then more Metals come
in every day every year and they come in
and they find their way and they collect
they bind on to the metals that are
already in you deposits in the brain can
get bigger so as more Metals stream in
like this they find the metal deposits
and then they actually enlarge the metal
starts to accumulate more metal occurs
and grows because the more metal going
into the body actually it goes and finds
the other metal in your body they both
join hands and now you're getting metal
deposits and if somebody has a big metal
deposit if someone has a really big one
you better believe it so many people do
they got big metal deposits
seizures
seizures big metal deposits
okay so if someone has a big deposit in
their
brain or two big deposits in their brain
okay and maybe a smaller
one and more metals are coming
in they find these big deposits these
deposits get bigger 10 years down the
road the deposit is even bigger 20 years
it's even bigger you're 50 years old now
the deposit ETS are bigger because
you're not getting medals out you're not
taking care of yourself on that level
nobody's teaching you nobody knows or if
you hear about Metals now you'll be like
let me try Zite it doesn't work or let
me try this it doesn't work or let me
try something else it doesn't work you
don't get the metals out it's smoking
mirrors it's critical Metals come out
there's no
games no time for games no time for
BS the medals have to to come out can't
do make believe crap where you all of a
sudden this is good for medal somebody
says and this is good for medals and
somebody says out there because it's
like an industry it's it's everybody's
just eating each other alive out there
to try to make a buck right but we got
to take it serious with the chronic Leo
because there ain't no time left for a
lot of people who are sick because
they've been sick for so long they have
to get the stuff out of their system so
they could live their
life the more metal they go goes in US
it hits the big deposits that create
seizure say or just sickness of all
kinds or severe PR fatigue or whatever
it is because it's feeding viruses as
more metal comes in the deposits get
bigger and they swell sometimes they'll
get so big that neurons start to Short
Circuit so as your
neurons right in your brain all these
neurons I'm going to draw a few neurons
right here you guys okay with that if
you if you're not caught up to what I'm
doing you just rolled in here these are
big heavy metal deposits right here
these three deposits inside of our brain
okay more metal coming in is making them
bigger your neurons which are these I'm
going to string them together you're
okay with
that shinging these neurons together
just for
fun okay what happens is these deposits
get so big they impede the neuron so now
they're walking themselves into the
neurons as they're walking themselves
into the neurons your memory is going as
they're walking themselves into the
neurons you're getting
Parkinson as you're walking into these
neurons you're struggling with all kinds
of neurological
symptoms and that's what happens more
metal goes in the metal deposits get
bigger and then they rub against neurons
and they start to D and then the next
part happens right
there the next part is the neurons get
corroded the metal corrodes and the
metal corrodes and then it out gases and
deposits come off of it and that's next
I'll give you that quick rund down cuz
we got stuff to
do so here's your neurons right here
bunch of
neurons right there they are we're
stringing them all
together there they are all that tissue
okay and then there's the metal here it
is a big old metal deposit see it right
here a big old metal deposit right here
it's growing bigger and bigger you got
more metal coming in left and right from
various places more Metals coming in the
deposits getting bigger and bigger and
then what happens is that it pushes
against these neurons
but worse the metal starts to corrode
we're on these really high fat diets the
high fat corrodes the metal more we're
getting more metal coming in and then it
starts to leech it's like a leech field
these are your neurons here and they
start to become dirty your brain gets
filthy inside because the metal starts
to leech and it starts to leech out gas
and start to corrode and as that Metal's
corroding it's entering your neurons see
those beautiful blue neurons right there
there you go look at that see those
neurons are getting contaminated right
there you are and when that happens you
wake up one
morning and you have a seizure or your
first great panic attack or something
else you wake up and you just don't know
who you are for a moment happens every
time for so many people all the time for
a lot of people out there
people say to me often like why bother
getting Metals out what does it matter
it
matters because it's something that gets
in her way and people don't realize it
and they suffer from it and they have to
live with those metals and it is no
fun so think I'll look at one more
little thing for you guys old Metals
versus new Metals this isn't important
place to talk about for a moment heavy
metals that we inherit have aged to them
like I said they're old they go back
2,000 3,000
years and depending on what part of the
world someone's bloodline stems from
older heavy metals also have a higher
oxidative rate so that's what happens
you see someone may have similar amounts
of metals in them than someone else but
the oxidative rate is faster in that one
person making them sicker and giving
them symptoms and sending them downhill
the other person has a a slower
oxidative rate where the metals are
leeching slower so this person they're
leeching faster this person they're
leeching slower that also determines so
many different symptoms when and
how an oxidative countdown occurred as
the metals aged those Metals became
highly unstable when they entered and
sat inside human bodies where metals
were exposed for years and years and
years going down our bloodline so what
happens is the older the metals are the
more we really suffer and so many people
are suffering in so such great ways
awful great ways all right so I want to
start working on some other stuff too
let's let's get into um let's get into
the intestinal tract for a couple of
minutes
okay we inhale Metals we eat Metals we
breathe in me Metals which is inhaling
them we get Metals in our skin we get
Metals in our bloodstream every single
day and metals circulate throughout our
bloodstream every single day and then
they find a home so when we eat toxic
heavy
metals the metals go down into our
stomach they go down into our intestinal
tract and they stay there they cling to
the walls of the intestinal tract they
go up the highway that goes to the liver
the hepatic portal Highway the metals
travel into the liver the liver tries to
filter the metals out and then the
metals get trapped inside the liver when
the metals get trapped inside the liver
they become food for you know what the
bugs the bugs the bugs as the metals are
sitting inside the liver so are bugs and
the bugs feed off of the metals and next
thing you know it you got yourself some
fatigue you
cannot explain you don't understand the
fatigue you can't explain it you don't
know why you have it but it's there and
it's just not a matter of you
overworking or over exercising or just
even being stressed out fatigue that
shouldn't be there sticks around because
bugs inside the liver will feed off of
those metals and that will happen now
people get tested for Metals
now it's something that's common since
there's been so much awareness with the
medical medium books all these years and
information so they're getting tested
for metals and a lot of doctors are like
well you don't have really any Metals in
here but what people don't realize is
they're in the organs spleen pancreas
liver inside the stomach tissue the
stomach walls testinal tract walls
they're in the heart Metals get into the
heart muscle and they hide in there
they're in lung tissue metals are in the
brain metals are in the spinal cord
metals are in the central nervous system
and they sit in there so when you test
for Metals you don't really test that
high in metal some people do because
they're having recent
exposures the only way to find Metals
through testing and blood testing is a
recent exposure that's happening on a
daily or weekly
basis and when there's a recent
exposure then the blood can you can find
Metals inside the
blood if there isn't a recent exposure
of a high enough
magnitude of enough then it'll just sit
deep inside the organs I've been putting
this information out there for decades
finally the blood labs are starting to
to admit this that metals are sitting
inside organs and they may not be
detectable in the
bloodstream thanks to mm
info okay so let's talk about getting
the metals out I'm going to make a heavy
metal detox smoothie one that I really
love and you can you can get Metals out
in different ways I talk about it in the
books and I had all the way since the
beginning that getting three out of the
five ingredients is critical three out
of the five so you got cant right here
that's one of the ingredients right
there you got wild blueberries that's
another one right there you got Atlantic
dols it's another one right there you
got spirulina you got barley grass those
are two more right there five will give
you the best
results five ingredients will give you
the best
results but it's important to try to at
least get three if you
can now a lot of people talk about
chorella and they're like well what
about that well that drops the metal it
doesn't hold on to it no one even knew
it even did anything with
metal until I started talking about over
the years that it drops metal it drops
it and a lot of people don't realize
that another thing is zeolites cannot
get metal out of the brain
keep this as a feather in your
cap because this is critical because
it's important to know that Zees will
never get toxic heavy metals or any
metal out of the brain it's not possible
it's basically a clay it can't get
Metals out of organs either because it
can't enter an organ there's no zeolite
variety there's no zeolite brand out
right now there's no type of Zite that
can remove a metal out of a an organ or
the
brain so when you're using Zees kiss
your money
goodbye kiss a goodbye very important to
know because what people don't realize
is if clay can enter your
bloodstream if clay can enter your
bloodstream on any level if zeolite can
enter your bloodstream in any level on
any level you'll just have a stroke and
a heart attack
you'll have a blood clot an aneurysm
blood clot or some kind of blood
blockage blood vessel
blockage because you just can't pump
that stuff into your bloodstream and
have it swim around it'll get caught up
somewhere and you'll die or have a
problem so it never enters into your
bloodstream it can't never has for
anyone and never will very important to
understand a couple little topics I
wanted to cover because we're talking
about heavy metal
detox and I wouldn't recommend a zealite
these days because there's
cross-contamination of zeolites that
aren't edible so what happens is with
manufacturing zeolite
products it's
intermixed not on purpose but by
accident with zeolites that are not
edible that's a problem all when it's
own that create dehydration one of the
reasons why I don't like zeolites is
because it dehydr ation issues you lose
critical electrolytes you get dehydrated
happens like that with all
Zees especially the ones that are out
there now so these are some of the
things that I'm talking about that are
really important and that's one of them
another another one right here okay very
important you can't get Metals out with
charcoal you can't get Metals out of
your bloodstream you can't get Metals
out of your organs with charcoal it is
impossible
it will not happen it does not
happen zealite and charcoal don't
work and zealite is just something that
goes into your stomach then down your
dadum then into your intestinal tract
and then out the door that's all it does
it can't enter the hepatic portal
Highway it can't cross the bloodb brain
barrier it can't do any of that it's
imposs possible if it did the person
would die and have a
stroke charcoal goes in the intestinal
tract and then goes out it's not a organ
or
brain toxic metal removal system so
that's important too to understand I'm
trying to read comments at the same time
you
guys so now you'll hear out there are so
many that well try try try this try that
that will do it and it doesn't so what I
like I like something with a track
record something that has helped so many
people and turned around autism yes
autism children that couldn't speak
could now
speak turned around all kinds of all
kinds of different issues in people got
their lives back in so many different
ways got them out of wheelchairs got
them talking again got them walking
again something with a powerful track
record got their skin better got rid of
the eczema got rid of the psoriasis got
rid of all of that that's what I'm
talking about that matters and that's
what we want not something I'm throwing
together creating some horeshit for
somebody to actually take or whatever
and you don't know cuz there's no track
record but the medical medium heavy
metal detox has the track record for
years and years and years and has saved
lives and you guys know many of you guys
have done it
has saved
lives all right so I'm going to go into
this a little bit I'm going to hit the
wild blueberry for a little bit you guys
got a couple of minutes on this try to
keep it as interesting as possible right
there okay a Canadian wild
blueberry or the main wild
blueberry
right and this right here is the
ultimate to use in your heavy metal
detox it's this it's the best one to
use now if you can't get a hold of this
one here which is the wild blueberry
North
America if you can't get a hold of it I
always say you can do blackberries but
blackberries can only remove a little
bit of metal little bit from the
intestinal
tract and the blackberries don't even
have to be wild now all wild berries out
there like wild
raspberries wild
billberry has a little
bit some capabilities of removing a
little bit of toxic heavy metals out of
the intestinal tract but can't remove
them out of the brain can't remove them
out of the liver can't remove them deep
out of the
organs and that's the difference now if
you don't have access to the wild
blueberry and gusta fium that one if you
don't have access to those wild
blueberries and you got to use another
blueberry or another different kind of
berry or a wild blueberry or something
like that that because there are wild
blueberries out
there and the wild blue let's go into it
a little bit okay European blueberry is
not this variety of wild blueberry it's
the billberry it's really important to
know now there are Bill berries in the
US there there's bilberries in Canada
there's bilberries in Maine there's
bilberries out there but and I have
access to bilberry but I've never put
bilberry in here so I want people to
know this this is important because I
think what happened is over time because
there wasn't access to this variety of
wild blueberry I think people are just
putting any wild berry they can find in
there and I got respect for that because
guess what that's good that's good put
in any wild berry you can get in there I
like the blackberries and if you can get
a wild Blackberry then that is the
ultimate it's not going to do what the
wild blueberry does and gusap fium is
not going to do what that
does but it's important to know because
what happens out there is then people
are just like whoa I'm doing it up like
I'm doing
it exactly the way it should be and what
they don't realize if the billberry is
in here it's not exactly the way it
should be but still sure if that's all
you got then do it but you're really
running on four ingredients if if you
don't have the wild
blueberry if you're using a billberry
then your your your heavy metal detox is
only running on four ingredients not
five that's all and I always say three
out of the five get three out of the
five so if you're somebody and you're
doing the heavy metal detox somewhere
anywhere in the
world and you're putting a raspberry in
there the wild raspberry are you're
putting a wild billberry in there or
you're putting a wild Blackberry in
there
that's that's that's good it's got a lot
of nutrients for other
reasons it's got healing properties for
other things but it doesn't remove the
the the metals deep within the organs
and deep within the brain and deep where
it needs to be so you're running really
four out of
five and if you're somebody that only
has cilantro you call cor coriander you
got cilantro and then you got DOL and
then you got say spirina that's
three it's still going to help but to
get maximum maximum
pull maximum you want the
five the five you need the cilantro you
need the Inus fium the wild blueberry I
know in Europe they call European
blueberry that's
bberry and I know there are wild
blueberries but there're they're very
hard to get they're very hard to get in
Europe you can't get them they're
they're they're very hard to find and
you can't get them so everybody's
relying on the billberry out there
that's fine you can put billberry in
there you can definitely put bberry you
can put Blackberry in there you can put
a huckleberry in there you can put those
in there but you're not at the maximum
pull to actually get the metals deep out
of the organs right you're running four
out of
five ingredients and look companies have
also tried to market the billberry so
much so they say that the North American
you know wild blueberry they say that
the wild blueberry from
Canada is
cultivated there's companies out there
now so hungry and so money hungry to hop
on the heavy metal detox ride that
they'll actually say that the wild
blueberry gusap fium in the United
States or in Canada is actually
cultivated that is not true this is a
wild food and it's not
cultivated that's important thing I want
to clear up so I've seen that out
there and the wild blueberry has more
antioxidants than the bberry so I want
to cover that for a minute that's really
important here
okay so there are some rumors out there
being spread because that's how it is
because people want to sell the crap out
of their
billberry I get it everybody's
everybody's trying to survive out there
I get it but they want to sell the CRA
crap out of their billberry so much so
that they will say that the billberry is
higher in antioxidants than the wild
blueberry they Gap fum Canada in the US
and they're wrong they're
wrong they are dead
wrong this wild blueberry right here the
gusol has higher antioxidents in any
billberry
fact but you see they'll spin it every
body spins whatever they want to do
that's what they do they spin it all oh
our bill berries are higher than the
wild blueberry no it's not it may be
higher than a cultivated blueberry like
a regular cultivated blueberry it may be
higher for than you know than
that they grow a lot of cultivated
blueberries in Poland maybe it's it's
higher than that one maybe it's higher
than another one that's cultivated but
not the inap fium not
the wild food that's sitting in front of
me so I want to clear some of these
things
up it's okay if you're running four out
of five it's okay if you're running
three out of five and that's all you got
you only got some barley grass juice
powder or you only got some spirulina
and some
cilantro and maybe some
dolls and that's a three you run because
that's all you got then make that
smoothie or make that smoothie bowl with
those three things okay you guys you can
do that
but
ideally ideally if it comes your way
someday or you're somewhere and you have
it and you can do all
five that takes it to another level
that's when it's a maximum right there
cilantro spirulina barley grass juice
powder dols wild blueberries like wild
blueberries not what they call Wild
blueberry a billberry no not that wild
blueberries
bilberries grow differently than a wild
blueberry bilberries grow in small
amounts very spread out so I question a
lot of billberry products out there
because you can't Harvest enough of it
to meet a demand which means it's
questionable to what else is in
there anyway okay we covered a little
bit of that let's start doing
this
if you need to make just a smoothie bowl
and you just want a bunch of fruit
chopped up in a bowl make sure if you
wanted the heavy metal detox you put in
the five
ingredients you put a little bit of
dols you got your wild blueberry you got
your
cilantro right you got your spirulina
barrass cheese powder and you put it and
you make a smoothie Bowl you know what I
do a lot I'll tell you right now you
guys you know what I do L I cut open a
melon crack the melon open and I put
spirulina right in the melon I put
barley grass right in the melon I put
some DOL liquid right in the melon right
and I put some wild blueberries right in
the melon and I chop up some cilantro
and I put it right in the melon and I
have basically a melon smoothie Bowl
basically and that's what I do because
I'm just trying to get the five
ingredients that's the key right that's
the main key I'm just trying to get that
in me all right but we're making the
smoothie
let's
get roughly two cups of the wild
blueberries in here
okay you can find real wild blueberries
in Europe real wild ones but it's not
billberry they're just calling billberry
the wild blueberry that's what they're
doing they're calling the the billberry
the wild blueberry it's not the wild
blueberry you see how it works I just
want to make sure that that's all clear
information
and then the sellers are doing that and
pushing that to make money right the
sellers of billberry products are
pushing it as the wild blueberry they're
actually saying it's a wild blueberry
and then you see the little you see the
little fine print
bberry our wild blueberries are so good
out here they're so great you should see
them they're actually handpicked by
people foraging in the woods and then
right there you'll see a little bit
they're calling it wild blueberry and
then you'll see a little bit in the
little spot there billberry like yeah
because you're picking bilberries
but you know because so much so many
people millions of people drink the
heavy metal detox around the world you
know that there's a market for it I
understand I'm not look I'm not calling
people out I'm just saying it like it is
of what's Happening here's cilantro
right
here I like cilantro by itself I like it
on everything and anything I use it as a
leafy green that's how I love cilantro
as a leafy
green but it's great have it here's
another thing to run by you really quick
okay if you get the five ingredients
during the course of the same day the
medical medium heavy metal
detox means you try to get the five
ingredients on the same
day same day that's what you
do you get the cilantro in your salad
you get the wild blueberry in your
breakfast you get the your spirulina in
a papaya put sprinkle it on a papaya
whatever it is you get the five on the
same day doesn't have to be at the same
time keep that in mind and you get the
medals
out you just have to get them in on the
same
day see how it goes I've always said
that all the way since the beginning
billberry is still good for you and you
can still use them to get some small
amount of metal out of your intestinal
tract it won't get it out of the brain
it won't get out of the organs but the
billberry will get a small amount out of
the intestinal tract and so will Wild
raspberry and so will a wild
blackberry and so will some Huckleberry
whatever it is that you got right it
will take a little bit out of the
intestinal tract but it can't go further
than that and it doesn't take a lot out
of the intestinal tract and the binder
the heavy binder quality is not there so
you can you know that's not happening
too so the wild blueberry right the
angustifolium is the like heavy
binder
all right so I got cilantro in there I
got the wild blueberry in there let's
pop in a couple bananas in there too
hello
bananas I'm very happy to see
you pop a couple of bananas in
there
nice nice you guys it's great to be here
I wanted to run this by people I want
them to be inspired to get Metals out of
their body because it is important
important to do
so all right let's get some spirulina in
here a little
bit okay I'll try not to make a
mess but I do make a mess all the time
in the kitchen got some barley grass
cheese powder let's go into that
next barley grass is not barley grass
cheese
powder Corella is not
spirulina it's not two different things
two different things
okay a lot of people will use they'll
see barley grass cheese powder but they
miss the juice the juice so they do
barley grass powder scratchy it doesn't
work it doesn't have that play it
doesn't bind on to the others it doesn't
act as a binder it doesn't remove
anything it can't be barley grass it has
to be barley grass cheese powder so we
threw that in
there all right all right crack open a
delicious
orange a little bit on there if you want
to use coconut water you can put coconut
water in there
too you can do that putting a little bit
of orange in there if you want to do
coconut water little bit in there just
like
that all
right what am I missing have you guys
been paying attention CU I'm missing
something I am missing something
indeed could put a little strip of
kelp is not going to do it kelp is not
going to do it see moss is not going to
do it I'm sorry but it's not I know
everybody wants to create
something because there's a SE Moss
Market it's like let's use it for Metals
well sorry but it doesn't get the medals
out there's a billberry market but sorry
but it doesn't get the medals out the
way it should I get it
I know it's a market for stuff I know
everybody's about marketing everybody's
about I'm selling crap it's everywhere
now every single person seems to be
selling
something I mean I turned on social
somebody was selling a foot balb and I
was asking s so is that going to work
and so is like du they're selling a foot
bomb all right putting in some doll
liquid
there all right blend it
up let's make it
happen all right
guys actually pretty psyched for
this
go you can always sing a little song
when you're doing it
too I'm going to get my medals
out choose whatever song or him you
[Music]
like
I like the Ping
good I like to give it a good
pulverizing let's click this off let's
move this
over all right thank you for hanging out
there for that I think I need a
glass
boom and right there there we
are nice oo good good uh camera
work
whoa I can pour a little bit more to the
top there we
are and that is the heavy metal detox
smoothie version can make smoothie Bowl
you can just eat these five ingredients
throughout the course of the day just
make sure it's on the same day that bit
of information is
powerful powerful it's
empowering
um I'm excited about this because I am
hungry now there's this congealing thing
that happens and I talked about this the
other
day the the inusa fium that wild
blueberry
congeals the most has the highest
congealing factor that I've been able to
find out
there and that's part of the whole
binding part so with the wild blueberry
does it helps to get the metals out of
organs but it also has an intense
binding quality for the intestinal tract
something sodium bicarbonate cannot do
something corilla cannot do something
zeolite cannot do something bentonite
clay canot do something charcoal cannot
do it can't do no can do no can do but
this is that incredible and that
powerful
right so
good hands down
delicious and what I like to do is when
I'm when I'm consuming the heavy metal
detox I'm not consuming any heavy metal
meaning I'm not out there purposely
consuming heavy metals but when I
consume the heavy metal
detox what a what a feeling when you're
getting it in you every day keep a
journal mark it
down keep a journal and Mark it down
that's what I do I did one today I did
one another day I did another one I did
another
one keep a journal and Mark it down and
then be like well I did seven I did
eight of them this month I did 10 of
this month and try to get that try to
get that to a point where you're like
doing every day for the
month and a lot of people they do it
once a week they do it every three days
they do it once in a while but try to
keep track so you know you're doing it
enough you're doing it for a few days a
week and then you're doing it for four
days a week and you're mve up 5 days a
week and you're getting an average and
you Journal it you're like whoa I had 20
heavy metal detoxes this
month it's a great way to do
it so good all right
guys just want to touch
base say hi to everybody you do it you
do it daily
Gina
incredible Tanya four years in March
amazing a do M do everyday for me yum
incredible
over there on YouTube you guys are doing
it do you have to drink the whole thing
drink what you can baby step it drink a
little bit make a smaller one if you
really have to it's
okay oh God I love that that's a
flavor it can't be
beat okay
guys
um love you guys you do it every day
great fantastic guys know I'm proud of
you incredible if you want to like soak
up and absorb that heavy metal
information watch this video from the
start you guys sign up to my telegram or
you know subscribe to my telegram if you
can all
right and um send up to my newsletter if
you can so you know what's going on and
um I am working on trying to do
a
book
signing if you guys want to bring your
old books you know I'm working on it I
don't know when it is yet I'm going to
try to find information I'm trying I'm
trying to find a place for it that you
know that could be a good Hub so if you
guys want to come
out and um I'm not going to travel
around the world right now I can't do
that but I'm going to try to find one
location and if you guys want to come
once I have dates and stuff like that
you bring your old
books and I will sign them I've never
done an official book signing ever in 10
years so it would be my first book
signing I remember when I when medical
medium book one came out and my
publisher was like when are you doing a
book signing too busy writing the next
book can't do
it next book came out I publisher said
when are you do in a book signing
because everybody does book signings
authors do book signings I'm like H
can't do it too much going on I can't do
it Anna says I've been drinking the hmds
for almost 9 years there is a birth mark
that is disappearing because of drinking
it birth marks are because of toxic Kevy
Metals it's true yep mm info and and um
so thankful that you're actually
drinking nine years nine years it's
incredible Pat you got all the books
incredible thank
you co White Springs you want me to come
to Norway
I can't get to Norway right now I can't
can't get to Norway I wish I can't I
wish but I'm trying to figure it out so
if you guys want to come out sometime
when I get a date I will do book signing
say hi anyway you guys all
right I will see you next time and if
you like the video give me a thumbs up
give me a like or whatever you call it
if you don't like the video give me a
thumbs up and a like anyway I'm keeping
out the middle finger keeping out the
middle finger today you don't have to
give me a middle finger just give me a
thumbs up okay anyway