this is incredible got liver rescue
right here i'm talking about the immune
system i'm talking about the liver i
haven't talked about the liver that much
so this is an important one liver
and our emotions
liver and our immune system liver and
our skin
think about that right there like skin
problems
all the different skin problems people
have liver
and emotions can get intense
when the liver is sick
or dirty
or weakened or stagnant or sluggish hey
you guys good to see you guys coming on
you guys know i did an amazon live you
guys many of you guys were there
probably right made that incredible food
i still have some of it here i still
have some of the pasta that came out of
this book so it's the veggie pasta dish
and this pasta is incredible you know
but anyway
you guys
you check out the amazon live platform
go there when you get a chance the link
is in the description of the video so
you should go and see the replay of
today's amazon live check it out i want
you to see how i made the pasta and
everything else and i did some cooking
tips too i just want to let everybody
know that now while we're going we're
talking about the liver a little bit
today right you're always talking to us
cheryl says hey well of course of course
you guys are important really important
you guys been through a lot and that's
the thing you know you guys have been
through a lot i mean
sure
you know here i am right talking about
liver rescue but why am i here why am i
talking about liver rescue why am i
talking about health why am i talking
about anything because you guys have
been through hell and back so many of
you guys have been through so much
so many ups and downs many of you guys
have lost your jobs because being sick
many of you guys have lost family
members because of being sick meaning
like you you just either you know you
just had difficulties in relationships i
know so many people they they have
relationships and their relationships
fall apart because someone's sick in the
in the relationship and it's so sad i
watched that for years
you know i mean so many times i've
watched that
and so health is just so important and
right now it's critical
to keep our immune system strong because
our immune systems get weakened and
beaten down that's how the system's set
up the system is set up to beat us down
to beat us down to beat us down even the
time change
just so you know you guys the whole time
change the whole time the one hour time
shift
that's actually to throw us off our game
and weaken our immune systems and
destabilize us that's what that is i'm
going to talk about that one day i've
been saying this for years but
i'm going to go into details on that if
you guys just came on here we're talking
about the liver we're talking about the
liver's immune system we're talking
about the skin conditions of liver
including acne we're talking about
emotions when you have a sick liver
things can get heated up emotional
emotional yellow rings true it's true
michelle l you said you knew
yeah
yeah the time change is not supposed to
happen they're not supposed to do the
time change
that's not any natural occurrence that's
control that's that's because
that's all about controlling the human
race
and weakening them because the time
chain change stresses people out gets
them sick that's what it does that's
what they do that's the whole point it's
actually to knock people down
they try to try to knock you down
wherever they can that's how it's done
out there
and knock you down wherever you guys see
it right you guys see it this is not you
guys on telegram you guys on tick tock
good to see you guys on tick tock they
try to knock you down wherever they can
okay
that's how it's done and the time change
is just one way they try to knock you
down
that's just one way there's other ways
plenty of other ways we're good to see
you guys here you know i love just
giving you any information i can we're
talking about the immune system what you
see in front of me right now is golden
seal
zinc
but you see golden seal
every single year around the holidays i
tell my friends and family you better
have your golden seal you better have it
every single year it's like you better
have your golden steel in your pocket
you better have it in your pocket you
better have it right getting a little
scratchy throat got to get my golden
seal out let me take my golden seal you
get something else is happening let me
take my golden seal someone was coughing
around me let you know a family member's
sick let me they flew off a plane let me
take my golden seal i'm all stressed out
around the holidays there's there's a
lot of pressure there's a lot of stress
i'm traveling i better take my golden
seal it that's critical for this time of
year
critical
i think glycophates are killing us all
there's worse stuff than glycophage
denise glysophates aren't killing us all
isophates like lycospas are not killing
us all i mean are they good no
no they're not there's there's way
bigger
way bigger fish
way bigger fish in the pond can i tell
you a bigger fish in the pond and
glycerates can i take you a bigger a
bigger fish blood draw that's a bigger
fish okay
that's a bigger fish
this is a bigger fish right here such a
bigger fish you cannot even believe it
that's how much of a bigger fish this is
okay
that's what this is
oh i'm gonna make my doctor's
appointment oh you want to take more
blood from me
they are killing
everyone slowly purposely not the doctor
on purpose doctors are great they're
trained
to bloodlet you to lower your immune
system let viruses take over let let
pathogens take over break down your
immune system and and quicken a death
whether it's 10 years it takes five
years or to keep you chronically ill
it's rigged like that
and that's part of it
glycomates
i get it you know that's a that's a bad
thing
blood draw
that's a tragedy here you are sick with
neurological alignment they take another
28 vials you never get better
never get better
thousands and thousands of people
chronic illness end up dying from
getting more blood drawn more and then
when you get sicker because you're
draining all your blood your immune
system you're taking your immune system
out guess what
you get sicker and they take more blood
oh my you're patient you're sicker
well nurse order up another 20 vials
what the patient just had it done last
week it doesn't matter your blood all
comes back
take another 20 vials and you go
downhill downhill downhill downhill
downhill until you don't get to the
doctor to take blood no more or you end
up in the hospital dying blood draw is
way bigger of a problem there's so many
other fish to fry i can we can fry fish
all day long that's what we can do hey
i'm gonna put this i'm gonna put the arm
on top of the blender is that okay
okay blender you guys i didn't have time
to clean up the blender after the amazon
live i didn't have time to get
everything too straight but you know
what i did have time to get a few of my
friends out here got my german shepherd
out here i did have time for that
piggy's over here i got the goat
and
i got the chicken there and uh
i got the black lab right
okay so
the whole anyway you guys it's good to
see you guys coming on tick tock we got
a good crowd on tick tock today we're
talking about the liver and emotions
we're talking about other things too
nicholas says vimergy having a sale for
the next few days
you know what that's a perfect time for
goldenseal for me and my friends then of
my family so i'm gonna let them know um
thanks for letting everybody know
so the whole point you guys is this is a
cool live right now we're talking about
a few things we're talking about when
your liver gets toxic we get emotional
why
and why why would you get emotional
because your liver's toxic
why would that happen why is the liver
why is the liver a part of us
getting emotional
i mean we can get you know and that's
the whole thing
it's a big it's a big piece of it when
the
rachel says rachel simpson says what
brand of golden steel pleases vimergy v
is in victor i emaz and mary e rgy and
what you won't find in here
is the mystery 10
ingredients that are in all the
supplements out there
that nobody knows is in there the
mystery stuff
that is allowed to be hidden in every
single supplement company's supplements
they in all supplement company
supplements out there there's up to ten
percent
hidden ingredients that don't have to be
listed in your supplements and vimergy
said uh uh
uh uh screw that
i know cause i'm friends with those guys
they're amazing hearts of gold mom and
pop
and um and i'm friends with i'm friends
with a lot of supplement companies
because i have to be friends is because
i want them to keep standards up right
and vimergy said uh uh uh-uh
there ain't gonna be no hidden five
percent ingredients in this we're not
doing it manufacturers they hide five to
ten percent
ingredients hidden mystery ingredients
and all everybody's supplements out
there all the best supplement companies
out there i don't care who they are
there's up to ten percent mystery hidden
ingredients out there up there in there
and remember she said uh
uh uh screw that
we're not doing that there's not gonna
be one to ten percent of mystery
anything in this that's number one
number two there's no alcohol in this
tincture
no alcohol alcohol is the bad thing in
tinctures it destroys the herbs so it
doesn't work
that's another thing i could go on and
on and on and go on i can't say enough
i'm not sponsored i'm not sponsored
by these guys
but i love them and it's just a fact
janine yeah yes the the change has
really the time change has really messed
me up explanation points i think i have
a mild case of c
i'm sick but celery juice olive leaf
extract plus medical medium protocols
it's hard
because i hurt
all over but i'm trying
proud of you proud of you yeah another
time change that's what it's it's rigged
it's rigged to
foul up the the human race
there's no reason for time change
there's no you think you think you think
the native americans you think the
native americans
think the indigenous you know indigenous
cultures you think they were like hey
everybody
we got to change the time on everybody
we got to set our we got to set our
clocks even though they didn't have well
they didn't have a clock they they
watched the sunset the sunrise we got to
set our clocks one hour ahead one hour
behind
i think the native americans 500 years
ago were like
hey everybody in the tribes we got to
set our clocks back hey let's set the
sun back how the sun's setting set it
back an hour
you think the native americans are like
hey set that clock back
right like you think they did that
you think that you think okay you think
a bear in the woods is like
oh i we got to set that you think the
bears all get together do you think the
deer all get together
in the woods and say you guys we gotta
we gotta set our clock back
go back an hour or go back an hour
forward do you think all the squirrels
and
all the woodchucks and all the raccoons
and all the beavers you think they all
got we got to set our clocks back
you think indigenous cultures thousands
of years ago were like you got to set a
clock you guys we got to set our clocks
back
i mean how insane is that
how insane is that
but you know why they do it
they do it for one reason only to make
your life a little bit harder to trip
you up every without it's it's a
thousand knives death by a thousand
knives there's one more cut let's say
we're gonna set the time we're gonna set
the time change make the time change
happen
right it's a
miriam it's not so kids aren't outside
of the dark for the school bus it's not
it's going to set the time change that's
not why it's set they don't care
the industries that set the time change
that do it they don't care about that
they don't care about that
okay the people that set the time change
okay
uh
they're not their kids aren't waiting in
the dark
somewhere for a bus
the powers that be in the upper echelon
the illumination who who creates the
time change
their kids aren't waiting in the dark at
a bus stop on some street
just so you know the illumination who
changes the time change doesn't care
about anybody's kids
anyway
exactly
so
yes
let's talk about a few things but that
mean but it's interesting it's
interesting
yeah is that dino exactly so you're
right we are supposed to be talking
about some cool things right now about
the liver liver and the immune system
liver and skin problems liver and
emotions
emotional liver there's an emotional
liver section in here which is really
cool just so you know you guys are live
on telegram we're live on tick tock
we're live on youtube
we're live on rumble we're live on
facebook
we're live on facebook too so i'm in the
table of contents so i'm just looking
for emotional liver right now you just
go in here like where's emotional liver
and what i love about what i love about
this book
is that what people don't realize
about
our liver is when it becomes toxic
we become toxic
when the liver becomes toxic our brain
becomes toxic when your liver becomes
toxic your brain
becomes toxic
because when your liver gets backed up
because that's your filter
your brain
gets toxic when your brain gets toxic
you get emotional
even more so
then maybe you would normally you know
normally we all get emotional you would
get emotional more so than maybe what we
would get you know normally
yeah
darcy lee says love it when you go into
the illumination i want the truth
yeah the illumination doesn't care about
anybody's kids
i mean you think the world is like that
i mean
you you guys see it now i mean
i i talked about this i talked about
this on the telegram private message
right the private message telegram
do you guys anybody on youtube anybody
on tik tok you guys on telegram might do
these private messages right
and i talked about a friend
right a friend's
child
right sick in high school
and had to stay home it's too sick too
long
and after a while nobody cared nobody
cared nobody cared it's exclusive on
telegram you should check it out right
the the private messages the exclusive
messages i mean and nobody cared it's
like
people the industries in the power at
the top and everything meaning the
higher echelon everybody they don't care
about anybody's kids
they don't care about anybody
why do you think everything's just going
so south too i mean everything just goes
so south all the time the industries
all of it
um all right you guys
you think they care about your kids when
they create all those chemical air
fresheners
and they got air fresheners pumping
5 000 dangerous chemicals in your home
for your children to breathe in do you
think anybody cares about your kids
there's air fresheners in everybody's
homes now poisoning our children
there's air fresheners in all the
schools now plugged in in all the
classrooms do you think anybody cares
about our kids
they're poisoning all our kids with air
fresheners
thousands of dangerous untested
chemicals the chemicals that are not
even monitored pumped into
into
those air fresheners there and then
pumping those plug-ins pumping in
everybody's homes and schools
poisoning children and pets do you think
they care about your kids
and speaking of kids we got a pandas
section in here by the way it's called
jaundice and baby liver that's in liver
rescue right now
so
this book is packed with information it
is healed already so many people i mean
so many people all through the years
it's really that special of a book so
it really is
so i got a section in here back here
it's emotional liver it's um it's
supplement protocols for that which is
really great
this is a powerful book
so i'm just looking i'll find it in a
minute too so i want to talk about some
other stuff too
the whole thing about pandas is what
people don't really understand is that
it's not just streptococcus pandas is
more than streptococcus
streptococcus is a co-factor in pan with
pandas and that's what people don't
realize it's the co-factor to pandas
severity's like well strep-strap strap
well
no um that's just one piece of it that's
a co-factor right
and so with the whole thing with strep
and different strains and the different
varieties of strep that everybody has
everybody has everybody walks around
with all the different strips right the
whole bit is any any child that had
pandas or as pandas ends up with
acne later on ends up with utis ends up
with ear infections more ear infections
ends up with all these other things
marcy
marcy says two kids two kids healed from
pandas here using medical medium
incredible
that's such good news
that's such good news that's amazing
news
holly tune says it healed me explanation
points no more autoimmune disease after
25 years of suffering i'm living proof
holly incredible i'm so glad liver
rescues touched a lot of people's hearts
it's been a lot for so many
if you guys just came on and tick tock
if you just came on on telegram
this came on youtube we're talking about
the liver we're talking about emotional
liver we're talking about what happens
when our liver gets stagnant and
sluggish it poisons our brain
the liver is supposed to hold on to the
poisons and toxins until we give it a
chance to safely guide it out
so what liver rescue is it's a way to
safely guide out poisons and toxins in a
way that can be really helpful so
someone can get that liver cleaned up
right but everybody walks around with
these toxic livers and then the brain
gets intoxicated and when the brain gets
intoxicated then we all of a sudden end
up getting blood draws that's a whole
nother thing all on its own julie said
cured hot flashes with liver rescue that
is that is so amazing that's so special
when our brain gets intoxicated with all
the different poisons and toxins
then
we're now in a place where we get we get
triggered do you guys know anybody i
want to ask you guys something do you
guys know anybody that gets triggered
easy
right a little trigger triggered into
anxiety easy
triggered soma says love the liver
rescue book so amazing you know anybody
that gets triggered easy in any way like
emotionally or their anxiety gets
triggered easy or they get you know
triggered in any way
right
mood mood swings and all that liver
gets so stagnant and so sluggish in so
many people
i just saw how can i stop sugar cravings
there's a mystery
mystery hunger section in here
and
so what happens is that when your liver
gets toxic like that okay
when that happens we get triggered easy
because the brain gets saturated so keep
that in mind
the brain gets saturated so everybody's
saying me
right there i see on tik tok everybody's
saying me it happens to me it happens to
me there too on youtube
allison so
we go through this thing where we can
get unstable right we feel unstable we
don't feel strong
like we just don't feel strong
we feel like we can break easy you guys
ever feel that you feel like you could
break easy you feel like you you're not
strong you feel like you're not tough or
something or you're you're sensitive but
you're not you are strong and that's the
whole thing people don't realize just
because if you don't feel strong and you
don't feel confident about your your
health and your health strength
it doesn't mean you're not the strongest
person out there people with chronic
illness and symptoms and conditions are
the strong ones
they're the strong ones but but yet it's
easy to get triggered because you're
bearing so much
and that's what people don't realize
when your liver gets all toxic
and sluggish right
it gets toxic and sluggish
and tired and stagnant
all the toxins go into the brain
and then if you already have
symptoms and conditions you're already
sensitive
you're already struggling so you can be
triggered easier and then you can feel
like you're not a strong person you
could feel like you're not strong and
then people around you're like oh
you know
god there goes your symptoms again and
there goes your problems again i mean
while you're the strongest person
because look what you're bearing
it's hard to have a symptom and
condition and be struggling so when
someone
like you guys and people i know are
struggling with something you need to
know how strong you really are even if
you get triggered easy and feel like
you're weak
you're not weak
because guess what people out there who
seem strong who don't have a symptom and
condition if they were sick they would
fall the heck apart
i can't tell you how many times i've
heard from people like oh my god
my husband got sick for the first time
in his life and he's crying like a baby
every single day meanwhile aw i've been
sick for 20 years
and i've had all kinds of conditions and
symptoms and he's sick with his first
thing he's bawling and he can't handle
it
i mean people with chronic heal i hear
that all the time people with chronic
illness
symptoms and conditions are really the
strong ones
but then but we don't feel strong we
feel weak we feel kicked down we feel
not confident right on telegram you guys
right on tick-tock you feel not
confident
and you feel you feel kind of weakened
but really you're strong but what
happens is you get triggered easy
because the liver is all
dirtied up
it's all filled with toxins
diana says i remember i started becoming
emotional around 25 i used to control my
emotions really well before
yeah
what happens is the liver gets
all clogged up
we get some symptoms
we get triggered easy because the brain
gets filled up with stuff
that's why because the brain gets filled
up with stuff the brain gets filled up
with copper that's a big one right there
copper
so much copper we get into our brain
toxic copper everybody's everybody's in
touch with toxic copper it's everywhere
it's coming out of air fresheners it's
in colognes and perfumes toxic copper is
everywhere it fills up in the liver
right
everybody gets filled up with aluminum
fluoride treatments anybody
fluoride treatments
anybody have a fluoride treatment it
builds up in the liver and builds up in
the liver and the next thing you know it
that fluoride treatment finally hits the
brain and now you're you get triggered
easy emotionally
emotionally then you get blamed in your
relationship if you're in a relationship
if you're not in a relationship you get
blamed by a friend if you're not in a
relationship you get blamed by a family
member but if you're in a relationship
you get blamed by the other person in
the relationship
you're just way too emotional
yeah it's her fault she's the problem
she's the one causing all this
and then you're at counseling you're at
marriage counseling or partner
counseling boyfriend girlfriend
counseling and you're out of counselors
and the counselor is just like now tell
me what's all the problem here
now that the council is like so what's
all the problem here and then the guy's
like she's just too emotional she just
can't keep her crap together every
little thing just gets her upset
everything's going on or or she's like
you know if it's flipped around she's
like he's just angry all the time he's
always angry
he comes home from work he's angry you
can't say anything to him he just wants
to watch what he wants to watch he just
plays on his computer he's angry i can't
get any words out of him he's
he's uh he's cranky he doesn't say good
night at night right like whatever it
is a big part of it
is that liver
i was a lot of a lot of guys out there
with angry livers
a lot of guys with angry livers
right
a lot of women out there with clogged up
livers
and then the brain
gets filled up with everything the liver
is overflowing and i love liver rescue
because i talk about all this stuff it's
like an incredible book i talk about all
this stuff it's on amazon the book right
you can get it free at the library if
you want but it's on amazon too right
it's on sale on amazon right now
furnika says
my husband blames me for being too
sensitive too emotional all the time for
for 10 years 10 of these years and what
happens is that
our livers get clogged up and stagnant
and they get all these things in there
like muck like
viral muck too they get all this viral
muck in there
courtney ma says my husband has an angry
liver
i believe it i believe it
and we get all these pathogens inside
the liver and it builds up and the
pathogens are eating things in the liver
the pathogens are eating copper and
aluminum the pathogens are eating stuff
inside the liver
and then
all that stuff comes barreling out of
the liver and it ends or ends up in the
brain the brain's toxic now now we got
brain fog and now we got short
circuiting and now we're cranky now
we're irritable now we're triggered easy
now we're emotional and that's what
happens
i'm giving you guys the rundown about
those angry livers everybody has
that's it right there everybody's
walking around those angry lives bella
kim says i don't know if it's my toxic
liver
or my bf that's making me emotional
laugh out
well your bf could have a toxic liver
you know another thing too we tend to
always blame ourselves it's always me me
me me me me i'm the problem on the
problem maybe it's everybody
maybe everybody has a little bit of a
problem right maybe we all have a little
bit going on
you know that's true too we all have
something going on but i love
but you know yeah
maybe we all not feeling good
maybe not maybe we're all not feeling
good
that's another thing too if you don't
feel good it's easy to get triggered you
got a lot of toxins in the liver it's
easy to be triggered if you're viral if
you got the pathogens and the
streptococcus it's easy to be triggered
what i love about the golden seal right
now is we're in that time of year when
emotions get
pretty rough right this is it it's the
pressure it's like bottlenecking it's
all the holidays coming on and then boom
thanksgiving then everybody's got to get
the chris you see the christmas lights
come out and then everything else and
then next thing you know it
you know everybody's all stressed out i
mean i hear about it anyway
yeah
so
sarah says ayurveda has been teaching
this for thousands of years
sarah arvetta hasn't been teaching this
for thousands of years and no disrespect
no disrespect i know i know they tell
you that
but they haven't they irvetta didn't
know about pathogens
um shen says ayurveda is man-made
i got
majorly duped by ayurvedic doctors and
so has
thousands of other people and thousands
of the people that came to see me in my
office over the last 30 years
so yeah it's no disrespect i know some
cool air vetted doctors ayurvedic
doctors that are really cool it's just
that ayurvedic medicine didn't know
about pathogens so they didn't know
about
viruses ever they didn't know that
epstein-barr causes fibromyalgia and
epstein-barr feeds off of copper and
causes eczema so for thousands of years
ayurvedic medicine didn't know that
there's no disrespect it's just fact
ayurvedic medicine talked about
talked about other things
but and they didn't talk about the liver
overflowing with poisons and toxins
either saturating the brain and causing
emotional triggers that's not ayurvedic
um
kirsten says ayurveda is a good
philosopher but this is now exactly it's
this times have changed
uh
wylie green says i think wilder green w
green ayurvedic set me back before
finding anthony
i i've heard that over the years
i have so
it's important to know the information
it really is got no disrespect for
ayurvedic medicine air vetted at all no
way but i'm just saying divine light
said something about ayurveda
ayurveda is evil and i know that from
experience because i paid thousands to
study arvetta before finding medical
medium divine light so glad to have you
here
truly
um
the whole thing too is is with ayurveda
some you know
ayurvedic doctor actually i know as a
friend of mine who says i'm gonna go do
a a gee cleanse a geek cleanse i'm like
uh
you can't cleanse with that because your
your gallbladder and your liver are
going to produce bile to try to break it
down and it's like what do you mean it's
like
you're gonna have to produce a ton of
bile to break it down so your liver
won't cleanse because it's in production
of bile it's like what ayurveda doesn't
know that i'm like here vetted doesn't
know a lot of things you know i was
trying to be nice
but anyway
but look whatever whatever makes people
happy too you know i'm not sitting here
to disrespect you guys
all of a sudden i see the ghee thing
keeping wait he's trouble he's trouble
yeah he's trouble
it is it's not a good thing stops you
from cleansing it's really hard on the
liver he's hard on the liver it's really
hard on the liver
and it's still
dairy
it's still dairy but it's really hard on
the liver too
lorraine says well i laugh out loud i
can imagine people joining
the live and thinking why is there a
hand on the blender
you are so much fun anthony love these
lives
i this is
gonna put it in the blender and
uh like one of those scary shows
no we're not gonna do that it's the
blood draw so you guys
let's still get into this we still got
some more i still got more to do let's
talk about methylation you guys want to
know something about methylation
methylation is in liver book let's cover
that a little bit
this is funny you know this is really
this is a fun day
anybody new here that's coming on i just
hope you're okay because dr nesbit just
came out of surgery right now
and dr nesbitt's here
by the way if you don't know dr nesbitt
he's a board-certified surgeon
he's a board-certified psychiatrist dr
nesbitt is a board-certified
he says he doesn't like ayurvedic
medicine or betta but then he says he
does like he he says he says he does
like it a little bit he says that he ate
a whole bunch of ghee
for dinner and he threw up
and he said that he felt better after he
vomited the ghee up
dr nesbitt the one thing about doctor
nesbi you need to know that he does
drink
then he drinks when he's performing
surgeries
dr nesbitt just performed a spleenectomy
and he said that he only had two shots
of whiskey before he performed the
splenectomy
he had a martini and two shots of
whiskey and he says he he wants to give
advice since he's a board-certified
surgeon psychiatrist he says don't mix
martinis and whiskey together he says it
was a bad concoction
i won't tell him that part what
i'm not going to tell them what else she
did no because somebody might need
surgery
one day and they might end up because
their health plan sticks them in your
way and you
all right i think i'm going to have to
put dr nesbitt back dr nesbitt likes
liver rescue though so i'm just gonna i
don't know if that's helping right
helping me right now dr nesbitt if you
like liver rescue i got it dr nesman has
to go back into surgery april 10. dr
nesbit came out
um
okay mthfr gene mutation
okay lose some of you guys
you know what it is
humor having a sense of humor
having some joy in the heart being able
to laugh a little it's really important
really important and that's not
that information that's in humankind for
centuries and centuries and centuries
that that's that's in human nature
that's human design laugh a little you
got to find some humor it really matters
so let's go into here we're in
methylation right now
methylation is an important topic
because what you'll find is you'll be
tricked into the methylation problem
right
you'll be told you have this gene
mutation
or mthfr gene mutation so that's the
whole thing with with what's happening
so you got an mthfr gene mutation that's
what the blood test shows but there's a
couple important things to understand
they don't actually see a gene mutation
very important to know
okay
a gene mutation
cannot be fixed if you have a mutated
gene
it can't be fixed
so if you have a mutated gene
it's not fixable it's your genes
right
and that's where i scratch my head
because thousands of people have done
medical medium information
and then
go to their doctors
and then their doctor says we don't know
why
but we think we misdiagnosed you because
you don't have a gene mutation anymore
because it's not showing up that you
have the mthfrg mutation
and so the patient is like well that
doesn't make any sense
if i have this gene mutation the doctor
says i don't know why that happens
either
it doesn't make any sense either so we
think we diagnosed you so that means
that your gene mutation test must have
been
it must have been
you know a pro must have been
false or fake or you know not right so
what happens is that
mth
mthfr gene mutations can always be fixed
once you clean up the liver
and know how to heal
you can get rid of the mthfr gene
mutation
okay because it's not genetic that's
really important to know so
what i'll give you a rundown too on the
gene mutation test the gene mutation
test is an inflammatory marker test
they should have never named it a gene
mutation test
they should have named it
an inflammatory marker test because just
like the antinuclear antigen test a a
just like the c-reactive protein test
the mthfr gene mutation test is the same
thing
it's just an inflammation test it's not
an actual gene mutation they don't see a
gene mutation under the microscope
they see elevated inflammation
it's a theory that you have a g mutation
so the mthfr gene mutation theory
is a theory
stating
that
you have a gene mutation when really you
just have elevated inflammation
and they're using an inflammation test
that they're calling
a gene mutation
test and that's what why it's all
screwed up
it's rigged
it's just an inflammation test that's
why you can reverse it
you can't reverse
an actual gene
that's the way it is your gene
stays the way it is if that's your gene
it can't be
changed it can't be reversed
okay
you can't
sit there like if you don't like your
nose
if you don't like your nose
you can't
change that
unless you go unless you do cosmetic
surgery but you can't change your nose
okay
if you have
a mutated gene
then you can't change the gene you can't
change yourself genetically
it doesn't happen gene mutation test is
a theory they call it a gene mutation
test when it's really an inflammatory
marker just like c-reactive protein or a
a anti-nuclear antigen test
that's why when people do medical medium
they get rid of their mthfr g mutation
they get rid of it too many thousands
and tens of thousands millions of liver
rescues
sold around the world
in almost every country in the on the
planet just so you know
doctors steal liver rescue information
and then run ads on all the social media
channels selling their products taking
out the information in here and using it
for themselves without citing it
this is one of the most popular books in
the world
it's saved countless lives
and an overburdened sluggish liver with
a low gra low-grade infection like
epstein-barr or shingles
a sluggish stagnant liver with a
low-grade infection like epstein-barr
shingles
okay
is the real cause
of inflammation markers ringing off both
a a c-reactive protein mthfr gene
mutation and neurological and
neurological line
and neurological line
really important enough
so
so it's critical to understand so when
you go to your doctor do what your
doctor says okay i'm just telling you
you can bring this information to your
doctor you go to your doctor and he
tells you you have a gene mutation
really you don't he just did an
inflammation test now you think your
genes are screwed up so now you think
you just have bad genes now you think
your son's jeans are messed up you think
your daughter's jeans are messed up you
think your family's got some gene
problem and you were just duped you were
just duped the wolves pulled over your
eyes you were tricked
is what happened tammy says tammy winter
says great information
wow great
so what happens is you guys the reason
why
countless people around the planet got
rid of their gene mutation
just like somebody already commented
right they got rid of their gene
mutation
because
they didn't have a gene mutation
they had a dirty liver with a low-grade
viral infection and they cleaned it up
using medical medium information and
tools and they went back to their doctor
and suddenly their gene mutation was
gone
all of our genes haven't gone bad in
just the last 20 years
15 20 years
for some reason medical research and
science believes that all of her genes
just went bad
and teaching doctors that
all of her genes went bad
chronic illness is exploding like never
before all around the planet all around
the world exploding everywhere
and her genes didn't go bad in two years
and five years
all over jeans just didn't go bad
okay so what they do is they tell you
you have gene problems to take your eyes
off the ball so it's like take your eyes
off the ball don't know that it's your
liver just say it's a gene problem don't
know that your brain is filled with all
this crap no it's a gene problem they
don't tell you how to fix it no because
nobody knows they don't tell you any of
that because the system's not built to
care
about anybody they're built to break it
down the system's set up to break down
and destroy and hurt and harm people
that's what it is it's just that's
reality
that's just reality
yeah
me too 787 good to see you usually you
leave comments on on youtube right
yeah it's exactly what you just said is
spot on
so anyway you guys so we talked about
live rescue for a little bit i made some
pasta i already ate some so i ate a
whole bunch before i came on here
but i made some pasta on the amazon live
make sure you subscribe to the amazon
live because that's where i'm cooking
that's where i'm cooking and doing the
cooking tips and everything and showing
you things that i like and all that the
link is in the description make sure you
uh subscribe for that give me a thumbs
up if you like the video by the way you
guys on youtube okay
and the link is in the description on
tick tock on tick tock the link is in
the bio
you guys on youtube link is in the
description facebook link is in the
description right
okay dr fine md autoimmune theory and
gene theory is a mass duping of the
populous
we've cracked the human genome for years
now
what has that brought on
what has that brought on other than
money for a new industry it's so true
etc they haven't fixed anybody because
of that
they've been playing with genes for
decades and decades now right for 50 60
70 years they've been playing they
started playing with jeans right around
world war ii
right before in the 30s in the late 30s
they started playing with jeans
and they
nothing came from it besides billions
and trillions of dollars going up
throughout the decades trillions of
dollars throughout the decades getting
funneled into it
and
they still don't have one answer to why
you have a heart palpitation
that's unexplainable they don't have an
answer to why anything lizzie liu says
i've had the same experience with mthfr
i didn't have it before and then got
sick and now testing positive for due to
two different types of ftmtf that's
mthfr gene mutation i got to tell you
one thing about that this is really
interesting
and
so here's how it goes you don't have a
gene mutation before
you get sick and then they diagnose you
with two varieties of mthfrg mutation
two varieties of mthfrg mutation
that's unbelievable and
it's it's so fraudulent i mean listen to
your doctor do your doctor tells you but
it's so fraudulent how the system is
when you think about it
you don't have a gene mutation in the
past but now all of a sudden you've got
one when you get sick
really it's because it was just an
inflammation marker detecting
inflammation not a gene mutation
and that inflammation
has a lot to do with the liver i'm going
to ig so i'm heading off to instagram in
a couple of minutes
and i'm going to turn tick tock back on
and i'm going to read some more
liver rescue everything else you guys
check out liverescue when you can
okay amazon.com it's on sale which is
really awesome it's a great gift for
people too during the holidays just
letting you know the liver is like
that's that's something you got to know
about like
if you want to be somebody that knows
something about health you have to learn
about the liver a little bit at least
enough to learn about the liver
i mean there's so-called health hacks
and experts out there i don't know
anything about the liver and the pieces
they chime away came from this book
right here so it's so crazy
how it works dr sherry green good to see
you
fatty liver is explained in liver rescue
dr sherry green you're awesome you guys
i love you
and i'm going to ig i'll see you soon