stovetop mac and cheese right here at
brain saver protocol so I'm excited
about that I'm gonna make some pasta
pasta
my oxygen levels just hang on I got an
oxygen meter on my finger let's hold on
here let me just read it
yeah
99 good 100 okay no fraction's okay all
right just hold on though here I gotta
make sure I check my heart rate I just
don't want to start this live yet
hold on just want to know what my heart
rate is per minute I'm sorry about this
you guys won Mississippi to Mississippi
three Mississippi four Mississippi
778 and said I think I'm right
okay about 70 all right
all right hold on though uh um I gotta
check my option on the other hand just
just bear with me this isn't a disorder
no way it's not a disorder
um hold on
okay option level good right there gotta
check one more time just hold on right
here I want to check my
heart rate per minute just bear with me
one Mississippi two Mississippi three
Mississippi four Mississippi five
Mississippi six Mississippi seven
Mississippi eight Mississippi nine
Mississippi
all right heart rate's okay gotta check
my blood sugar I got a monitor on my arm
right now check my blood sugar I gotta
make sure that's right every hour I'm
checking my blood sugar too yeah all
right just let me take a look at it's
private though it means I have to take
off all my clothes I have it underneath
here just give me two seconds here let
me see what's your girl looking okay
looking okay must be doing something
right there all right
you guys we're talking about blood sugar
hypoglycemia hyperglycemia to my insulin
resistance Let's uh what else can we
talk about all about that blood sugar
then we're just gonna say it straight
off the bat right now in order to have a
blood sugar issue whatsoever like a
blood sugar issue outside of the fact
that someone isn't eating say
a blood sugar issue you have to have
three things one out of three things
wrong you could have all three things
wrong you could have your liver be a
problem your pancreas could be a problem
or your adrenals be a problem you can
have adrenals and pancreas and your
liver is fine you can have pancreas in
your liver your adrenals are fine you
can have liver adrenals and pancreas
having a problem all three of them but
these are the three things right there
that determine if you're going to be
having a blood sugar problem so that one
day one day down the road
after eating a little too much of this
or one day down the road after eating a
little too much of this right here
right or one day down the road having a
excuse me I'm gonna take an ice cream
break if you guys don't mind I got an
ice cream right here whoa let me
see sorry sorry sorry I gotta check my
oxygen levels one more time
okay oxygen at 100 feeling good about
that because on hold on uh one
Mississippi she must be doing this
before
okay I'm just trying to figure out my
heart per per minute I don't think I
have this one down yet but I will
the point I'm trying to say right here
what we're talking about we're talking
about blood sugar we're talking about
new trends that happen all the time A
lot of people are checking their blood
sugar every hour they're monitoring
their blood sugar and then they think
they got it down with what they're
eating they're eating healthier they're
eating whether it's plant-based or
they're keto or a healthy what's
so-called healthy animal protein based
diet they think they got it all in check
I'm not talking about diabetics okay I'm
not talking about type 1 diabetes I'm
not talking about
um type 2 diabetes I'm not talking about
all the different types of medical
medium coined a long time ago in the
terms of how many types there really are
I'm not going into that I'm going into
like every day whether you're in Fitness
every day whether you're concerned about
your blood sugar
I'm talking about that aspect of it
right now people think that they're in
control of their health because they're
looking at their their blood sugar
they're monitoring their blood sugar and
they think they have total control over
their health and then as they're eating
and doing things and taking care of
themselves but what can happen is it can
create an eating disorder it can create
OCD it can actually add to somebody's
OCD it can become overwhelming it can
create anxiety it can be something that
it's more important than what you're
doing in that moment is more important
than what's happening in that moment or
that day it can confuse people a whole
bunch of things that are happening with
that so I want to go into blood sugar
issues also monitoring blood sugar and
so forth so let's go let's roll into it
a little bit
first and foremost
somebody
living their life
perfectly fine
they don't have a problem
and then suddenly their A1C is rising
they're at the doctor's office
they get some blood work
their A1C is up
and something's wrong and they're like
what's wrong right
and what people don't realize is that
it's a process over the years of three
things breaking down the liver is the
most popular one the most important one
as far as with blood sugar to start with
because the liver starts to get stagnant
and sluggish and when it gets stagnant
and sluggish and starts to break down it
puts a burden on so many different
levels on the body so the liver starts
breaking down
the ability to break down fats to
disperse it with bile reserves that
starts to break down and wear down
so fats stay in the bloodstream even
longer they stay in the liver even
longer and that gets people in trouble
so
I want to bring this guy in here we're
making uh
stovetop macaroni and cheese
and a little bit hang around for that
because I would love to make that for
you guys
macaroni and cheese
all right
so people get stagnant sluggish livers
they do
most people who get the stagnosticish
livers are getting it because they're on
the high fat diets their whole life
because everybody is eating a certain
amount of fat every single day whether
it's for breakfast lunch or dinner if
you're intermittent fasting you're still
going to eat fat at the end of the day
you're going to have it either six
o'clock eight o'clock at night nine
o'clock at night four o'clock in the
afternoon but you're going to end up
eating fat at some point even when
you're intermittent fasting
but the fats over time burden and break
down the liver
and when it burns and breaks down the
liver we end up getting blood sugar
problems
that's why type 2 diabetes when people
start eating better and better
suddenly they either need less insulin
or the numbers appear better their A1C
is better
because their liver is not burdened down
by Fats as much anymore so people be
like well I don't do fast food anymore I
don't do restaurant food anymore I don't
do junk food you know greasy food fried
food I'm doing lean animal protein I'm
eating more salads
I'm eating healthier and my A1C is
dropping
because their insulin resistance is
reducing
because what they were doing before
though over the years LED them to a
stagnant sluggish liver
eventually putting a burden on their
pancreas
eventually creating a problem where it
even weakened their adrenals and then
their A1C started to climb
so that's one way we get problems with
blood sugar issues another is
if pathogens get into the liver
and someone has the Epstein-Barr virus
the Epstein-Barr virus has been in the
liver for a long time
it's causing wear and tear it's
producing a tremendous amount of
byproduct
that byproduct builds up in the liver it
starts to get dysfunctional coupled with
the high fat diet along the way
and then the liver starts to break down
and get sluggish and stagnant any kind
of viruses the liver is like the virus
home hhv six hhv7 said a regular virus
shingles virus herpes simplex 1 Herpes
Simplex 2 all the different Epstein-Barr
viruses plus bacteria too all Harbor and
hide inside people's livers and over
time
if we're not taking care of our liver
and we're eating all these high fat
dishes and high fat meals and all these
Foods we're not supposed to be eating
every every single day we're burdening
the liver plus we're feeding most likely
what the choices we're making we're
feeding the bugs that reside inside the
liver and then that grows oh more and
more creating a a breakdown of the liver
stagnant sluggish fatty liver usually
too all around and then the blood sugar
becomes unstable and people have
problems and sure people can be like
well I can go and start exercising I
could get my life back if you're not
chronically ill and you can exercise I'm
gonna go and watch my diet I'm going to
watch my calories I'm going to eat
better maybe I'll do maybe I'll do a
little intermittent fasting maybe I'll
eat a healthier diet maybe I'll eat more
salads whatever it is if they start
noticing improvements their blood sugar
comes down a little bit and they start
to kind of recoup and they seem to get
their bearings seem to get ahead of it
but in the end it's not fixing the
problem completely and they end up
eating way too much fat no one fixes
what's wrong as far as the viral issues
that happen inside the liver and inside
the body the breakdown of the the liver
when it's actually infested with
um pathogens and people don't get ahead
of that so over time people just get
sick and one thing that I think people
have to understand that no matter what
everybody is going to be sick with
something no matter what you can see the
best trainer on social you can see the
um healthiest weight lifters
bodybuilders on social they're still
going to be sick with something
eventually it doesn't make anybody
indestructible nobody's indestructible
people get sick no matter what and in
the end they're gonna get sick if they
get sick later on in life they get sick
later on in life if they get sick in
their 60s they get sick in their 60s
they get sick in their 70s whichever it
is it hits them one way or another
so it's important to know really what's
going inside in the body so you can
avoid as many pitfalls as possible and
get yourself to a place where you can at
least avoid some of the worst conditions
or some of the most Troublesome or
mysterious conditions as you're living
your life but either way when people say
oh I'm gonna live forever well we can't
live forever we can't live for hundreds
and hundreds of years
it's just not going to happen we're not
going to live to be 500 years old we're
not going to be lived to be 600 years
old it's not going to happen so with
that in mind we have to protect
ourselves as good as we can and notice
that people see young people and they
think whoa I'm going to listen to that
young person because that young person
has it all down that 25 year old who's
you know doing the bodybuilding
who's eating all the right things it
seems that's where I want to be that's
who I want to be and don't realize that
that's a far cry from chronic illness
it's a far cry from mysterious chronic
illness because you can get mysterious
chronic illness at 19 years old 15 years
old 10 years old 25 years old in
whatever age and there's a big confusion
to someone who actually is an athlete or
someone who is young and strong
to somebody who's chronically sick and
actually has problems with their health
that's mysterious like an autoimmune
condition that they still don't
understand or anything about what they
about that autoimmune condition do they
understand blood sugar is kind of this
thing where it's a little bit taking
over because you got all these people in
the world right now that don't know why
they're struggling they don't know why
they have anxiety they don't know why
they have depression or eczema and
psoriasis they don't know why they have
chronic fatigue syndrome and autoimmune
diagnosis lupus they don't know why they
have tingles and numbness and aches and
pains and back pain body pain head pain
they don't know why they have blurry
eyes
and they don't know why they have
burning skin and Tinkles and numbness
like I said before in Vertigo and
dizziness and there's this group of
people
that doesn't know why so when they
search around on social and they look
around the internet they run across home
maybe your blood sugar is it your blood
sugars your blood sugar is your blood
maybe it's that and then it feels like
you can gain some kind of control
monitoring your blood sugar not even if
you're not a diabetic so then it's easy
to fall into let me see my blood sugar
and let me see what I'm eating and let
me see what my blood sugar is doing but
really that's a trap
because it takes us away from really
what's wrong
the real things that are wrong and the
real problems people have and why
they're sick it pulls us away from that
so we miss the ball we don't have our
eyes on the right ball instead we end up
falling into traps where we're checking
our oxygen levels every hour we're
checking our heart rate we're checking
our blood sugar every hour or two hours
and then it becomes this Obsession where
our whole life is about our blood sugar
and we're watching it and we're
monitoring it and we're looking at our
monitors and it's a different there's a
big difference when you're a type 1
diabetic or type 2 diabetic right and
you want to keep an eye on it people
shouldn't otherwise people shouldn't
live their life worried about it
athletes shouldn't live their life
worrying about it just people who aren't
athletic shouldn't worry about living
their life worrying about it and in
general in people who are chronically
sick shouldn't worry about it either
there's more important things to worry
about
um Melissa on IG says I haven't had any
blood sugar issues since starting
medical medium foods and that takes me
to the next place is medical medium
information
medical medium Protocols are already
blood sugar supporting
they always were like medical medium
Protocols are never like intermittent
fast on coffee all day long make sure
you stay on coffee you know make sure
you're
you know just drinking your coffee every
single morning and throughout the
afternoon intermittent fast
and that's it until you eat sometime at
some later point of the day there's ways
to do it where you're not eating
a whole bunch of intense heavy food in
the morning
where you can actually keep that away
and you can still take care of yourself
which leads to fats I want to talk about
fats if you guys are open to that it
plays a an enormous part of the blood
sugar roll is how much fat intake we
have how many fats we're consuming that
plays a massive role into in blood sugar
stability so I want to go into that a
little bit too so I'm just going to move
this guy over if you guys are okay
and here's the other thing too
intermittent fasting leads to blood
sugar crashing that's something to
understand all on its own
foreign
so what you see in front of me right
here are adrenals
and kidneys but you're looking at these
adrenal glands right on top of the
kidneys
now adrenal glands are a critical part
of how we keep blood sugar stable so
when you're doing medical medium
information
you're restoring adrenal glands
that includes if you're doing any of the
medical medium cleanses if you're doing
the 369 if you're doing the 369 Advance
if you're doing the monocleens heavy
metal detox whichever it is it's
supporting of the adrenals it's why
people are here it's a big part of why
people heal and get stronger when
they're doing medical medium protocols
such as the medical medium cleanses the
28 day cleanse is supportive of the
adrenals and there's something that I
hear out there every now and then it's
like I'm cleansing too hard
it it's going to be hard on my adrenals
I'm cleansing too hard it's too tough on
my adrenals that's not true
unless you're doing something that's not
a medical medium cleanse maybe you're
doing some other cleanse out there and
then I can't speak for that I can't say
well I don't know if that's hard on your
journals I do know that just
intermittent fasting alone is hard on
the adrenals and this isn't an
intermittent fasting show but I'm saying
that because a lot of people are doing
it and they're burning out their
adrenals while they're doing it and
that's really important to know so when
you're doing like a medical medium 369
or a mono cleanser heavy metal detox
cleanser a 28 day cleanse
a medical Medium you're supporting your
adrenals even while you're cleansing
even why poisons and toxins are leaving
the body it's still supporting your
adrenals not only supporting them
restoring them and bringing them back
but I think what happens there are other
cleanses out there in the world in the
industry Health industry that do hurt
the adrenals and there are other cleanse
cleanses out there and people do them
that actually say oh my adrenals my
adrenaline it's from too much cleansing
but that's not MediCal medium
information or medical medium cleanses
that's a critical piece of information
to understand
now in order to protect the adrenals you
have to have enough mineral salts enough
Trace mineral salts
so that's critical what you'll find on
medical medium cleanses is you'll find
this right here
which is really important to see and you
guys know what this is right here this
is the celery juice
celery juice
is one of the most supportive for the
adrenal glands because of the trace
mineral salts
critical for adrenals
so somebody else's cleansed out there is
not going to have celery juice in it I
don't know what it's going to have in
there maybe it's going to have some
weird Paris parasitical blending send
down and mix with water maybe it's going
to have something else maybe they're
going to say you can still do your
coffee maybe they're going to say you
can still do cacao nibs and your you
know your cacao maybe it's going to be
any of that maybe it's they're going to
say you can still do your apple cider
vinegar
and they're going to tell you that's
fine hey do your apple cider vinegar
some cacao nibs right there
some cocoa powder right there
some apple cider vinegar right here
all of those are destructive to the
adrenal glands
highly
injurious to adrenal glands over time
why am I saying this
what does it matter because people are
worried about blood sugar well if you're
really worried about blood sugar then
you might want to know what affects your
blood sugar when adrenal glands weaken
and start to break down when they start
to go downhill your adrenals your blood
sugar gets crazy unstable it just starts
to go wacko important to know and so
people with their high on their caffeine
are high on their drugs right all these
different things they're high on
stimulants they're high on their coffee
all the time
they're high in their chocolate ice
cream let's see if I have chocolate in
here today I got chocolate ice cream
they're high in their chocolate ice
cream and their adrenals are taking a
hit boom boom boom boom they're taking a
hit every time you're having that cacao
every time you're having that chocolate
every time you're having your chocolate
this is chocolate coconut ice cream that
should be fine I'm just gonna have some
chocolate coconut ice cream with almond
milk in it totally different aw you
don't know what you're talking about
that one's safe and really good both
people don't realize it's still gonna
Hammer your adrenals and break them down
over time very important enough
so everybody's being trained to be on
stimulants all the time
it's like I'm on stimulants I'm on a
high I'm trying to chase a high
caffeine and stimulants
add it to a high fat diet
both of that is really hard because a
high fat diet is stimulating all on its
own so here's what happens when you go
and you eat something like this
when you eat a nice greasy cheeseburger
tastes so good bite into it so yummy
you're biting into that flesh with that
cheese
and it's greasy and delicious and juicy
you get an adrenal High
that's when it hits
when you get your pizza
and it could be a vegan pizza vegan
pizza can be really high in fat totally
jacked up with fat
and when you get all that fat in your
system your adrenals have to thin out
your blood so your adrenals are pumping
to thin out the blood and that's hard on
the adrenals too
so what you'll find is that when you're
doing like a medical medium cleanse and
369 Advanced or the 28 day cleanse
you see that the fats aren't there for a
reason to finally restore your adrenal
glands
but giving you enough calories glucose
to help keep you going to keep your
brain going to make you strong keeping
the fats out so you can cleanse poisons
and toxins
without getting sicker
and that's really important right there
on it so let's go into that a bit
when people are eating too much high fat
your pancreas takes a hip with that
constantly
so not only does your liver take a hit
but your pancreas takes a hit
so a lot of people are on high fat diets
and it's hitting their pancreas hard
it's hitting their adrenals hard because
their adrenals are releasing all this
adrenaline to thin out the blood
because you need that adrenaline to move
that fat around and help disperse it
and then the liver's got to release all
this bile
and that takes us to like another level
what happens is that
everybody's on the high fat diets
the liver's doing double time their
adrenals are doing double time they're
pancreas is doing double time
all three
and then something's got to give
the A1c
blood sugar instability
hypoglycemia when it's uncalled for
hyperglycemia when it's uncalled for
blood sugar instability up and down
goes down real fast
goes up real fast
isn't stabilized well you know I saw
this new practitioner and they said you
better eat some nuts with your cheese
I saw this other new doctor and this
other new doctor said I better eat like
some salmon with berries
I saw this other practitioner
and that practitioner told me that I
should have an apple with peanut butter
on it
it helped to keep the blood sugar stable
another practitioners said I should have
some tofu
with some vegetables and that'll keep
the blood sugar going it's like all this
stuff you hear out there and there's a
lot of confusion to food combining with
blood sugar
and that's where we run into a mess
because if someone sells somebody the
idea that you can monitor your blood
sugar
and food combined around it and watch it
and as as if that is going to be a
control for you
then
that's trouble trouble in Paradise all
on its own so I want to cut into that a
little bit
my husband's doctor just told him
he's headed for diabetes now he is
listening to me about eating better and
applying some medical medium tools
incredible congratulations to him I'm
proud of him
and I'm proud of you too see guys I'm
just boiling a little water right here
because I'm going to be cooking pasta in
a little bit I'm going to make make some
stovetop macaroni and cheese which
sounds like not a good thing to eat at
all sounds bad
stovetop macaroni and cheese
Elevate evolve says I'm not perfect with
this information yet but I keep trying
and don't give up I'm continuing to make
progress even though I still struggle
with food addiction I cannot express how
grateful I am proud of you thank you for
being here
one of the three things starts to go
bonkers
whether it's the adrenal glands the
liver or the pancreas
you might be somebody where it's too
adrenal glands and liver another person
it's pancreas and liver another person
it's adrenal glands and pancreas another
person it's just the adrenal glands but
when they start to go south blood sugar
becomes unstable it drops too fast
you get the shakes
it goes up too fast
you get the dizziness
it goes down too fast you get both it
goes all over the place and you go to
this doctor and this doctor and this
doctor see you're not diabetic you're
not a diabetic but
what I recommend is we monitor your
blood sugar all the time and you make
sure that you're doing your cheese
sticks
with some peanut butter an apple
we got to make sure that you're doing
just the right Blends or you're eating
one thing here and then one thing here
and a half an hour later one thing here
one thing here it's a guessing game and
that's the confusion but here's what's
amazing about it all
what you're going to see now and where
we're heading to in Alternative Health
and Wellness is you're going to see
science
you're going to see
like check this out
here's how many people did this here's
how many people tried that and it worked
here's how many people did this there
was a study that says this and you're
going to see a lot of that and it's
gonna you're gonna buy into it and in
the end you're just going to be playing
the same old guessing game with your
health and chronic illness
and all that's fine is if you're a
healthy person everything seems okay
and you're doing your exercising you're
working out you're a trainer you're an
athlete or you're somebody that just
works out you eat good
and you can just play with that you can
play in that land where wow all these
people good results at blood sugar if
they try this let's do this monitor here
let's try and all that's great but when
you're chronically sick you're really
sick and you've spent a lot of time on
mattress island or in bed which is
mattress island or couch Island it's an
entirely different story it's back to
the same old drawing board
Lindsay on IG says I used to wear a
glucose monitor and had crazy lows and
highs of blood sugar and now it's all
normalized and no need to wear a monitor
thanks to Medical medium lifestyle which
takes me to the next point
mm info allows people
to not have to go into eating disorder
land
blood sugar monitoring eating disorder
OCD obsessive compulsive Behavior land
[Music]
it can help protect people and protect
them from falling prey into going
backwards I noticed something right now
in the health movement
is people can come out with a convincing
approach suck a whole people a bunch of
people in through advertisements and ads
and money suck them down a funnel
get them sold on something and now
they're checking the blood sugar every
half a freaking hour
and you can lose your mind doing it
you can lose your mind you get sold that
it's control
you're going to be achieving for
yourself you're going to be sold that it
means that you're in self-control now
you are in control of your destiny of
your life of your health you just wear
that blood sugar monitor sign into this
program make sure you look at all the
stats and Things fill out all the stuff
they want you to fill out pay a little
1999 or 39.99 here uh-huh
and in the end
you're chasing a unicorn
is what you're doing
and me I'd rather chase a unicorn
than Chase an apparition
of a unicorn
and then find myself in the end just
stuck back into the same old hell they
don't know why I'm sick they don't know
why I'm fatigued they don't know why I
have eczema or psoriasis they don't know
why I'm dizzy blurry eyes aches and
pains my legs feel like sandbags my arms
feel like sandbags I got tingles and
numbness I got vertigo tinnitus all
kinds of popping sounds in my ears
infections lung infections I don't feel
good I catch the flu or the sea every
single month
and most of my time is spent
on the couch or in bed and I got sucked
into a whole nother scam and
that's what happens to people every day
so Michelle says people didn't know how
to get enough calories without fat they
did not
mean info put that out there to get
calories enough without all of the fats
yeah so people don't know how to get
enough calories it's true
and if you know medical meme information
you can learn that you can get enough
calories and do it right
so you can sustain yourself and protect
your adrenals but going back to this
very important point one thing I hear
every now and then that was kind of
chanted into the medical medium
community
was I'm detoxing too fast it's hard on
my adrenals
no
it's not
unless you're doing something
that isn't
what you should be or could be doing
unless you're doing something that isn't
what you're supposed to be doing
very important to know
it's like it's like literally a zombie
bite
a zombie bite I'm detoxing too much it
must be hard on my adrenals no
nothing is hard on the adrenals
unless you're doing something to be hard
on your adrenals
that's all
that's all what's hard on your adrenals
caffeine are you doing chocolate just
want to know do I have to do fly on the
wall again
and usually people are feeling real
symptoms and it's not detox it's real
symptoms
I'm sure some people do feel the malaise
of an intense detox if they were really
toxic and really sick to begin with but
even then it's not what people think
meanwhile so many people are going
through fat withdrawal MSC MSG
withdrawal chocolate withdrawal how much
chocolate are you on how much coffee are
you on
how much MSG are you on or you want
nutritional yeast because that stuff
makes you high do you know why people
need to pound that stuff
like they need to pound it like I know
people where it's not a teaspoon of
nutritional yeast
it's
a court of it like they have to pound it
in the recipes it tastes like cheese
it's so good it's it's like the Brewer
Yeast was it's just yummy the
nutritional yeast of Brewer Yeast
because of that MSG we get high on it
and boom our neurons are going off and
firing off
and people are so used to being high all
day when you come off of it you feel
you really feel it
you aren't High Enough
then you come off
and you feel it you go through a
withdrawal if you were up here all the
time
so
we're talking about blood sugar if you
guys just got here we're gonna make a
stovetop macaroni and cheese we're gonna
do that in a few minutes just covering
some blood sugar information let's go
into vinegar and apple cider vinegar so
people believe
in the health field that apple cider
vinegar stabilizes blood sugar
and
no it doesn't but what
vinegar does apple cider vinegar does
is it destroys the bones
it destroys the teeth
it ruins teeth
you do 10 years of apple cider vinegar
eventually your teeth will dissolve from
the inside out
from the inside out
I don't know how or in what way or
I don't know if it takes an angel
coming out of the sky
I don't know if it takes
a gigantic squid coming out of the ocean
I don't know and devours a ship I don't
know what it's going to take for people
to stop their vinegar or to learn what
their vinegar does to them I'm doing
medical medium and it's hurting me
I'm doing medical medium and I it ruined
my health I did medical medium
no what you did was vinegar
you couldn't stay away from it it was
impossible it was in every single
condiment in your refrigerator
it was your apple cider vinegar shots
you did lots of chocolate don't say you
didn't do lots of chocolate you ate in
restaurants which was loaded with canola
oil and vinegar and MSG
you did your popcorn
you did your high fats because you were
only low fat or no fat for two weeks or
three weeks in your life if at best if
at best
and with all that probably ups and downs
and challenges and deficiencies you had
long before medical medium information
came your way
severe severe deficiencies in your life
see eganza says your books are amazing
cleared my acne I've had since 13 years
old I'm 34
now happy to implement
mm protocols
which leads me to this topic I wanted to
say
people can heal
they actually can
it really can
and I don't judge people I don't judge
them for what their
intercepted by
what's happening in health and wellness
is not like it was six years ago four
years ago eight years ago 15 years ago
it is a smorgasbord of
I'm not saying it because I'm like Mr
Big Man the medical medium's the best
I'm the best
has nothing to do with it
this information comes from above
is where it comes from I'm just a
messenger but it's important for people
to know
that yeah
the environment has changed people get
lost easy out there and they're trying
so many different things it took all
these years
with the fight I had to fight to try to
get alcohol out of herbal tinctures did
you guys know this
there's more glycerin tinctures out
there in the world now without alcohol
because of medical movement from the
fight
the fight
even people I won't mention their name
popular so-called popular in the genre
of health and healing
different doctors and stuff like that
pounded people to death with alcoholic
tinctures
just grain alcohol pounded them to death
with corn grain alcohol
it took years to get alcohol out of
supplements and it's still in there and
it's still out there but but it's less
than it ever was
but then social happens and
the amount of advertisements and
products that have junk and garbage in
them food products that have junk and
garbage in them it's just no way to keep
things clean out there and I don't judge
people if they turn around and they
leave medical medium for five seconds
they take their attention off and now
they hear some dude say no you actually
cacao powder is really good for you
it's helpful it's helpful for your
adrenals it's helpful for your heart
it's got antioxidants in it it's so easy
to be brain
so easy and then you're like whoa I love
chocolate I'm gonna be on chocolate
you should do apple cider vinegar
because apple cider vinegar is the real
thing and make sure you do it with
Mother you shouldn't do the other
vinegars but wait a minute medical
medium once told me and I'm forgetting
right now somehow I'm forgetting
something's taking over my brain
I thought medical meme says that apple
cider vinegar actually dissolves your
teeth and can actually damage your liver
and actually hurt your health in your
connective tissue wait I'm forgetting it
for some reason I'm forgetting it there
it goes I forgot I don't even remember
medical medium apple cider vinegar is
that good I'm going to take some shots
of it now maybe it'll help my blood
sugar
it's easy to get derailed by the amount
the amount of propaganda that's out
there both in the vegan land and the
animal protein land all of it I see
people putting liver in their smoothies
animal live I don't I have nothing
against people eating eating animal
products medical medium information is
about you can eat animal products and
learn the information and heal and still
do it on animal products you can do it
on plant-based you can do it vegetarian
you just have to learn the information
so you can heal people are putting some
of the most toxic stuff I've ever seen
ever in their smoothies they're putting
actual beef liver which is the toxic
waste the toxic dump they're putting in
there
these are the things that are going on
out there and I'm not even scratching
the surface
Shamrocks and sunflowers says actually a
medical medium is the best
it's the only thing that is healing My
IC and I tried everything
it's incredible
Alene says when I heard your podcast
about swelling that's that's a really
great episode it was an Enlightenment
for me I have
um lipedema
lymphedema I ordered your liver cleanse
and other cleanse book excited to start
because it's so hard I'm really proud of
you it's a great great way to start
great place to start
really important
so I'm gonna pop some some macaroni in
here
I'm just going to add a little bit more
water to this first real quick
guys I'm making the macaroni and cheese
have that boiling for a while so I'm
going to add a little bit more water
[Music]
it's really hard watching people
become slaves
slaves
the blood sugar scam
that's happening out there in the world
I know we want control and we want to
feel like
we have full control over our health and
wellness
but
every prediction
if that's what you want to call it
that I put out there
comes through over the years comes truth
one way or another
every
time I say something like carnivore
people are going to be on honey
and apples
they end up on honey and apples
the plant-based people all go back to
eggs right when they leave plant-based
they go back to eggs set it for years
long before
whatever it is
long C is Epstein-Barr and then it comes
out later that long C is Epstein-Barr
multiple sclerosis is caused by obscene
bar infections
published it first and then years later
science puts it out
that's the cause of multiple sclerosis
and these are just a few things
and I'm telling you now the whole blood
sugar game
where you got a monitor stuck to you and
you're playing around with graphs and
charts and you're signing up to stuff
and you're eating this food in this in
combination and eating this in
combination you're looking at your butts
you're completely getting smoking
mirrors bait and switch
is what's happening
so I'm making the stovetop mac and
cheese
and even with me saying all of that I'm
making macaroni and cheese and you might
be like that guy's crazy
everything he just told me and he's
making mac and cheese
but it's mac and cheese without the bad
stuff Michelle says my family won't
listen even though I've helped them
before
I understand
so I'm about to
make some good stuff right here I'm
going to get the potatoes ready
[Music]
I'm making a fat free
cheese for the macaroni so it's stovetop
macaroni and cheese cheese it's not
vegan cheese in the sense where you know
the vegan cheese you can buy in the
store which is loaded with natural
flavors
it could be loaded with soy to be loaded
with all kinds of different things maybe
it's an almond cheese maybe it's
something like that but there's always
something in there
that shouldn't be in there
and there's always a percentage of
something bad in there that shouldn't be
in there either
now
[Music]
how do we stabilize our blood sugar like
the true way of stabilizing our blood
sugar we minimize the fat intake in our
diet
we lower it
and it all depends on where you're at
is it your pancreas your adrenals and
your liver
that are struggling is it just your
liver is it just your adrenals whatever
it is that's happening out of those
three
and most people
it's liver and adrenals whichever it is
though
once you start removing some of the fats
out of your diet
eating
enough calories
that are in the safe Zone
making sure you're hydrated just enough
blood sugar problems start to dwindle
and start to disappear
it's something that you don't want to
have to worry about I don't worry about
my blood sugar
I don't say throughout my day Anthony
William says crap my blood sugar
like my blood sugar is totally off I
gotta worry about it where's it at it's
you know like I have to be scared about
my blood sugar
Chase says I'm not talking about eating
a whole chocolate bar talking about
eating a single square of dark chocolate
from actual cacao haha countless studies
proving the benefits
why do you have to eat a single Square
are you afraid
you afraid something chase afraid of
something
why are you eating a single Square
huh because you're scared to eat
the whole bar
why
because you eat a whole chocolate bar
every day you're gonna feel it you're
gonna start getting sick it's gonna wear
you out how about two chocolate bars
no disrespect I love your comment and I
appreciate you being here seriously
I do why don't you have four chocolate
bars
why are you eating a square I'm curious
I just need to know somebody tell me why
are you eating a square
because you're afraid you're just going
to go into the chocolate draw
where's the clock right now
I give you chocolate I need my high I
gotta keep it to a square I gotta keep
it to a square
somehow I gotta keep it to a square
there's chocolate bar right here
because you're scared of the
chocolate
caffeine is a neurotoxin I'm gonna eat
this little square piece of chocolate
but to tell myself there's countless
studies out there I know it there's
countless studies out there it doesn't
matter if it makes me feel crazy or if
it makes me start yelling at somebody or
it makes me feel depressed and sad or
I'm crying in a corner or I need another
Square it doesn't matter if I'm addicted
and I gotta have the chocolate bar
there's countless studies that says this
chocolate's so good for me I'm just
gonna have a square
why the hell are you eating just a
little square
why
you're keeping it back like I'm just
going to have a square because that
shit's crazy that's why because you know
it ain't good for you and that's why
you're eating a square if it was good
for you you'd be eating two or three
chocolate bars every single day boom
ninety percent cacao 70 cacao whatever
because the stimulant gets you high
and you don't like the way it feels but
there's payback baby there's cause and
effect when you eat that chocolate what
goes up must come down and guess what
comes down and guess what gets shot and
guess what gets beat up is your adrenals
your adrenals
Trio glands
a little piece
of jewelry I miss a little piece because
I'm only gonna hurt you a little bit not
a lot I'm only gonna hurt you adrenal
glands a little bit not a lot I'm just
gonna have a little tiny piece of
chocolate because
gonna hurt you that bad I'm just gonna
eat that that feels good I feel high I
remember adrenal glands the studies say
that there's really good stuff in
chocolate I know what the study said
about that thing everybody took and I
know about that study that they said
about those drugs they know I know about
that bad study they said where asbestos
was really good for us and that millions
of people are dead because asbestos
cancer I know the studies were they
always say they're right but they say
the cacao study is right
together
you guys welcome to my kitchen I'm
making stovetop macaroni and cheese cold
white spring they believe that in the
right amount it's medicinal they say
water is also unhealthy
if it gets too much
the right amount of frog poison to make
me high and my brains out and puke
my brains out amongst a whole bunch of
you know people around a campfire at
night oh give me that frog poison I hear
it's really good you put it in an edible
okay let me take that little edible frog
poison just a little bit is medicinal
you see oh yeah
you know what's really screwed up we
talk about how we care about what we put
in our bodies out there that's all I
hear out there is my body I'll do what I
want with it I only put the best inside
my body I only put the best inside
my body it better be the best whatever
our Farms are grown in the best
conditions and the best that everybody
just wants the best all the time
they go to the best stores they just
want the best stuff right but I'll go
and just for the sake of it put some
poisonous psilocybin or some frog poison
in my veins and in my heart and in my
brain because I'm looking for a high
I'm looking to get effed up in my brain
because life's too hard
and life's too hard
I better smoke double the weed tonight I
better just like
really take in that weed because you
know what life's really hard I get it
I'm not judging anybody because guess
what life is hard and it pushes us to do
things
but don't throw the scientific BS at me
about what a study is on cacao because
women know
did they got all be careful with that
stuff
for a lot of reasons they know that
stuff will make them sick
jacked up panic attacks wiped out and
addicted like you're a fiend in a like a
fiend
IG as a doctor I read dark chocolate was
good for you so I would eat it thinking
it was healthy so I bought and ate it
regularly not anymore thank you aw
anybody here who eats chocolate I'm glad
you're here I don't judge you that's the
last thing I would ever do if you ever
ran into me in the street or something
like that it's like aw
I really got hurt about the chocolate
thing I stopped following you and I
don't know I I don't really read your
books
I just didn't like the chocolate talk
I'd be like dude
it's okay I mean I'm not I'm not saying
anything like hey you're a bad person
because of it that's not it life's hard
if chocolate's all you're on and you're
not on something far worse
that's a miracle all in its own that's
how screwed up this world is if you're
not drinking a pint of whiskey every
night
then you know what exactly
if you're not doing a ton of
cocaine like every night this is amazing
that's how crazy this world is and
that's how messed up this world is I'm
gonna pop some pasta in here
but
I'm just saying
the pasta I'm using is on the medical
medium directory
foreign
pasta is on the medical medium directory
you know when you're watching Youtube
and stuff and you see all the ads come
in and now people are doing is they're
actually doing their own like ads right
in the middle they're like telling a
story and then all of a sudden it leaves
there and it gets edited and now they're
like
if you sign up for our 39.99 blah blah
blah blah and you gotta wait for him to
stop and it's like okay back to the
story
cheese in a little bit too but I just
want to wait just a little bit
before I make that but I am gonna peel
the potatoes you want this to be like
a cheese where you don't want the skins
on the potatoes
so I'm taking a fork and just taking
this you don't want to like a brown
cheese this is going to be
a beautiful
delicious cheese without the nutritional
yeast the MSG without the additives
this beats any vegan cheese out there I
don't care what anybody says hands down
I mean some of the vegan cheeses are so
bad out there I'm like unless you have
an issue you're probably better off with
the Cow Cheese
that's pure
I mean that's how bad the vegan cheeses
are I'm just kidding like when someone
says hey come over aw I'm gonna make a
really great dish and I got this killer
vegan cheese I go
all right
that's not making me want to have your
dish
some crazy vegan cheese and new vegan
cheese out there in the store that's not
making me want your dish
you guys follow me on
telegram if you get a chance T dot m e
slash medical medium
telegram okay exclusive audio messages
I'm going to be leaving a lot of them
pretty soon
and who knows what I'm gonna say I have
a feeling I'm going to be saying some
pretty intense stuff sound through the
medical medium newsletter if you get a
chance as well sign up to the medical
medium news letter for all kinds of
different notifications of all our free
stuff
free free free
that's what we do
follow me on Tick Tock you guys I'm
trying Tick Tock again
I'm giving it a shot
I'm trying it again
we were on tick tock
spirit and I
Spirit of compassion and I were on tick
tock
we were getting up to
like
we're heading up to a million followers
on tick tock
right
I was doing these videos that were
really funny so I heard
well they they cracked me up as well
though
and then Tick Tock said you no longer
can be on here and then they let me come
back
and so I'm back on Tick Tock and I'm
gonna be doing some fun stuff so you
might want to you know
follow my Tick Tock I already steamed
these potatoes so that's something to
know so you're not like wondering what
I'm doing right here with raw potatoes
you might be like whoa wait a minute are
these raw potatoes he's got right there
I'm just taking the skins off of these
potatoes
moving them out
boom
I'm just gonna have a little bit of this
frog poison
yep when he says oh my God peeling hack
yeah take a fork steam potato
I just took the skins off I mean you
might have a little bit left over just a
touch that's okay
that's all right pasta is boiling up
it's getting there
we'll be done soon
pasta pasta
so good
this is a wheat pasta with high in
gluten I'm kidding I'm kidding someone's
gonna take that and they're gonna edit
it
I'm kidding this is actually a
gluten-free pasta
so it's really good
so let's go into it a little bit
Lauren says what if your nutritional
yeast doesn't have MSG
that's the problem
I'm really glad you said that
really glad listen to my podcast about
nutritional yeast
there is no nutritional yeast that
doesn't have MSG
there is no
nutritional yeast that doesn't have MSG
there's no apple cider vinegar
that doesn't kill your liver
burnout
your stomach lands in your stomach and
kill your HCL
and dissolve your bones and teeth there
is no apple cider vinegar that does not
do that
you guys know what happened
do you remember
when conventional wisdom
and conventional Medical Science said it
is safe
to breathe in asbestos it is safe
to have lead in gasoline it is safe to
smoke
it is safe to have lead in paint chips
it is safe to take a thousand drugs that
they took off the market
because they had to pull them from the
market because they weren't safe
are you forgetting that whole thing that
happened because in alternative medicine
they're doing the same thing
chocolate's good for you
and maybe if you're not chronically sick
and you want to play with a little bit
of chocolate so be it
but if you're somebody that's really
struggling with a chronic illness that's
what I'm talking about I'm talking about
like death by a Thousand Cuts remember
I'm talking about like what chips away
at you when you're already struggling
and sick
alternative medicine in Wellness Health
and Wellness has made it
that's good that's dumb has made it
so that
they tell you everything is good and it
isn't
I've never been the food police
I need a place to put this pot
right
guys bear with me a little bit
I am just getting some macaroni here
in a bowl
and I'm gonna actually make some cheese
now
I'm not the food police when my friends
or family come over I will make them
anything they want
if that means I have to go to the store
and pick up something
that's on the medical medium warning
warning don't eat if you're sick
even if it's something like that I'll go
pick it up if I got company over and
they're like well I'm hankering for this
I'll be like all right where do you want
me to go
I'll go find it I'll go to the store
what do you want you want cheese I'll go
find it
it's not like this you come to the
medical medium house and it's like no
you only eat with the medical medium
actually you'll need this celery juice
you're just gonna drink celery juice
here and that's all you're gonna have
[Music]
right
okay
so what I'm gonna do is pop these
potatoes in the food processor
I'm not the food police one of my
friends or family come over I don't tell
them what they should eat I'll prepare
them something
anything they want
and
I'll tell them about options and stuff
to heal or
tell them about some good stuff they can
have
all right
I'm gonna get these potatoes in here I'm
gonna cut them in pieces
so I'm just gonna actually break them
down a little bit
foreign
but if you're really sick
and you want to go as far as you can
with your healing process you want to go
as far as it needs to take
but if you're a guest in my house
and you
are there
yeah
I want to make sure I'm a good Hoster
all right so I got some potatoes in here
for my cheese
and I'm gonna put some carrots in here
as well
steamed carrots
I'm going to add some water to this
I'm going to do some
um onion powder I'm going to do about
two tablespoons of onion powder
you want a decent amount of onion powder
in here
okay
I'm gonna put a little bit of garlic
powder in here too
there we go a little bit of purple
yeah and we're gonna put a little bit of
dried oregano in here too
it's gonna be really good
a little bit of turmeric
which will probably add to obviously the
cheese color there's no soy in here just
so you know there's no soy in here at
all
I'm gonna add some lemon juice fresh
lemon juice
a little strainer here
what about I got a just a large amount
of pasta I made and made basically two
boxes of pasta
so it's gonna take
more than really
a small amount of lemon but
I put a little bit more in here
a little strainer here
add a little bit of water to
two thirds of a cup
should do it
the lemon helps to give it this zesty
good flavor
you can add salt
if you like
I have some some family coming over and
I think they're gonna have this dish
so I might have to put a little bit of
salt in here
there's people that can't live without
salt they can't live without the flavor
the taste of salt like they won't eat
their food they just won't if it's
missing
okay
put the lemon juice in here
let me try this you guys okay with this
see what happens
all right
let's get a lid on it and put a little
water
in there as well
start with that I'm going to add some
more if I need to kind of like add
and I'm gonna need a wire
it's my favorite thing to do
boom
a little bit more
and there we go
you can do this in a blender
but you usually in blenders you've got
to add a little bit more water and I
don't want
a really
like
it's coming out really good
had a little bit more water because he
used a lot more potato than normal
I'm hungry
beautiful color Grizzy Grizz says
beautiful color
that's a compliment I'll take any
compliments look at this
really great thank you
everybody else like this is this okay
Karen says question
who cleans your kitchen when you are
done making a mess
a whole team of people
that because I am too Above cleaning
I am so Above cleaning I'm just into I
go get my massage after this
I go take a run
and I get my nails done but so I can't
be bothered with cleaning I do the
cleaning I do the cleaning
I break my butt and clean up the mess
I made the mess I will clean it
so that's the cheese right there now
this is the creamy cheese
putting some on just like that
amazing amazing so I'm just gonna get
the cheese to get in here a little bit
I'm gonna add some more I like it creamy
there we go
now I'm just mixing it in a little bit
here
laughs
it's piping hot so it's actually
and I might even with the rest of this I
might even add a bunch more
into this one
the rest of it
no Dairy no fat no butter no oil
there's no oil in here this is non-dairy
no soy
no vegan cheese that's filled with
natural flavors and everything else
that's terrible none of that either
[Music]
this cheese is the good part I don't
want to waste it I want every bit of it
in here because this is really how this
becomes so good
amazing
gotta give it some mix time
now you gotta think this is a dairy-free
mac and cheese
is what it is
now you can go one step past this if you
would like
you can put this in a baking dish
set the oven for
um 350.
set the oven for 375 and you can put
this in a baking dish and you can make
baked mac and cheese you know how you do
that work and then you actually put it
right in
foreign
cheese right there
I mean
you can definitely do an oven where
you've just toast the top if you really
wanted to which is incredible
but there it is
incredible that's the stovetop macaroni
and cheese you guys we talked about
blood sugar
talked about stabilizing blood sugar now
one of the things that happens a big
mistake that people make with blood
sugar
is they're in a vicious cycle and I
wanted to cover this because this is the
part I actually didn't cover yet so it's
important they're in a vicious cycle of
insulin resistance
where they have to eat the thing that
doesn't help them but it yet it feels
like it helps them
in order to stabilize their blood sugar
so if someone gets the shakes or they
get the low blood sugar or the
hypoglycemia whatever it is that they're
you know that they're dealing with or
they're monitoring their blood sugar
but they're told to eat things to
stabilize their blood sugar when in turn
it doesn't stabilize their blood sugar
but yet it feels like it does
so it's like whoa I have to eat
something right now I'm having a blood
sugar low I'm having a blood sugar
problem and then they go and eat some
hummus and I'm saying hummus is terrible
or anything
but because of all the tahini or the oil
in the hummus
they feel like whoa that just stabilized
me and they just had a bunch of fat and
that just stabilized me
and but yet that's not the answer to
fixing a blood sugar problem
regardless
I need some chips a lot of people do
this thing like just need a few chips
they open up a bag of chips it could be
like a healthier bag of chips in the
natural food store
and they go and they open a healthy bag
of chips and they eat like three or four
chips and they get stabilized right and
they think whoa I'm stabilizing my blood
sugar or they eat a handful of nuts or
half a bag of nuts and they're like I'm
stabilizing my blood sugar
or they have some bacon
and they're like whoa I'm stabilizing my
blood sugar but it's a catch-22 because
here you're having blood sugar problems
and then you're using things that put
you into a vicious cycle where the
problem will never be fixed and it'll
just keep going and going and going
because you don't fix the actual root
problem Rose Jackson said the absolute
disrespect and slander we receive from
everyone when we speak about your info
as though we are in the wrong because
it's not science
yeah I know I know you guys bear it you
bear it well man and I'm honored to be
in this with you truly
takes a special soul to see through the
smoke
to understand what this is and what the
information is in the medical medium
book series
to understand what's in in the podcast
the medical Ian podcast
it takes a special soul to understand
that
and to see it and see through everything
and then you know to hear crap from
people out there in a world that's sick
right like they got all the answers
stovetop mac and cheese right here
that's the recipe
it's in the brain saver protocols
check the book out if you'd like
all right you guys
covered some blood sugar information
blood sugar talk quick rundown right now
that just keep in mind that any of the
cleanses in the medical medium books is
supportive of blood sugar problems
critical to know anybody who's actually
worried about their blood sugar numbers
if you're dealing with blood sugar
issues it's good to know why
we have problems with our blood sugar
and it's good to know how to address it
and to beat it over time
and
also protect your adrenals at the same
time and restore and cleanse your liver
anyway guys thank you for hanging around
and um
I'll see you next