live right now
live on tick tock facebook youtube
telegram
so
talking about different things we're
going to talk about trendy traps that's
one thing right there
trendy traps how many of you guys ever
fell into a trendy trap
like taking anything that
may not have helped or thought it was
gonna save you or thought it was gonna
turn your life around
but it didn't right you know how many
trendy traps are out there so right now
the whole parasite thing is a major
trendy trap right now right
it's like everybody being said well
maybe it's a parasite well that trendy
trap
has been around forever okay someone's
sick they got tingles and numbness they
got aches and pains they don't feel good
they got burning skin they got
intestinal trouble they got stomach
aches back pain neck pain head pain
right severe fatigue
okay ticks and spasms and brain fog all
that anxiety depression and then nobody
knows why anybody's sick
so it's like okay well what is it what
is it well it's parasites that's what it
is parasites
do this parasitical cleanse now you go
and you do this parasitical cleanse and
you're doing this parasitical cleanse
and in the past
in the past it would just be like do
this parasitical cleanse
not even like change your diet or
anything like that just do this
parasitical cleanse and then people
would do it
and it would tear their guts apart
and they wouldn't get better
they just wouldn't get better
you know and so but the parasitical
cleanse kind of
died out it already gave people 20 years
of a ride lots of different parasitical
cleanses and alternative movement
okay
already gave them a ride
it already did its thing it burnt itself
out it bros up a little bit and then
burnt itself out and died
an ugly death
right
but now
it is coming back same thing with
alkaline ionizer water machines okay
because not going to ionize the water
machines they've been around they've
been around all those years no one got
better you go and buy expensive water
machine
and you're drinking your alkaline water
you still got your aches and pains
tingles and numbness ticks and spasms
brain fog neck and back pain you still
got your fatigue
and all those machines went into
everybody's closet
again it went into everybody's closet
right
you know which ones stand out and you
know which ones don't stand out because
back then
that died in ugly death too so the
ionizer water machine world just went
tanked
right and then social media picked up
and social media picked up
okay same thing coffee enemas people did
the coffee enemas coffee enemas all
those years ago coffee enemas
they did them they did them didn't fix
them made them sicker
didn't fix them
right
and then that kind of died
an ugly death that kind of died
but then social media came on and then
boom
everything started picking up
right coffee enema supplies started
picking up let's get it out there
alkaline ionizer water machines parasite
cleanses right i'm just naming a few
few trendy traps just a few
there's dozens okay dozens
but social media picked up
and then the marketing happened to
marketing
all the heavy marketing
right
and then the incentives with all the
marketing with the trendy traps
but none of those things and so many
more like the rife machine
that was a disaster disaster the rife
machine back 20 years ago
people buy the rife machine and sitting
there you know with the right machine in
their hand
and then boom still their neurological
symptoms burning skin aches and pains
ringing in the ears tinnitus vertigo uh
severe brain fog floaters in the eyes
neck pain back pain all these other
issues still stayed there but you still
had your rife machine
right but then like i said everything
changes all this money gets dumped into
all these things to revive them they die
this ugly death
all of these things all did throughout
the years and then they get revived
they get revitalized by money
because now we've got a whole new world
got the social media world and just dump
a whole bunch get the investors get the
shareholders on board and dump a whole
bunch of money into things
and get them back up oh buy a rice
machine oh buy an alkaline isonizer
let's do that okay i'll get another mat
to lay on okay i'll get uh maybe i'll
pick up a hyperbaric oxygen chamber you
know people laid in those things and
laid those things and laid in those
hyperbaric oxygen chambers they never
got better
when they were sick really sick when
they had the neurological lyme and they
had all the other conditions right
people have that now okay
man they've been around those oxygen
chambers
but everybody was stuck
everybody was stuck
right and then by default people started
learning through medical medium tools
and stuff about getting rid of that
gluten going all the way back when i
used to say 35 years ago get rid of the
wheat people look at me like i had two
heads i had two heads that's what they
would look at my life that's what it
would be where's my other one here here
it is it'd be like hey get off a wheat
everybody get off a wheat
what
get off of wheat
what do you mean get off of wheat
because you look like an alien right now
a.w
wheat everybody wheat germ remember
wheat germ
i'd be like and i'd be like we i'd be
like we germ and they're like yeah weed
germs good for you that was a trend too
the wheat germ trend
right i'd be like no it's bad for you
germ that's gonna keep you sick
and they think i had two heads when they
heard wheat like wheat germ
they was like crazy let's say you got to
get off a cheese oh wait a minute my raw
cheese is so good for me no you've got
to get off the cheese
geez dairy's bad dairy's bad i thought
you just had to be lactose intolerant
and then that's what makes dairy bad i
didn't know that
that
dairy's bad you got two heads aw you got
two heads
because that's the scariest thing i ever
heard is is dairy products are bad
right you got to get off the eggs you
got to get off the eggs
right they'd be like eggs oh my god eggs
are good for you
break down from your head down to your
legs
eggs are good for you what do you mean
we're supposed to be eating more eggs aw
you you're definitely like you got two
heads because
definitely you just landed off of a
spacecraft
and
until those tools started to kick it in
people people got off those processed
foods and they back down on the butter
it's another one too back down on the
eggs and the butter and other things and
the dairy and the gluten right they
start picking up speed
they do they start picking up speed and
all of a sudden for some reason wait a
minute you know
what's working what's not working like
what's starting to fix me a little bit
what's not starting to fix with fix me
back in the older days you just had the
gimmicky stuff
you had the rife
machine you had the alkaliners alkaline
ionizer machines
you had the oxygen hyperbaric chambers
right hyperbaric oxygen chambers you had
all these other different things right
you had these right and
at the same time
you had all these you know people
weren't they weren't moving forward they
weren't moving forward so these things
would be all stuck in people's closets
that's where they would be it's like a
whole closet full of all this stuff
you'd have the mat in there you'd have
the you know the foot bath in there
you'd have all these different things
right
but
one of the things is the parasitical
cleanses was big right the parasitical
cleanses
that was a big one
right
it's like everybody's got a parasite
everybody's got a parasite you go to a
doctor of like not a conventional doctor
but you go to an alternative person it's
like you got a parasite that's what's
wrong with you
really what do i need to do oh do this
you can put a whole bunch of olive oil
in here and put a bunch of stuff in
there and put this cleansing stuff in
here you can put these powders in here a
whole bunch of probiotics
and still stay sick here's some clay
here's some bentonite clay that's
another trendy trap right bentonite clay
maybe do a coffee enema under boot with
your bentonite clay
it was endless it was always like this
it was always like this
this is
what life was like back then but now
it's still life now
right
these things revive these old things
revive themselves
people get on board with a ton of money
and
the one thing all these things hate all
the shareholders to all these different
endeavors
what they hate
they hate with a passion
is that right there
they hate it
when this
got more known and more known and more
known and more known
it pissed everybody off
is what it did
okay
you can go into a juice store right you
can go into a juice bar
and get yourself a fresh celery juice
and turn your life around
and start turning your life remove the
needle when nothing else could
when nothing else could
when all these people
seasoned people who've been through hell
and back who tried everything they tried
all the clays they tried all this they
tried diatomaceous earth particles they
tried the apple cider vinegar
they tried all these different
techniques and things they tried ozone
therapy right tried ozone therapy
and all of a sudden
they said you know they heard from
somebody else or heard medical medium or
heard something from his book or heard
from another person
or maybe who recommended it because of
medical meaning they heard about the
celery juice and they start drinking it
and something changes
really changes the needle starts to move
right
starts to move but here's what's funny
there isn't hundreds and hundreds of
millions of dollars invested into
brainwashing you to drink celery juice
in fact it's the opposite
did you guys know
there's money invested to stop you from
drinking celery juice
every single day out there
that's right
there wasn't a single article positive
about it
they just tried to stomp on it with
everything they had the media
the industries
how many dietitians oh celery juice
isn't good for you you should just eat
the stock because i'm a dietitian and i
know and i'm gonna oh i'm invited to go
on an article to rip down celery juice
and make sure i tell people there's no
science behind celery juice
i'm a dietitian and there's no science
behind celery juice and they're going to
make sure they stick that in every
article
there's money invested
shareholders
money out there
to take down celery juice
like a real spiritual battle
good and evil
did you know that
a real spiritual battle of good and evil
to take down celery juice
to stop it
and
make it seem like trife
make it seem
not really
could do anything it's just a vegetable
yeah you can chop it up and throw it in
something
you can
have a celery stick and a carrot
and
really it's not going to help in any way
okay
and that's
what has happened where
there's been money
millions of dollars
invested
to shut this down
millions
while
millions of dollars are invested to
bring back
the old garbage
like the fulvic minerals that never got
anybody better in the last 20 years
except if you're drinking celery juice
like
in the closet
get my celery juice down and then i'll
go and talk about fulvic minerals
because it's an mlm campaign i'll go
i'll drink my celery juice
you know and do my yoga drink my celery
juice and then i'll go i'll go talk
about alkaline ionizer water machines
because yeah because i'm part of the
pyramid scheme
and it was that that got me better not
the celery juice
and
but the celery juice
has turned so many lives around at this
point
it's really unbelievable
but it's also an eyesore it's been an
eyesore
one thing is the celery
powders like celery juice powders that
came to town because they were trying to
hop on the bandwagon well that got
crushed pretty much
because we know through the books and
all the information talking about it
that the powders don't work
so they really can't they can't really
get as far as they need to go it's a
fresh celery juice
we know that you freshly juice with your
juicer or you go into a juice bar and
you buy it right freshly juiced that
turn that turns things makes things
happen that makes things happen
that gets you better
so
the one thing about the trendy traps out
there is they're still out there and
there's still many of them out there
lots of trendy traps
and
the parasite one i was talking about
because that one's making a comeback
because of the parasite cleanses
because of the parasite probiotic stuff
because the microbiome talk
but fecal matter implants
coffee enemas
various probiotics with all this stuff
in it including clays and bentonite clay
really are not the answer
they're not
i'll give you a little run down on
parasites just for a quick second here
if you catch a
parasite you die
or the parasite dies
there's no in between
you drink some bad water
right out of a puddle
you drink
some water
out of a pond
and you get a parasite
you [ __ ] your brains out
and throw up your brains out
until one of you makes it whether you
sit in the hospital
on iv and painkillers until you win the
battle
okay or you lose the battle
there's no in between with parasites
you don't walk around with parasites in
you you don't
okay you can walk around with worms
but that's not a
parasite worms are worms
and guess what
people walk around with worms and
they're never sick you can walk around
with worms and eat chocolate cake and
pizza and there's people they're not
sick they don't have chronic illness and
they're playing tennis they're doing
whatever they're playing tennis they're
drinking martinis they're drinking wine
they're partying they're staying up all
night they do that to 30s and their 40s
they never got sick yet
it never tipped to scale with other
things
they have worms in them
yeah
you can live with worms in you you can't
and
those worms won't make you sick
unless
it's a five foot tapeworm
but you'll know and you'll know quick
now parasites
you drink some nasty water
you're down in mexico and you drink that
water
what do you think that is when you get
sick what do you think they tell you not
to drink the water in mexico
because when you get that parasite it's
you or the parasite
you win or the parasite wins you don't
keep that parasite that you picked up in
mexico
from that water
you don't keep it i've known so many
people they've gone to india
right
they've gotten a parasite
eating in some restaurant i know some
people here in the united states lots of
them they go into a restaurant they pick
up a parasite
right you're in europe you're traveling
and you eat something somewhere some
street food
you pick up a parasite
it's you're the parasite
you stay sick gravely sick until the
parasite's gone
you sit in the hospital
or at home
you barf
you [ __ ]
until the parasite's gone
it's one or the other you are the
parasite there's no living your life
slowly getting sick with neurological
symptoms and then getting
and then that's a parasite
living your life with these parasites in
you and you know you're slowly getting
sick and you've got neurological fatigue
and you've got problems
galore and you've got eye floaters and
body pain and you're going now to fancy
functional medicine doctor he's like
well you got parasites we're doing a
stool simple sample and you got parasite
no
not how it works
what you really have
are viruses
not parasites which really have
the herpetic family is the one that's
the epidemic of all time
everybody's epstein-barr side of
megaloviruses everybody's hhv sixes
everybody's simplex ones and twos giving
them all the neurological problems
the brain fog the sicknesses and
everything else
okay and then to boot you can have
some streptococcus three four varieties
of strep
and what happens is that's why people
are sick
they're sick from these things
so the parasite trap is a trap
is what it is
it's a trap that started because nobody
knew why anyone was sick
alternative practitioners didn't know
why anybody's sick conventional doctors
certainly didn't know why everybody was
sick with chronic mystery illness nobody
knew
nobody knew
right
and so theories evolved candida the
candida trap right oh it's gotta be
candida better just try to kill all your
candida oh wait a minute maybe it's
parasites you better just try to kill
off all your parasites
so let's start jump you know let's start
dude maybe it's mold mold's a trigger
is what mold is
that's a trigger
that's why someone else in the household
can eat all the mold they want oh my god
my husband can get all the mold he wants
he's living in the same house i'm in i'm
bedridden
as his wife
i'm bedridden i can't get out of bed i
can't i can't function i have brain fog
that's killing me my husband he's just
coming and going he's eating the mold
he's breathing the mold
because he
doesn't have the things in his body
the other person has
see how mold works molds a trigger to
lower your immune system so viruses come
out to play
right
so we go on these
searches
what is wrong with us what do we need
well i better do the hyperbaric chamber
i better do ozone i better do the rice
machines i better do the alkaline
ionizer water machines i better do you
know laser light i better do you know
get the stool test and maybe parasites
parasitical cleanses let me do that
and it goes around and it goes around
and it goes around
you know and if you're not sick enough
you can play in all that and i know
what's what you got the coffee animal
you got the hyperbaric the oxygen
chamber you got this and that and you
don't know what's doing what right
you're not sick enough so you don't know
what's happening anyway you get sick
enough and you get seasoned enough along
the way
and you're sick or seasoned enough in
that and you've been sick chronically
ill for a long time then make or break
man you know
you know when you get worse
anyway
it's important stuff when you think
about it there are millions of dollars
going in to taking out taking down
celery juice
just so you know
there's all kinds of propaganda about
you you'll have skin problems when
you're drinking celery juice
you won't be able to go into the sun
that's insanity
it's not just
some simple
attacks
it's
premeditated paid for attacks
out there
because
the power of celery juice
is such a threat
to conventional and alternative medicine
an incredible threat to alternative
medicine by the way
i'll turn to medicine people oh man they
hate it tooth and nail
even though there's lots of doctors
using it their patients are coming in
they're using it lots of people go
coming in using it but it just really
gets everybody's goat for a lot of
reasons because
it's really annoying here you are you
don't know why anybody's sick to begin
with you're trying to push all these
other things on them right and then
someone walks in and says oh just the
celery juice is changing my life
and
someone and it's it's kind of
unfathomable it's like wait a minute
crudite
so i've been i've been screwing around
as a doctor
for 20 years and you're going to tell me
crew today got you better
so they can't even
doesn't even register
no it's the 16 it's therapeutic it's
herbal medicine it's 16 to 32 ounces of
celery juice herbal medicine and that's
what it is that's changed my life
medical medium a medical medium
i heard of him
and you know and it's
celery juice
it's turning people's lives around is
one of the powerful tools medical mean
powerful tools but it's one that's
undeniable it's undeniable the power it
has and what it does for people like
it's really undeniable
and
it's antiviral and antibacterial
that's why people are sick it's the
viruses
right i think we're learning that by now
right
everybody being held up
to the last whatever it's been now
right
just losing track of the months
right world turned upside down
right
are we kind of realizing
the same way
you know the viral the plague happens
all these decades
herpes family of viruses have been
released
into the environment
the epstein bars the shingles
cytomegalovirus
hhv-687 hhv 9 through 16 all the
undiscovered varieties all the strains
and mutations
and epstein-barr is a funny one
same thing with simplex one too and same
things with shingles is you can have
more than one variety and when you have
more than one variety of those viruses
inside the human body you can
spawn
a new mutation and then you pass that
mutation on to somebody else
they're sick with their neurological
lyme symptoms
lupus
chronic fatigue syndrome me chronic
fatigue syndrome
fibromyalgia ra
hashimoto's thyroiditis
hyperthyroidism
okay thyroid problems in general
hypothyroid in general
right
these are just a few eczema psoriasis
you need a virus in there too did a ligo
you need a virus in there too it's not
just the metals that i teach about right
you need the viruses in there
but the viruses
right there
are the big deal
it's why people are sick bell's palsy
that's the shingles virus
trigeminal neuralgia that's the shingles
virus but here's the sad part
you can be suffering from trigeminal
neuralgia have some bell's palsy at the
same time have chronic fatigue brain fog
go to your different doctors
and someone will just say oh it's a
parasite doing it and now it's just a
guessing game and a guessing game so now
it's just a total guessing game back to
that and the musical chairs go on
so
what i love about celery juice
is its power and what it does
and you know trigeminal neuralgia not
just the shingles simplex one
simplex one can actually bring on that
trigeminal neuralgia too
teeth clenched inning jaw tightening
but someone might think hey well that
fever blister i have right
a fever blister
it's gone it only shows up once in a
while when i'm stressed out and then i
get this fever blister it's simplex one
all these viruses were raised
they were raised in labs
with eggs as their incubator
and they were created
they proliferated and then they were
released
purposely
into our environment
in many creative ways
many creative ways
which is why we have the epidemic of
chronic illness today right now
you see why celery juice is such a
threat
but it's a threat
to more than conventional medicine and
big pharma and pharmaceuticals
it's a threat more to anti-anxiety
medications antidepressants that make
the world go around right and all the
other medications and blood clotting
medications and all kinds of different
medications right not only is it a
threat to all the different meds the
opioid
epidemic
big pharma cells all the opioids right
this is not just the threat to all of
that it's a threat to the massive
conglomerate massive
industry the alternative medicine
industry
and all the different fads and trends
that were in the past that never got
people better like really better after
everything they've been through and the
money jumped into it to rise those
things up and rise them up
so it becomes now the war on the
chronically ill
because how's the chronically ill person
gonna find their way
especially when a whole bunch of [ __ ]
has always talked about celery juice
because you won't see nothing positive
out there because no one's spending the
money
to write it of course you guys say
things positive about celery juice and
the person next door does and the person
down the street does right and i'm
saying things that are positive about it
right so we're saying positive things
but no
industry
nobody behind there's writing
all these
fake bogus articles of positivity
and then putting it out there
about something like they do but
everything else like they do with the
ionizers and they do with all the
different other things and like they do
with all the different gut products and
everything else anything that anybody
wants to sell they're in the clays
and the coffee enemas so all these
things get written about these things
because the money and the engine
involved to do would not just write it
but to get it in the system so it
doesn't get kicked down
so it doesn't get kicked down
and
celery juice doesn't have any of that it
just has the word on the street
the word of the people
how pure is that
it's got the organic movement the word
of the people on the street healing
right not millions perpetuating like the
apple cider vinegar narrative so that
you think apple cider vinegar is what
you need to be on when the stuff rips
you apart and it dissolves your teeth
the money involved in apple cider
vinegar is
you could not even hundreds of millions
of dollars go into advertising that to
shove it down everybody's throat
yeah there isn't hundreds of millions of
dollars shoveling shoving down celery
just down your throat it's a threat to
everybody else in the industries
so it becomes this thing where
it's underground
it's like one of those things it's
incredible really every last bit of it
you guys if this this sale was actually
coming to an end probably pretty soon
um this is the mm-900 hps
i love this juicer i love it okay
and
you get 50 off on it right now
comes with a celery juice book right
but i want to tell you like
what i love about this juicer
if you got it then you know what i'm
talking about it's quiet
right i love that
but
and i just i hear about it all the time
right now is people are buying less
celery
it adds up and then you end up paying
for your juicer
okay
and
[Applause]
how cool is that right
i get asked every day what juicer do i
use
all the time okay and you can use any
juicer you can use your own juicer if
you want whatever like if you or any
juicer juicing celery juice is
incredible
this is a cold pressed juicer the pulp
comes out dry
so the pulp comes out dry
and
that matters because if you have to buy
two heads of celery
now
i have to only buy one or
if you're someone that has to buy six
heads or something for the week or eight
heads of celery for the week
right you might be buying five
[Music]
instead of eight or something right
three extra heads on the house that's
how it works and that's what this juicer
does it's like three extra heads of
celery that goes in the bank and then it
adds up it's another two dollars here
another two dollars another five dollars
here then eight dollars another ten
dollars here next thing you know you
paid for the juicer over again and
you're like what
and that's what i love about the juicer
it pays for itself i'm pretty sure this
one from my calculations has paid for
itself way over a dozen times
and
that extra money you can buy other food
so not only do you have their medicine
but you're saving extra money to buy
your other food right so not only do you
have your herbal medicine but you're
saving you're saving money
to you know
to buy your other food and that's what i
love about the juicer that's like one
thing there
you know and
i got a lot of reasons why i like it
like the other thing is doesn't have the
metal gears grinding into each other
then the centrifuge ones burns
it the centrifuge ones where it's just
like they make all that noise and you're
running it down the chute and it's
spitting out right and all that well
those centrifuges right
they're burning the juice so they're
heating it up and just kind of scorching
it
and i'm not a fan of that
this is a cold pressed juicer but then
somebody be like wow there's better cold
pressed juicers out there oh really
because those are the metal gears
rubbing against each other
so uh
it's not better than this
[Music]
and so that's why i really love this one
i love the fact it's quiet because i
juice really early in the morning
or i'll juice before i go to bed so if
i'm working on the book you guys like if
i'm working the book till four in the
morning or something
and
i don't want to wake up the house
so
i could juice at 4 30 in the morning
before i even went to bed
after working on the book
and not wake up the house and then get a
celery juice in me as i'm going to sleep
i know that's not a healthy lifestyle
the celery just parts a healthy
lifestyle but i know
going to sleep at 4 30
in the morning or five in the morning
it's not a healthy lifestyle but i've
had to do it a lot when writing the book
because once then when you're in the
groove and
you're listening to the spirit of
compassion and getting this incredible
information down
sometimes you just don't want to quit
for the day
you want to get as much as you can
but yeah
and then you know wake up eight o'clock
in the morning after that and then start
all over again
but i love the juice for a lot of these
reasons
um
look
if everybody
was all set with their juicer and they
weren't asking about it
be great i probably have more time to
do some other stuff right
but right after the sale everybody's
gonna say where can i get a juicer and
then they're paying full price
and then i'm like oh god i feel bad
[Music]
[Applause]
so when there's a sale on the juicer i
just want to let you guys know because
this way look maybe we can get some
people that don't have to pay full price
don't feel good about it
it's 50 off right now and at the same
time you know the celery just broken two
glass bottles for free
with it
but
all right we got plenty there plenty of
celery juice right there
[Music]
[Applause]
give you some tips tips that i've always
given you and i'll talk about what it
does for you too i want to run it by i
think i want to go deeper into that a
little bit about the celery juice and
why it's so important so go into a
deeper on a deeper level okay
which is really great
i'll strain it first you want to strain
it first of all this pulp right it's dry
and i you know i was at my friend's
house the other day
and he had a different juicer
and it was it was just spitting out all
the wet pulp became a wet mush in there
and then what he had to do is he had to
take that pulp and he had to put it back
on the machine
and it didn't give him really much juice
after that but it still came out sloppy
and wet i said you can stick it back in
over and over again all you want but it
doesn't have that same it doesn't have
that design to actually squeeze the
juice out so he gave up because it was
just coming out wet and sloppy
and just coming out wet and sloppy what
what that was what it's doing it was
terrible right and so that's dry there's
no juice on the bottom of this it's like
dust that the stuff just comes out like
you know and
so that's important
um
it's like basically air dry the hole
which i love
gotta strain it okay
so
doing that now
seems like i'm spilling this one for
some reason i haven't spilled it in like
a week
when i'm making it every morning
but i lost a little
i'm gonna do that
so how about if i just get everything
moved out of the way so i don't there
you go
tip
don't don't strain it
while you're trying to do it over the
juicer like that make yourself some room
so you don't make a mess
try to do some weird thing when you got
the juicer right there
simple as that
i should have probably moved the juicer
out of the way
giving myself some space so i wouldn't
make a mess
so
these are some of the things i love
about the juicer which is incredible
right
so let's talk about like what it does
for us okay
so why do it
it's like why do it okay so i have that
right there
just cut into that a little bit i want
to get this over here
[Music]
okay i'm going to give you a couple of
different
rundowns on why the cellar is just so
good we're going to talk about the heart
a little bit too as well
so
why are people easily blood clotting
people have been blood clotting for
decades and decades
and decades okay
and one of the reasons why they blood
clot if they have any toxins or poisons
inside their blood
right
and the blood is too thick
they're gonna get set up for a blood
clot
they're gonna be
eligible for a blood clot that's
important to know so when the blood
is too thick
and then you have a buildup of too many
toxins too many poisons
right
chronic dehydration
that's another thing too
and too much fat floating around or
stuck inside the arteries the heart okay
and all through the body and in the
veins you're gonna get set up for a
blood clot
celery juice
not only hydrates properly because it's
a complete electrolyte right not only
does it hydrate properly
okay
but
it's a natural blood thinner
without it being ever a problem
what that means is
it starts to break up that fat meaning
start to dissolve fatty deposits
that shouldn't be there the fatty
deposits that actually cause
problems blood clots other things like
that so it's it's the cleaner upper
where it starts to dissolve
the poison
it starts to neutralize it it even binds
on to it to pull it out
and that alone is like incredible really
right there that's that's the winner
right there all on its own it's cleaning
your blood
there's a whole bunch of people there
like lymphatic lymphatic lymphatic
system got to do my lymphatic massage
got to do my lymphatic drainage i'm
going to do my lymphatic therapies i got
somebody who knows all about lymphatic
they're going to give me all kinds of
tonics i'm like okay well where's the
celery juice
because you can do all the lymphatic
stuff you want you can do all your
little lymphatic lenses and all your
different tricks and you can do your
massage too
but you can't clean that lymphatic
system up
until you use like tools that really
work like celery juice is one of those
tools that's why people start getting
better another another reason why
celery juice works on cleaning up the
lymphatic system is because it's fixing
the liver
your lymphatic system's only as good as
your liver
you have a dirty liver and that's not
being fixed your lymphatic system is
going to be never ending it's going to
be the never ending trash pile like the
garbage patch out on the west coast
right in the pacific
it's now way bigger than texas
it's far bigger and it's moving now to a
point where it's pushing to the coast
to the west coast
the problem with the garbage patch
pushing to the west coast
is it squeezing out the wildlife so
people are starting to see wildlife
that's not supposed to live on the coast
so i was talking to a friend of mine
and he said he saw wildlife studies fish
he says he saw fish that live way out
there and don't live on the coast
and they're finding fish that's pushed
out
so because the garbage patch is now
moving to such a rate right well if your
liver is that toxic like the garbage
patch
and it's that filled up with junk and
stagnity and all kinds of toxins and
everything else
your lymphatic system
is part of that garbage patch
you you can clean the lymphatic all you
want
you can do all the cleansers and things
that are you know all theoretical or
whatever you want to do
but unless you clean up the liver
it's not going to happen
it's just not it's like cleaning up the
coast it's like walking on the west
coast right now on the beach and
cleaning up garbage meanwhile there's
this massive monstrosity out in the
water in the pacific that's just
gobbling everything up no one's going
out there to clean that up
and that's the liver
that's the monstrosity problem of all
the junk and garbage that's where it
really is centered for everybody you got
weight gain that's coming on and you
can't get rid of that weight gain or
that weight gain's problematic
and you're doing everything you can but
you know you can barely control the
weight gain
that's the liver saying hey i had enough
i'm filled with toxins i'm filled with
poisons i'm filled with all kinds of
trouble all kinds of different things
and
petrochemicals and solvents and
everything else metals
everything's in there right perfumes
colognes
all of it and
so how do we clean up that liver
including any kind of viral sludge or
things like that in there
how do we clean up the liver well celery
juice is actually one of those things so
now you're you're hitting you're
pinpointing
you're doing pinpoint
you're locking it down
you're actually locking it down you're
using the celery juice to go into the
liver
start cleaning up that garbage patch
right there
and then the lymphatic system actually
lymphatic system actually that's the
next that just naturally starts to clean
up
it's why you could be 40 something years
old and you've like eaten really lean
meats or or you're vegan and you're
eating you know good quality vegan food
and you're working out you're exercising
and then you die of a heart attack
happens every day
every day
and you're like this guy that's running
on a treadmill
pushing weights
in great shape
dies of a heart attack at 42 years old
you think that's just one guy out of 10
000. oh my god it's so many guys it's
unbelievable and women too
and
because we're not addressing the real
issue the center that storm in the
center here right so celery juice is
that great weapon that great tool you
can use every single day so when you're
drinking your celery juice you're like
you're really cleaning your lymphatic
system you're really cleaning your liver
that's just you know yeah it's one of
the medical medium tools there's others
too you can combine
but that one right there is really
important and there's good reason for it
and then your intestinal tract
so you go to the functional medicine
doctor and he's going to be caught onto
the trends of microbiome and oh you're
going to need all this fermented foods
and microorganisms and that's your
problem guess what's been done
been done before and everybody still
stays sick who's chronically ill
sure if they get rid of your gluten and
your eggs they don't know why you start
getting better you get rid of your glute
and your eggs and you get rid of your
dairy you get rid of processed foods you
might be somebody that's not sick and
all of a sudden you start seeing some
some benefits so you think oh he's got
something there maybe my microbiome but
really
what you have
is
a whole bunch of different bacteria
like the bad bacteria like the
streptococcus and you got the viruses
like the epstein barr
that's why you got the brain fog and you
got the fatigue and the sickness and the
fibromyalgia and all the other issues so
what happens is that when you go
to your functional doctor or somebody
which is great you got to have a
functional doctor you got to have
somebody you love but when they start
pushing the parasite cleanses and
everything else
that's really not the direction the
direction
is going after the bacteria
right
with something that kills it but doesn't
kill the good bacteria another thing too
is a big confusion that people have
is that
they think you can put in all these
microorganisms and that pushes out the
bad stuff it doesn't they don't battle
each other
they're not against each other so
bad microbes in your intestinal tract
don't go at war with good microbes
so you can push all the theoretical
microbes you want or fermented
microorganisms or probiotics you want in
your gut
but it'll never push out while you're
the reason why you're sick it'll never
push the reason why you're sick out it's
why so many people with fatigue and the
brain fog and the aches and pains and
the vertigo and the dizziness and the
balance issues and the jaw pain the
trigeminal neuralgia the bell's palsy
the back pain neck pain the sciatica the
plantar fasciitis and everything else
they don't get better
because you can't push out a problem
using good bacteria
that's impossible bad bacteria and good
bacteria don't battle each other they're
not at war with each other they're not
against each other
so you can push anything you want in you
that you think is theoretically a
microorganism that your body might want
to receive
you put it in there you still stay sick
or you keep on waving back and forth
back and forth confused
so
i'm just and that's thousands and
thousands and thousands of dollars right
going in this specialist and this
specialist now i got to see my
neurologist now i'm going to try this
new cleanse now i'm going to try fecal
matter in plants now i'm going to try
more probiotics now you're in and then
i'm going to do this cleanse this
therapy i'm going to get blood work so
that's another thing too and then
they'll bleed you to death
so
so you got to know how to protect
yourself because the next thing you know
it now they're bleeding you to death
more blood more blood at the doctor's
office more blood more blood
oh
parasites more stool samples more blood
and
now we're down another you know we're
down a path even deeper into it
so this is thousands upon thousands of
dollars if you have health insurance
okay
i guess so a lot of it the co-payments
alone kill people so i don't know and
then all the different therapies are not
covered many of them
but
that's why celery juice is such
a threat and these people are already
deficient everybody you guys know like
everybody's deficient
right
everybody's deficient already they have
blood drawn from them they're already
deficient
they got adrenals already deficient
stomach lands already deficient they
can't produce the gastric acid they need
to produce
everything's already deficient okay and
people's teeth are falling apart why do
you think all the podcast doctors all
have fake teeth
i have you guys figured it out yet i
mean it's just unbelievable it's it's
incredible really
got all these guys there of course they
got all their teeth done they got the
implants and the veneers and everything
else i'm not saying that's a bad thing
if you want but the point is is
that
there's deficiencies in everybody
everybody's running deficient rampant
and what are we putting back in us
i think the celery juice is incredible
because you not only kill the bad
bacteria
but you're restoring
and restoring
so you're restoring back into you're
putting back in
to the bank
and that's the key
that's the big thing right there you're
putting back into the bank
and i love that you're also helping to
not just kill off the bad bacteria in
the gut because it neutralizes it breaks
down the membrane of bacteria and
viruses
but it flushes out dehydrated
gristle that everybody has in their
intestinal tracts everybody has this
dehydrated fat dehydrated gristle all
wrapped up inside their intestinal tract
lining they got all this gristle there
and so it starts to break that apart so
we end up getting rid of that
way better than sodium bicarbonate trend
diatomaceous earth particle
uh trend fulvic mineral trend whatever
and
what happens is
that
we're on all these different trends
they're being paid for out there
non-stop lots of money going in and then
we're told
celery juice
what that that's a vegetable it's not
going to be enough meanwhile what it's
done for people and turning people's
lives around is just absolutely
extraordinary
the thing is when people get their blood
removed constantly and they get vials of
blood removed constantly and that's
what's happening when we go to our
practitioners it doesn't restore your
immune system doesn't come back in a
week or a day your immune system doesn't
come back in three days or four days
critical electrolytes don't even come
back that fast and we're already
deficient so we get more deficient so we
get the blood drawn all the time and
then we're getting more deficient and
more deficient it doesn't just all
restore in three days or five days you
just can't have everything fixed you get
the blood work we just lost critical
needed macro minerals those don't get
restored really fast
and then
our cbc doesn't get restored very fast
because we're sick to begin with we're
already deficient we've already have a
low immune system we already have a
struggling immune system if you guys are
sick we're already struggling so
the blood the the blood podcast blood
draw podcast the medical mean podcast
apple podcast is important to actually
listen to someday when you guys get a
chance
that's an important thing to listen to
but i love celery juice because of all
the different things it does including
helping restore the adrenals and
everything if you guys
are yeah i know so many of you guys are
doing celery juice i know that i'm so
proud of you truly i really am proud of
all you guys anyway the juicer just so
you know the sale is not going to last
too much longer and i don't want people
you know having to pay full price
because everybody's going to ask me
what's you know you're the celery juice
guy what
what juicer do you use to be like well
you just missed the sale it's 50 off now
okay and then you can get uh celery
juice book with it
for free two glass bottles
you got that too
and uh you guys i'm gonna go live
back on tick tock back on telegram
and ig instagram so i'm going there in a
little bit and we're going to be live
again so i hope to see you guys
guys come on over we'll have some fun
it's gonna be great