[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now now what
we're talking about today is more than
decades ahead of what's out there now
and it's unfortunate because we're
talking about trigeminal neuralgia and
here we are in this day and age in what
year we're in with the technology we
have and the so-called science to the
degree we have and I'm not mocking
science to the point where hey we don't
have the best technology for for you
know computers and everything else and
everything else that meaning it could
get better I'm sure and better and
better each year as the years go on of
course and but I'm trying to say
something about chronic illness it's
disastrous absolutely disastrous
trigeminal neuralgia is a prime example
of how we're helpless in chronic illness
without the right answers and and as far
as science and research goes forget it
with trigeminal neuralgia it's just you
know just offering a drug um and boom
that's about it maybe two drugs uh maybe
some sleeping pills for people who are
suffering from it that's it no answers
to what it is what causes it what's
going on there there is there is some
information going around now that's just
seeping in the medical communities
because of my information in medical
medium book one about trigeminal
neuralgia and so we're going to explore
that today so we've been able to help
spirit and eye and it's been a it's been
a big deal when you think about it we've
been able to crack the case of course
because you know I've always had answers
for people suffering with trinal
neuralgia I always have and so it's time
the whole world knows because there's
that many people suffering it's that
devastating it could be mild versions to
to really serious versions it's it's
unbelievable unbelievable what people go
through if you got it if you're dealing
with trinal neuralgia you know what I'm
talking about and we're not going to
take it lightly okay we're not going to
I'm going to try to keep a sense of
humor the best I can today but I get I
get upset when I know where science and
research is with chronic illness in
certain areas and so I have tolerance
for certain areas that it's that that
they're just they're backwards in or
they're going the wrong direction
there's tolerance you know blaming
everything now on genes when that's
actually not the not the problem with
with autoimmune disease you know things
like that I I have tolerance for that to
some degree but when mostly women who
are suffering with trigeminal neuralgia
plenty of men too it's it's it's like a
torture a torture you just no one
understands no one gets it unless
they've had it unless they've had it no
one understands the torture that
trigeminal neuralia puts people into and
what's torturous about it a couple a
couple of things not only the pain and
the agony we're going to discuss all the
symptoms about it too not only all that
but also not knowing what it is what's
causing it just guessing games out there
and no real answers no remedies and and
that's what makes it really difficult we
got remedies we got answers we got them
here at this show and there's a reason
why we got him in this show because this
is the only show the only show where the
information here isn't repackaged or
recycled Theory that's been going around
out there among the medical communities
both alternative and conventional
recycled repackaged garbage over and
over and over again scrambled like
scrambled eggs on the internet and in
books it's ridiculous it really is this
is the only Health show where the
information is not tampered with it
doesn't come from interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botch research lobbyists medical
lobbyists internal Kickbacks persuaded
belief systems private panel of
influence ERS health field health field
payoffs and or trendy traps I'm going to
say that in front of every show because
first of all you need to know this
information is clean it is clean it's
how you can heal when you know it's
clean it's important to understand that
it's important to know thumb hasn't been
on the scale of any of this information
to persuade it if you knew how much
money is invested it's investors and did
you ever make an investment into
anything at all did you invest into
anything I mean the simplest thing did
you ever invest into a used car did you
ever invest into something at all when
you invest in something you buy a used
car okay you're in you're you're you're
invested you paid money for that you
paid $5,000 or whatever it is for that
used car and it matters to you what the
outcome of that car is going to be
through its duration how it's how you're
driving it and everything else it
matters matters and what happens in the
medical field and alternative arts and
heal in in the conventional Arts there's
Investments going into into Endeavors
medical Endeavors and it has to come out
a certain way or they will never invest
again in that area or the lab
technicians or the doctors will never
receive a penny again for all their
life's work if something doesn't come
out even partially in somebody's favor
this is how it's done in alternative and
conventional
medicine and this is why the information
is skewed wrong backwards going in a
backwards Direction in every way
possible and guess who suffers people
with trigeminal neuralgia and guess who
else was suffers people with hashimotos
thyroiditis wrote a book about that plus
a whole bunch of other things if you
haven't gotten a thyroid book yet I I
don't know what to say just please
please please get it because it's not
just the thyroid there's over a hundred
symptoms and conditions I explain what
causes them and I go into more than
anybody knows about the thyroid and
everything else information is never
ever even been heard before out there so
it's important um and I don't even talk
about half of what's in there a fraction
of what's in there on the radio so
that's something to think about so you
have to understand one thing in order to
have answers for something like trinal
neuralgia it can't be contaminated it
can't be contaminated by all the groups
I just mentioned that run alternative
and conventional medicine and the
citations and the studies from all that
alternative and conventional medicine is
all contaminated it's skewed and
contaminate I'm sorry to say it it just
is I have to be straightforward about
this of I'm not you're not going to know
where to go and you be swimming around
in the merry around something I wrote
about musical chairs in the merry ground
in the health field and that is not fun
at all all the information here comes
from a pure untampered Advanced Clean
Source a higher source I was given the
gift for and you know some people don't
like the fact I was given a gift at the
beginning when I was a child I I I hated
the gift because because it wasn't for
me it wasn't for me cuz every time I'd
be like wow I got a gift I'm you know
and spirit be like it's not this gift
isn't for you this gift is for everybody
else this gift is for people who have
trinal neuralgia this gift is for people
who are dealing with all kinds of
autoimmune diseases this people that are
dealing with all kinds of mystery
symptoms and conditions which is every
autoimmune disease as far as Medical
Science understands it's all mystery I
don't care if they name it I don't care
what they say about it it's a mystery to
them 100% they make you think it's not a
mystery so you feel things are under
control but that's not how works it's a
demented system I'm sorry but it is and
it's really sad and I was given the gift
and when when I was a child and you know
as I was growing up you know I couldn't
say oh great I got this gift it's is so
great spirit said no it's for everybody
else the gift is for everybody else but
it makes it makes people in the in the
places certain places in the world that
believe in certain belief systems in the
medical Arena whether it's science
research whether it's alter medicine
whatever it is it makes them angry it
makes them really angry to know I got an
in on something no one else
has so they they just you know they lash
they lash out they lash out been dealing
it with my whole life especially now
because especially now at this day and
age now because there's so many people
healing there's so many thousands of
healing people healing not just the
thousands I've healed in personal
oneon-one for 30 years plus okay worked
on more people worked on more people
youever go to the doctor's office and
there'd be like a crowd of people in the
waiting room okay I did that from 6:00
in the
morning and you know if I was lucky 700
in the morning it would start but it did
at 6:00 in the morning till midnight
with that crowd in the in those rooms
seven days a week I went three four five
six years without even Christmas off or
a half a day off not even Christmas Eve
off and that's what I did for years and
years and years and years I've helped
more people and anybody has who's had
the length of career that I've had and
I'm saying this so you know where I come
from and where I'm coming from in half
those years I did it for nothing until I
almost died from it because I couldn't
even buy food and I couldn't even pay my
rent and I couldn't even keep a car even
though I couldn't drive I always had
somebody drive for me because you know
I'd be doing readings on the highway be
getting readings all the time and I got
to be careful because if I'm if you know
if I'm driving and stuff I'm at a stop
light I'll get readings from somebody on
the right side of me readings from
somebody on the left side of me spirit
will be telling me what's wrong with
anybody and in the old days I'd be
tempted to wave them down and say hey
look did you ever get this checked out I
don't do that anymore you can't do that
anymore you could do that in the old
days you couldn't do it now so the deal
is sorry about the long-winded beginning
we're going to get the trial neuralia
trust me and we're going to really cook
into it I I promise we're going
to but the point is is that yeah is is
when you're given a gift and you guys
got gifts I'm sure you do and I'm sure
somebody's been jealous about your gift
too because everybody has a gift of
their own but when it comes down to
chronic illness and science and research
is lack of understanding of it and
doctors that actually spend all this
money and they go to school and I love
all doctors but they go to school they
spend all this money and they're not
given what they need for medical school
both alternative and Convention
we're in a bad place we're in a bad
place and tri neurologist sufferers it's
a prime example I'm saying this because
if you only knew if you're someone who
hasn't dealt with it if you only knew
what it's like you could not imagine why
something's not being done about it in
the field of medicine you could only you
could just you can't even
imagine so when someone can't sleep for
4 days in a row and they got to be
drugged to go to sleep because they have
pain on the side of their face on the
side of their head they got burning on
their tongue and burning on their mouth
they got they got shooting stabbing
knives going into their
ears and they can't sleep for 3 4 days
and they're they literally have to be
drugged if you only knew what that was
like and I hope you never do and then o
only and then you'd say why on God's
Earth on God's green earth why the heck
is something not being done about this
plus a whole bunch of other diseases and
illnesses and symptoms and mysterious
conditions how come and I say to Spirit
still every day I say to Spirit why am I
half why am I the one that has to
deliver
this why am I the one that has to do
this and like I said I've helped people
for decades and did it for free for
decades and decades and then I had to
eventually charge to some degree and
then I had to get some donations through
the years when you know and just to stay
alive to help people 3:00 in the morning
mommies would be bringing their babies
knocking on the door for answers I'd
never even slept for years and years and
been through hell and helped a lot of
people and doing it and now I just got
to help in different ways I got to do it
through the books and I got to do it
through this way and do it through the
show that's what we're doing we're going
to talk about trinal neuralgia we're
only a few minutes in so bear with me
it's just that some of these things you
know I woke up this morning and I said
people need to know they just need to
know what what someone goes through with
trial neuralgia and they need to know
how how fault faulty and how faulted and
how demented the system is both
alternative and conventional they need
to know that someone said to me hey
you're just all about attacking
conventional
medicine and and it was like it's not
about attacking anything I mean if you
don't stand up for what's wrong
sometimes and it's both alternative and
conventional I said to this person no
it's alternative
too it's alternative to if you don't
stand up to try to correct what's going
wrong then how are you going to help the
children of the children to come of the
children to come of the children to come
how are you going to help how are you
going to do it if you don't stand up if
you don't do something about it so hey
look let's go into uh let's go into the
trinal neuralgia let's go into that so
what does it feel like to begin with I
explained a little bit about it some
people can have just a tingling
sensation constantly on one side of the
face Maybe back of the head on the other
side of the face and just keeping mind a
lot of these symptoms I'm going to tell
you aren't even diagnosed as as trial
neuralgia they're not even diagnosed
that way like a doctor would even know
that's even what that is they'll be
looking for something else so um so and
you and not to mention what people go
through just trying to get a diagnosis
or they go through they get MRIs they
get CAT scans they get they're seeing
you know 10 neurologists they seeing
Specialists it is no picnic man it is no
picnic it's brutal it's brutal I'm I'm
just letting you know and so you can
have these tingle Sensations on the side
of the head you can have a weakness on
the side of the head a weakness where
you're like weak on one side of the head
some doctors be like oh that's that's
multiple sclerosis I mean just it's just
a crapfest out there it's like the wild
west still with no understanding about
what's going on and what causes anything
oh man it just gets me going it gets me
going so so you can have a few different
things going on when you have the
sensations you could have a burning on
the side of the face you could have a
burning in the jaw you could have a
burning on all your gums these are all
different sometimes people have more
than one symptom but there's all
different varieties you get the burning
in the in all in the gums all in the
gums you could burning on one side of
the gums okay one side you could have a
burning on the upper side you could have
a burning burning at the bottom side of
the gums you could have a burning all
through your mouth you could have the
burning on your tongue
only and you can have all that plus pain
you can have all that no pain you can
have just the weakness on one side of
the head you can have the tingles on one
side of the head you can have
devastating pain in the ear okay and the
okay and you can also have and some of
you might have this pains in the corners
at the bottom of the ears
so right at the bottom of the ears I got
my fingers not in my ears but I get the
fingers underneath my ears you know in
the neck and those little delicate
Corners there where we can push in and
you feel your Jawbone the back of your
Jawbone we're talking pain all shooting
down in there and that's brutal I've
seen people suffer for years with that
kind of Agony you can also have pain on
the jaw where it's just a a a sharp pain
like a toothache pain a toothache pain
you can also have have not toothache
pains but and that okay that leads to a
whole another thing I can't tell you how
many people had their teeth drilled
pulled with trinal analia they've had I
mean dentists you know have tried to
remedy these situations have drilled
through teeth good teeth bad teeth
looking for answers you name it have
seen that too many of you probably gone
through that they don't do that as much
anymore a lot of the dentists are
finally catching you know wind a little
bit they're catching catching a little
bit of knowledge where okay this didn't
work I'm not going to do it to this
person
now you can have a sensitivity with all
the teeth where hot cold and then Den is
like well it's kind of like a it's that
you're just a highly sensitive person
with your teeth you know maybe your
enamels weakening no the nerves it's
trial neuralgia it's just a different
variety and different kind a different
variety and different kind of trigeminal
neuralgia all right and so you can you
know so there's so many different it
could hit the eyes transanal neuralgia
can take out an eye hurt the eye make it
go you can't even open you're squinty
you can't even look through
it it's it's it's like that it's like
that it's like
that and you know I mean it go it just
just it goes to all kinds of different
levels all kinds of different levels
okay but here's the bottom line you have
to understand something with trigeminal
neuralgia it's it moves too it moves it
creeps it creeps that's a creeper
okay it could start out small get worse
worse worse worse it can start out
really bad then go down to like a
minimum kind of thing where you're
living with it living with it living
with it and then creep back up again it
could get triggered easy too easily
triggered with just aggravation an
argument with somebody
confrontation with someone can trigger
it and make it just spiral through the
damn roof nobody knows that nobody knows
that they don't only the people that
suffer nobody knows that I don't even
think anybody even is even can register
that one you're you're going along okay
you got the triam neuraly you got the
nerve pain and you got you know whether
it's a side of the face or any of the
symptoms I just said and you're going
along and all of a sudden you got to
talk to somebody that's just they're
just
annoying they're annoying because
they're causing confrontation on purpose
or they're just it's somebody maybe it's
a family member that just has a bone to
pick with you in that moment maybe maybe
it's somebody at work and oh my God it
can just it can just literally pronounce
and bring out the worst of that Tri
germinal neuralgia within minutes within
minutes yeah I know I know it's
unbelievable and and it it's hard on
people it's hard on people I said I know
because Spirit was um tuning into to
somebody actually in the audience um
actually talking that second saying how
that's awful and how bad that is and and
and oh my God and everything and yeah I
know I know it's that bad um here's the
deal it it it not only creeps and moves
but it can get into like I said the eye
area it can get into the head it can get
in the side of the head it can go up to
the top of the head it can go to the
bottom of the head and here's the
problem with trigeminal neur neuralgia
it can run down the
shoulder it can run down the neck it can
run down the shoulder and
neck it can even run down the chest how
can it run down the chest because I'm
going to tell you why because when I
tell you what causes trigal neuralgia
when I tell you what causes it and how
that affects other nerves in the body
like your Vegas nerve that's the first
time I I mean the F first time I brought
the whole Vegas thing to the world
through the books through medical medium
book
one and um teaching people about the
Vagas nerve and how it gets affected by
viral issues you get where we're going
by viral
issues okay cuz we're going somewhere
with that we're heading somewhere with
the viral
issues so the tri the trial neuralgia
can reach the vagus nerve the frenic
nerves frenic nerves are the nerves that
run on each side of the chest and they
run through your chest and they go up
through your neck into your head the
sides of the heads they connect sides of
your head they connect to the trigeminal
nerves eventually find their way with
tiny nerve endings connecting into the
trigeminal
nerves and these frenic nerves run
through the chest and they can tighten
the chest they can cause problems in the
chest they can cause problems in the
shoulders they can cause problems in the
neck and they get in next thing you know
it you got somebody with the worst
trigeminal neuralgia that's getting into
other places like frenic nerve issues
vagus nerve issues and it's getting all
wound into all those
areas
right right I mean some of you I know go
through that there's no question there's
no doubt about
it and what does it do it keeps you at
home it makes it so you can't work some
people work with it on drugs some people
the drugs don't touch it on any level
and they just you know they're they're
they're just living with it every day
with no
answers what we got answers we got
answers today I'm excited about this we
got answers today so I just want to make
sure I cover every symptom the trinal
neuralia can cause I mean it can get the
roof of somebody's mouth I've seen that
before it can get the roof it can get
the back of the tongue it can get the
back of the mullers in the jaw the back
of the jaw and the mullers sometimes
then somebody will say well that's just
you know that's just your mandal you
know your your your mandolin joint
that's just the mandible joint that's
just your mandible joint and there's
going to be like that and um um yeah
don't get that confused with with with a
little fruit the Mandarin orang little
fruit I said but it's the man yeah the
mandible joint there okay so they get
confused with that they say well your
joint's messed up you know you got this
joint and they're now sizing you up you
got the tri ginal neuralgia but they're
sizing up with all the gear all the
mouth gear they're trying to correct
your jawline they're trying to correct
everything you're trying to correct your
bite they got all this going on I've
seen people go through hell with all
that and still not fix it because what
they had was something else which was
viral and nobody knows it's viral they
starting to know now because I put it
out there there if you hear it out there
you're going to get it from thieves
that's stealing the night what I say by
that is it because they won't cite where
they got it from and they got it from me
it's important to cite where you get it
from when you have truthful information
like this in all the shows and all the
books it's important to cite it some
people do some people don't but it's
important it's done I'll tell you why so
the person who's getting help can get to
the source of where all the answers are
for these problems and not get it
confused with a mixed bag in nuts now
because someone's got a bunch of other
belief systems that has no idea about
how drinal NRA works but they're
starting to get wind of it they're
starting to get wind of
it and they're starting to sense it's
viral some doctors are being like I
think this is
viral and it is viral and we're going to
cover which virus and we're going to go
into it deep in the whole bit we're
going to do that now so let's cover into
that so what causes trigeminal neuralgia
it's a virus it's from the herpetic
family it's the only family that can
cause trigeminal neuralgia that can
affect a trigeminal nerve and can affect
Vagas nerves and can in in affect frenic
nerves and can cause the problems I'm
talking about it's the herpetic family
and only the herpetic family and guess
what science and research doesn't even
know any of that it's so important to
know because if you're a new listener
too you're going to be like well where's
he getting the information the internet
no never ever and any book I've ever
written so far you guys any book I've
ever written and I just finished one
that's going to come out later this year
any book I've ever written there's not
one word out of that book that comes
from an internet or another source it's
just from Spirit alone and spirit alone
only these medical books are written
from hearing Spirit speak and that's
what these these medical books are
written how they're
written and that's why we have anwers
for trial neuralia let me tell you some
of the flaws about also about the
industry with with not understanding
something about the herpetic family the
herpetic viruses the herpetic viruses
are the ones that actually flare up
nerves they're also the ones responsible
for lime now if you're if you're angry
about what I just said because you're
saying how can that be bacteria whatever
you don't even know the history of how
it really went from the beginning to
where it went where they decided to call
it bacteria the reason why they called
it bacteria the reason why they did that
because because it sold the treatment it
sold the antibiotics because when it was
diagnosed as viral back in 1973 Lyme
disease was diagnosed as viral back in
1972 and 3 when a whole bunch of the
best doctors knew it was viral 100%
there was no treatment so then nobody
could make any money it was called a
dead duck a dead duck illness that's
what it was called because there wasn't
a penny to be made off lime disease so
back the late 70s came early 80s someone
had to make the bucks so they they
called it bacterial for a reason because
the amount of antibiotics that have been
sold and used for Lyme disease is
unbelievably astronomic you could not
believe the multi multi multi
multi-billions almost touching a
trillion pretty soon on the antibiotic
sales for lime it was the Cash Cow and
it's still kept that way purposely the
industry still keeps it that
way okay but even lime is viral I'm
sorry to say that if you're totally
angry about this right now go to go to
book one and read my lime chapter listen
to the lime show that I also have okay
I'm not saying bacteria aren't present
I'm not saying there isn't any bacteria
I'm not saying any of that I'm just
saying it's the herpetic family that
causes neurological problems please
understand that if you want any help and
you want to help your family and if you
knew how many people were wasted with
Lyme disease over the last 30 5 years
their lives ruined wasted or killed off
themselves because of antibiotics and
the unknowing of the fact that it was
viral you wouldn't believe the disaster
and the wake and the hell that people
went through and the families that were
literally ruined dissembled just
destroyed over not understanding lime
was viral instead believing it was
bacterial greatest disaster in human
history and chronic medicine is that
alone but guess what the people that
came to me over the last 35 years all
got better with lme because it was viral
and spirit knew what to do and they live
their lives and they're happy and
they're still healthy now and that's the
difference and that's why with trial
neuralgia we have to think the same way
and do the same thing because when we
know what's wrong with it we have to
know what to do to heal and get it
better and move it forward and that's
the key and that's how you do it trinal
neuralgia is herpetic family viral
that's what it is it's the only virus
that creates treal neuralgia the Family
itself herpetic family it hits nerves
like frenic and Vegas nerves I said that
already but it's important to hear it
again because it can go right over a lot
of people's heads some people say you
repeat yourself and then some people
said well I didn't understand what you
said I needed you to say it again I
can't win I can't win but I try to
repeat myself where I can't important
places like this this is really
important so how does it work what virus
is it what virus in the herpetic family
it's the shingles virus 100% the
shingles virus now I don't have a lot of
faith in research and Science and
chronic illness I I'll give you an
example research and science still says
out there and they teach all the doctors
this backwards wrong information they
teach the
doctors that the chickenpox is the
shingles so if you had the chickenpox
you got the shingles down the road
they're two different
viruses two different completely
different
viruses so just to think about that
blunder that serious medical blunder all
in its own think about that one right
there then where are we really
going that blunder is so big and it's
not being
corrected okay the chickenpox virus is
one virus in the herpetic family it's
one out of hundreds and hundreds the
shingles is entirely different virus in
the herpetic family and in the shingles
group itself there are over 31 varieties
that I've been able to document with
spirit and help people heal over the
decades and one of those shingles
varieties one of those varieties causes
trigeminal neuralgia it causes the
problem and so here's how it goes you
don't have to have a breakout of
shingles in order to have trial
neuralgia you could have had a breakout
in shingles years ago didn't know little
patch on your leg maybe a little patch
on the arm maybe a little patch on the
breast maybe a little patch on the neck
maybe a little patch behind the ear
maybe a little patch on your back you
could had
that but most people will try geminal
neuralgia don't really get the shingles
breakout some a lot of people do some
people don't many most people
don't but it's a shingles virus that
actually gets to the nerves it's a non
rashing shingles virus that tends to
rash sometimes but I call it non-
rashing because it's not the big rashers
it's not the typical variety I talk
about in medical medium book one with
shingles itself where you get the herpes
zou ripping across your your side
ripping across your lower belly ripping
across your back or your your butt
ripping across there there different
varieties of shingles trino neuralgia is
a whole different variety research and
science doesn't even know about the
different varieties of shingles we're
not even there yet we're so not even
there yet 50 years 60 I'll dead gone you
know whatever and they're still not
going to know and maybe maybe somehow um
you know God God willing God loving God
knowing that the information spreads
that we're putting out there and
something gets done about it you know I
hope to God but anyway the bottom line
is with the trial neuralia VAR variety
of virus the shingles variety that
causes that when you know what's wrong
and you know what it is and you know
what kind of virus it is then you can go
after it then you can go after it it's
not the same virus that causes Bell's
paly Bell's paly where the droop happens
whether the droop in the eye the droop
that's a shingles virus too but it's one
of the 31 varieties it's a different
varieties of shingles it's a different
variety of
shingles some people can have the bells
paly variety and they could have
trigeminal neuralia variety you can have
two some people people have the the
straight herpes Zer variety where that
just rips across their back and their
stomach and then they get trigeminal Nur
neuralgia also which is a different
variety because we can have multiple
varieties of shingles in our body we get
a multiple we can catch a variety of
shingles we can catch a variety of
shingles you know I was just I was
talking about how you know I'm always
I'm always yeah I'm paranoid about
catching things so be only because
Spirit has tortured me by telling me
about the tuberculosis on a plane seat
or the Mera on a plane seat or you know
whatever so I've always always I've
always been you know because it's there
and spirit knows it's there so I've
gotten really weird about stuff so when
I grab door handles in public places I
take my pinky and I go underneath and I
grab it I know I talked about that
before but because yeah I don't want a
variety of Jingles that I don't
need right now I don't because I'm my
forget touch something in a certain way
and stick it in my eye rub my eye cuz
I'm tired all the time because I stay up
late writing the books with Spirit
sometimes when spirit's on a roll we
don't stop I don't care if that takes 30
hours straight of information coming
from Spirit I got to write down and
write down word for word with a pen and
a pencil here's the
deal so let's work on getting it better
and figure out how to get it better for
everybody everybody's going to have a
different situation some shingles
viruses are going to be rooted in pretty
deep they're there a long time some
people have been through a lot of
standard Medical Treatments you know
been through the steroids been through
the different drugs and everything else
and they've gone through a lot so that
doesn't help the situation um that fills
the liver with a lot of medication so
and the shingles is M the shingles its
main home is the liver to start with so
it camps out there that's where it
starts that's where it grows that's
where it does its thing then it launches
off and gets to different areas of the
body and so some people have a track
record of a lot of medications they have
a track record of immune system not
doing good because of it all they got a
track record of a lot of other
situations involved so it takes a little
time to
heal some people it heals fast just a
few weeks some people it takes a couple
of years of being strong and diligent on
what you need to do and you can't lose
sight of what it is you lose sight of
what it is then you don't get better
because you got to know what it is I say
it every time I'm going to say it again
half the battle is knowing what's wrong
the other half is doing what's
right for it that's how you heal that is
how you
heal and so you just have to know that
it's so important and so what's the
first half it's knowing what is it's a
virus it's the hepatic virus it's in the
shingles family it's one of the
varieties of shingles out of the 31 that
caused the flare up can I tell you what
happens when you know the truth can I
tell you what happens your immune system
gets aligned because when there's
confusion in your brain and doubt and
confusion and and and mystery in your
brain and you've been through hell and
you've gone to 10 neurologists and
nobody knows what's going on with you
guess what your immune system doesn't
line up to what's really happening so
it's hard to figure out how to fix it
and you get into a jam and then you get
stuck that's how it
works but when you know you know I hope
you got all that I hope you guys got all
that when you know what what's causing
it your immune system kicks up a notch
because guess what messages get to your
immune system they get to your immune
system that you're in it now you're in
it you're in it to win it you actually
know the culprit you know the Invader
it's not autoimmune it's not your body
attacking itself that's what they're
going to say about trinal neuralgia
pretty soon they probably already do
they probably already do they already
say you know
it's it's the body attacking itself cuz
that's all they got that's all they got
in their bag we're this far along that's
all they
got you know and and and you know and I
believe it's on purpose just call me
call me a little you know funny about
that but I believe it's on purpose
because come on how can we be here this
day and age and have no answers for
autoimmune disease all in of the
hundreds and hundreds of autoimmune
diseases we got no answers for any of it
so you know so here here's the
deal here's the deal so let's let's get
into this and figure this out we're
going to go after the virus once your
mind knows you're going after the virus
that's one big piece of it then we're
going to go after it we're going to use
things to go after it we're going to get
you on the right things you can go to
your practitioner and say here here's
what I
heard here's what I heard I can take
this or do this and this and this is a
shingles virus and your practitioner
you'll find a practitioner that'll be on
board on board listen if you have a
doctor and you really like that doctor
and that doctor is a great doctor but
your doctor doesn't want to know
anything to do with this this shingles
virus and trigeminal neuralgia keep your
doctor keep on going because you know
because I'm sure he or she is really
helpful with all kinds of things but
make sure you go find another one too
and get another one and have two get one
that will understand and listen to
you get one that will understand and
listen to you so you can get better and
then tell that one look this is what
I've heard this is what I know this is
what's going on this is what you know I
need to do just help me with this you
can do that if you if you don't like
being
alone and doing
things so what do we need to do we need
to kill off the virus knock its Army
down what your feeling with all the pain
and everything else is a neurotoxin a
neurotoxin it's a virus the shingles
virus eating a food it likes and then
when it eliminates it eliminates a toxic
poison I talk about in thyroid
healing but I was talking about the
Epstein bar because all herpetic viruses
leech they they they they eliminate a
neurotoxin and they cause different
symptoms different neurological
conditions each each herpetic virus
causes different neurological conditions
the shingles herp virus causes one of
the varieties causes the trinal
neuralgia you're dealing with and when
it releases this
neurotoxin into the bloodstream the
neurotoxin goes to adjacent areas where
nerves
are and the trigeminal neuralgia
shingles virus leaves the liver it likes
to go up into the jaw it likes to go up
into the dral nerves it likes to go into
even the frenic and and and vas nerve
sometimes up in those areas and it likes
to get into the neck and other areas and
it then pees and poos it pees and and
poos when it pees and poos it's peeing
and pooing neurotoxins those neurotoxins
are
extremely allergenic to a
nerve extremely
allergenic and then if you've had an
injury with the jaw or an injury with
any of those nerves or if a dentist
jammed a needle in and it it it it it
really poked hard it went in some
cockeyed way right in that jaw when
you're getting d to work then if the
shingles virus is present in that moment
or kicking around it will find that
little wound and go to it and then
settle in nest in and start working its
way in the nerves and releasing more
neurotoxins flaring up the
nerves this is what the virus
does this is what it does Spirit has
advanced information doesn't
Spirit yeah for sure yeah I was telling
people this when I was a kid and people
their heads would spin all right so
listen here's the
deal we're going to go after the virus
let's talk about what we can use to go
after the virus so you're going to be
slowly killing off the virus it's going
to take time some people have more
levels of the shiggles virus than them
causing more pain some people have less
levels some people have been through a
lot some people have have like I said
they got a lot of toxins in them and the
food they're eating is feeding the virus
okay so eggs I talk about that all the
time how come I don't like eggs because
they feed the shingles virus they feed
every single bug in the body you don't
want in the body especially the herpetic
family get away get away from the dairy
course the
gluten you know what happens with people
and experts in the field of autoimmune
or in the field of alternative medicine
and the book writers and all the other
stuff that put the books out and they
talk about gluten and they don't
understand that your body's not
attacking itself because you're eating
gluten you got a virus that's feeding
off of gluten and then causing problems
the virus is causing problems we're not
even there yet with the latest
alternative experts that are on the
doctor shows and they're doing whatever
they don't even have a clue that that's
how it works to this point it's actually
embarrassing at this
point I just I just we're so far behind
so what happens is when you're eating
that gluten you're feeding the shingles
virus and it's going to be eliminating
more neurotoxins if you have a lot of
heavy metals in your system if you have
heavy metals in your jaw from dental
work from years ago if you have all
these things it can become food too so
you want to be on the heavy metal detox
smoothie so the medical medium heavy
metal detox smoothie I don't trust any
other heavy metal
detoxification treatment on the planet
except for Spirits the heavy metal detox
smoothie I don't trust a single one of
them first of all
Corella which is which is supposedly
supposed to be heral that is God for
removing heavy metals it drops them
nonstop it can't hold on to to heavy
metals it if it even remotely
removes some heavy metal it'll drop it
in the wrongest place after it's grabbed
it so I mean that alone other heavy
metal treatments I don't trust any of
them I'm sorry I only like the one I
have because that one I trust because
it's not a contaminated Source from some
ridiculous belief system out there so
make sure that you're doing the heavy
metal detox smoothie because you want
the heavy metals out because they feed
the shingles virus it's one of the
things the shingles virus likes if
you're big on animal protein minimize it
I would even consider and it just this
isn't
because I want you to be plant-based you
know someone said oh you just want
everybody plant-based that's not true I
just want while you're six something to
be done right in the right way from the
information I have and then you go on
your Merry way you want to eat all the
animal protein you want later on when
you're better go do it have fun
and you know that's not it just I would
with some real trienal neurologist
sufferers I would just back off the
animal protein altogether just just just
just get rid of it you know it's not
about becoming a vegan it's not about
what it's just it's just get rid of it
all get your trigeminal neurologia
better get rid of all the different
animal proteins the chicken the wood
because what happens is is it's not that
chicken feeds a shingles virus causing
the trigeminal neuralgia is that chicken
will just be a it it won't be doing it
won't be helping to heal it so do you
have time do you have time to waste
you're dealing with your trigeminal
neuralgia for years or for six months or
for a month do you have time to waste
you want it to last another year or two
or three keep on eating chicken because
it takes the space of something else
that can actually heal your problem
because when it comes down to all the
different fruits and vegetables
including potatoes especially
potatoes that's a great one for triin on
neuralgia potatoes it's an incredible
one credible food it's got a hell heck
of a lot of line content extremely high
bioavailable line that you can't even
get when you take line which you should
take while you have trinal neuralgia too
is lyine and in the potato it's got an
answer for helping to stop the shingles
virus so when you don't eat a potato
because all these Trends these new
trends are ripping apart nightshades
again and ripping apart a
potato when you don't eat that because
of an an idiotic Trend that's out there
now because say like eltin Trend or
whatever it is you're going to keep your
trinal neurologia around that's how it
works that's how Trends work that's why
they're tricky remember at the beginning
of the show you remember at the very
beginning when I said at the very
beginning I said trendy traps I said or
trendy traps trendy traps prevent
healing they come out constantly because
it's something that someone can hang
their hat on the the lectin guys are
going to hang their hat hat on the the
fructose intolerance guys are going to
hang their hat on someone needs to hang
their hat on a trend it doesn't matter
if you suffer for the rest of your life
they'll hang that
hat as long as it's something to hang
their hat
on but so forget the potato thing being
bad it's actually important for
trigeminal neurologist sufferers because
it helps get rid of the shingles virus
guess what if anybody knew if any trendy
person knew expert out there knew what
caused trigemino neuralgia that would
just be the start a little inkling of
what they would need to know but you got
the information here I say this because
I'm determined
with spirit and me determined with the
passion and the caring and the wanting
you to heal determined for you to know
that and I worry if you're going to get
distracted instantly the minute you hop
on the internet the minute you see some
other book the minute you and then you
get stuck with your trigeminal neuralgia
for years back when in the old days I'm
going to tell you right now in the old
days and somebody came to me with trinal
neurologia they weren't distracted they
were able to heal and able to heal fast
because they weren't distracted Because
the Internet wasn't even born yet
because because literally there weren't
any you know there weren't any health
books out there you couldn't get
distracted I'm not saying everything's
all bad and all Health books are bad I'm
not saying that at all I'm just saying
you couldn't get distracted from what
you were
doing and so it was hey this is what's
going on here's the advanc information
here it is the year 19 1990 whatever or
19 1991 here it is the year 1994 the
1997 here's what you need to do here's
your protocol that's right get your
tramal nervia better it's the shingles
virus bam you're better done you're not
distracted and now it's hard it's hard
for people all they have to do is just
turn the wrong way and someone's saying
some some cockamamy thing and that's the
problem so in order to heal trigeminal
neuralgia you have to get that corrected
too you have to stay on point and you
have to stay diligent and you got to
stay with it because you're going to get
lost out there and it hurts me to know
that because I know what it's like to
suffer because I've been given the gift
to actually tap into that with people
and I know the with the compassion and
everything else I'm not saying I'm the
most compassionate person out there I'm
not saying that at all it's just Spirit
has basically placed upon me throughout
my life a little sensitivity extra
sensitivity inside of me to actually
know and sense and feel somebody's
suffering that's
right a little bit more so than the
average bear and I've had to Bear it and
the whole point
is I want you better because I know what
you're dealing with I know what you're
dealing with and I want you better so
here's the deal line get the line take a
lot of it 4,000 milligrams twice a day
that's what I would do talk to your
doctor talk to your doctor but I would
do like 4,000 milligrams twice a day if
you want to do one 500 milligrams your
sensitive person talk to your doctor
talk to your practitioner talk to the
person that helps you talk to your
health coach talk to the person that
helps you and start out with 500
milligrams that's just what I would do I
would do a lot you know I would do a lot
more I would do about you know 3 4,000
milligrams if you
can and then you know I still would eat
potatoes and I would go plant-based you
get your trigeminal neuralgia better go
back to your Animal product diet if you
want stay off of dairy stay off of eggs
stay off of all the things I talk about
in the medical medium book stay away
from canola oil stay stay away from soy
stay away from yes stay away from soy
you better believe it stay away from
soy stay away from pork pork is
disastrous
disastrous for for people with chronic
illness stay away from it but when
you're dealing with treem Neurology you
want to be plant-based if it's too heavy
and too scary start small do one Animal
product a day one Animal product a day
that's all that's all just do one a day
okay so we need some herbs too we need
some herbs Mullen Leaf Mullen Leaf
alcohol-free of course go to my
directory always go to my directory if
you want to know the safe supplements
supplements that are safe I'm not
selling supplements just know that it's
there for you so you know where to get
what to get the safe ones so you get the
you get the Mullen Leaf can take a good
few Dro or fulls of that no problem if
you're sensitive do less always talk to
your practitioner and doctor I'm just
telling you right now you can do the
Mullen Leaf that's a big one all right
the pro that's a huge one propolis is an
amazing weapon against your gemino
neuralgia all right that's an amazing
weapon against it without without a
doubt lemon bomb still a great weapon
licorice root incredible
weapon these are these are these are
amazing for treino neuralgia piarco pod
Arco okay get
piarco that's a great one right there
vitamin C take a lot of it you can you
got two options you got the liposome
vitamin C the one that I like the good
one the leposa company I love that
company did you know they took out they
took out any bad ingredients they they
they literally redesigned their
liposomal SE to stand above all the
other liposomal CES all the other ones
so make sure you go and you check out
which one that is on the directory all
right make sure you got some chaga
powder all right you know which one to
go to there my favorite is vimergy
that's the one I use every day and and
whatever barley grass juice powder I use
the vimergy barley grass juice powder in
my smoothie every single day so that's
the right one too and you know do the
heavy metal detox smoothie make sure you
got all the right things spirina is
incredible for trigeminal neuralia you
know why spirina helps restore the
damaged nerves from the neurotoxins from
the shingles virus that's why spirina is
amazing you know there's people out
there that say oh spirina is bad or
whatever there's you know trendy stuff
goes around someone's always trying to
just rain on somebody's parade meanwhile
you steal and Rob someone's ability to
heal and that's what that's why I call
them thieves they steal the ability for
somebody to heal that's another thing
too honest to God it's just so frightful
out there with that spirulina can help
somebody with trigeminal neuralgia the
B12 the right kind of B12 it has to be
adoil kabalin and methyl kabalin I was
the first one on that whole thing first
one on that whole thing it's the adino
cell with the methal K balamin it's the
only way to get the trigeminal nerve is
better there the methylfolate you do the
methylfolate that's helpful for trial
neuralgia MSM a little bit of
MSM that one's also really good little
bit of that so you can get a little of
that in you which is really helpful a
little bit of olive leaf I always find
is helpful too cat's claw cat's claw you
want cat's claw for trinal neuralgia
could take a couple of drop or fulls of
that every day it's really important
that's a great one people with
trigeminal neuralgia also always have a
whole bunch of other other things going
on with your health I'm sure you know
this you know a thyroid problem can
creep up other things can happen the
whole bit and so when you compile the
trigeminal neuralgia the pain and the
suffering and the agony that goes along
with that and you compile that with
other things going on your health it is
unbearable and I really understand I'm
with you man I'm praying with you you're
going to get better I don't care what it
takes we're going to do it and you just
got to keep a light heart got to keep a
light heart throughout the process with
everything you got you know people who
deal with chronic illness and they're
suffering with chronic illness man
they're just like it's unbelievable what
kind of souls people are where they just
they push ahead they Forge ahead they
fight for it they fight for it like no
other like no other talking about
spiritual growth it pushes spiritual
growth like no other no other I don't
care if somebody's sitting on top of a
mountain top and they got their hands
folded and they're just you know and
they got their legs crossed and they're
just you know they're on they're seeking
spiritual enlightenment let me tell you
something people who are chronically ill
chronically suffered who have been
through hell and back have gone through
so
much that's the kind of Enlightenment
that supersedes all the mountain tops
anybody can go be marching on to and
doing not saying don't do that I'm just
saying for people I'm glad you're doing
it I'm just
saying talking about walking over coals
talking about walking over hot coals I'm
just going to tell you right now people
who have actually suffered with real
problems with real things going on with
their health neurological problems with
things xiety and everything else which
trigeminal neuralgia can create a lot of
anxiety it can all be part of that
because of the different frenic nerves
involved in the Vegas nerves what people
go through walking on coals is a joke
it's a damn
joke all
right anyway the bottom line is so what
else can we do for it um so we got we
got some of the herbs we can do for it
okay um licorice root for sure that's a
secret weapon to it without a doubt for
dral neuralgia turmeric that's a great
one too you want to consider that one to
bring that one in and we're dealing with
a virus so these are really good
antivirals zinc zinc is a winner for
trienal neuralgia it's a winner for this
it's a winner because zinc deficiencies
allow shingles to be rampant and go
crazy in the whole bit make sure like I
said you do the heavy metal detox
smoothie that that's happening no matter
what make sure some people they can put
cold on there and it and it works and
then some people can't even have to cold
touch them some people can put warmth on
their face or their head or the side of
their head or their neck and sometimes
that can touch it and sometimes it can't
people have gone through the gamma with
all this it's disheartening and and it's
it's just unbelievable unbelievable what
people do um Elderberry syrup that's
helpful too you could take a little
Elderberry syrup that's helpful okay
Elder Elder flow tea can be helpful
elderflower tea that can be helpful with
trigeminal neuralgia so consider that
one too listen I'm with you I wish these
shows were longer um because I I just
could talk all day to everybody here get
started on that to begin with if you get
started on that you're going to be on
the road to Healing on the road to
getting past this you're going to be
getting there get it started on that I'm
going to do another followup trial
neurologist show and I'm going to see
where everybody's at I'm going to try to
do a read all the way out there and see
if we need to cover anything more but
people are going to start getting better
I love you I care about you guys God
bless you one day at a time bye-bye