hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now this is
the only Health show anywhere that has
information where it doesn't come from
interest groups medical funding with
strings attached botched research
lobbyists internal Kickbacks persuaded
belief systems private panel of
influencers health field payoffs are
trendy traps that are common in
conventional and guess what alternative
Comm medical communities all the
information here I share comes from a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
Source a higher source the spirit of
compassion there nothing more healing
than compassion and the reason why I say
this that this is the only show because
information out there and I have to
remind new people that are listening to
the show information out there there has
cross-contamination or contamination
from long ago attached to it like for
instance if you ever hear my metabolism
show you'll know that metab metabolism
all on its own is totally totally you
know it's it's complet completely
there's flaws everywhere there's holes
in it everywhere it's an ancient it's an
ancient realization that our bodies are
alive and functioning and it was
ingrained in the early medical schools
the
universities
globally long ago and then it it got
grandfathered in his law so now there's
even lots and lots of metabolism books
coming out now constantly and just so
you know it's not even feasible
everybody burns calories differently and
at different times you can't gauge that
that's not even gauge B and that's part
of metabolism there's a lot of other
things that are wrong with metabolism we
talked about but I'm using that as an
example of how when something's
grandfathered in because of early
funding early funding that's usted
grandfather law documents that you guys
don't even realize that are sitting in
vaults in ancient University vaults that
you can't mess with so metabolism will
live on forever and nobody will even get
it and realize that it's a liver problem
that it's problems with the body you
know that the all kind we talk about on
the metabolism show we're going to talk
about it again but that's just one prime
example another prime example is
Hashimoto till this day until I brought
forward that the body doesn't attack
itself okay because that's grandfathered
in that's grandfathered in from the
1950s that that autoimmune is your body
destroying itself that's grandfathered
Ino this is because of early funding
that went into something and it's
poisoned because it's wrong information
and the best experts in in thyroid
Health right now are still putting out
information that sure they're saying hey
it's triggers they're finally picking up
on that hey it's this and that you eat
better you start getting a little bit
better your numbers get a little bit
better on your thyroid but they still
think the body's attacking itself
instead of what I've been teaching all
along that there's an Invader and a
virus that gets inside the thyroid that
literally is the sole reason for
hypothyroidism and and and Hashim Modas
and everything but these are examples of
how it's all contaminated I'm sorry to
say it's sad to say there's nothing I
can do about it besides give you guys
the truth all the time and give you guys
Advanced information that doesn't have
prec contamination that everybody's
still passing around and that's why
you're listening to the show that is why
you're here listening to the show so
that's the whole point it's what I'm
trying to say so um check out the
thyroid book that's coming check it out
you know hey you know lock it down so
you don't forget um and and and get a
copy now that's that's that you know
it's going to take a little while to get
to you because it's you know said still
with that pre-order but but lock it down
you don't want to you don't want to miss
out on this and I got to tell you
something about the thyroid book just so
you know I'm not sitting here blowing
hot air about this thing and um if any
of you have had read medical medium book
one or life-changing Foods you know that
I I I try not to fall short with
information you know when spirit and I
we do these books it's not just some one
concept or two concept and we just you
know we run away with that one or two
concepts and we sit on it and throughout
the whole book and then you know sure
you get a couple of goodies we don't
want that we want hundreds of goodies
this book here I mean it was painstaking
painstaking what what I had to do with
Spirit to get this information to you
about what happens when you don't have a
thyroid what happens when your thyroids
missing what happens when you know you
you've had it surgically removed how it
still can't stop you from healing and
still can't stop you because of
information has never been out there
before of how it works about how there's
still tissue left over even after
surgically REM be being removed or when
it's get radioactive iodine kofs of how
you can still bring your thyroid back
and fix it that's just one the
Undiscovered hormones also that no
expert knows about that Spirit has
blessed me with the Undiscovered
hormones that your thyroid really has
that does more than T3 and T4 that's in
this book you can also how the thyroid
your own healthy thyroid can help
someone's unhealthy thyroid heal you
can't just lock it down if you're if
you're hearing this now go go to you
know whever you got to go to the web go
to the the medical medium page lock it
down and get a copy coming to you I'm
just so proud of it because I know
what's going to happen is you we and
intended this book so you can become an
expert I mean that's the whole goal is
you become that expert so so you become
Unstoppable for so many reasons and even
if you're not helping anybody in the
moment you don't know what's going to
happen in the future you don't know who
you're going to inspire who you're going
to help and this thyroid book isn't just
even about thyroid so if you're saying
hey I don't care about thyroid I don't
got a thyroid problem I don't know
anybody with a thyroid problem this is a
waste of my time that's not it this
thing is so packed with so many other
things so you just you can't go wrong
anyway I'm telling you because I'm
excited and I'm excited because it's
it's going to change lives and more so
than just uh you know uh getting the
diet clean um which information out
there you get the diet clean get rid of
processed food you know take a few
supplements for your thyroid you you
know the whole bit no this is above and
beyond I want you to know this um today
we're we're talking about Parkinson's
Parkinson's disease Parkinson's is a
funny thing because it it really
shouldn't even have its own name it
shouldn't have Parkinson's disease it
shouldn't be what it is there are
hundreds of neurological mystery
conditions what's the cause of
Parkinson's out there unknown
unknown exactly
unknown that's the cause of Parkinson
out there here we are in this day and
age where we sit now it's unknown
because guess what in medical research
and medical science and medical
communities I'm just going to tell you
right now all chronic illness is unknown
I'm sorry but all chronic illness is
unknown it's not unknown here at the
medical Medium show not because I'm a
wizard a smart you know a smart Wizard
and I got 20 million
degrees you know in medicine and and
everything else that's not it at all
that's not it at all it's it's because
of the information The Source I get it
from a source that I've helped heal and
helped recover people and and and and
recover and restore lives and bring
their lives back in in third for 35
years and maybe even more since I was a
little kid a little baby a four years
four years of age and so the whole point
here about this show is exactly like
Parkinson's disease it shouldn't even
have its own name it should just be
called unknown mystery symptoms once
again let's be honest let's get out of
medical denial it's so painstaking I
can't even tell you I go through waves
waves in my life you guys waves where I
just I just you know bite my lip and I
and I say all right I I fine fine I get
it um no one knows what's wrong with
anybody I get it except when it's
mechanical I get it okay um yeah I could
live with that let's Forge ahead Spirit
let's Forge ahead keep on helping people
and then it and it eats me up sometimes
and then and then I I kind of let it out
I let it out and it's absurd it's just
nonsense the way it works with chronic
and mystery illness I'm not talking
about I'm not talking about if you need
a if you need you know a tooth filled at
the dentist office I'm not talking about
if you really have a heart valve problem
because it's damaged maybe damaged
mysteriously and mechanical problem
could be mysteriously damaged absolutely
mysteriously damaged viruses get into
people's hearts and cause damage in the
valves and the ventricles and and and
that's what happens and and hey maybe
medicine and research and science
doesn't know why doesn't know why or
maybe somebody's diet is so bad that
they're just getting you know they're
just getting fats fats just caked inside
their heart and inside their veins and
inside their arteries for too long and
you know and and this stuff is just
growing in there and breaking off and
causing heart attacks and problems like
that that and and believe it or not even
partially that's a mystery even though
it's it's it's not so mysterious
depending on
diets but the point is is even though
medicine you know today in science has
incredible things thank God and they're
still moving forward including
alternative medicine still moving
forward and and and thank goodness for
this we're still in a world of mystery
with the health and we really are there
are children all across this country
alone never mind globally that are sick
and they're all just well by the way
they're all just being thrown into the
lime trap that's where it all goes now I
got to keep on saying that because
that's where it's all going now 15 years
from now everybody's going to on the
planet's going to have Lyme disease and
every mysterious illness and condition
people are just going to throw their
hands up in the air and it's going be
like it's Lyme disease when it's not but
I got to tell you so when it comes down
to neurological problems and you'll look
at Parkinson's it's a hot mess it is
such a
hot hot freaking mess it's not even
funny it's it's that bad it's one of
those just like ALS is a hot mess and we
talk about that we talked about that
with the ALS show and with Parkinson's
Parkinson used to originally started out
where it's this Tremor someone's got a
Tremor they got a shake you know their
head's shaking um their leg shaking
uncontrollably it's getting real stiff
their arms shaking their hand shaking
tremoring tremoring and and gets in the
way of functioning and then the
neurological meltdown occurs uh years
later or anything like that and that's
that's what it originated
with but now even even medicine has to
back itself up it has to protect itself
so grandfathered law medicine has to say
well you know wait a minute you know the
the the best clinics are discovering
that Parkinson's is also these other
things that you know little bit of
dementia uh some delusion some psychosis
well wait a minute wasn't that other
other illnesses that were diagnosed
differently back in the past we we you
mean you're bringing those in now so you
were wrong about Parkinson's to begin
with so wrong that now you guys got to
bring in other crap that's going on with
people so you got to be bringing in
other symptoms other conditions you got
to bring up other mysterious symptoms
conditions neurologically that you have
no clue no matter what's going on in the
best clinics I won't mention the clinics
to just just dial in best medical
clinics and three will come up four will
come up it's a joke it's a total total
total joke and you know and that and and
by the way I've known people that had to
come to me over the last few decades
that have been to every Clinic those
best clinics over and over again and
just the the answers they get at these
clinics I used to get and still get now
I mean would just make your head spin I
swear to God maybe you maybe you're one
of them maybe you're one of them I mean
those clinics originally used to tell
people they were the king of telling
people they had nothing wrong with them
it's all in your head and you need to
you're bored you need to get a job you
need to do something with your life they
were the king of that then they they
they try to elevate they try to advance
then they brought in all the holistic
people in there the clinics now are kind
of a hash Posh and it's just
unbelievable but see what happened was
it was a failure with Parkinson's just
like a failure with so many other
illnesses I'm being harsh today I'm
being harsh today oh my my God I'm being
harsh today listen I can't help it I
can't help it you you guys got to
understand I can't help it sometimes
sometimes it just you know it's so
ridiculous for real so it was a failure
so now they had to bring up bring in all
these other items call items all these
other conditions all these other
symptoms and they kind of the reason why
is because the minute something starts
to
stink something starts to stink and that
grandfather-in-law starts to stink way
too much it's it's it's time it es and
flows a little differently so then you
know modern medicine starts saying well
you know no Parkinson's is is more than
just Tremors you got you got uh you got
delusion you got hallucinating you got
psychosis
Neurosis um you got uh aches and pains
aches and pains aches and
pains okay
okay aches and
pains you know you know what I'm you
know what I'm getting at right they have
to throw that one into
that what a mess up mystery aches and
pains that yes are neurological nerve
pain but throw it into the Parkinson's
package now because it was a failure
diagnosis and a failure understanding
everything about it is
flawed no answers completely unknown
just like everything else including
autoimmune yeah that's right that's
right and so why don't we throw in aches
and pains how about that how about them
how about those apples how about them
apples how do you like those apples so
you know and by the way apples are
really good for Parkinson's apples are
really good for Parkinson's let's not
forget that right now I got to remember
that hey here's the
deal here's the deal there's so many
different neurological conditions and
symptoms they're all mystery they're all
mystery unless you've been hit by a
car they're all mystery unless you fell
off a building they're all mystery
unless you know you fell on your face on
a sidewalk which happens to everybody at
some time in their life I don't care who
it is you know and and you know they're
they're all mystery unless you know you
get chemical poisoned chemically
poisoned someone spraying you know
pesticides and fertilizer your neighbors
got fertilizer going in you know
pesticides going in their lawn you don't
have that in your lawn but they got it
going in their lawn your an apartment
building and you walk outside and some
guy's sitting there with a tank on the
back on his back and he's got a sprayer
in his hand he doesn't see you and he
sprays you right in the face as you walk
by which happens all the time 3 days
later that person's getting mystery
neurological symptoms but there's a
reason for that if they know how to
connect the dots to
that and you know these are all injuries
they're
injuries yeah that's right that's right
that's right so here's here's the deal
here's the deal so if you've been
diagnosed with label lime disease
neurological lime how do you like that
one now exactly it goes there
Parkinson's and that's the whole thing
too just so you know a lot of the
Parkinson's crowd is getting thrown into
lme they they're they're going they
Doctor shopping you get a lot of
Parkinson's people they're Doctor
shopping they get get to a lime doctor
and guess what they're diagnosed with
they don't have Parkinsons they've had
lime the whole time you know I just you
know what can I take a second out and
bang my head on the desk right now I'd
like to do
that and here here's the deal here's the
deal so you know so a lot of the a lot
of the multiple scos people they're all
multiple sclerosis people they're all
getting thrown into this doctor
searching I didn't have M mess this
whole time oh wait a minute I've had
lime this whole time it's
painful
painful because they've suffered as it
is and and suffered as it is and I get
it a new diagnosis can be refreshing and
I get that I totally get that don't I'm
not making I'm not jabbing at that that
part I'm jabbing at the fact that it's
it's still nobody knows what's going on
they don't that's why we do this show
that's why we do this
show so what creates neurological
problems what creates
Parkinson's what do we do there you know
and and to begin with we have to talk
about what's happening in the brain
something got into the brain something
got into the brain and and things get
into the brain mildly with all kinds of
neurological problems you can have a
virus in your liver like Epstein bar
just a virus in your liver it's not in
your brain it's in your liver it's
releasing a poison and science and
research has no idea about this this is
so ahead of their time so Advanced you
know you know it's part of how you know
part of why I have to say it this way
it's because it's that bad out there
it's that bad out there know you when
you put out book one the medical meum
you think the world's going to change
I'm like okay Spirit I'll put this out
the world's going to change all at once
it's not going to change all at once I
still see some of the best practitioners
best practitioners out there meaning the
most advanced experts out there they
even have a clue what's in book one many
of many of them do but many of them
don't even have a clue what's in book
one so they're out there just talking
the same old crap the same old crap it's
like how do you change how do you turn
it around I'll tell you how keep on
moving forward get the thyroid book
because you wouldn't believe what I put
in there to help change the that's it
we're just going to Title Wave this
thing we're going to move it forward
together I'm needing your help I need
your help I need your help so don't
don't forget to lock down that book
don't forget lock it down now so you
don't forget later I've seen that happen
all the time because and look go to my
blog read the articles look at the
Instagram stories all the time look at
the Instagram stories of people healing
just you know come on in and join in
join the party with me I need your help
I I that I need your help I really do
and so we can do this together so we can
move this
forward so here's how it works when it
comes down to Parkinson's or any kind of
symptom that's being thrown into any of
these things you can have a virus inside
the liver sitting there could be hhv6 it
could be shingles it could be Epstein
bar most of the time Epstein bar loves
to sit in there and and release poisons
and when that Poison's released you
could get stiffness in the body they can
be like stiff you can also get a little
fatigue because it's just poison
floating around there irritating the
nervous
system you can get aches and
pains just from a simple little bug
sitting in the liver no big deal no big
deal there's no Panic there's no
Parkinson's there no Parkinson's at
all and what happens is the Tremor of
Parkinson's the Tremor of Parkinson's
the shakiness you guys is heavy metals
in the brain it's heavy metals in the
brain so if you're someone that's got
some serious mercury in the brain which
they're never going to ever really admit
yeah you can go to clinics find a
holistic doctor be like you know you got
you know elevated we're doing a hair
analysis you got to elevated toxic heavy
metals but it's still never going to be
grandfathered in itself into real study
and science to figure out where where
the metals are in the brain how it works
I talk about this in the heavy metal
detox I mean the heavy metal um show and
and the tremor from Parkinson's is
separate and you can still have a Tremor
without even it being like a Parkinson's
Tremor that real bad shaky Tremor the
bad shaky Tremor that's got people's
head shaking and it's got their arm
shaking and it's got I mean it's it's in
the
way that's a serious Mercury deposit
that's that's that's bleeding not blood
it's bleeding over it's like runoff it's
like a factory you got a
factory you got a factory out there okay
and in some field big old factory and
they're just manufacturing poisons out
there some big old corporations some
ugly Corporation not good ones ugly one
and they're just they're just dumping
these poisons out into a little bit of a
a
river and it goes into one River and it
starts to bleed out of the fields into
that River what happens is the Mercury
sits there it ages it it it breaks down
and it
bleeds
dentists actually are aware of this
better than anywhere anybody else in
medical research and science even if a
dentist doesn't realize it they know
that the the Mercury tattoos you get
Mercury tattoos from from old uh mgms
you know the Mercury tattoos in the gums
they know that that's that's bled over
from the old Mercury amalgam they're the
only ones that understand it even if
they don't even though if they didn't
even connect the dots ever to realize
that when you got mercury in somebody's
brain and it starts to bleed over and it
doesn't mean you're getting a Mercury
technically in your brain brain from
Mercury amalgam but I'm just saying you
could get a little but you know there's
plenty other places to get mercury in
the brain I'm telling you right now I'm
telling you right now so when that
mercury up there starts to bleed over
into tissue starts to run into that
River toxic waste running down that
field and hitting that River from that
big old corporate Factory
right you know that b big place and then
you know and it and it and it bleeds
over into the river and runs out
out what happens
is it starts to saturate other tissue I
want to saturates other tissue you got
electrical impulses going crazy they're
going bananas they're bouncing off the
walls they're hitting they're hitting
each
other with the Tremor and shake the big
bad big bad Tremor that means that not
only is an electrical impulse trying to
get somewhere but can't because it's
running into Mercury deposits tissue in
the brain could be anywhere in the brain
if it's your arm then it's somewhere
else in the brain if it's your head
that's shaking it's somewhere else in
the brain if it's your toe that's
shaking it's somewhere else in the
brain and when it's
hitting hitting that mercury
deposit it's not just hitting it because
you can have hundreds of neurological
conditions that are heavy metal based
that are Mercury based and other metals
hundreds of conditions where it's
hitting the metal but it goes somewhere
else else it reroots
itself but with Parkinson's Tremor
Parkinson's
shake the bad one it's actually coming
back down the neuron the wrong way
science and research guess when they're
going to discover that I'll be dead I'll
be gone I'll tell you that even if if
you believe in lives coming back or past
lives everybody has different beliefs a
lot of people believe they have all
hundreds of past lives you know know hey
man I'm on board with anybody's belief
system because I I I learn from it too
you know I mean yeah I ask Spirit these
questions and I always ask Spirit hey
does somebody have a past life does
someone you know someone going to have a
a forward life but I like hearing what
people say because people have intuition
in their own internal soul and Body on
their own personal experience of what
they think about a past life or or
moving forward and and so cuz I like
people have their own you know unique
their own unique you guys do you have
that attachment to your you know to the
whole thing your third eye the pituitary
gland to your soul to your spirit and
you got that hey you know yourself when
it comes down to these things and you
may feel hey I had a past life so then
you know I I go by what people feel
about these things and and you know even
if I had 10 more lifetimes in the
future if that's even possible if I had
10 20 more lifetimes they still wouldn't
know that that's what happens with the
electrical impulse electrical impulse
running down in Earth neur on and it
hitting the
Mercury but instead of derailing and
going into a different part of the brain
tissue which I talk about what happens
for everybody with heavy metal in their
brain giving them you know
ADHD um all different kinds of things
that we talked about autism everything
else not even just that just just normal
quirks and normal OCD OCD like the OCD
show how it goes around how it carries
information it needs to carry this
information but what happens with
Parkinson's is that neurological that
neurotransmitter okay that electrical
impulse running
running down with what neurotransmitter
chemicals attached to it is what I'm
saying running across that neuron it
hits the Mercury deposit and then it
goes back the neuron the other way
that's what the Tremor and the shake is
that will never be discovered in in
science and
research I I don't know when it will be
I don't know and if this if we don't
blow this Earth
up you know 500 years from now a
thousand years from now maybe maybe
science will have a chance to figure
that one
out I don't even know if the show exists
by then
maybe if you'll be able to you know find
it and uh so here's the deal so when it
runs back the the uh it runs back the
neuron it it travels the neuron down the
neuron the wrong way because there's a
shock reaction that happens with that
heavy metal in that tissue and I'll tell
you what it
is on the other side of that tissue
there's also a
neurotransmitter that's trying to hit
the wall at the same time it's a Mercury
deposit with neurons and both side of it
with the neurotransmitters trying to hit
the wall at at the same time and then
being shot back down the
neuron cuz even if you didn't have that
see if you didn't have that that neuron
on the other side of the met the metal
deposit the Mercury deposit if you
didn't have it on the other
side okay and then and then that neuron
that neuron came on the other side came
across and hit the
wall it still would have try to find A
New Path it has another neuron on the
other side of the Mercury deposit
throwing out El electrical impulse
across and slamming into the Mercury at
the same time the other neurons sending
an electrical impulse slamming into the
Mercury and there's a short out a short
out of the ultimate kind a short
out and they both shoot back the neuron
the wrong way meaning backwards it's
like driving your car for forward and
then stopping while somebody's behind
you and then slamming it into reverse
and going
back because what's happening is there's
already another electrical impulse
getting ready getting charged up with
neurotransmitter chemicals with mineral
salts precious mineral salts getting
revved up and hot like ready to go like
busting out of the gate like a horse and
a horse
race
you know like an Olympic Athlete like
getting charged up before they go down
that like Sleigh Ride On Ice the death
defying slay ride on ice or an Olympic
Athlete it's about to snowboard 500 feet
in the
air I I don't know why people do that I
mean I get it I get it they got a gift
and the talent for it and but boy does
that scare me I wouldn't do
that if I'm proud of anybody who does
whatever they do that's that's like that
I mean it's amazing here's the thing and
as that charge is getting ready as that
it's getting ready it's like that skier
the Olympic Athlete skier that he's at
the top or she's at the top about to go
down that slope you you know what's
getting charged up right there you know
what's getting charged up in that
person's brain right can you imagine
person's brain and in that in that
person's body can you
imagine can you imagine if there was a
skier that was going up the slope
backwards because when they got to the
bottom so the so say there was another
athlete that went down the slope already
can you imagine if that athlete for some
reason even though it's not possible in
this situation all of a sudden start
going back up the slope
backwards with speed while that other
athletes at the top the very top sitting
there getting revved up like you can't
believe to come
down and when that skier jumps off that
slope and comes down and they both
Collide
Midway you got
Tremors you got Tremors and shakes
Tremors and shakes that keep you up at
night tremors and shakes that make you
need a tremendous amount of of of you
know of
pharmaceuticals I won't name all the far
Pharmaceuticals but yeah all that Pharma
that you need to try to control it those
in the
shakes and there's that explosion that
occurs when those two hit when those two
skiers hit on that slope one going up
the hill backwards full speed and
another one coming down full speed all
charged up and when they hit an
explosion
occurs this explosion is equivalent to a
massive
bomb a massive bomb on planet
Earth that's what it's equivalent to
internally in the
brain yeah your head doesn't explode
it's different it's different on a scale
that can't be measured and and that's
what happens and so you got two neurons
there's a big hunk of mercury slammed in
the
center you
know and and that those electrical
charges are are being launched down that
neuron across that neuron and hitting
the metal deposit one on each side of
the metal
deposit and then they're bouncing back
after that explosion with another charge
running down that neuron that hits it at
the same time over and over and over and
over and over again and that's why
Parkinson's disease a lot of brain
surgeons have to go in there and they
have to cut
tissue cut nerves they have to open up
somebody's brain and they got to go they
got to go
searching
which is actually amazing that's that's
part of you know you know neurosurgeons
are are miracle workers many of them are
and that's the part of science I like in
general I'm not saying go get you know
your brain opened up I'm talking about
we're going to remove heavy metals but
the point is is I'm talking about how
science you know we could still remove
aneurysms out of people's brains and
save their lives with robots with like a
surgeon in the back playing around with
controls it's pretty amazing so I mean
there's all kinds of parts of science I
love just never get me wrong when I just
rip apart chronic illness I can't help
it if I don't rip apart chronic illness
nothing's going to change Spirit told me
that Spirit told me that Spirit doesn't
like my delivery Spirit doesn't like the
way I rip things apart Spirit would
rather have me do it in a way that
Spirit would like which is soothing calm
wonderful but that's not
[Laughter]
me I said spirit this is who you picked
this is who you got this is the best I
got all right just you know leave me be
and here's here's the deal here's the
deal that's what happens with
Parkinson's as part of as far as the big
Tremor as far as the big Shake part as
far as everything else the multitude of
symptoms that happen it's so many
different heavy metals in the in
different deposits copper aluminum you
got lead you got Mercury you got arsenic
you got cadmium you got there's more
than that you got Alloys you got Alloys
someone has copper in their head and
they got mercury in their head you
wouldn't believe what happens when you
got two things in your head you got
aluminum copper Mercury you get these
alloy
compositions and you get this alloy
brain and then all kinds of symptoms can
occur but but with neurological
neurological conditions you can have the
viral conditions you can have viruses
feeding off of heavy metals viruses that
reside in our body and you can even get
a virus in the brain you better believe
believe that you know it's the most
bizarre thing ever I got to tell you is
there was a drug commercial on and one
of the side effects was it you may be
one of those rare people that get a
virus to the brain because of this
drug now I'm like somebody
somebody knows that viruses get into the
brain out there something meaning
somebody out there knows
it now what virus are they talking about
they probably don't even know what virus
are they talking about what family are
they talking about don't even know don't
even know but they just know that
somebody can get a virus in the brain
I'm glad we're that far with research
and science so in some cases
neurological conditions you can get
absolutely you can get the hhv 6 in the
brain hhv 10 11 12 those are
undiscovered by the way you go on the
internet and you say what's he talking
about
hh12 it doesn't exist no it does exist
it's just not
discovered and and spirit knows this so
I'm working on the perimeters of what
people know now and I have to be
cautious to how far I push it and how
far I go because it's so far ahead of
the
game so here's the deal when it comes
down to Parkinson's you think you got
Parkinson's whatever it is I mean
whatever it is neurological line
whatever it is first of all you got to
work work on getting heavy metals out so
you don't have a fuel for a virus a
viral condition
so you don't have a fuel for a viral
condition that's what you got to do ALS
Ms a million different symptoms and
conditions with you know hundreds and
hundreds and hundreds of medical names
now we have for neurological
conditions hundreds of them so a lot of
doctors a lot of doctors and Clinics
wanted their name on
something okay so you know I get it I
get it it's like uh it's like almost
sometimes in the case of of of whatever
you know someone someone's in a career
and they want their name on something I
get it so there's a lot of different
diseases and illnesses with names on
them and whatever these names are
whatever it is over the years we still
have to look at heavy metals and we have
to look at viruses anything Parkinson's
related anything e it doesn't mean you
have a virus in your brain it doesn't
you get have multiple sclerosis and
never have a virus in your brain or
anything you can have all these
different symptoms and conditions you
could have the lesions you can have all
the different you know neurolog iCal
symptoms and and you can just literally
have simply an epine bar in the liver
just releasing some
neurotoxins neurotoxins are poop that
came out of the virus but then guess
what you look that up and guess what
you're going to find you guys viruses
don't eat viruses don't eat I love when
someone tries to correct me on
that on Facebook or some article or
something somebody who just they just
can't
stand the fact that this information's
out there they hate it I there's people
that don't hate it they love the fact
it's information's getting out there and
they love it they the professionals that
love that and but they hate there's some
that hate it and they say viruses don't
eat anything look this up I knew this
I'm a biologist viruses don't eat
viruses eat they eat
they drink well they don't drink they
eat eat and drink it's all the
same and they bring it in they bring in
food that makes them Thrive heavy metals
are one of
them heavy metals are one of them if you
stick mercury in a solution of viruses
say you single out viruses I don't care
what virus it is that you single it out
you put it in a vial with Mercury the
Mercury will keep that virus
alive it'll keep that virus alive for a
long time how is that possible that a
that mercury in a vial will keep a virus
alive how does it do that how does it do
that it keeps those bugs alive because
those bugs are feeding off of the
Mercury it's food so the bug can stay
alive and eat and
live
so here's the
deal there's all these different
neurological conditions tingles numbness
aches and pains okay restless legs
everything all right and and we've
covered a lot of details in a lot of
this show about CFS fibromyalgia about
the Epstein bars that create so much of
this about the tingles and numbness
Epstein Epstein bar creates and so many
different um symptoms that we deal with
in vagus nerve condition conditions
frenic nerves conditions where you know
you got pains all over your ears and
head got pains on your forehead you got
ticks you got all these different things
spasms and all these neurological
problems and they talk about the viruses
and what happens with the viruses and
how the viruses work with all this and
it's the heavy metals that's the other
hand of it but when it comes down to
Parkinson's Parkinson's is mercury
deposits of mercury and I'm sure someone
with Parkinson's has more they got all
kinds of of heavy metal in there but the
Mercury there's a reaction that happens
with those electric impulses that shoot
back like I explained that cause the
ultimate Tremors and the shakes of of
Parkinson's but the medical world is so
confused with Parkinson's all on its own
that they know they had to add to it so
they add a ton of symptoms now to
Parkinson's it's all a HH posos and a
confusion totally totally now they don't
even care about Tremors and shakes
anymore they just care about delusion
dementia and stiffness with it let me
tell you something someone with dementia
is is is they have they have toxic heavy
metals in their brain causing the
dementia that's number one their
stiffness is from an Epstein bar that
has nothing to do with that that's just
somebody with later stage Epstein bar
with body stiffness that you can heal
from that you can't EP Epstein bar can't
hurt you
you can stop it once you know the truth
about it and once you know the truth
about viruses and once you know the
truth about why you got neurological
lime and why you don't feel good and why
you got all these different problems you
can heal this you can get better you
can't epine you EP bar can't stop you
the power you have when you know what it
is besides you know I I even like
Epstein Barb because you know what it in
in other viruses and other bugs because
it pushes you to it pushes you to a
place you never thought you'd ever be
with your your life in good ways because
then you overcome it and then you become
a Force nobody could touch including no
virus can touch and nothing can touch it
can become a Force and and ride over it
and not be held down and
stopped and rise above
it but here's the
deal see so somebody has dementia or
they got some kind of symptom that's
related they got Neurosis or they got
you know something in the Alzheimer's
category whatever it is that's that's
somebody with a lot of heavy metals in
the brain no question but they might all
of a sudden have some fatigue and
stiffness which is also a viral
condition but that's never figured out
it's never put into it they can they
can't organize this nothing can be
organized in modern medicine
conventionally an alternative like it
needs to be the alternative is way
better obviously it's way
better you know and and and I worry that
alternative medicine has blended into
conventional medicine they blend it
together I worry about that back in the
older days back in the 80s they were so
separated and maybe that wasn't good
either that they were so separated they
were separated literally there wouldn't
be a clinic with a natural practitioner
the first ND was in California in the
very early 80s the first naturopath in
California in the very early 80s I know
personally that it it's it's it was like
it was like they were so divided
conventional and alternative but the
good part about that was the alternative
didn't want to touch any of the old
grandfathered garbage that was all wrong
about conventional medicine didn't want
to touch
it and now though you know alternative
medicine's kind of Blended in together
so what that means is when conventional
medicine just felt like they discovered
that the body attacks itself with a
theory but back of the 50s that
autoimmune is the body destroying itself
that the alternative medicine because
they're blending now you got all these
young people young doctors coming out of
it they believe that grandfather law and
that's the part that's the mistake about
blending those two
together you know we need to still be
separated with some ideas but still be
together with others it's so hard to
figure that out so that's why this show
is different it's why you listen to this
show so you know what's really happening
so we all can learn I'm not I'm not hard
on doctors I think they're greatest
thing in the world I'm talking about the
system itself it's a whole another game
here's the deal so with
Parkinson's you want the metals out I
like the heavy metal detox it's my
favorite you know the the the heavy
metal detox the medical medium heavy
metal
detox you you got you got to invest in
that thing it's a good thing chaga
mushroom I really like I use the viy
chaga mushroom the
viy and that's the one I use check it
out you know that's the one I use um you
know that that's a great one and and um
that's great too for all of this it's
great for this because the vimergy uh
cha mushroom powder I like it because it
it dissolves so well and what I like
about it is it gets deeper into the
liver it kills off viruses so if you're
someone that doesn't even you don't know
what you have and it's neurological I
like using chaga for neurological for
you know for for breaking down viruses
breaking down the Epstein bar breaking
down other viruses
but you know when it comes down to
neurological you need the B12 that's
critical you need the B12 I talk about
the one I talk about you know you know
there's a lot of different things you
can get too I like Coen coenzyme Q10
when it comes down to
Parkinson's um um I like glutathione
when it comes down to neurological
problems and Parkinson glutathione okay
and you can you can go to medical
medium.com and look up the right kind
don't don't get a don't spend $80 I
don't sell supplements but I got a
directory though don't spend $80 on a
really bad
glutathione that doesn't that doesn't
even work um I like spirina but that's
part of the heavy metal detox okay that
you can use for Parkinson's El
glutamine um that's a great one uh
neuromag I like neuromag check that out
Gaba I like that for Parkinson's a
little bit of that listen everything you
just take you know if you you're dealing
with a conditioner you know somebody
would condition talk to your holistic
practitioner bring these bring these
ideas to that holistic practitioner or
that conventional practitioner and and
and work on some of this Sam E I like
that one for Parkinson's it's a good one
it's good these These are great because
it it nourishes supports
neurotransmitters because neurons start
burning out when that whole thing occurs
that I mentioned earlier about the
electrical impulse slamming into each
other like they do with the Mercury
between them
and basically what it's like is
this you got a metal wall a thin metal
wall okay and you you have you got to
run 20 ft and bang into that wall cuz
you something inside of you is demanding
that you try to knock that wall down so
you run full speed 20 fet and you slam
into that wall get ready at the other
side of that wall of metal the thin wall
of metal there's somebody else running
full speed at the same time and they
slam into the wall while you slam into
that thin wall and you guys slam into it
together and then you guys start heading
back while there's two other people on
both sides getting ready to run full
speed that's how it happens and then and
and the neuron Burns Out starts burning
out and and the neurotransmitter
chemicals start burning out we start
losing because they're being used up
used up so I like Samy supports that
gabit supports that neurom maggot
supports that Al glutamine supports that
spirulina supports that glutathione
supports that chaga even supports that
to some degree even though I like the
chaga for killing down the viruses
Siberian jining I like that it's support
it's supportive for this as well
supports the
adrenals in a way that can be helpful
for Parkinson's any neurological related
to Parkinson's or any kind of lime
related neurological anything like that
Siberian jins sing taking a deep breath
here I talk so fast sometimes that I I
don't get air in so just bear with me
someone said a while back on one of
these shows you know he sounds weird
he's breathing in the mic so
much that's because of a lot of reasons
because I'm talking so fast I'm thinking
I'm listening to Spirit all at the same
time you got to get some air in plus I'm
kissing the mic I'm kissing the mic all
right that's my mic that I have
methylfolate
methylfolate that's another one too you
bring that in um
MSM methos sophono methylene s MSM I
don't even think I said that one right
but that's what it is
MSM so these are some of the supplements
to be focused on as far as antivirals
always have a little bit of zinc and you
always have that going on um I do like a
little bit of licorice for any kind of
viral stuff that's going on
neurologically cat's claw is also I
always say cats claw I've always said
cats claw all the way to the beginning
years and years and years ago all the
way to the
beginning and and because catclaw is
great antiviral knocks down those
Epstein bars knocks down all these
different things so that's a great one
too um but you know look if you're
dealing with somebody with any kind of
Parkinson's related issue any kind of
issue related neurologically these are
all helpful you can experiment you can
bring in a little bit with your doctor
your practitioner however you want to do
it but and get the right ones make sure
you're getting the right ones when
you're doing this um and um so the
bottom line is it's not hopeless when
you have neurological conditions always
know that it's not hopeless I've seen
people with the worst Tremors and shakes
get them to the mild Tremors and shakes
till they were gone and some people with
really bad Tremors and shakes I've seen
it where they've gotten it where it's
doable where you don't even know it and
they don't even know it they don't even
know they still they kind of sense it
here and there buzzing humming inside
the body is not you know Parkinson's
either you know that's just a lot of
neurotoxin from a viral condition with
the buzzing and humming that's inside
when you feel that it's known so many
people with neurological symptoms but
right now Parkinson's get so outdated so
messed up so flawed and the medical
world that they had to bring in a list
of symptoms now they had to file them
into Parkinson's and here's one of the
reasons you have because it's
grandfathered in with old investors old
investors of old funding so you got to
bring in new symptoms to revive it
because they even know everything's
going to Lime same thing with multiple
sclerosis they bring in new symptoms
because they have to revive that old
grandfathered interest groups that way
into that it's such a brain screw I
can't even tell you no pun intended it's
so
bad it's so bad so we have to rise above
all of the nonsense of the different
names of these illnesses get down to the
root of what's causing the condition
itself and get working on that and
realize that it needs an overhaul all
this needs an overhaul every last
illness every last chronic issue out
there needs an overhaul and that's what
we're trying to do here in some way when
I was a child spirit said we got a lot
of work to do and I was like I don't
want to work what the hell are you
talking about I don't want to work and
spirit was like you just swore don't say
hell never say that word so spirit
always always let me know let me know
never say anything like that spirit said
that you're going to have a lot of work
to do we got to do it in this lifetime
we got to get it done and and you're
going to need people's help you're going
to need their help to get the
information out there so they can heal
move forward so they can tell their
story so they can teach others and we're
going to be doing a lot of work I said I
don't want to do that I I just I just
want to go outside and and climb a tree
and live my life as a child and spirit
said you could do some of that but we
can't we we got to be on it we got to be
on it and I'm on it for you that's the
whole point I'm with it for you guys I'm
there I'm going to stay there with you
guys and we're going to get this stuff
done you know get a hold of the thid
healing book I want to help I want you
guys to be an expert I'm with you bless
you thank you for just being there with
me and uh take care okay take
care