constipation
IBS bloating constipation
IBS and more so many people I got Celiac
I got Crohn's I got colitis I got IBS I
got bloating got gastric problems
gastritis cramps cramping extreme
distension so many people are suffering
with so many different gut problems and
it's like the same thing it's like this
probiotic that probiotic this gut
cleanser that gut cleanser
ACV charcoal back to the probiotic back
to the gut cleanser back to the shogy
back to this back to that and it's like
boom boom boom boom boom intermittent
fasting that's getting my bloating down
my bloating is down now it's all fixed
intermittent fasting whoa it's back now
I ate it's back and and over and over
and over it goes because that's what
happens with a lot of people is they're
battling bloating constipation other
things too loose St not loose dos then
it's constipation then it's back or it's
just straight straight plain old
bloating and that's what it is so we're
talking about some cool stuff right here
now I know a lot of people they fight to
get their bloating down they get the
lymphatic drainage lymphatic massage
they get their stomachs worked on so
that's a big thing right now everybody
goes in and someone's working on their
stomach now they're using machines on
their stomachs right to try to get the
bloating down and then right when it's
it's like getting a new haircut okay you
get a brand new haircut it's perfect you
love what you're seeing you walk out of
the the salon and then some wind hits
you hop in your car you're like it's
still looking good I still got my
haircut I still got my style it's all
good by the end of the day it's getting
worse worse worse by morning you wake up
and your hair is not what you wanted it
to be it's not where it was when you
just walked out of that Salon the same
thing you you go get your stomach worked
on you get your lymphatic drainage
worked on you're getting your stomach
just right then you walk out of there
and you're like okay my stomach's down
and then you sip some water or you drink
something whatever that is and then boom
it's back for a lot of people or you
just start seeing it slowly coming back
then next day it's slowly coming back
Third Day fourth day you're bloated
again you got the distension you're
stuck you're back to where you were so
let's talk about like true true causes
if you're fighting any kind of bloating
at all any kind of bloating at all you
got to go to your liver liver that's
right doesn't mean eat liver you don't
want to eat liver to fix your bloating
because that's not going to fix it
because people talk about that stuff too
they'll try anything it's all about
biohacks out there non-stop but your
liver something's going on stagnant
sluggish
liver stagnant sluggish liver why is it
stagnant why is it slug sluggish from a
lot of different things you guys I'm in
Liver Rescue right now I'm just looking
through here and talking about some cool
stuff we're going to talk about this so
what happens with people is their liver
gets filled up and that filters stuffed
and clogged and then it starts to become
dysfunctional and then it doesn't
produce the bile it needs to produce to
break down your
fats and then it starts to weaken and
it's over 2,000 chemical functions start
to become
dysfunctional and so now your liver is
only running on 700 chemical functions
now your liver is only running on 900
chemical
functions now your liver is only running
on 300 chemical functions because your
liver is stagnant and sluggish and it's
stuck and it's overburdened and over
tired and the the 2,000 plus chemical
functions that your liver does to keep
you healthy keep you alive keep your
skin looking good keep you doing good
all that's
diminishing and then over time you get a
fatty liver without even realizing it
people will get a fatty liver and then
your A1C goes up and then your blood
sugar is all over the place so if you're
somebody that's dealing with blood sugar
problems and that's what you're living
with and you're always trying to like
balance your blood sugar you're always
trying to figure out that magic
combination well let me this let me eat
that I'm going to have salmon with a
grapefruit I'm going to have a piece of
meat with a celery stick I'm going to
have something with something I'm going
to have sushi with an orange I'm going
to do whatever it is that you're I'm
going to have nuts and seeds with
raisins whatever you're trying to do to
balance that that blood sugar problem a
lot of people are like I eat hummus to
try to balance it I eat beans I eat
grains I eat fruit I eat vegetables
everybody's just fighting to balance
their blood sugar out there what they
don't
realize is they're battling a problem
much bigger than what it seems it's not
just about
glucose it's about a liver becoming
dysfunctional so one of the things that
happens when your liver becomes
dysfunctional is your glucose storage
diminishes and starts to disappear your
glucose storage so right here in your
liver okay every time you eat something
that has any kind of carbohydrate any
kind of
glucose say fructose and fruit it goes
into the liver and it helps to restore
the storage bin down in there so every
time you're eating something with a
carbohydrate because if you don't have a
carbohydrate if you don't have a sugar
if you don't have that fructose or
glucose you don't have that starch from
something what happens is you don't
refill all of your cells with needed
energy because our energy derives from
sugar our brain thrives and lives off of
sugar that's what our brain lives off of
you take sugar away from our brain it
dies in 10 seconds you take sugar away
from the brain cells start to die in 5
seconds and it just goes from there like
as the seconds are counting down the
brain starts to die so sugar and glucose
needs to store into the liver so that
your liver is releasing little bits of
it keeping your blood sugar balanced you
hear what I'm going right here how
important this is keeping your blood
sugar balanced your liver is like your
blood sugar balancer right there people
don't know that instead they're just
they're trying to master a food they go
and buy a hack foods and they're trying
like I'm trying to eat this and this and
at 12:00 I'm eating this and this and at
1:00 I'm eating this and this and
they're trying to figure out how to keep
their blood sugar their hypoglycemia
their hypoglycemia blood sugar spikes
they're keeping monitors on themselves
they're all freaked out about their
blood sugar they don't know what's going
on and what's really happening deep down
inside is you got a tired liver that
that doesn't have a glucose storage bin
anymore or the delivers overburdened
stagnant sluggish and it's not
functioning good enough to release
glucose properly it's not functioning
good enough to be able to release spurts
of that glucose to keep you strong so
you're not hitting the ground so you're
not you know hitting the wall so you can
function and live your life so your
liver needs to actually control that
glucose release and it sends out glucose
ose right into the bloodstream so that
you're stable so what happens is people
walk around they think they have the
worst blood sugar problems because it's
a blood sugar problem they're like it's
my pancreas what's going on am I
pre-diabetic what do I have going on
meanwhile it's the liver it's tired it's
beaten down it's problematic it's
stagnant it's
sluggish and that's what's going on so I
want everybody to know that the liver
plays a role in so much of your health
over 2,000 in chemical functions and
when it get stagnant and sluggish
everything starts going wrong you start
bloating you might get some
constipation you might get all kinds of
other issues along with it and then
there's the adrenaline so let's get the
adrenals out for a little bit that's
another thing that happens we run on a
high all the time we're always trying to
get high everybody's out there trying to
get high they're living off of
adrenaline they're running on adrenaline
every day and then they're burning out
their adrenals every day adrenaline's
being released and that adrenaline gets
absorbed into the liver and starts to
absorb into the liver and it tires the
liver out another reason why people have
stagnant sluggish liver that leads to
bloating is because their adrenals have
released so much adrenaline so so many
people are on caffeine every day they're
on their coffee and their adrenals are
just flooding everywhere
like more caffeine the adrenals are just
releasing it out right more matcha tea
more coffee more cacao more caffeine and
it's just like stimulant stimulant and
the adrenals are just flooding and
flooding and
flooding that's not the only time the
adrenals are flooding when we're on a
really high fat diet all the time we're
eating fats everywhere whether you're
plant-based you're vegan whether you're
you know vegetarian whether you're just
animal protein a lot of people they're
on such high fat diets there's so much
fat in their diet that they're on an
adrenaline High because the fats get
into the bloodstream then your body does
this emergency situation where it
releases adrenaline to thin out the fats
inside the bloodstream so you don't have
a heart
attack and so all that adrenaline high
is happening with people they're walking
around stimulated all the time and so
it's important it's important to heal
the liver work on healing the liver
restoring the liver so many people's
problems are are the liver okay eczema
psoriasis
dermatitis the liver plays a role in
that right there any skin problems you
don't
like any kind of different dark spots on
your skin all kinds of different skin
issues the liver plays a role right
there
bloating yes even constipation other
digestive trouble the liver plays a role
right there so let's move into it a
little deeper okay one of your liver's
most important jobs is to disperse bile
and break down fat and if it doesn't
disperse enough bile guess what the fat
goes ran it ran it it sits in your gut
and it goes bad and it goes rancid and
it starts to harden up and it sits on
the walls of your intestinal tract and
your
gut the other role the liver
does is it actually makes it so your
stomach glands in your stomach stay
stronger so that they can create
hydrochloric acid and the hydrochloric
acid breaks down protein the weaker your
liver gets the less protein you break
down and then your protein ends up
rotting and putrifying and then you can
be stuck with all kinds of flatulent and
gas additionally tacked on to your
bloating so quick rundown stagnant
sluggish liver that's dysfunctional
that's not doing its 2,000 chemical
functions but instead it's doing 500
chemical functions or 400 chemical
functions it gets tired it can't
function as good as it needs to function
it gets hot it starts to heat up and
then it loses its ability to store
glucose so your blood sugar is all over
the map like this so when you got that
stagnant sluggish liver you guys your
glucose is all over the map and you're
just like everywhere it's like my A1C my
A1C where's my glucose I'm spiking I'm
lowering I'm spiking I'm crashing the
liver plays a huge role in all of that
the other thing hydrochloric acid the
liver keeps your stomach glands and
stomach stronger if the liver's strong
it keeps your stomach stronger your
glands in your stomach stronger
producing higher quality quantities of
HCL which really helps someone actually
break down proteins you guys I see a lot
of people asking me what I'm talking
about talking about bloing constipation
and IBS in Liver Rescue I don't know if
you have this book right
here and then I also have cleanse the
heal with me right here if you guys
don't have this book this book has saved
countless lives already around the world
check it out when you can it's an
Incredible Book cleanse the
heel cleanse the heel is an important
book for cleansing the liver
Okay so let's go into a little deeper
into it we're going to cover some other
stuff all around this so it's critical
to know what's going on inside your body
if you don't know what's happening
inside your body you're going to be
running around like a chicken with your
head cut off trying to biohack always
looking for an answer being stuck in the
mud but when you know what's going on
and why you're feeling like you do why
you're struggling like you do and you
know why things can change you can turn
things around you you can heal you can
move forward and that's critical to know
so back to the liver a little bit
keeping a strong liver makes it so your
HCL is produced and stays strong and
breaks down your protein critical or
your protein will sit there and rot in
your gut and you'll have protein gut rot
inside your gut where it'll purify and
release ammonia and
gases and then you want your liver to be
strong to produce strong ample bile so
the bile can break down and disperse the
fats that you're eating when you do eat
fat in your food a weak liver means the
bile will actually go
rancid with the fats your own bile and
the fats together will actually join
together and purify and all go ran it
because your bile wasn't even strong
enough to break down the fat so your
bile even lost its shelf life people
with weak livers they end up getting a
fatty liver liver starts to get toxic
and fat and when the liver is in that
condition all these things can go wrong
as
well another thing with the liver is
cholesterol readings when you go and get
your blood test liver problems mean
cholesterol
problems right there on its own high
blood pressure liver problems unless
there's a blockage somewhere and even
then if there's a blockage somewhere
with high blood pressure or heart
problems it starts originally from the
liver all the way back in years before
it starts with the liver keep that in
mind so I don't talk about it enough
lately but in order to stay healthy we
have to keep our livers healthy and
strong so we can stay healthy so
cleansing the liver strengthening it and
bringing it back is key it's critical
for
healing back to the high that
everybody's on everybody's chasing a
high said this before people love to
chase highs and when we Chase highs and
we're stimulated or jacked up on our own
adrenaline we weaken our liver even more
Liver Rescue is a legendary it has
changed the health of people worldwide
it's changed the medical system it's
changed the health system system
influencers every day all around the
world including on podcasts or talking
about information in Liver Rescue It is
it this is the book that brought liver
information to the world no one's ever
even heard
before this book right here is worth a
read to gain control and empowerment on
your health let's go into it a little
deeper all
right so you're eating whatever you
choose to
eat you're bloating from
it so you might be somebody that's
intermittent fasting maybe you're
holding back food maybe you did a water
fast and your water fast was like seven
days or 10 days or 14 days or 21 days
and you did it water fast and your
bloating went down and you're proud of
yourself cuz your bloating went
down and maybe you just you're somebody
who's intermittent fasting you're
probably yourself cuz you're bloating
went down or maybe you're somebody that
just didn't eat much for a few days and
you're getting lymphatic drainage and
you're getting your stomach worked on
and they're working on you and they're
even using machines on your abdomen
abdominal machines to try to push all
the fluid out of your
skin and then the next day it's back you
end your water cleanse it's back you end
your intermittent fasting moments it's
back you end you know you're done with
your lymphatic drainage after a little
while it's back there it is your
bloating is back what the heck is going
on that's what has to be addressed or
it's just a
game it's a charade it's about managing
now it's important to manage you that's
what you have to do if you know those
inner secrets about yourself where you
can manage just right to try to keep
balance to keep the bloating down to
keep the constipation at Bay if that's
something you have or even the IBS or
anything else around it if you have a
secret
recipe and you're using that secret
recipe then then that's great but you're
also managing and
micromanaging but you're not getting
down to the root to the root which is
critical and that's a big deal we want
to get down to the root so let's hit
ammonia gas what happens with everybody
okay people get stitches they get cramps
they get all kinds of problems with that
they get gastritis they can get cramps
and stitches that run all the way up to
their neck all the way up to their neck
and even the top of their throat their
shoulder people can have gastric cramps
and gastric problems where they're
bellowed over they're hanging on a couch
they're in their bed they're on the
floor they're trying to move around
they're trying to do yoga positions
they're trying to let gas out that's
trapped and they're trying to get that
trapped gas out right but in that gas is
ammonia and ammonia is something that's
produced from a lot of things being
stagnant and sluggish in here ammonia is
produced
from foods that are actually putrifying
and not breaking down proteins that are
putrifying and not breaking down fats
that are rancid and pathogens that want
to feed
on what's going on that isn't being
digested that's starting to rot
pathogens bacteria that's not good
bacteria and when that bacteria that's
not good bacteria is sitting here
swimming inside your small intestinal
tract and inside your colon your
Elum it's feeding on ranet
undigested ammonia gas filled putrified
protein
and rancid
fats so the bacteria is feeding and then
the gas in the
flatulence produced by that bacteria
along with the ammonia gas that's
actually cycling
through that gas becomes toxic where
you're getting a stitch now so you're
feeling a stitch like oh man or oh I got
to let that gas out I'm feeling a stitch
or I don't feel good or my stomach's
kind of blowing up
again and what it is it's toxic painful
gas you might be somebody that doesn't
have the painful gas because the
bacteria might be a different kind of
bacteria or you don't have a lot of bad
bacteria feeding off of things but you
still have rotting putrified protein and
rancid
fats all inside the intestinal tract and
the gut that's leeching out ammonia gas
and putrifying
and that's creating flatulence
flatulence and gases well so you have to
just you have to roll around on the
ground on the floor you have to move and
shift your body to try to release that
gas to get it out and you might be
somebody where the gas just streams out
every day like that and you might be
somebody where it's trapped and you have
inflammation inside the the intestinal
tract from pathogens from pathogens
inside the intestinal tract and that
those pathogens have little spots in
here that are
inflamed and that inflammation makes it
so the gas gets stuck so let's go into
that a little bit I want to talk about
stuck gas because that's a big deal for
a lot of people right
there so when you're in small intestinal
tract you can have narrowings and you
can have distension and swellings so a
lot of people they small intestinal
tract okay has
inconsistencies where they're expanding
in some areas it's kind of like the
pipeline is expanding in certain
areas or Contracting in certain areas so
the gas isn't moving through properly so
it builds up in one area until it builds
up and then you move and then boom it
starts pushing through and pushing
through and that's what happens and
there's other people that have different
areas like their elium
so right here you know their Elum
problematic the gas is stuck there it's
inflamed the gas won't move through and
it's just stuck and it's in the right
area the right lower region and they're
always like this or they're in the
bathroom and they're trying to go to the
bathroom and they're always holding this
spot they feel that discomfort and
there's that kind of person too and what
these little in inflamed areas in this
in the small intestinal tract from from
bacteria in the lining in the wall or
even viruses in the lining in the wall
they get trapped in
there and when they're trapped in there
and they're in that lining you get a
swelling and an inflammation and then
the gas heads down the pike and when it
hits that spot it gets stuck and it
blows up and now you're bloating so
you're somebody that's actually bloating
so what you got your lymphatic drainage
your lymphatic massage M they might have
done like an abdom abdominal roller on
you you're getting work done you're
getting that out you walk away 6 hours
later you're starting to build gas up
the gas is building up in pockets and
now you're bloating all over
again happens every day to people you
guys just want to say real quick before
we move on with this medical medium
podcast that Apple podcast new episode
it's healing tools and techniques to
keep you strong check it out when you
get a chance medical meum podcast at
Apple podcast okay healing tools and
techniques to keep you strong
advertisement free podcast it's the only
advertisement free podcast out there um
that's a number one podcast um so check
it out you guys when you get a chance
all right we have five new episodes
blood brain barrier is one of them so
don't miss that episode that one alone
is worth listening to we got the micro
doing episode so check that as well
right there some micro doing and the
alcohol episode as well so make sure you
check that drinking one out that would
be a great one to actually listen to so
medical Me podcast at Apple podcast 5
new episodes but the healing tools and
techniques one by far will blow your
mind new episode each week so keep a
look out all right okay we're in here a
little bit how many of you guys are
dealing with g that feels like it's
trapped how many of you guys are dealing
with a little bit of
constipation how many guys are dealing
with you guys feeling like your blood
sugar is up and down and you're drained
or when you go to the bathroom you're
drained after you go to the
bathroom how many of you guys are
dealing with with distension and
bloating or you're really distended how
many you guys are dealing with that
bloating right there okay
okay so we're just going into this a
little bit a little deeper and deeper
it's important to know what's going on
inside your body it's critical okay Tera
says why can emotional stress trigger
bloating for some people emotional
stress for some people can trigger off
adrenaline okay and when the
adrenals start flooding because it's
emotional stress in the adrenals and
that adrenaline it can then fil are
right into the liver and the liver gets
stuck very stagnant in the moment if
it's already stagnant and that can kind
of short circuit the liver a little bit
a lot of people deal with that that's
one thing there's a bunch of things that
can happen though when we're under
emotional
stress so so many people
have five or 10 pounds on them of
bloating but yet it's not
fat so this is is interesting really
interesting that's why when someone does
something like they'll go and they'll do
say a water fast they go do a juice fast
or they'll go do
something well what happens is they have
like 10 to 15 PBS 5 lbs 20
lb 20 lbs of swelling of
fluid in their intestinal tract swelling
in their liver stagnant sluggish right
food F in their intestinal tract that
hasn't moved in a long
time gas and all kinds of different
fluid throughout their
system and they're bloating and what
happens is they're bloating from all of
that and then when they go and they do
any kind of cleanse or they stop eating
it starts to go down and they start
releasing it they release the some of
the old putrified stuff some of the food
out of their system some of the fluid
retention goes
down and then they notice that wait I'm
5 lb lighter I'm 10 lb
lighter but it wasn't 5 lbs of fat that
they just lost and it wasn't 10 lbs of
fat that they just lost they're now 5
PBS lighter 10 pounds lighter of
putrified stuff that's in their system
fluid retention
pus stagnant sluggish fluid filled liver
and they stopped eating and it went
down or they didn't eat much that went
down a lot of people who are
intermittent fasting they go without
food and they're just on coffee all day
they're on stimulants all day they go
without food and they're noticing they
slim down a little bit but it doesn't
mean they're losing fat really quickly
or anything they're losing swelling and
bloting but we can't just do that we
have to do things where we take care of
ourselves and we eat every day and we're
doing things that are cleaning it up on
a daily basis and healing the stagnant
sluggish liver to begin with so we're
not all over the place like up and down
and all that a lot of people feel a
little better in the morning after
sleeping when they drink
water afterwards they bloat right back
up so you go to bed at night you're
bloated you're out to hear you go to bed
you wake up in the morning and it's down
your liver got a chance throughout the
night to pack up some toxins and sh chip
it out and your bloating is down now and
then you drink water all of a sudden or
something else and you're starting up in
the morning and the bloating comes back
fast and it comes back fast and now it's
building up all day long so your
bloating is building up a lot of people
try not to drink much during the day or
eat much during the day because they
don't want to be bloated so they're
withholding food all day long they're
withholding fluid all day long and
you'll notice like a lot of times times
influencers tend to go really
dehydrated really dehydrated they're
drinking their coffee only all morning
all afternoon and they're literally
dehydrating their themselves then they
go and they get a lymphatic drainage
while they're dehydrated and their
lymphatic uh therapist says make sure
you drink a lot of water when you're
done with this and they don't even want
to drink water they get done with their
lymphatic massage and they have a little
Sip and it starts to come back a few
sips and it starts to come back so a lot
of people right now that fit into their
swim suit and so forth they're like
going dehydrated and that's not the way
to do it either that's not healthy
either it's not the way to battle
this so Nicole over there on IG says why
does green juice bloat
me well if my my thoughts here with that
question are what happens with a lot of
people
so nothing else bloats you it's only
green juice so you're just somebody
that's never bloated or you're not
bloated and then it's green juice that
only bloats you like you're not bloated
ever you live your life you eat your
dinner you eat your breakfast you eat
your lunch you're living your life
you're drinking what you want eating
what you want doing what you want and
all of a sudden you have a sip of green
juice and you're bloated now or is it
you already have a bloating problem
you're fighting bloating all the time it
just so happens when you're drink green
juice too you get bloated from that as
well because that's probably what's
happening I think
right so it's not like you go through
life and you're never bloated ever and
then all of a sudden green juice makes
you bloated but soda doesn't coffee
doesn't nothing else makes you bloated a
bagel or plant-based eating or vegan
eating or animal protein eating whatever
it is nothing gets you bloated it's just
green
juice it's just something to think about
or you get bloated all the time you're
struggling with bloat but when you have
grain juice it seems to come on a little
bit more if you're somebody you're
really toxic a lot of stuff is sluggish
your liver's sluggish and you put some
pretty healthy stuff in you there's a
good chance it's going to start
detoxifying you right away and you could
get a little bit of bloat from stuff
being pushed out starting to get pushed
out people will eat only a little piece
of meat or an
egg or a piece of chicken
just a little piece with like two leaves
of lettuce and a little piece of chicken
because they don't want too much in
their stomach they don't want to feel
that bloating because if they eat too
much they're bloated and people go on
dates and people go on dates they never
tank if it's a brand new date somebody
and someone goes on a date and they're
sitting at the table in the
restaurant no one's tanking no one's
like I'm going to eat this big stack of
panc pakes in front of you right here
I'm stuffed and then and then you leave
the table just stuffed right I'm going
to eat this 12 oce steak right now on
the on this first date right here people
go on dates they usually hold back food
all day long you know anybody that's
ever done
this when women go on dates they hold
back food all day long all day long for
the date cuz they don't want to blo out
they don't want to be bloated on any
level they want to be able to fit into
to whatever they want to fit into they
want to look good for their date same
thing with guys guys will just all of a
sudden they'll be intermittent fasting
the whole day so that when the date when
the date happens everybody's holding
their stomachs in no one wants to be
like bloated and then when they order
dinner they're eating a little something
that's how you can always tell if it's a
first aid out there like no one's eating
anything and then you know that's what
happens because if they did no one's
going to just tank and then be bloated
and that's how it works people people
eat very little a lot of times during
the day to keep their bloting down so
they can feel like they're like flat
right and then they eat a vegetable and
fruit with fiber and water and lots of
just water
rich and they eat all these vegetables
and all these fruits and all that all
that pulp and that pecting and that
fiber and that water Rich right those
nutrients are all going down and it it's
feeling kind of like bulk and all of a
sudden they're feeling it in their
intestinal tract let's talk about that
let's head into that direction a little
bit that's that deserves a little bit a
few
minutes if you guys got a few minutes
why is it that a lot of people who are
eating like leafy greens and fruits and
vegetables and they can feel that
roughage so much and they say I can't do
that I have to be carnivore I can only
eat meat only I can only eat eggs only
because every time I eat a vegetable or
a fruit or something anytime I even and
eat any of that I feel it in my gut and
it doesn't digest and it doesn't break
down I can't eat raw because if I eat
raw I can feel it it it kind of hurts it
makes me feel uncomfortable all that
roughage is moving through me and then
they go to somebody they go to a health
coach or whatever the health coach is
don't have all that roughage you can't
have all that roughage just eat eggs
only do just eggs every day like have
six eggs a day how many people seen
people do that a lot they like six eggs
a day eat eggs and cheese this way you
know you're not like dealing with all
that roughage of all the vegetables and
all the
fruits but that doesn't fix it the eggs
and the
cheese that doesn't fix it so what
happens is the reason why people can
feel all that roughage sometimes like
raw lettuces and raw kale
and raw collared greens and raw zucchini
and raw redbell peppers and raw Tomatoes
they feel it because they're inflamed in
the intestinal tract so when that's
moving through you you feel it more and
the nerve endings on the intestinal
tract Linings are sending signals to you
that it's not digesting it's not
breaking down but it is breaking down it
is digesting you just don't know it so a
lot of people they go into panic they go
into fear and they think they're not
breaking down their food and they can't
eat lettuce and they can't eat a tomato
and they can't eat a red bell pepper and
they can't eat an apple because they
feel it and it's just too much roughage
and it's moving through them and they're
better off just eating like eggs every
single
day something soft like ice cream and
eggs and
cheese and maybe chicken or something or
some meat and that's all they feel like
they can do but they don't realize it
that what happens is that the fruits and
the leafy greens and vegetables are
actually letting people know there's hot
spots in their intestinal tract those
hot spots are inflamed areas where the
nerves are sensitive because of
pathogens viruses and bacteria that are
in the Linings of the intestinal tract
nesting in there and when they're in
there NES
they're creating inflammation which are
hot spots so as you're eating the
roughage and the roughage is going down
there and the lettuces and the greens
are moving through they're hitting those
hot spots and that's when people are
feeling it like I can't digest I'm not
digesting something's wrong I can't
break down the food I need to be on just
like four eggs a day and and some kind
of like mono you know carnivore thing or
something and they don't realize it is
they got sensitive nerves in sensitive
Linings and they're just feeling it it
doesn't mean it's not breaking down or
digesting so let's get to the liver a
little bit more okay rejuvenating the
liver bringing the liver
back that is one of the big keys if you
want to take control over your health
it's bringing back the liver and so many
people are you know eating better and
they're doing better things now out
there and so their liers improve
improving just from the good things
they're doing doesn't mean it's getting
them out of the woods
entirely so bringing back the liver
getting it out of stagnancy and
sluggishness getting it out of
overburden bringing it back key right
there to IBS to bloating to
constipation getting your stomach strong
so let's go into the stomach a little
bit you guys important
okay inside your stomach are glands
those glands produce your HCL that HCL
is
everything
everything that hydrochloric acid which
is a seven blend seven blend of acids
that HCL is critical to breaking down
your food but also breaking down
different aspects of the food so that we
get the nutrients we need and we get
what we need to get out of it right
there okay so the stomach stomach glands
HCL big part of recovery big part of
recovery for the liver
too so if you're somebody that's out
there and you're like I got hypoglycemia
my blood sugar's all over the place I'm
struggling with that I got bloating I
got problems constipation I got IBS or I
had IBS or I got gas where I got all
kinds of stitches and
cramps
gastritis
diagnosis maybe some of your Crohn's
colitis maybe somebody dealing with
that ammonia gas leeching through the
body maybe you
smell maybe you're somebody and you
stink so you just got smell coming out
of your pits and you got smell coming
off of you and people somebody or
somebody in your family or somebody your
friend is just like man you
smell you go what's going on are you
okay you got a strong smell what is
going on with you maybe you're somebody
that just they
stink that's another thing too it's from
getting toxic and getting the liver
toxic and everything being all hung up
and stuck and sluggish stagnant so it's
critical to get these things better so
another thing too let's go into it a lot
of people's livers are inhabited they're
inhabited
from pathogens and pathogens you're
sitting inside the liver viruses
bacteria sitting inside the liver ebvs
hhv 6s cyto megl viruses hhv7 simplex
one 2 all these different bugs
strep staff H
pylori all sitting inside the liver
making it more stagnant and more
sluggish so eating foods that don't feed
those bugs is critical to recovery so
knowing what foods to eat it's critical
to have the information right there like
deliver rescue and cleanse the
heel right there important
information one of the reasons why so
many people heal from celery juice
drinking their celery juice every day is
because it's restoring the stomach
glands inside of the stomach the ones
that produce your gastric acid which is
your HCL and the celery juice every
single day gives you a liver flush you
have it in the morning especially gives
you a liver flush helps to push the
poisons and the toxins out and another
thing the celery juice does too is it
lowers
pathogen
proliferation breaks down bugs and
pathogens bringing them down to a lower
level over time it's just one of the
medical medium tools if there's any
reason to do just that tool alone it's
these right here medical medium is not
one siiz fits all it's customizable with
hundreds of healing tool options and
protocols to get you better so you
understand what is going on so one of
the best places to start if you have
bloating is the medical medium morning
cleanse check it out when you get a
chance you guys it's a medical medium
morning cleanse it's right here in
cleanse the heel it's one great place to
start if you have any bloating IBS any
kinds of intestinal track issues if you
think you have a liver problem if you
got blood sugar issues too this is
critical right here got the mono eating
cleanse you can customize to yourself
and you can customize for yourself so
many other different cleanses that are
in cleanse to heal that is a book you
have to have to make sure you get it
when you get a chance okay there's
protocols for bloating and here is as
well anyway you guys check out medical
Me podcast at Apple podcast when you get
a chance released five new episodes The
Healing tools and technique episode that
I just released is mindblowing very
healing powerful and then you got the
micro doing the alcohol one you got the
bloodb brain
barrier check those out when you get a
chance and then you got food Wars too
that's a great episode as well and um
Tam just cleans the heel is an excellent
book Incredible join the medical medium
broadcast channel on IG okay so on IG
it's and it's called mm inside scoop
it's on IG so join that Broadcasting
channel I'm leaving messages every day
so make sure you check that out also
check out my telegram get on there I'm
leaving messages on
Telegram and also get on my medical
medium newsletter let's talk about
constipation a little
bit
constipation most constipation issues
are from inflamed areas inside the
intestinal tract somebody might have an
inflamed area in the elen somebody might
have an inflamed area the descending
colon the ascending colon and what
happens is because it's inflamed poop
can't move through okay another reason
why people have constipation issues this
peristaltic action has stopped because
their vagus nerve is causing a problem
where the vegus nerve is inflamed not
getting the right signals to the
intestinal tract so it's neurological
constipation is what I call it so it's
another reason so many people get
constipation and another reason why it's
because when they're inflamed they're
inflamed with a lot of bad bacteria in
certain pockets of the intestinal tract
and expansions and narrowings have have
occurred and so the fecal matter gets
hung up and stuck in different areas
between that and the peristaltic action
not being there plus areas that are
inflamed all these things can heal so
many people on MM info have gotten their
inflammation down in their gut restored
their
livers and they're going to bathroom
great better than they ever did their
whole life Susan says my bloating has
gone away since starting the morning
cleanse incredible that's in cleanse the
heel anyway you
guys an asro travel says not any not
anymore thanks to Medical medium but
used to be a huge health issue for me
open the heel says on YouTube all
bloating healed with medical medium
thanks so much you guys I love you guys
check out the books when you get a
chance I want you better I want you
healing and um get on my newsletter
going to be making some big
announcements pretty soon Charlotte says
how long can it take on medical medium
to heal major bloating and severe flu
retention everybody's different
depending on how many exposures how
inflamed they've been how long they've
been inflamed all of it but you can get
that customized information from the
books and you guys just letting you know
right now so I'm going to be
doing a book signing at some point I'm
just for warning everybody it's going to
be in La I do know that I don't have a
date yet but I'm letting you know it's
looking good so I've never done an
official book signing ever since what is
it eight books ago nine books ago and so
uh just keep an eye out get into my
newsletter so you can know where that's
going to be so if you just bring your
books to me just
boom I'll sign it anyway guys and and
when it comes down to like how long it
takes to heel blow to get depend on what
you're doing are you doing enough celery
juice are you doing the morning cleanse
how long you're doing the morning
morning cleanse are you doing the monoc
cleanse because you're you had a
diagnosis if like Crohn's or colitis you
You' been sick a long time all these
things matter with bloating some people
get their bloating better in days and
weeks and some people it takes months
because they're healing a deeper issue
in the intestinal tract and gut yep are
you staying away from troublemakers are
you staying away from caffeine are you
staying away from charcoal or you stay
away staying away from
ACV are you staying away from toxic
water like all the new fangled water
Trends out there be be careful beware
what are you doing got to got to look
out there too you're not doing sodium
bicarbonate I hope not things like that
you got to be cautious about what's your
history how many antibiotics have you
had throughout the years how many
infections how many UTI how many you
know different gastritis attacks how how
much antibiotics you used all these
things matter determine how fast you're
going to heal but that's the whole point
everybody customizes it and they go and
they work on it and they heal anyway
guys all right
um I'll see you next time keep a look
out check things out get on my
newsletter okay going to be making some
announcements and I'm looking forward to
it and it's been great you guys love you
much I'll see you soon