hello I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing
information and secrets about health
much of which is not found anywhere else
and is decades ahead of what's out there
now as I've always said who has 10 or 20
years 30 years to wait for answers who
has 10 or 20 30 years to wait for
anything I mean come on I mean you know
I know we have to be patient today in
the world and as human beings we have to
be patient it's one of the things that
we have to learn to be it's a big part
of being you know human is is patience
but we we we need answers though we need
answers cuz when we don't feel good it
feels like a week is a lifetime when you
don't feel good that's how it works this
is the only Health show where the
information here doesn't come from any
kind of medical interest group medical
funding with strings attached bot
Research Medical lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs or trendy traps all in
alternative of course in conventional
medicine but in alternative medicine too
and that's what's happened the world has
changed it's not the same place at all
the information here comes from a clean
Source an untampered with Source a Pure
Source Advanced source for anybody new
listening to this radio show cuz we get
you know the hundreds and hundreds and
thousands of new people that hear about
the medical medium show and they come on
and this information is comes from a
higher source and none of that is
attached to it all there's no agenda
agenda
driven situations going on behind the
information here very important to
understand the gift was given to me
since Age 4 where I heard a voice
perfectly clear perfectly clear that
told me what was wrong with my
grandmother and and and it has done so
every day since giving me information
anytime I need need it which I put in
the books medical medium the series make
sure that you look into those books if
you're brand new to the show you're
going to be you're going to be surprised
you're going to be surprised it's not
just a book about say like a a biography
of me or something like that or Memoir
or something like that it's not like
that it's it's or or a book with uh a
little bit of information and and and
those books are great too fun books are
great no this is serious this is serious
stuff I take down the information as I
hear it
H uh from Spirit and I make sure we have
it and and I put it in the book
painstakingly one word at a time until
we have the book done check it out
thyroid healing check out thyroid
healing um I really packed it in I
packed it in somebody I know recently
said to me you
know you packed this thing you packed it
there's there's no other word to use
besides that it's the only word that
they could think of because it was so
packed with good stuff chalk full of
nuts totally packed yeah and you know so
um check that out there's so many cool
things in thyroid healing that you know
the true true causes of Hashimoto
hyperthyroid
Graves um it just so much is in there
and and information extremely extremely
Advanced information never before known
or heard about Epstein bar I mean I even
took it to another level from book one
medical medium about Epstein bar and I
even put more information that I didn't
fit in the book one about Epstein bars
this is serious this is a serious book
so anyway check it out check it out for
sure um we're talking about fibroids
we're talking about fibroids today this
is a this is a a very very important
subject very important subject I can't
tell you how many people have uh come to
me over the years and especially when I
had the office in the old days how many
people came to my office with this situ
situation and um you think it's not a
big deal you know as if a man hears
about it it's not a big deal it's like
okay what is that well meanwhile it
could be a big deal it could get pretty
serious I've had a lot of women that
that have come to my office that I mean
they've had size of of of um I mean just
size of eggs fibroids the size of eggs
bigger than eggs I mean so big like even
grapefruit size they can get really big
really disruptive really problematic
really difficult to deal with um
bleeding can occur just lots and lots of
bleeding lots of difficulties and it's
not an easy thing at all to deal with um
and and sometimes surgery is you know
optional sometimes it's not even
optional with this it's unbelievable
with women have gone through I've seen
it all and it's uterine fibroids both on
top of the uterus ins inside the uterus
and um it's it's been it's given women a
lot of difficult decisions to make um
and it's been just cumbersome and in the
way in so many in so many ways so I I
just think this is an
important aspect of chronic
illness that you know that needs
attention on the medical Medium show
bottom line it needs attention and
attention that hasn't been contaminated
with you know private panel of
influencers that just want you to think
fibroid is a certain thing or a certain
way or whatever because that's where the
money went and um because the agenda
goes you know with money and that's how
it works both now in uh alternative
medicine so misinformation is out there
everywhere on the internet everywhere
everywhere you look about fibroids and
if you even look into it you someone was
telling me also recently and they said
you know it's so strange you know how
fibroids work I go yeah no I do they say
well how come how come if you go looking
into it what's the cause of Fire
fibroids the answer isn't there there is
no answer there is no answer a little
bit of theory maybe some
speculation I I I said well what do you
mean it's like that with all chronic
illness it's like yeah you're right yeah
no of course I'm right it's like that
with all chronic illness what what you
kidding and even if there is a known
cause to a chronic illness chances are
it's totally wrong or planted that way
Plant it wrong it's planted that way
chronic illness is a weird weird thing
for the industry they hate it it's like
dirty laundry for the industries it's
dirty laundry because it it truly shows
it
truly
uncovers that the that the medical
industry absolutely doesn't have their
finger on the pulse of the people
doesn't have their finger on the pulse
of chronic illness on any level it just
exposes tremendous amounts of medical
denial and because of this it all gets
funneled into the gene thing even the
fibroid and the reason why I'm saying is
is even the fibroid the whole thing with
fibroids is oh it's hereditary oh it's
it's genes no it's
not it's not
hereditary it's not Gene related once
again insult insult insult women insult
people insult people's intelligence
insult people's beings and who they are
just insult away just insult every
second is what the industry does by
doing that that's what they do when they
do that it's horrendous no there's a
real cause and you can have it your
daughter can have it her daughter can
have it their daughter can have it
somebody else's daughter can have it
somebody else's mom can have it somebody
it just goes right down the line because
there's a real
reason why everybody's got it going on
there's a real reason why everybody has
it so let's just you you know what just
just just just treat people like they're
dumb just treat them like they're dumb
oh it's it's it's jeans let's just let's
just keep doing that oh no we're going
to put another 20 trillion dollar into
jeans because it you can get suckered
into it because it's oh it's jeans you
see your nose your nose looks like your
your your father's nose and it looks
like your mother's nose you see see
jeans you see how it's an easy cell you
can't escape that oh wait a minute um
you oh you just you just like your
mom just like your grandmother did oh
you got the same rose-colored hair as
your
grandom oh see and and see jeans Oh no
you're sick oh no that's jeans oh it is
okay great it's an easy cell it's
disgusting because it's it's it's it's
an
insult it's a way to dumb down the
people and then take tons and tons of
money and mess with jeans in the
industry in the back in the labs and
then feed us some stuff that we do like
to hear your DNA strand depend you know
you can live longer if your DNA strand
looks better and just look at all the
trillions of dollars that went into our
industry and we can give you some
different things about
jeans and okay yeah and if you have an
if you have an illness or even even if
your baby has an illness oh it's genetic
always genetic no it's not it's
not jeans do play a role in our life
but not in chronic illness and I'm
saying all this because I just throw
anything in the genan basket anything
and they threw fibroids in the gene
basket it's
unbelievable it's disgusting it is
because it's negligence to womenkind
it's negligence to women it's
negligence to humankind is what it is
and that's what they do that's not the
doctor or whatever you do it's not the
doctors we need them they're good people
you know everybody everybody you know
every now and then I get somebody and
other person says oh I hear it you don't
like that what are you talking about you
better go to your doctor you better
shake your doctor's hand and tell them
that you love him and you're so thankful
they're even helping you that's what you
need to do you tell your doctor I'm
thankful that you're sitting here in the
trenches in the trenches day in day out
and you're trying to help people every
day you get up you put your pants on you
put your socks on you put your shoes on
you put your white coat on you grab a
piece of crappy
toast and then you just and you run
outside the door and you get to your
clinic you get to your office you get to
wherever it is you get to the hospital
wherever the heck you're
working day in and day out whether
you're natural functional medicine
natural medicine uh regular MD whatever
stuffy old MD that doesn't like anything
natural whatever you
are whatever you are you shake your
doctor's hand you tell them thank thank
you for doing what you're doing even
though I feel miserable even though I
got symptoms even though you may not
even know what's going on with my
chronic illness thank you for doing what
you're doing it's the kind of respect I
have towards doctors serious
stuff but it's the industry the industry
doesn't help the doctors the industry is
not helping the doctors with Lyme
disease at all they give them some bogus
information from new fangled Labs that
just got it all down think they got it
all down doctor has no idea what's going
on at the lab ever just gets the
information says borderline you got
borderline lime borderline wait a minute
how can it be borderline it's either no
or yay yay or nay when it comes down to
if it's nay you still can have a
pathogen if they can't find a pathogen
you can still have one yes if they find
a pathogen they found a pathogen you
have a pathogen you could have a lot of
different pathogens the point is you
can't have
borderline what a stupid mistake those
labs made by doing that cuz you're not
going to see that anymore any more
that's a mistake by the way that's a
mistake and you're not going to see that
anymore because they don't want the gig
to be up at the lime Labs you need to
know that when it's the borderline thing
that was a bad decision on their part
you're going to see that disappear soon
and it's never going to be borderline
it's just going to be more and more yays
yays yay yay more and more you have lime
more and more you have lime out there
and less borderline because the
borderline shows something's wrong
something's mischievously St stupidly
wrong over there because
you can't have borderline pathogen you
either detect it you can't detect a
little bit of the pathogen it means it's
a yes if any bit of a pathogen's
detected you can't have borderline and
this is where it's said this what I'm
saying the industry is screwing with the
doctors in every way in every shape form
and possible so doctors have don't have
the right information don't know what's
going on this is how it's done this is
how it's done and the amount and and
it's unbelievable when money's starts to
file into this whole thing in all the
different aspects of chronic illness it
it becomes negligent and it leaves the
person in the dark and it gets all
thrown into jeans in the end yeah
insulting people cuz people do have the
same hair color as their mother they do
have the same hair their noses are the
same they do have the same lips they do
have some same features around the chin
bone structures so it's such an easy
cell it's
sick it really is so let's get down to
Let's Get Down to the truth about
fibroids I have to talk about this a
little bit because if I don't then then
you'll never know because if you never
know then you might you might just go
somewhere and say oh I'll listen to this
other medical show from this other
practitioner and then you know and and
just not realize what's even going on
you got to know that's the whole point
of the show spirit said look we got to
start doing things people got to know
the truth I said all right I'm on it I'm
on it I'm on it I'll shake shake out of
it let me uh let me snap after let me
wake up let me keep on going I'll keep
on going Spirit what else do we have to
do to get people the
truth okay all right what's the cause of
fibroids what is the cause what well the
industry says oh done clear maybe it's
estrogen
maybe maybe maybe it's
progesterone
maybe maybe it's too much red
meat that's also a concept in the
industry too much red meat maybe it's
too much
alcohol you know
maybe
maybe red meats a trigger for something
else because yeah a lot of red meat will
probably guarantee some
fibroids a lot of eggs will guaranteed
fibroids for
sure but why and the industry doesn't
know that though they here's what it's
really funny they'll put believe it or
not the industry will
actually give an uppercut or a low jab
to red meat I mean they'll just punch
the Sucker Punch red meat right in the
stomach and they'll just say you know
let's throw this one in and let's throw
alcohol in you know we notice that women
that eat a lot of red meat they tend to
have a little bit more fibroids which
we're kind of noticing let's really
let's Sucker Punch that one but they
will never sucker punch
eggs they'll never sucker punch those
darn eggs really interesting how it
works
eggs are the ultimate ultimate
proliferating food for fibrates you want
fibroids you eat eggs you don't want
fibroids to go away you eat you eat
eggs the ultimate ultimate fibid Creator
it's the ultimate
trigger the ultimate trigger could
estrogen too much estrogen progesterone
possibly create a
fibroid
yeah it could possibly feed a fibroid
but why what's the cause it's not
estrogen there's people out there that
have so much estrogen they have tons of
estrogen they eat a lot of red meat they
drink a lot of alcohol they do things
that would prompt fibroids but they
never get the fibroids because you have
to have something else in the body to
feed to throw it estrogen to throw it
progesterone to throw it red meat to
throw
it stuff right you have to have
something these are just triggers why do
you think you know it's the same thing
with like the old guy that smoked for 60
years he smoked for 60 years
cigars you know stoies
whatever those cancerous stoies you
smoked him for 60 years he's 84 years
old he eats a donut in the morning I I
know guys like that by the
way you know I know guys like that they
get up they have a you know they have
a whatever they have some canoli in the
morning some canoli yeah seriously they
have the croissant croissant or
something in the morning I don't even
know how you say croissant if someone
said in a real French way recently I'm
like wow that's pretty cool I'm not
French and you know and the thing is is
that and I like the way it sounded it
made me want to go and get one made me
want to go and get one and then I've
heard somebody say cant they said
croissant they go I had I said what did
you eat today and they said I had a
croissant I said what I said you know a
croissant and it took me a while to
figure it
out people say it all kinds of different
ways I love it I love it and you know um
I've seen guys they eat that they'll eat
that they'll eat anything they have that
for breakfast they have a box of donuts
for breakfast they're smoking like
chimney you know the scotch we'll have a
scotch whiskey later on that
night and uh you know their lungs are
filled with 60 years of smoke 70 years
of smoke 70 years and they don't have
lung cancer it's like why the hell do
they don't have lung cancer I don't get
because they needed something to feed to
create the lung cancer they needed
something inside of them to feed the
lung cancer
I and I've seen that with some women
it's really rare and it's rare getting
rare every day it's not like oh my God
you know I found when I found Elder
people in the old days I say you know
when I'd go to like a a nursing home or
something like that or or if I'd go
somewhere you know there was just less
older people in nursing homes things
like that you know when I was younger I
used to visit all those all the time you
know I had clients and people be like
look you have to come to the nursing
home you have to see you know because
nursing homes they won't they won't do
anything for the people there meaning
they won't take like natural B12 and
give it to them they they they never do
it the the the the the siblings have to
really be involved like you have to be
really be involved I remember so many
times so many cases where they'd be like
Anthony you got to come out here and you
got to take a look at my my
great-grandfather you have to my
grandmother my great-grandfather you
have to take a look I'd go out to a
nursing home and I was like how come
there's not that many old people here
and the old people here that are here
they're really really old and
then that one decade goes by and they
like whoa why are there a lot more
younger people in here whoa another
decade goes by oh my God that person's
45 years old and dying in the corner oh
dear lord what that person's
38 and you go in there now into these
places and it's unbelievable
I mean you find them in their 20s
wasting away with mystery disease and
dying either in one of those places or
at home or or whatever it's unbelievable
and then and then it's crazy there's
less old people there's less older
people there's less older generation in
these
places they're all younger now you're
going to tell me that's genes too that
all happened in the last 30 years genes
completely changed in the last 30 years
and and all these young people are sick
so so genes that have been going on for
thousands of years since humankind going
on for thousands of years since
humankind thousands of years all of a
sudden in the last 20 30 years genes
changed completely just completely
changed and then chronic illness
exploded like no other no other yeah you
watch TV everybody looks healthy on the
TV besides there's a zillion cancer
commercials now but if you you know but
you look at TV you see all the actors
they look healthy of course Spirit tells
me they're not and many then I still see
things in and out of it all if I watch
TV but if you look at you look if you
look on television because if I go over
a family member's house and they got the
television on and I I have to stand
there I have to watch it and I'm like
God it it everybody paints a picture
like the whole world is healthy you
wouldn't believe chronic illness has
exploded hundreds of millions of people
just in the us alone 200 million plus
Americans got
problems but it's not genes it couldn't
happen in it couldn't happened in 20
years that's the insult
insulting so things have changed and
everything and fibbr are now they're on
the rise like never before and remember
earlier on it wasn't like that but
they're on the rise the whole fibroid
thing so there's triggers for fibroids
and that's what the industry kind of
doesn't want to really say they just
don't even know the C they try to make
it cause the trigger as cause that's a
mistake you know in the Hashimoto
thyroid
book I don't do trigger as cause I know
the cause I put the cause in the thyroid
healing book I do the triggers
separately you go into somebody else's
thyroid stuff and you check into it they
have the trigger as
cause completely backwards like
Antiquity it's unbelievable here we are
what year is it and they still don't
know come on come on it's
unbelievable so that red meat the
alcohol gets thrown in gets thrown in as
hey this is this is what's creating the
fibroids throw estrogen in it too that's
what's creating the
fibroids it's not fibroids are a virus
it's a small virus virus I talk about
day in day out fibroid virus is Epstein
bar it's in everybody and if you feed it
just right it's going to come out and
it's going to create some stuff and and
it creates a fbid a growth a
growth can create a lot of growths and
it could create some and just you know
and and what does it love to feed on it
loves to feed on certain things lots of
things dairy products why isn't dairy
products in there as a trigger
whoa because for some reason you know
you just don't want to not you don't
want to Sucker Punch the yogurt
industry you just don't because yogurt
are yogurt's supposed to be healthy for
women it's one of those things that
lines up and it's supposed to be healthy
for women it's disastrous for women
yogurt is the worst thing for Women's
Health you don't believe me fine nothing
I can do then you don't believe me you
know you could be brand new to the show
and you're like oh god the guy thinks
yogurt's bad for you unbelievable all
that natural you know acidophilus and
everything else he doesn't even know
what he's talking about no I do I do
yogurt feeds see yogurt feeds the virus
up bar the variety that causes fibroids
the variety that goes to the
reproductive system that causes
fibroids and yogurt feeds
it if it didn't I wouldn't be picking on
it why would I pick on
it Scott why would I pick on
it you know but it feeds but here's what
the industry does it
protects certain items and it makes sure
that women eat more of those items oh
got to get my calcium I got to have my
milk I got to have my dairy products I
have to have my calcium I need my
protein for my cheese and as a woman the
industry tricks you and it's like no no
here's a little snack pack you open up
your snack pack and I got my nuts which
is okay I got my cheese
squares all right and I got my little
ham
pieces it's protein it's perfect for a
woman on the go it's absurd and they do
this purposely so that you never learn
so you get a fibroid and they do it so
that your daughter gets a fibroid they
do it so that your daughter's daughter
gets a fibroid also keeps the industry
happy keeps the industry fat and happy
boy that's why that's there that's why
that's there they protect those cheese
squares they they Sucker Punch red meat
cuz red meat doesn't really cause
fibroids to to to a degree it's just
that red meat red meat eaters usually
also like cheese and crackers they also
a lot of like cheese they like a lot of
eggs they you know that kind of stuff
they won't pick on those for a
reason remember agenda I said it in the
beginning you know also somebody of the
other day said you know you got this new
beginning I don't like it in your show I
hate it there's a new beginning in your
show and I've known you for a while
Anthony and there's this new beginning
you talk about all these groups blah
blah blah and the
information I go too bad if you don't
like it it has to be there I have no
choice because spirit I had a talk with
spirit and spirit tells me that people
just think you can get this information
anywhere else all the people the new
people that come to the show and and and
they don't know the other information
how it's contaminated and spirit doesn't
like being affiliate affiliated with
contaminated information that's on the
internet and both Natural Health and
conventional health and I I have to I
have to honor that so it is what it is
but those agenda groups they protect
those little cheese squares they're
protected so you get fibroids
more so you get more fibroids and you're
thinking well who's protecting it my
doctor isn't no your doctor isn't your
doctor's good it's all good but there's
private panel of influencers private
panel of think
tankers that you couldn't believe
exist you have no
idea they protect those cheese squares
they protect eggs in fact when you got
PCOS what's the most recommended food
for the body for a woman's body when you
got PCOS which is also Epstein bar
caused and people with PCOS usually have
uterine fibroids too and they usually
get them at some point they have the
they have the cysts and they have the
the fibroids and they have the cysts and
what's what's you know what's the number
one food
eggs get off of fruit make sure you get
off of
fruit You Know That Snack Pack won't
have a piece of fruit in it but it'll
have oh little squares little squares of
cheese oh some nuts that's good it's
unbelievable they oh little bacon slices
not bacon slices little ham slices and
hey I'm passionate about this topic with
fibroids because I can't stand people
getting taken advantage of women getting
taken advantage of that's my sore spot
right there that's my sour spot because
I've I've dedicated my life to womenkind
where I've seen chronic illness and it's
been the majority of the people who have
come to me for decades since I was young
starting with my grandmother and it
hurts it hurts it hurts and without
womenkind you can't nothing gets done
right because I don't care what anybody
says women are still smarter than men I
mean you know you know men are great too
men are men men are smart too men are
smart too I know that and Men Are Great
too you need men for men are important
too I know they're just as important I
just say this because I get red up
because of seen a lot of H things happen
in chronic illness but um I've helped
helped out a lot of men in my lifetime
and uh there's some great people out
there both women and men in the world
and salt of the earth and you can't you
can't touch that the salt of the earth
so here's the deal here's the deal we
got to watch out with the foods because
the foods play a massive
role because they're the trigger to an
Epstein bar virus that kind of goes into
the reprodu productive system that kind
of gets into that reproductive system
and causes some
trouble and we have to be really mindful
about that we have to be on that it's
important first of all we got to do
things and knock down the Epstein bar
virus that got into the reproductive
system and that EP bar virus causes
pregnancy complications all the time for
women all the time this isn't just
pelvic inflammatory disease which is
strepa cacus Strep cacus which is you
know antibiotic resistant strep cacus
that gets into the reproductive system
and causes a lot of different
inflammation in different areas and
that's
PID yeah because there's so many
different varieties of strep and you can
pick up strep anyhow it's just it's easy
to pick up but but the deal is and
people have it they have strep in them
but the Epstein bar is the that's makes
that that growth which kind of like a
smooth piece of
muscle Mak can get big real big so what
we got to do is we got to knock those
down
we got to you know there's there was I
remember this one case I think it was in
2000 so it was uh what 17 years ago and
um she wanted to do things natural she
was suffering a lot of bleeding um the
doctors said that that it was it was
bigger than a small great fruit the
fibroid the uterine fibroid and it was
causing tremendous amount of pain and
they just said look hysterctomy
hysterectomy and I understand I
understand you know I understand when um
when doctors they feel they have no
choice and you know and there's certain
situations and circumstances where you
have to do hysterctomy I I you know what
women have had gone through and there's
reasons for that and there's a lot of
things that happen and
occur and you know we we try to avoid if
we can naturally in any way possible or
even conventionally in any way possible
absolutely but in in some cases you you
just can't avoid it and it's it it can
happen totally totally and and uh so so
this this woman she had a serious she
had a serious fibroid it was just it was
agonizing and she said well what can we
do about it I'm desperate I'm desperate
I said well we can do something about it
let's change your diet let's overhaul it
let's overhaul it to such a degree we're
talking about the whole bit we're going
to do every green juice we're going to
do all the fruits just fruits and green
juice you're going to live on for a
while it's not your permanent diet you
can go back to the foods you like and
different kinds of foods except for the
ones that create create a fibroid and I
said you know we we just have to with
fruits and green juices and she was like
that's going to be hard to do but I'm
going to try it she did the fruits and
green juices meaning got enough calories
lots of bananas banana smoothies banana
smoothies and celery banana smoothies
and celery lots of different veggies
lots of leafy greens but lots of bananas
lots of different fruits bananas being a
staple and it was it was not it's not an
easy diet it's not but she didn't have a
lot of options she was bleeding and not
just bleeding very
seriously but I mean she was suffering
suffering and they they had this they
had this fibroid
measured they had it measured and they
were watching it and she did this for 30
days she went back they couldn't find
it it was
gone baffled they were baffled I mean
when I mean baffled I mean baffled they
were scratching their head they were
confounded to such a degree baffled they
were so confused it just made no sense
they asked her did you go for surgery
somewhere we can't we just this doesn't
make sense she like go for surgery
you're my doctors what are you talking
about I asked her what happened she says
well I I took a bunch of different herbs
and I'm going to talk about that I'm
going to talk about that I took a bunch
of different
herbs and and I changed my diet
radically just for a short time for the
days this healer
guy he uh he gave me some directions on
this and they're like this is not
possible they they were stunned but
stunned
stunned speechless speechless I know
because they talked with me they talked
with me they said I just can we talk to
the guy she said I I don't know he's
really busy he worked from 700 in the
morning till 11:00 at night at the
office and they were like okay well just
please can we talk to him found a little
time they got on the phone with me for a
little bit and they
said how did this happen and I said well
you know what happened was we stopped
feeding the virus that's inside the
fibroid and they said what virus inside
the thyroid this is 17 years ago it was
like a spaceship landed a spaceship
landed from outer space and a bunch of
aliens came out of the spaceship and
greeted said hello humans they were in
total disbelief they're like what do you
mean virus what are you talking about
virus this fibroid started because of
estrogen that's what it is it's an
estrogen fibroid we don't know you know
this and that and whatnot trying to tell
me trying to give me science try to give
me science that's not even clear and I
said yeah well it's a virus it's the
they were what kind of virus it said the
upen bar they go they laugh they go oh
my God yeah
right I
go laugh as you may or must but I'm
telling you what it is that's the
Epstein bar virus like kep bar virus
that's that's what that's the mono thing
she doesn't have mono I because she had
Mono 30 years ago and they're like yeah
what are you talking about I go oh my
God I I I I got my brain cells were
burning up I was getting stupider by the
minute I this 17 years ago was getting
stupider by the second I said all right
listen I know you're busy I'm busy too I
know you're you know you're doing your
thing I got to do my thing I can't I
can't talk I can't do this anymore and
they said no no wait seriously we're
gonna we're not going to laugh I'm not I
swear to
God and I said look laugh all you want
she had Mono 30 years ago the virus
hides out in the liver and hides out in
the reproductive system after the
mono and it sits in there and it awaits
to be fed there's different varieties
and they're like different varieties of
Epstein bar people still do that now
they're like different
varieties I go yeah there's different
varieties I go and some are more docile
some just are just fibroid causers some
don't really do much they give you a
little mono sometimes you get a mono you
don't even know you had Mono and then
later on you get fibroids down the road
and so forth and if you're eating and
drinking or doing things that are bad
like you're triggering it or you're
under severe emotional stress and she
was under a tremendous amount of
emotional
stress and now I think about it's 9 17
years ago I think this is 19 years ago
19 years
ago that's what this is it's about 19
years
ago the time's flying so fast I'm just
I'm baffled by the way time flies
actually so it's close to 19 years I
think it was
98 99 I think it's
98 and you know they were so confused so
confused and I was explaining the whole
thing about Epstein bar how it works
what it's doing how it feeds how it eats
How It Grow the muscle the smooth muscle
the growth how it works underneath where
the virus is located all of
this and now you better not eat eggs and
she was being she was eating a lot of
eggs she was eating two eggs a day to
get her protein she was putting them
hardboiled on her salad and then she was
just having them in the morning too
sometimes she' do three eggs sometimes
she three four eggs a day recommended by
the doctors they said eggs she needs her
Protein that's the whole point I said oh
dear lord we're back to that again and
here we are 19 years later you still
hear the same mumble jumble they protein
protein oh my God eggs are the best food
it's like nothing changed it's why
Spirit also changed my My Life by saying
okay you're leaving the office for now
you buy office spirit said we can't I
said no I don't want to leave the office
said spirit said no you got to put this
out on books you got to put this out on
the radio you got to do what you got to
do this is just it's not getting
better so the idea is we got to knock
down the upsteam bar but what we can do
is not just do that we we take away the
triggers it's great it's great remove
triggers no eggs ever no dairy products
ever
lower the amount of red meat cuz red
meat's so filled with adrenaline that
that could trigger it a little
bit and if you're under a lot of stress
the the the uh adrenals pump out so much
different so much in complex hormones
when you're under fear or stress or
anxiety or anything else like that in
your life or any kind of problems that
could feed the virus and create a
fibroid so we have to try to de-stress a
little bit we have to DEC
compartmentalize if we even have to we
have to you go to the beach we have to
say waves they're crashing on the beach
that's what I'm seeing I'm not I'm not
seeing I'm not seeing the divorce I went
through I'm not seeing you know the
problems I got at work I'm not seeing
this and that I'm not just I see waves I
see I see clouds you got to you got to
you got to get the stress levels down so
there's adrenals calm down a little bit
it's all part of stopping fibroids and
younger women they get the fibroids
absolutely because they got the Epstein
bar early of course you get the Epstein
bar really early you're 14 years old
once those hormones start kicking in
they can feed the Epstein bar once
anything kicks in stress responsibility
you know there's there's there's I mean
young women that that they have to all
of a sudden go middle middle school to
high school and that that alone is just
a tremendous amount of stress they get
mono you name it high school um High
School you're 18 19 years old you got to
go to college and that alone is really
stressful you get mono in college mono
becomes a problem you get a fibroid by
the time you're 29 years old you get a
little bit of you get a little bit of um
PCOS possibly developing your doctor is
like okay you got to go on the pill the
pill itself is problematic too a lot
because the pill can stimulate a fibroid
because the pill can aggravate Epstein
bar feed Epstein bar so that's something
too that's that's a concern but we do
the best we can so what I'd say as you
work with diet you knock things down
lots of fruit fruit is incredible for
the uterus the uterus and fruit go hand
in hand the uterus creates a fruit it
creates a fruit it create it it that's
the whole point it grows a
child it's like a pod that grows a
child it grows a
baby that's the
fruit that is the
fruit I mean that's fruit is so critical
so
important it goes hand in hand with the
woman's reproductive system so to take
out
fruit for some you know
terrible lame reason in the
industries is it's just something you
don't want to
do but oh yeah that's right they put a
little bit of fruit and yogurt they do
there's the sarcasm again I can't help
it I can't help it so one thing and I
told you I I told you there is the
sarcasm in there because of the passion
because I I feel bad too and but the
sarcasm I can't help it a little bit of
that comes out I said to spe a long time
ago I said look you can't change me
though I remember I was a kid and I was
sarc I was a sarcastic little kid and
spirit said look I don't expect to
change you I just need you to stay
alive that's what spirit said I need you
to stay alive just stay alive and just
and just and work for me for the people
I said I guess I can do that but you're
not going to change who I am I said to
Spirit you're not going to make me more
spiritual I'm not going to put a gown on
and and walk around in a gown I'm not
going to be all more spiritual I'm not
going to have flowers in my hair I mean
I love that I think it's really cool I
got a friend that looks like that all
the time and I think it's really cool
but I can't do that I can't have my
hands together 24/7 in the prayer mode
and stuff and the prayer posst I can't
do that all the time I am extremely
spiritual but I like it my friends do it
because you know they I don't know they
look so cool I don't look
cool then you know if you if you look
cool doing it then then that's that's
awesome because I always say God you
look so cool I love it like you look so
cool they're like well you can do it too
you can look really cool you can totally
look like spiritual L and I go no I look
like a geek look like a geek look at my
photo like I'm a geek and you know and
the thing is is that a sarcastic like I
guess a little geek and you know and I
said Spirit you can't change me I'm not
going to go more spiritual in a way
where I look more spiritual I'm going to
be sarcastic and spirit said it's okay
doesn't matter doesn't matter we love
you who you are we just need you to stay
alive and get the information out little
bit by little come on I said all right
all right all right I'll do it I had a
struggle with with that actually the
time I got into the early teens and mid
teens I was like I can't take this
anymore everybody else is having fun and
doing what they want to do and I got to
hear Spirit 24/7 247 about fibroids but
then I realize it's the most important
thing in the world is making sure we get
fibroids better than women that's the
whole point that's the I mean women in
reproductive systems to keep the human
race going keep us strong keep women
strong
because they mean so much in our
lives my God going back in history all
the way to the
beginning and it's the most important
thing in the world and so um it matters
it matters herbs raspberry leaf
incredible for knocking down fibroids
because it does level out the hormones a
little bit hormones that feed EP steam
bar estrogens a woman's estrogen is not
necessarily the estrogen that feeds the
the Epstein bar virus creating a fibroid
so
much it's it what it is it's estrogens
that are in Foods estrogens in eggs
estrogens in Dairy estrogens in yeah red
meat little bit in there estrogens in
all kinds of different things though
estrogens and Plastics estrogens and
solvents medications you name it it's
unbelievable and and those are the
estrogens that that that need to get
eliminated and pushed out of the body
and they collect they build up in the
liver the liver has the liver and the
uterus are like they're married together
they're married together the
liver it's like the
husband the uterus is like the wife
seriously
seriously the liver gets all toxic it's
all toxic and all filled with
crap no I see where this is going I
don't think this is going in a good
place the liver gets all toxic and it
gets all fil filled with crab and
everything right and then and then you
know and that's a problem because you
know the epscene bar sits in the liver
and it's you know doing its thing it's
not just that all the poisons all the
estrogens are trapped in the liver the
liver traps all the estrogens the liver
is cleaning up all this stuff and and
and has all this
stuff and you know and that's not good a
clean liver helps out a clean liver
helps a uterus get better
a clean husband helps a wife get
better you know and so it they're like
hand in hand the estrogens get all
trapped in the liver the liver holds a
lot of different bad estrogens cuz
trying to protect you but they they the
liver gets so clogged up because of say
red meat too much red meat or too much
eggs or whatever it is too they get
clogged up fried greasy food whatever
and it's not good the estrogens they get
they have to get released they get
release but they don't get out of the
body in time reproductive system takes
takes it I mean it gets saturated a
little bit feeds the Epstein bar
raspberry leaf is great incredible
that's a great one you do lots of tea
lots of raspberry leaf tea nettle Leaf
oh my God dear Lord man nettle Leaf is
like it's like ah it's like this it's
it's this heavenly
Heavenly beautiful thing nettle Leaf
it's a God's gift to women kind God's
gift to womenkind is nettle Leaf nettle
Leaf is
incredible he could do so much with it
it's it's not it's it's unbelievable
great for fibroids incredible for
fibroids is that nettle
Leaf it's it's a great one and he's are
just you know he's easy breezy so isn't
like a jungle weed you got to go and
fight for you know out in some jungle
somewhere you know on a different
continent and it's not that manetta leaf
is that powerful is that amazing and
then lots of different fruits of all
kinds
berries apples oh apples really help
really help the reproductive system for
women salads yep salads that's right you
know how men are like oh like salads
it's a girls thing girls girls eat their
salads thank God girls are eating their
salads even if they throw an egg in
there at least getting their they're
they're getting that happens all the
time eggs are always thrown in
the salads you know if you're going to
eat an egg regardless and you're going
to have one no matter what I say or what
I do or whatever have it in a salad
that's the best way to have an egg you
that's the best way seriously if you're
going to have one boy they taste good
those eggs God they taste good I mean I
haven't had one since I was a kid but
boy do they taste
good yeah no I miss those I miss those
so here's the deal here here's the deal
um we got to take away the eggs got to
take away the dairy okay we have to be
careful with that lower the animal
proteins lower them get the liver a
little bit better the fibroids will go
way faster you won't
feed the Epstein bar fibroid variety you
won't feed it and you can be in a better
place a much better place you can reduce
it like in that in the end of that story
of my client back 19 years ago I've had
dozens and dozens of those after that
dozens I just picked that one because
the doctors it was it was in the earlier
days and the doctors just laughed at me
they laughed at me about that she wasn't
laughing her husband wasn't
laughing her husband wasn't laughing in
fact she met somebody a new person and
they be they were you know a new person
she got married again that husband
wasn't laughing at all that husband was
so happy to see her happy it was just it
was it was just because she he saw
pictures of the old days he saw what she
went through he knew the struggle he
learned the struggle he he you know he
listened and he was happy you know the
family the daughters were happy
everybody was happy the doctors weren't
happy because was too much too much they
were they were they were happy for her
but they were just this is you know come
on they they saw it as in like a
miraculous intervention that had to be
something Angelic which I did like them
thinking
because I like that cuz that that does
happen in the world but it's been a lot
of lot of gotten a lot of fibroids down
over the years lots and lots and lots
and you can do it lots of lettuces
Kale's a good one any kind of lettuce is
actually amazing romae lettuce is
amazing for
fibroids very important spinach spinach
is an incredible fibroid reducer an
incredible one fennel just remember that
one fennel put it in Juice celery of
course lots of celery fennel just
remember fennel I got to say three four
times know the bulb the fennel bulb if
you need to steam it steam it chop it up
and steam it in a vegetable soup put in
vegetable soup with all the the fennel
in there tastes like a tastes a little
like licorice that's a great one don't
be afraid of that one papaya amazing for
fibroids what a fibroid weapon papaya
mangoes a fibroid weapon too berries
especially a f apples fibroid weapon um
banan fibroid weapon yeah bananas evil
bananas evil
bananas unbelievable great cucumbers
cucumbers zucchinis incredible fibroid
weapons I love those amazing winter
squash a fibroid weapon all these are
weapons to fibroids all of
them without a doubt they are lemon bomb
Oh my God lemon bomb Epstein bar hates
lemon bomb especially Epstein bar that
got into the uterus that got into the
reproductive system for years and years
and years has been sitting there waiting
to create a fibroid
hates Melissa hates Melissa like no
other no other
Melissa knows what Melissa's doing let
me tell you the phytochemical compounds
in
Melissa literally go after Epstein bar
it's just amazing what happens there you
know not you can't mess with Melissa I'm
telling you that right now you can't you
can't and you do you know the Melissa
incredible you know lemon bomb that's
the you guys know that that's the name
for
balm it's so cool that's so cool and and
it says a lot it says a lot names mean a
lot names mean a
lot they mean a lot and so it matters
names matter and and and when you when a
name is attached to an herb whoa it's
incredible because you got the spirit of
a Melissa that doesn't take any crap at
all that's strong passionate about what
she's doing I want wants to stomp on
anything in her way and that's what
lemon bomb reminds me of and that's what
lemon bomb reminds me of and it's it's
really cool and so that's that's a great
one with lots of lemon bomb tea lots of
lemon bomb tea the whole bit and I know
these are Basics I talk about these a
lot because because a lot of illnesses
and chronic illnesses are Epstein bar
derived many of them are and you know I
use a lot of these other ones and and
and women they're suffering with all
kinds of different things lemon bomb's
great for chronic fatigue it's great for
all kinds of different things related
with Epstein bar
and you know it's
important but these are some of the
basics to get started on if you do the
foods you have something in your hand
really powerful ashwag Ganda is a good
one too
ashwagandha ashwag
gandha that's a good one what is it Ash
uh w a g n dhaa DHA I think that's the
uh the spelling if I could remember
ashwag is a great one too little bit of
that that goes a long way for with
fibroids it is helpful so that's another
good one and um but in the food realm
all fruits of all kinds cherries really
help with fibroids cherries cranberries
really help with fibroids cranberries
right right all of these are helpful and
then any vegetable is helpful you know
all vegetables are helpful sparus work
really good with fibroids too I've had
great great relief you know with
fibroids with women over the years
spirit Spirit would say juice asparagus
juice
asparagus and you know in the days when
people didn't even know you could juice
asparagus be like juice asparagus they
would juice it every single day raw
asparagus juice it and the fibroids
would
reduce they would
reduce we can take
control we can take control and do what
we need to
do so see these are some of the things
to consider
and once you know what creates your
fibroids you only get stronger I'm going
to tell you that right now once you know
what creates your fibroids you only get
stronger Epstein bar weakens when you
know the truth which makes me upset
about the
industries they either don't know about
Epstein bar with all the different
things that spirit and I know or if they
do know God help
them meaning God help them because
they're messing up bad by not letting
anybody know what what's the real cause
of anything thing if they do
know and you know seriously it's sad and
because when you do know what causes
something you get stronger your immune
system goes after the very thing that
causes a fibroid when you know what's
going on when you know what's wrong it's
half the battle I say it every time I
got to say that one more time half the
battle of healing is knowing what's
wrong what's the other half what's the
other half knowing what to do knowing
what to do
okay and also remember that I love you
and I care all right thank you for
listening thank you for taking an hour
out of your life to listen to me you
know just cry and complain and
everything else just thank you and take
one day at a time you can heal you will
heal you just you give your body a break
be easy on it have some compassion for
yourself pat yourself on the back be
easy be easy on yourself okay just know
that I care and I stand behind you 100%
I'm with you one day at a time one day
at a time it's not an easy place to live
in this world but we're lucky we're
lucky in so many ways bless your heart I
can't wait to see you again I'll see you
see you next week all right love you
take
care