Amazing. Is Patrick still here? Is he
still here tonight? Patrick,
this guy right here.
Seriously, I just want to give a mic to
you.
Hi guys.
Thank you so much. It's been such an
honor the last 3 days. I just like
reflecting on some of the conversations
I've had. One of the conversations
really stood out to me where it was two
sisters and it was 10 years that went by
that they haven't dined together in a
restaurant because of her sister and her
chronic illness. It's stories like that
that really make me excited to
participate and be able to provide this
type of cuisine and have you guys be
able to be out in a restaurant, enjoy
the community.
[Music]
I love Cafe Gratitude. It's like a place
I've been coming to for a long time. I
love the food. I don't even have to
think about the ingredients. I don't
have to think about whether it's bad for
me. It just feels so good to be able to
go to a place, be able to trust it. I'm
incredibly grateful for Cathic
Gratitude, the creativity that they put
into it. I want to thank Patrick. We got
in contact with him and said, "Hey, you
know, we have a child with special
needs. We need like a table." And he got
us our table. Just enjoy food together
without having to worry about how it's
going to affect us. Is amazing. It feels
like the best party ever.
[Music]
There's a good vibe here and I think a
lot of it begins with the food at Cafe
Gratitude. Being able to metaphorically
break bread with your people is oh it's
so magical. I love it. Just really
amazing souls. Everybody here has gone
through the healing journey. So I feel
like there's just an essence of
gratitude here which is so perfect for
the place. Right. Everyone has this
beautiful light and is so joyous because
they've decided to take back the reigns
of their destiny and they're doing what
they love. And just to just hear their
stories and to share space with them has
been so special. and to connect with
this broader community of people who
just love being here and being in
communion with people in a world that is
more fragmented than ever. People here
remind me and offer me hope that the
future can continue to look more
interconnected and more peaceful and
more loving because that is what we were
all built to do. And it's beautiful to
share that with people. It's it's
unbelievable.
Just super grateful for you and we're
glad we can, you know, help the
community. So,
thank you so much. We love you guys so
much. Thank you.
[Music]