[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium I'm Anthony William you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I bring about the
most advanced healing information
decades ahead of what's out there now
very important show we have going on
this is a big one right here it's all
about fasting all about fasting we're
going to be talking about fasting juice
fasting water fasting intermittent
fasting we're going to be talking about
dry fasting we're going to be talking
about all of it and it's it's a really
it's really an important show I think it
is because there's a lot of people doing
different kinds of things out there and
trying different kinds of things and and
are they good are they bad do they work
do they not work the whole bit
everybody's different we're going to
talk about why and how and what's the
safest way to go about things and and
what we can do so I mean this is really
a good show because um because there's a
lot of confusion out there and I want to
air out that confusion and I want to
make sure I want to make sure that
everybody has the best opportunity to
heal on all levels now what you're going
to find out is that I don't have this
belief system I'm not swallowed up into
a belief system that's that's also
supported with all kinds of excuse me
that's also supported with all kinds of
supplements that you know packages you
have to buy and you have to buy a
package from me or you have to buy you
know hey here's part of my fasting kit
here's part of my fasting thing oh here
you know do this do my fasting course
pay this pay $1,400 pay
$5,000 you know like you're not going to
get any of that from me there's nothing
there's no belief system sucked into a
moneymaking machine on this end so
that's something everybody needs to know
with all my shows all my information all
the information I put out everything
else and so it's very critical to
understand that I don't even sell my own
book it's a publisher book that's that's
the whole thing people know how it works
with books when when you have a
publisher and they go out and the
printing and everything else and all the
work involved and you know it's not the
same thing as if you publish yourself or
you have your own ebook and you make all
the money and all the stuff that people
do so there's there's really it's
important to understand when you're and
the reason why I'm saying all this is
because when you're dealing with fasting
and you're dealing with different belief
systems and Trends and different stuff
like that misinformation there's a lot
of stuff behind them they don't know
that's happen that you get tricked into
and you're not going to get that here
you're going to get literally you're
going to get you know the truth the
information that's not swallowed
swallowed up by some investor or some
belief system or somebody invested into
like you know $500,000 in supplements
and put all these kits together so they
can tell you how to dry fast and then
make sure you take these herbs and make
sure you take this and make sure you
take that and then they try to train you
to also be one of these people so then
you go it's like a pyramid scheme and
you go and try to get other people on
board and whatever nothing like that
nothing like that is happening and on
the beginning of the show you'll notice
there isn't a 15minute infomercial on
selling kind of some kind of diet system
or selling kind of some belief system or
some whatever you're not going to hear
that either and I have to just make that
clear for anybody who first came on here
who's never heard the medical medium
radio show it's all about you and that's
what it's really about and that's what
it's really really really about it's
about your healing process about your
family it's about your loved ones it's
about the people you care about it's
about all of that and you just you know
what happens is we get so brainwashed by
all all the propaganda and all the sales
and all the systematic selling of things
and products and belief systems and diet
systems and all this other stuff that we
just get numb to it and then we think
everybody does that that's that's a
public figure or somebody who's out
there whatever it is we think everybody
does that it's not true we don't do that
here I don't do that and that has to be
clear so when it comes down to fact
fasting and water fasting and dry
fasting and intermittent fasting or any
kind of fasting whatever it is you just
know it's free what we're talking about
is free from some you know Bowl that's
behind it from some some agenda that's
behind it so you always have to know
that and that's important that's really
important to understand so look let's
get into the show let's do this I think
I've you know held you guys out enough
with that right now and I just I just
you know it's just it's important stuff
believe me is important you need to know
that the information you get is free
from you know something that shouldn't
be involved in it it's just it's just
it's really it would matter to me it
would matter to me so if I was looking
for help it would matter to me so I so I
I Pro so I'm just thinking I'm assuming
that would matter to everybody else too
um so so here's the bottom line here's
the bottom line there's all these
different fasts out there and and all
these different programs and all these
different kits and all this different
stuff
and there's really no there's nothing
behind this as far as you know when you
think about the different there's
there's not there's there's people's
theories there's uh theories there's you
know belief systems there's things that
people tried on themsel and it might
have worked for them but it didn't work
for somebody else there's a lot of
things mixed up and matched into it and
you got to be careful um you know with
Liver Rescue with Liver Rescue uh my
latest book Liver Rescue I talk about
how the liver doesn't like to be pushed
it doesn't like to be pushed it's like a
child about to jump into the swimming
pool off the diving board for the first
time ever and is standing um at the end
of the diving board okay standing there
and getting the courage and getting the
the faith and the courage and getting
that willpower and building that Spirit
to want to make that plunge on her or
his own and jump into the water you know
and and that child if you got on the
diving board and you pushed the child in
without the child realizing or knowing
it and the child was thrown into the
water and got a gulp of water and was
choking and gasping on the water on the
side of the pool and all trust would be
broken all trust would be broken it
would be it would be a pushed event or a
forced event when it shouldn't be it
should be something that naturally
occurs with the child's own you know
being and Consciousness and everything
else to jump off that diving board for
the first time into a swimming pool you
know and I remember I remember being a
child and I was I was you know I was at
a a friend's house and there was
everybody was swimming there and I was I
was um 8 years old and I remember that's
what happened and I saw that I saw a
child that was on the diving board for
the first time ever a little girl and
she was she was on the diving board and
an adult was behind her and then pushed
her in just pushed her in thought that
that would be the best way to do it and
I'll never forget it because I I was I I
saw it was wrong totally wrong and I
knew why it was wrong in every way and
um and spirit did knew why it was wrong
in every way and I'll never forget that
and I I and I and I talked about that in
Li rescue because what happens is when
you cleanse and you fast you may be
pushing a part of your body that doesn't
want to be pushed and that is really
what happens and we have to be careful
so when we're we're doing different
fasts and we just we're trying different
things and we're going jumping into
things we don't know what our organs are
feeling we have no idea and have no clue
you know which organ is that little girl
on the end of the diving board that gets
thrown into the water instead of having
to do the process properly or the right
process of jumping in and building up
you know building up that faith and
everything else and you know would
happen in that trust and what happens is
there's an organ in our body called the
liver and that liver of ours and yours
doesn't like stupid fasting meaning
stupidly done fasting it doesn't like it
at all and a and it's really important
to know this because no one knows what's
happening inside the body out there it's
amazing what happens I mean it's just
got tons of practitioners out there and
doctors and all these different people
and and what not and no one really knows
what's happening inside the body it's
all hit or miss out there it really is
and that's that's what's scary so so but
this organ that we have which is the
liver it it doesn't like to be what it
does is it holds on to poisons for a
reason it holds on to toxins for a
reason and if it's pushed too hard it's
going to release all of them not all of
them a large amount of them into the
bloodstream and it's not going to leave
your body it's not it's only some are
going to leave the body the rest are
going to float around cause causing harm
and they're going to float around
causing harm to the brain they're going
to float around causing harm to the
pancreas and they're going to float
around causing harm to the spleen
they're going to float around causing
harm to other parts of the body to the
nervous system especially and they're
even going to float around causing harm
to the adrenals so when it's about
cleansing no one's thinking about
something inside of them no one's
thinking about that whatever kind of
cleansing it is meaning whatever kind of
cleansing whatever kind of fast whatever
kind of whatever it is no one's thinking
about wait a minute you know what is my
liver really going to do and how does my
liver really work and what's really
happening here and this is why we have
so many mistakes in the industry and and
and people get sucked into so many
things and yeah some things work some
things don't but
regardless everybody's different
something might work for someone someone
someone might something might not work
for another person I'm going to I'm
going to talk about that I'm going to
discuss all that and talk about that as
we're going through the show um so what
happens is our liver likes to release a
certain amount of poison that it doesn't
have to soop back up so what happens is
if we push it and we just jump into some
fast or we do something like a dry fast
or we do something whatever Poison's
been inside our liver it you know
everything all the different chemicals
all the different toxins all the
different heavy metals all the different
solvents Pharmaceuticals all throughout
life from starting from the beginning
everything that's in there and then some
pesticides DDT herbicides that believe
it it the liver has it all in there
Plastics petroleum tons of petroleum
based stuff I mean it's amazing what's
inside the liver and so if we the liver
just likes to release a little bit of
this at a time and a little bit of this
at a time and that's why you know spirit
and you know gave me the 28 day cleanse
so it releases a little bit at of the
time a little bit at a time because what
happens is if you jump into some crazy
fast
yeah I know some of you are probably
like upset because you you're in totally
into fasting and you still can fast but
I'm going to talk about why we have to
be careful in different levels and and
different things for different people if
you're toxic if you're ready already
really really toxic fasting is not what
you want to do meaning water fasting
straight water fasting um dry fasting um
you know you've got to be really careful
because what happens is if you have a
really toxic liver and it's f and it's
sluggish and it's loaded with poison and
you push that liver off the diving
board okay when you push it off the
diving board into the
pole there's going to be a problem
there's going to be a major problem it's
going to release too much poison even
though it's not going to release all of
it there's no way because it's it's it
because when livers are toxic they're
loaded and it takes takes takes a lot
while to get your livers cleaned up I'm
going to tell you right now and I talk
all about that in Liver Rescue but what
happens is
that the liver will release more poison
than it wants to release and then that
poison won't leave the body only a
little bit will hit the kidneys and
leave the body the rest of it will wreak
havoc what I mean wreak havoc it will
get into the brain it will get into the
nervous system and it will get into the
pancreas it'll get into places and and
on top of that the liver has to sop it
all back up it has to work 10 times
harder to stop all that toxic poison
poisonous debris back up cuz the liver
has to suck it all back up and that's
that's you know that's how it works so
we have to be we have to be responsible
which I just don't see that out there
with all the different Frills and chills
packages all the different fasting stuff
all the different whatever it's
literally it's literally like I mean
it's unbelievable on how not
responsible it is out there so so the
bottom line is it's all about protecting
something when you're fasting and I'm
going to tell you how to do it I'm going
to tell you what you should do you know
depending and everybody's a little
different so I'm going to try to give
you as much information on the
differences you may have yourself that
can you know that can be the difference
there now to begin with if you're really
toxic you've been eating standard
American for the most part you haven't
really done any fruits and vegetables
you've been eating a lot of animal
products or you even been eating a lot
of animal products and still eating
fruits and vegetables and you're not
eating that you know bad and you're
eating pretty clean you still could be
highly toxic toxic for years and years
and years the liver could be totally
filled with tons of poison because
that's what that's the organ that gets
filled with that much poison and then
someone convinces you to go on some
fasting program
wrong wrong to do wrong to do what
you'll do is you'll just you'll hurt the
adrenals you'll you'll you'll saturate
the brain with poison which the brain
does not need you'll weaken the pancreas
and you'll over tax and over stress and
overwork the liver and make it harder
for the liver to heal later so what
happens is we have to do things a little
differently you know like the 28 day
cleanse in the first book medical media
I mean 28 day cleanse is because that
that is to make sure that anybody who is
already healthier gets even healthier
and cleaner so that if they did do a
fast or a two-day water fast or a 7-Day
water fast or they did something it
wouldn't be a disaster and it wouldn't
be it wouldn't be hard on the liver it
wouldn't be super hard on the liver and
so that's something to really understand
and so what happens though if you're if
you're toxic and you're coming into
you're coming into something say you're
just you've been eating the way you're
eating and that's how you've been eating
all these years it's not that good you
got or you're or you've been eating
pretty good but your liver's loaded and
nobody knows nobody knows and your liver
loaded with poison loaded with toxins
and and and then you go and you jump
into a
fast and and that's not what you do
that's not what you should do and in the
end you know we get hurt because of that
later on in different ways it's in and
so I mean that's that's kind of an
example right there there's something
about gradually eating better and better
and better gradually eating better and
better and better so you know so you
don't end up so there's this you adapt
so your liver can actually adapt so so
and that's the key that's one of the big
keys let say you're somebody who's been
doing everything you've been doing all
these different foods but have you been
doing everything have you been doing
celery juice for 5 years have you been
doing celery juice for three years have
you I mean think about it totally
cleansing recovering your pancreas
totally cleansing recovering your your
your spleen totally cleansing recovering
your uh liver your nervous system you
know what's funny is there's people out
there there's so many people now that
have um that have the the medical medium
books go around the world right you're
probably bumping into them and stuff and
and you know and at the same time is
people hop on board on the internet
they'll hop on Instagram they'll hop on
Facebook or they'll hop on different
forums and oh yeah no I tried that it
wasn't really helping but when you look
at it I mean you look at it they didn't
even do the celery juice for two weeks
what did they try you know what happens
every day I see it out there and you
know did someone do 32 oz of celery
juice for the liver for their body for
their health and you know or even 16
ounces of celery juice every single
morning for a year did they and remove
the no Foods remove the eggs the dairy
the wheat and you know other things like
that did they do that and you know like
so that's the whole point is there's
different way there's different levels
of getting to a point where if you want
to do a fast were you doing at least the
other things to get yourself ready for
one so what I'm saying is is if you if
you get tied into some fast out there
tied into some cleanse tied into
something and it's selling you a bag of
goods and it's making you buy like
thousands of dollars of stuff and then
telling you you can sell thousands of
dollars of stuff whatever it's doing you
know some do that some don't some just
make you buy stuff some whatever whether
it's by you know uh crazy people that
created the cleanse some mad man that
created the cleanse whatever it is
that's out there whatever you're doing
out there make sure you get yourself
ready for it because if it's not a good
cleanse and if it's not a good fast if
it's not a good situation you got your
body in a place that could possibly
adapt to it and protect you and the
whole thing about the medical medium
information and what what uh spirit and
I been doing is making sure you have all
the foundation to protect you to heal no
matter what you do so even if you make
mistakes even if you fall into a belief
system even if you fall into something
even if you whatever you'll be better
off and still safer because because it's
it's all about protecting things inside
the body that nobody understands and I'm
just saying this because it's got look I
got to tell I got to say the truth
that's all I have that's all I have to
do you know Spirit told me so was a
little little boy just tell the truth
just tell the truth and the truth is
this information and say it and don't be
afraid to say it so I promise Spirit
since the day day day I got the the gift
and spirit was talking to me that I'm
always going to say it like it is and
not be afraid of hurting someone's
feelings and that was the key I remember
when I was a little boy I'd be like well
I'm going to hurt somebody's feelings if
I if I tell them what you're telling I'm
going to hurt their feelings because
they believe in something else spirit
said doesn't matter you have to tell
them what it is they have to hear the
truth and so and so with the fasting
thing you know it's important to know
that if you're yeah if you're really
highly toxic if your liver is really
overburden which most likely probably
especially if you've been sick for a
long time and you got viral issues and
everything inside the liver you want to
you want to do something like a 28 day
cleanser you want to do the cleanse and
Liver Rescue you want to do the cleanse
and Liver Rescue so you'll see the
cleanse and Liver Rescue it's it it
literally is above the rest because it's
it's about making sure your liver gets
cleaned up to the end like cleaned clean
cleaned up without hurting your liver
hurting your bloodstream and everything
else okay so let's go into some some
water fasting talk okay have I water
fasted have I water fasted yes I have
have I water fasted a long time yes I
have I've water fasted an extremely long
time one that probably is way too
dangerous for so many people you know
you know I I when I water fasted for a
long I did a lot of water fast in my day
and I did water fast for Spiritual
reasons okay and you know with with
struggling with spirit and struggling
with with with having what what I called
the curse all these years which was the
gift of hearing spirit so I you know I
did spiritual fasts with um with water
fasting you know throughout my life
starting at age 12 I you know my first
water fast was at age 12 I water fasted
for 7 days straight with just water at
age 12 I'm not recommending that I'm not
and no 12-year-old should be doing that
okay I did it I was lucky I had Spirit
okay so I had spirit to guide me and I
had Spirit to also tell me I I shouldn't
have been doing it either but I did it
anyway but I had Spirit guiding me and
helping me through it I did a 7-Day fast
at 12 years old okay okay at 18 years
old I did a 21-day fast at 18 years old
of straight water and I'm not even going
to tell you how many days I've done even
after that because I don't want to
influence anyone thinking they could
water fast too long okay but I have done
longer than 21 days in water fasting and
I mean a lot longer and it's stupid it
was stupid and I was spiritually doing
it for my own emotional spiritual
reasons being a human being and uh and
at the same time dealing with what I had
to deal with growing up which was you
know which was with spirit so it was
pretty intense time for me now have I
helped people water fast over the water
fast over the years if people you know
would come to me and they really truly
wanted to and they wanted me to guide
them I have helped people so they
wouldn't make mistakes or it was the
right thing for them or the right way
for them you know I've seen all that is
water fasting okay some water fasting is
okay for people some sometimes it is but
I like water fasting for people that
have already gotten to a certain point
you know so the liver isn't traumatized
so they've already been eating good I've
been eating good since I was 8 years old
and that's how long I've been eating
good even a little before that but
around 8 years old so I've been eating
clean since 8 years old and that eating
clean since 8 years old has allowed me
to keep my liver clean so I'm giving you
a little bit of private information
information about me because you know I
always want to tell you guys everything
about me but every time I talk about me
then everybody starts yelling on the
internet stop talking about yourself and
talk about talk about you know us and
our problems and our illnesses so I try
not to excuse me I try not to talk about
myself so
much so so the whole thing is is that is
that when you when you're getting to a
point of being clean enough and you're
cleaning out your liver and you're
cleaning out your body and cleaning out
your organs and your bloodstream and
everything's coming out of you enough
gradually over time cuz you've been
eating good for a while what happens is
you know you can do things like that for
your health so if you were sick or you
had a problem or something happened and
you want to heal something quicker or a
sickness comes over you and you want to
heal something quicker you catch
something you catch somebody's strap a
caucus you catch somebody's you catch
somebody's you know whatever or you just
you know you get a bad flu or whatever
happens in your life you know you want
to be able to also be able to fast but
you don't want to be Force forcing your
liver and forcing yourself into such a
such a difficult situation where your
body's fil filling up with so many
toxins and poisons that you get affected
by it in negative ways and believe me it
can so so if you're someone who wants to
water fast I support it I don't support
long water fasts I don't think they're
necessary because a lot of people go
into fasts water fasts being
nutritionally deficient being completely
deficient with deficient of zinc
deficient of different minerals but yet
they're sick and they have viruses so
what happens is when you water fast too
long your immune system starts to weaken
and viruses like the shingles and the
EBV and hhv sixs and the cytom magler
viruses and all the herpetic viruses
that create Lyme disease that create all
these different illnesses that I talk
about all the time in my books and
everything else all these viruses have a
way of being able to jump out and and
come out I know fast fasting experts
that don't even understand how viruses
work and how how viruses affect and make
people sick and they fast their people
and and these people come out of fasts
and some of them can can all of a sudden
get really sick and they got a whole
thing of shingles running down their
side a whole thing of this going down
after it it's like doesn't and they're
always like oh it's cuz you're cleansing
you're cleansing you're cleansing no cuz
you went into a deficient you've been
sick all this time you went into a
deficient and you know you're you're
mineral deficient your other kinds of
deficiencies and then you fasted and it
was just too hard in the system the
immune system took a little bit of a hit
and so you know so there's different so
I support water fasting I do you know
but it has to be it has to be not too
long for certain people there's some
people they could do it a little bit
longer some people people shorter you
know what I like for water fasting is
like a two-day water fast the most I
like two-day water fasts if someone
really wants to do one 2day is actually
perfect it doesn't freak out the liver
to such a degree where the LI is
actually dumping everything at once and
then having to pay the price by sucking
it all back up and then weakening itself
and getting sluggish afterwards because
that's what happens some people who fast
and they fast for a while regardless of
what kind of fast they shock the liver
so much that they gain weight after
they're fast later on regardless of what
diet they're on and everything like that
they gain all their weight like all this
weight because they liver totally took a
hit from the F fast so you don't want it
so two days I like it's a more
protective to the liver depending on who
you are it's more protective it's more
safer it's more better so it would be a
two-day water fast and you have to be
drinking water you have to be drinking
water so you know so I like those
because you can do a two-day water fast
and I don't want you doing a two-day
water fast while driving around dropping
the kids everywhere dropping the kids
off everywhere um going here going there
you should never in in in my opinion and
in in my experience when you water fast
you might get a dizzy spell some toxins
might come out your blood sugar is going
to drop you're going to you might get
weak you might get all these different
things now I know there's supersonic
people out there that can water fast for
3 days and they're like oh my God I feel
great and they're driving around in
their car they're driving around in the
car but still anything could happen so
it's the kind of thing where you do your
two-day water fast on the weekend you do
it at home and you know you you can you
know do what you need to do while you're
doing it some you know and that's okay
now here's the deal when you're dealing
with neurological problems people that
have neurological illnesses and they
they're really weak nervous systems and
because of EBV and neurotoxins floating
around in the bloodstream things that
fasting experts don't even know about
they don't even have an idea about all
that kind of stuff and so so what
happens is once you have all that and
you do a fast it could be really hard on
somebody's central nervous system could
shut down their central nervous system
weaken it so that when they come out of
the water fast they're they have to work
20 times harder that's why I don't like
long water fasts because so many PE
people have neurological issues they
have anxiety they have depression they
have headaches these are all
neurological they have fibromyalgia
aches and pains they have fatigue it's
all neurological they have all these
different things going on so when you go
into a long water fast you get screwed
totally screwed you end up being that
one person that can't come out of it so
you're at a water fasting place and
you're just and you can't come out of
your water fast everybody else is
they're recovering and they're drinking
and they're eating and they're they're
recovering they're eating a little bit
of food every two hours you out of the
fast or eating a little bit of food but
you're but you're like you're dogging it
or a couple of people are dogging it and
they're not really recovering and it's
taking them literally two weeks to
recover because of neuro fatigue because
of neurological symptoms neurological
issu giving you every Edge I can
possibly give you with this so if you're
going to have a water fast I mean I
would do two-day water fasts the most
and in fact if you're ever going to
water Fest from here wait until you have
a copy of Liver Rescue in your hands go
get a copy of Liver Rescue and have it
in your hands and just make sure you
read all that about the liver and
cleansing liver and cleaning it up
because I have a cleanse in there that's
protects your liver and can really get
you healthy so without you having to tax
your body or jump into another thing
with the water fasting is once you go
two or three days and you're and you're
working with somebody on it or doing
your own you tend to put a lot of people
tend to go their fourth day fifth day
and they don't stop and it becomes an
addiction it becomes an addiction it
really does and it's hard to break that
addiction where you don't even want to
break it you're just in it and you just
want to keep going and then like a
Madness occurs and a Madness occurs when
you're water fasting too just so you
know when you're like in your five six
seven eight days you got moments of oh
my God I'm having Clarity it's euphoric
and then you're like but there's Madness
that occurs throughout the whole process
and that Madness could be like I don't
want to break my fast I'm on my 14th day
I don't want to break my water fast it's
like it it just it yeah what I'm saying
is you have to be careful I I would say
if you're doing water fast you do
two-day water fasts and and you can do
you can do them periodically you can do
it once a month two-day waterfest if you
really want to do it and that's somebody
without neuro fatigue that's somebody
without neurological fatigue that's
somebody without lots of viral issues
and neurotoxins and Dermot toxins and
everything else that I would say do a
two-day water fast that's somebody
without all of that and so let's talk
about dry fasting you do you want to
know about dry fasting it's called never
do it ever ever ever ever I'm going to
say this right now and I I can't help it
but anybody who actually any
professional any professional or any
expert that believes in dry fasting is
completely completely in the dark and
had doesn't really understand the body
and that scares the hell out of me I'm
just going to tell you right now I don't
care what war I'm starting and I don't
care what issues I'm starting I don't
care whatever I don't care whose
feelings that hurt I'm telling you that
and I I'll tell you why I'm telling you
that because if it's to stop somebody
from dry fasting so they don't hurt
themselves and and anybody that's around
them their loved ones and stuff like
that then then darn right I'm going to
say this because it matters okay I don't
care about the pitchforks and the
shovels and the Torches that might be at
my door
dry fasting is idiotic it's not the
person who's doing it's idiotic it's the
it's it's whatever experts who talk
about it are being good or whatnot it's
absolutely idiotic I have to say this I
know it sounds really you know I sound
obnoxious saying this like this but I'm
just telling you and so dry fasting no
off the table never never never it's a
great way to traumatize the kidneys it's
a great way to shut down the kidneys
it's a great way to put your kidneys in
in shock it's a great way to just
literally like fill your bloodstream up
with so much poison like so much poison
you can go into like almost sepsis it's
literally a an idiotic move for for
experts to be into dry fasting at all if
you're in a program and they have in
that program some of it is dry fasting
you should be out of that program I
don't care what you paid for it I don't
care what you paid for it or what it's
selling you or what it's trying to teach
you you should be doing I would get out
of it and if you're getting upset
because you're totally into it or you
support somebody who you know supports
somebody who believes in entirely and
they sell it and everything else and
they're selling it out there whatever
and you you you bought into it and
you're getting mad at me I'm sorry I'm
really really sorry but it's for your
own good it's for your own good I
promise that I promise that am I selling
anything no okay am I trying to make
money off the show no all right so am I
selling some kit no am I trying to help
you yes yes I'm trying to help you so
that that's what you have to understand
um so with dry fasting off the table not
even in option it's really destructive
it hurts the kidneys it hurts the liver
it hurts the nervous system it literally
can cause serious brain problems kills
brain cells we're at a place on planet
Earth right now we can't lose brain
cells we can't we're losing them rapidly
as the human race right now
in in where we are and where we stand on
planet Earth brain cells go like never
before and and and yeah and that's I
mean it's unbelievable what's happening
that's why brain diseases are on the
rise an alltime rise it's hard to keep
our brain cells good what I mean by that
is high production purification of brain
cells going on what I mean by healthy
brain cells not not unhealthy brain
cells and you know it in and so what
happens with d fasting it it destroys
and takes out a lot of brain cells
unnecessarily and and that's not good
either so keep that off the table that's
not even in here so juice fasting we'll
talk about that a little bit too juice
fasting is is a good one too I mean it
is some people but remember for
everybody it's a little different
everybody it's a little different some
people have adrenal issues some people
have um um some people have weak
constitutions because of adrenal issues
maybe their nervous system isn't that
strong maybe they too many toxic heavy
metals uh maybe they have um um their
heart isn't that strong a lot of people
there's a lot of people that walk around
their hearts aren't that strong they're
they're just they have weaker hearts and
there's a lot of different things going
on in each one of us and every every
person some people have different levels
of bacteria some people have different
levels of viruses some people have both
um and so we have all this happening so
juice fasting uh you know is something
you can do with what I always say with
juice fasting is you don't go long term
even with juice fasting because when you
juice fast long term you if you jump
into a juice fast and you go into it
long term you could be putting a lot of
pressure on the liver you could be
putting a lot of pressure on the liver
you could be pushing the little girl off
the diving board and you could be
literally pushing that liver off the
diving board and you it's something to
really kind of think about and take in
consideration um juices are amazing and
incredible but juice fasting also means
that you know you're not it depends on
what's in your juices if you're juice
fasting and there's a carbohydrate in
your juice it's much better it's much
better so if you're going to jump into a
juice fast I'm okay with it but it it
has to have something in there you know
like apples have to be in there too it
has to be something that gives you some
calories and that's important because
that'll slow down your cleanse it'll
slow down your cleanse so your liver's
not going into shock so your liver is
not dumping a tremendous amount of
poison into your bloodstream so your
liver is not actually you know like
saturating your bloodstream by releasing
too much and if you think that's good
it's not good because your liver sucks
it all back up and only a little bit
leaves it's better off that the liver on
its own literally jumps off the diving
board on its own by releasing a little
at a time a little at a time that's it
that's it and this way the body can
process it this way the kidneys can
handle it this way the body can take
care of it cuz the liver is going to
protect your kidneys it's going to
protect your pancreas so when it
releases all when it's pushed to release
all that poison that I talk about in
Liver Rescue when it Le when it releases
all of that
junk into the
bloodstream it doesn't it doesn't damage
adrenals it doesn't damage the pancreas
it doesn't damage you know other aspects
of it doesn't damage your kidneys so
when you're juice fasting it wouldn't do
just green juice only I wouldn't do
something like just green juice only I
wouldn't do kale and spinach and um and
celery juice Believe It or Not only if
it's going to be longterm I wouldn't do
that I would have cucumbers in there I
would have apples in there I would have
pears in there I would have other things
in there I would even do oranges I would
have oranges in there and that kind of
juice fast ensures your brain is getting
glucose it's getting glucose it's
getting sugars critically needed
sugars so it doesn't get injured and
that's a whole another thing critical
needed sugars and and another thing so
this way even your liver gets critically
needed sugars it gets glucose and that's
important too and your liver can still
cleanse so if you're doing a juice fast
make sure there's carbohydrates in those
juices that's really important and it
doesn't have to be in every juice if
you're doing a juice fast F if you're
doing a juice Fest for more than a
couple of days you're going to be
cleansing a lot more yes you're going to
be pushing your liver a lot harder but
like I said before you jump into any big
cleanses or any big fasts you should
just get a copy of Liver Rescue and
consider it just consider the section of
fasting and how I talk about that too
before you do anything and if you don't
like it what you're seeing or whatever
it is and go to somewhere else and do
something absolutely but I'm giving you
the what not to do to keep you safe
if you are out there doing different
fasts and stuff like that so if you're
somebody that has a pretty strong
Constitution and I mean not that Viral
feeling pretty strong can handle not
even eating for a little while can even
handle not even
eating and you know like like going
without food and you know your blood
sugar doesn't crash hard and you don't
need a nap and you you you can get
through your day and you can do a
million things if you're one of those
people you know yeah you can do a juice
fast for a little while longer yeah you
can I mean you're still it's possible
you'll still be pushing the liver too
hard and it'll be dumping a lot of
poison out but if you're doing a juice
fast with the carbohydrate I'm talking
about by having the apples in there the
with all the greens and having some
orange in there with all the greens and
by doing our pears in there with all the
greens now if you're doing that and some
even some watermelon in there with with
everything like just you know juicing
some watermelon with all of that you
know you can you can definitely be much
easier on the liver not so harsh on the
liver it won't have to dump all this
poison at once and it can protect you
for the Long Haul so 3 years down the
road five years down the road you're not
hitting the wall and not realizing why
it's because you did all these crazy
fasts or did these dry fasts or did
these other things three years ago four
years ago and then your brain it ran out
of glycogen storages that's what happens
your brain starts running and running
out of glycogen storage so then she just
start kind of hitting the wall and you
start getting confusion and you just
don't know why it's because you did you
did a a 10-day dry fast three years ago
you did you know you did a water fast
for 14 days you did too many of this you
did too many of that and you never
restored and that's a problem too you
can go to you can do you can do
different fasts out there and different
programs and stuff like that but it
doesn't mean they know how to make sure
you restore what you lost because they
don't even know what you lost I mean
I've talked to some experts in all these
fields over the years and they don't
even know like the brain is actually uh
made of glycogen storage they don't even
know that it loses all that carbohydrate
soft tissue it starts to atrophy when
you're fasting dry fasting and other
kinds of fasts and they don't even know
this so they don't know that how you
have to restore it you have to restore
it with lots and lots of celery juice
and that's another thing too none of the
programs out there fast out there are
ever using plain straight celery juice
just they're never using that as a
recovery tool or even a fasting tool in
the juice fasting and that's a mistake
all on its own so they have all these
different juices but they don't even
have straight celery juice so you can
protect your brain so you can protect
your liver so you can protect what's
right rightfully yours you see why I'm
frustrated and you see why I had to do
the show and so it it these are all the
things to to to consider all the things
to consider I'm not trying to make it
complicated if you're if you're a strong
person and you've already if you've
already been eating good good for a
while eating clean for a while maybe
even the 28 day cleanse for a while
maybe just eating
clean for a while not a lot of junk not
so much fats not so much fats and not a
lot of junk and you're eating clean for
a while more fruits and vegetables more
fruits and vegetables and you're doing
your lemon water because your lemon
water is cleansing your liver every
single day a little bit and you're doing
all of that and you're doing some celery
juice every single day so then you want
to jump into a little bit of a water
fast okay you know what I'm on board you
want to jump if that's what you really
want if you want to jump into a juice
fast done right yeah okay I'm on board
I'm on board so but what I recommend is
you do the celery juice but you really
do it there's people out there I see it
all the time they don't even do their
celer jues but then they get pushed into
some fasting program and in that fasting
program they also sell like a zillion
herbs with alcohol in them I'm gonna
have to cover that for a second okay if
you're running into like some kind of
some guy or some gal's
program that that has supplements in it
and they're recommending all the stuff
and there's alcohol in those supplements
then you're in the wrong place you're in
the wrong
place absolutely 100% the alcohol it it
kills all of your internal bacteria in
your intestinal tract in your gut
destroys all of your good bacteria and
microorganisms so if you're doctor
practitioner you're expert your Guru
doesn't know that and they're selling
you kits with alcohol in
them that's right there should tell you
back out because what happens is that
that that's what one of the most oh my
God I can't even tell you how important
that is all that alcohol all that
alcohol gets inside the liver all that
tincture alcohol gets inside the liver
all that tinure alcohol wipes out all
the microorganisms in the gut all that
tincture alcohol blows out your
hydrochloric acid
reserves and that's just that's just to
start with that's just to start with I
don't care if it's grape alcohol I don't
care what kind of alcohol it is so you
have to know that and I noticed that
there's fasting fasting you know kits
and fasting things out there and gurus
and stuff promoting that and then they
have that in there and you spend all
this money and you're you're dumping
straight alcohol tinctures and straight
alcohol in your system I've never seen
anything just so ridiculous so just look
out for that look out for that okay um
so if you're somebody that if you're
somebody look I would I would do the
celery juice I would really do it I
would really do it and I would really
eat
clean and then you can do a juice fast
but first before you do anything I would
look at the Liver Rescue and just look
at
that and feel it out and see how you
feel about it
and because honestly it's and it's it's
really easy to do too it's really easy
to do when you get it you'll see it but
the bottom line is is um I do I do yes I
do support water fasting small
increments for the right people that
have already gotten themselves clean
enough so they don't shock their liver
shock their bodies fill it up with
poison and then go backwards later on
including hurting their adrenals later
on so I do support water fast testing if
you've you know when if you've gotten to
a point where you've done the celery
juice for a year you've done the celery
juice for 6 months you've been working
on healing you've been doing all your
you've been really cleaning yourself up
fast tracking out of the fact that
people feel like they just don't have it
in them to do any of the work and they
want to FastTrack something that's scary
so they just jump into some fasting kits
some fasting program whatever it is just
be careful
um
and juice fasting the same thing but
juice fasting you want to do a long-term
juice faster you know like you want to
be a long long-term juice faster there
better be a carbohydrate in that juice
it can't just be only
only um non-starchy vegetables and green
leafy greens has to be there has to be
always celery involved but you have to
also have the carbohydrate ones you have
to have the apples you have to have the
Cucumbers you have to have these options
you have to have peirs you have to have
oranges and even you can be creative you
can you other other things too you could
have watermelon whatever it is that has
to be in there that's really important
if you're doing juice fast along with
the greens along with lots of celery
juice by itself by itself and then other
juices with the carbs in there with the
the healthy the healthy carbs in there
so your brain does an atrophy so you can
actually get the electrolytes strong so
you can actually do what you need to do
while you're fasting and removing
poisons and removing toxins let's talk
about intermittent fasting now first of
all most most of you probably know about
the the adrenal snacks I always promote
you should be eating every couple of
hours okay you know that and um and that
that's a critical thing to understand
that you that what happens is that
people that people have these weak
nervous systems most of the people that
have ever come to me and have ever you
know gotten the medical medium books
they're dealing with a lot of
neurological problems anxiety depression
migraines of all different kinds neck
pain back pain pain body pain Tremors
shakes Twitches severe fatigue
neurological fatigue brain
inflamation um tingles numbness ringing
in the ears they're dealing with
everything
neurological everything neurological
burning Burning Sensations you know
everything under the sun and it's the
people that have always they're always
seeking real answers they're seeking the
truth so they can move forward and heal
and and that's that's that's what it's
all about that's that's what it's all
about and um and with that th this large
group of people that we have that's out
there in the world and that needs help
it's if they go too long without eating
their adrenals and their nervous system
and their neuro fatigue can get worse so
the every the every couple of hours and
eating is to protect this to protect
everyone so it's like you and you don't
have to eat a large meal every couple
hours it's just once you go go 2 three
hours without food once you go 2 three
hours without food your blood sugar
drops and you're running on adrenaline
now so now your adrenals are running and
you're running on adrenaline adrenaline
makes more neuro fatigue and it makes
more adrenal fatigue and it makes more
liver problems and it makes more blood
sugar problems so always always
advocated you know to to make sure you
you have snacks throughout the day and
you're not pulling that whole thing that
we're taught when we're younger when we
go to college or anything else even
though I never went to college and we go
to college and we're doing whatever
we're doing it's you know you're just
like you're running on empty all day
long with ad with adrenaline running and
you know it's like that kind of thing
and we kind of carry that out to the
workforce and when we get older and
everything and then when you're sick and
you can't get out of bed and you got the
neuro fatigue and you're sick and
everything the the you you also can't go
too long without getting some fuel in
you so that's why you that's another
thing too it's important to have the
every two hours but intermittent fasting
I do also support
so there's some people where it is
helpful where they they don't eat
anything in the morning a part of that a
part of that um you know H happens
because if they do eat in the morning
they feel kind of thrown by everything
they feel thrown they don't feel right
or they just feel like their digestion
can't handle it yet so I totally totally
totally support intermittent fasting too
and there are people out there that I've
had to say hey look why don't you just
do why don't you why don't you do your
lemon water in the morning and just go
that go until
11:00 and then at 11:00 you know have
your first
snack and you know and there's there you
know or you know you can go longer but
it's only it's not a forever thing for
people so always remember that if it it
could work for you in that moment in
your life it can work for you for that 6
months it could work for you for that
year but always but
never never fall into to the to the
feeling that that's the way it always
has to be and you always have to do
intermittent fasting where you you don't
eat for half a day or you don't eat for
3/4 of a day don't feel that that's a
forever thing that might be a moment in
your life might be a moment in your life
where you're doing that and then you're
eating later in the afternoon and you're
eating at the end of the day and and
that feels good for you and that feels
like it eases off your digestion so what
happens is a lot of people a lot of
people have inflamed intestinal tracts
inflamed dadums they even have hypers
sensitive nerves and their stomach
Linings and in their small intestinal
tract and their large intes they have
highly sensitive nerves so when they put
food in every anytime they eat they put
food in it it it rubs on everything so
it goes through the stomach through the
dadum down into the small intestinal
tract and it rubs on all the nerves and
they feel like they can't digest they
feel like they're in pain and they feel
like they're hurting so they don't want
to eat and they feel better if they
don't eat for like half a day or eat for
a little
while and and then they you know until
they finally have to eat so I mean I
total look I'm supportive of it totally
supportive of it if you can't eat the
every 2 hours to keep your blood sugar
stable to protect your liver protect
your adrenals so they don't run and
flood the body if you can't eat every
two hours try every 3 hours you know if
you can't eat every 3 hours yeah try
every 4 hours if you have to something
like that but you but the but the point
is the point is is that you can
intermittent F you can do that that's
okay if that feels good I I have
recommended that for a lot of people
over the years I have and but it's not
longterm too you try it out you see
there's going to be times in your life
where you feel like you can do it and
you feel like it makes you feel good and
it eases things up and and it gives you
more clarity during the day and stuff
like that then that there's some people
that feel that way and then there's
times where it may you may not be in a
place in your life where all of a sudden
now you're under some different stress
and you got to do this or you got to
work or something has to happen and you
can't run like that and you need to do
the adrenal snacks you need to do the
adrenal snacks you need to do the blood
sugar support snacks you need to make
sure you're getting some fuel to your
brain you're making sure you're getting
some sugars to your brain so you can
function and so it could it could very
at different times in your life um so
what do I like I like juice fasting I
like water fasting I like intermittent
fasting I do I do I do I do I don't like
dry fasting but in the in the way I'm
saying I like the try I in the way I'm
saying I like the water fasting and I
like the juice fasting intermittent
fasting okay in the way I'm saying and
um I know a lot of people they can't go
without they can't go without a snack
for out a couple of hours and if they do
they start falling apart I've had people
contact me recently where they were so
busy and they were running around all
day long and they're dropping their kids
off at soccer and they're doing this and
they just all like they started just
getting shaky and shaking every day and
feeling weaker and and when you really
looked at it they ran about seven hours
during the day six seven hours during
the day without one thing without eating
one thing one thing and their blood was
literally
crashing and like crashing and and and
they were out of glucose and their
nervous system was getting weaker and so
you know intermittent fasting doesn't
work for everybody but there is a small
crowd that can try it and it can help
them until things change and they get a
little stronger or or things change and
they feel like they can eat more and
their inflammation drops down in their
intestinal tract from all the other
things they're doing and eating clean
and not eating um the wrong Foods so
yeah so intermittent fasting I support
too so these are these are the three
different options three different
options if you're you know getting told
if you're getting something tells you to
jump into a long water fast I would just
wait and at least get Liver Rescue in
your hands so you can understand more
about fasting more about how the liver
works so you're not paying a price down
the road with the liver it it's
important because we got to care care
for our liver and care for and get it
cleaned up safely so that if you do a
juice fast longer you know how to
protect yourself if you do a water fast
longer because that's what you want to
do spiritually or something then you
know how to protect you could protect
yourself more and that's the key so
right now I'm basically what I'm saying
is gradually go from like doing the
celery juice every day making sure
you're doing like the celery juice every
single day making sure you're eating
clean doing the no Foods making sure
you're not doing eggs dairy and you're
not doing too many animal products or if
you're vegetarian vegan you're not doing
too many nuts and then you're doing
you're do and too many oils you got to
be careful and making sure you're you're
graduating to a point where you're
cleaning up your liver over time whether
it's a 28 day cleanser you're eating
better and you're cleaning up the liver
you're getting yourself prepared you're
getting yourself nutritionally fortified
so that if you do two-day water fast on
the weekend or 3-day water fast on the
weekend you know even super advised by a
practitioner and so forth so you do a
juice fast with with the right juices
that I talked about earlier so you can
do these things and not hurt your liver
and move forward and heal and not
saturate your body with too many poisons
that would be amazing that would be
amazing okay and for intermittent uh
intermittent fasting you know play it by
ears you can try it out see how you feel
anyone can try that out but at least you
know you can fall back on other options
like the snacks I love you guys this was
an incredible show thank you for hanging
in there for me I really appreciate it I
know I was Haunting and hoing about all
kinds of different things bless you God
bless you I'll talk to you next show bye
now