[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now as
I've always said who has 10 or 20 years
to wait for answers for their illnesses
people have waited so many years in
literally sick for so many years without
having answers to heal people who have
come to me over the years didn't have to
wait anymore they got the answers they
got the answers many many many years ago
they live good lives after that because
of it they've been healed since they
don't even go and look at other
information out there that's all
scrambled eggs on the Internet or in
other books because they know what
healed them they know what to stick to
and they don't get thwarted or confused
when they see other stuff going around
like lectin like the whole lectin thing
the whole lectin Theory and the whole
lectin blunder that people are trying to
hang their hat on unbelievable and so
wait till we go into this this is so
important because you know what happens
with the whole thing with with medical
research and science is that medical
research and science still ignores what
causes chronic illness today still
ignores what's C causing chronic illness
this is on purpose so it trinkles down
to the alternative movement too where we
just ignore the truth of what causes
illnesses in people all the different
autoimmune diseases all the different
symptoms and conditions all the mystery
of all of it in the thyroid healing book
I talked about over a hundred symptoms
and conditions and I talked about what
the real cause is but they don't even
have answers to the simplest aches and
pains to the simplest with the simplest
tingles and numbness to the simplest
little you know migraine there's no
answers there's no answers for anybody
for any of it it not even for acne
there's an answer for it I mean we have
the answers here but that's how it works
it's unbelievable the lectin theory the
letin theory is unbelievable and I'm
going to talk about why so you can be
careful so you don't cheat yourself out
of a healing process because if you want
to go on a wild goose chase along with
the last 50,000 Wild Goose chases that
have all come out over and over and over
again and you want to hop on to another
one which is the lectin fear and you
want to hop on into that that wild goose
chase and you want to keep on going with
that you're going to be stuck in the
same place you started from a long time
ago while somebody made a hell of a lot
of money out there people made a hell of
a lot of money all hanging their hats on
the lectin phase for a while Bank
rolling it Bank rolling it what you get
thed for another decade in your life
while you're sick it's so perfect it's
unbelievable how it works and you got to
be careful because the whole point is I
got your back here and I'm looking out
for you that's the whole point I'm
looking out for you and giving you the
direction that you need to go so it's
really important this show here if this
is the first time on on the medical
Medium show this show and the
information here doesn't come from
interest groups on any level medical
funding with strings attached botch
research lobbyist internal kick packs
there isn't all this money coming in in
different places I'm not selling all
these things and all kinds of money
coming in different places when you're
listening to the show it's about the
information that isn't out there it's
about Advanced Clean pure information to
be put into your hands so you can heal
your family and your kids and yourself
this the information here doesn't have
strings attached to it with all kinds of
with all kinds of dirty things going on
behind it botched research with the
thumb on the scale the medical lobbyist
medical internal Kickbacks persuaded
belief systems private panels of
influencers persuaded belief systems got
to be careful with those because they
wreak havoc and they stop you from
healing you don't believe me let me tell
you there are 250 million people in the
US us alone that are sick right now with
symptoms and conditions running to their
doctors don't even know what's wrong
most of them when it comes down to
chronic illness I'm not talking about
nuts and bolts I'm not talking about
when you need a heart valve change I'm
not talking about when you when you take
a kidney out of someone I'm not talking
about those kinds of things I'm not
talking about when someone has an
appendicitis not talking about when
someone has a hernia I'm not talking
about nuts and bolts I'm talking about
chronic illness very important to
understand and there's no health field
payoffs or trendy traps involved in this
information this is so important to
understand it's pure untampered with
clean from clean Source I was given a
gift whether anybody likes it or not
okay I didn't like getting the gift that
I got because it wasn't even for me
anyway it was for you guys so I was all
upset when I was young because spirit
said you know this gift isn't for you
and you know I felt like oh I was told I
was a gifted child I was told I was a
gifted child because I could see disease
and illness and see what's going on in
people and no answer ansers and get
information that was Advanced meaning
the information you hear on the show I
was talking about it 4 years old all the
you listen to all these radio shows and
read the books that information I knew
since I was four years old okay so just
so you understand because it was coming
through no matter what through a voice I
hear starting from that point and so
we're going to cover this this is this
is important to not today this is a good
show where to even start oh man where'
he even start with this one this is a
massive blunder occurring right now
so let's let's talk about it for a
little bit so you're a great mom so
you're a great mommy you look after your
kids making sure they're never hungry
you look out for your family maybe you
do some charity work on your spare time
but if if you even have any Spirit time
maybe you don't it doesn't matter maybe
you work at a community center maybe you
maybe you just you you you're a good
you're a good listener you listen to
your friends maybe you're not a good
listener but you also help your friends
when you can maybe you give good advice
when you can maybe you care maybe you
care about someone maybe you care about
your family maybe you care about people
in general maybe you care about
anything maybe you're just a really good
person maybe you've risen out of the
ashes you've risen out of the ashes a
few times in your life you've been
through hell here and there you've had
some difficult times some struggles
you've had some let Downs you pushed
through it you persevered your rose out
of the ashes through a variety of
struggles that may have come your
way but you're inherently a good person
deep inside you're a good person but the
one thing you can't do is park your car
good you really stink at it you really
stink at it you never hurt
anybody you never heard anybody parking
your car nothing ever happened and if it
did who
cares who cares if you bumped into
somebody else's car but you don't even
do that you just don't park good you're
not known to be a good Parker so you
going know back up the car and you're
like oo I can't parallel park this is
really hard you're you're you're 2 feet
away from the curb you're 3 feet away
from the curb and you're
trying and word gets
around word gets around rumor goes
around
town you're a terrible
Parker and then it goes from there to
something else you're just a bad person
Rumor Has It
you're just horrible you hurt
people and rumor has it it's even worse
than that you you all of a sudden rumor
has it where you just don't even have a
place in the
community you can't even get a part-time
job because no one wants to take you on
because of rumors because you're
electing you're
electing even though the community in
the town all has it
confused even though you're inherently a
great person a good Soul a good person a
good being you don't mean any harm to
anybody you didn't cause any harm to
anybody didn't cause any harm to anybody
at all somehow a rumor kind of took
off and you're considered bad all around
bad all around so all the good that
you've ever done helping
others all the good you've ever done
when you washed When you washed your
friend's daughter's
knee when she got when when she scraped
the cement from her when she fell off
her skateboard and you and you actually
made sure you you clean the
wound and you put the Band-Aid
on and her mommy who was a friend of
yours was just so grateful that you did
that and you did that all that gets just
thrown thrown away like it didn't
exist or the time where you were
listening to a
friend and friend was spilling all her
pain and sorrow and everything and you
truly had compassion and were listening
and wanted to help in any way you
could you said look you can stay over
here at our house sometimes or whatever
if you need to and all that disappears
everything good you've ever done just
gone
gone everything good you've ever done
for anyone and
anything even the things that nobody
even knows about that you've done how
about that the things that the things
that you've done for people that nobody
really even knows
about the neighbor every you know the
neighbor every time a paper the Sunday
paper comes and the and they leave the
paper in the street versus in the
driveway you're up earlier so you get
out there and you actually pick it out
of the street and you put it in your
neighbor's driveway by their
mailbox or just in their driveway
whatever and no one ever knew because
you just it was just small stuff you
just didn't bother saying anything just
small gestures of caring about anything
or doing anything but they're important
they're important
and you know even to bigger things but
all thrown away because a rumor has it
you're a bad person you're toxic you do
nothing but wrong and it all started
from just not being a great Parker and
just somehow it took off in all the
wrong
directions because yeah because you're
electing is what it turns out to you
actually are electing and that's just
one example of what I'm even saying now
I don't know if you're catching on yet
some of you might be already know where
I'm going but I'm going there let I just
want to say something for decades
medical research and science has been
purposely developing toxic harmful
theories to explain the causes of all
your illnesses symptoms and
conditions which is to them a mystery
which is to them a mystery so research
and science has been trying to create
all these reasons why we're sick we're
sick and they've been doing it for
decades and decades okay it all started
with it's all in your head that's why we
were sick it's all in your head that's
where it all started from it's all in
your head you're crazy women are crazy
you're crazy if you got some symptoms
that are unexplainable in research and
Science and the doctor doesn't know what
it is you're crazy that's how it all
started then it went to hormones
everything's hormones now it's all your
hormones hormones is why you're sick
everybody's sick everybody's sick
because of their hormones that's that's
why they're sick they're only sick
because of their hormones it went to
that and then it went to the autoimmune
Theory the autoimmune Theory where the
body is attacking itself and destroying
itself attacking healthy cells and
healthy tissue your immune system is
attacking healthy tissue because they
can't explain what's really going on so
they name everything autoimmune which is
your body attacking itself which I did a
whole chapter in thyroid healing if you
want to know all the details in that the
body does not attack itself on any level
the theory was misguided to believe to
begin with it was funded and backed by a
lot of money and interest groups they
had to come up with a theory they fought
with a bunch of different theories they
didn't have they didn't have real real
documented information or studies but
they went with the autoimmune Theory it
was the best way to protect the medical
establishment because what it was was if
the medical establishment doesn't know
what's wrong with you they need you to
be the Fall Guy they need you to be the
Fall Guy so that's where it went
then okay and it's not the body
attacking itself it's pathogens
attacking the body I talk about it in
the book I talk about it on the radio
shows you know that now
and your body's building antibodies to
go after the pathogen the virus or or
different variety of viruses or whatever
going after the pathogen not your
healthy cells the pathogens go after the
healthy cells so that was nobody still
knows that by the way nobody not even
the best lectin experts even know that
now they don't even know that it's
incredible not even the best the best
immunology immunologists even know that
right now because somebody hung their
hat on a theory they had to actually pay
for and grandfather in and make it law
so you lose so you lose these laws that
are made make it so you lose that's
right you lose it doesn't feel good
losing but everybody keeps on losing and
losing and losing it's
unbelievable then it went to it got spun
into some different directions you
create your own illness you create your
sickness so that's what happened there
it's going into that direction by people
who who aren't sick and don't have any
answers for people who are sick and they
get kind of spiritual and they're like
oh you created it you created it you're
creating it you're just you're not
spiritually aligned you're creating it
then it went to that whole thing that's
pretty recent actually that's really
recent I wrote about that too you know
that's really A demented one and
then then it's gone to Foods Foods
causing your illness food Foods okay
that's interesting that's kind of an
alternative twist it it is led into not
bad right Foods causing your illness
causing your
inflammation Foods don't cause
inflammation oh dear
lord it's unbelievable where we are
today and the stupidity that we still
were the place that we're at is
unreal Foods don't cause
inflammation till this day nobody knows
in research and science alternative or
conventional that there's that food
feeds a virus which then for fuels
itself releasing a poison or causing a
direct attack upon the cells inside the
body until this day research and science
still don't even know not even the best
people in the business the best top
doctors you can find out there or
so-called the best people in the
industry still don't even know that
viruses eat food they actually
eat they actually consume through their
cell membrane they actually absorb food
fuel themselves feed and eat and
eliminate like any species they still
don't know
this so food doesn't cause inflammation
on any
level this is why people without
pathogens inside their body live to be
90 years old they didn't have any
autoimmune they live fine they exercised
their whole life everything was great
sure they cause they got other problems
going on they got heart disease finally
by the time they were 88 years old but
you know that's expected with all their
high fat consumptions of foods they've
been eating the high fat diets and
clogging up their arteries and
everything like that of course of course
and if they did get a cancer yeah
because cancers are from viruses viruses
create cancers viruses feed off of
foods but
none of that's really known I mean it's
known out there that a virus can create
cancer that that is known out
there but what's not is a virus feeds
off of food and then creates the problem
not the food not the food and in the
best sit the best areas of level of
knowledge that we have and alternative
and conventional the best experts on the
circuits I don't care where they are
still don't even know that still don't
even know
that they don't even believe
that so that's the next place it's gone
so with that comes a new Theory with
that comes a new Theory so the lectin
theory eltin
theory is said to believe it's a car
carbohydrate binding protein eltin it's
in all fruits and
vegetables like legumes and nuts and
everything and some grains and and all
ingrains and it's the reason for illness
today it's the reason for why we're sick
today unbelievable arrogance un
incredible entitlement incredible
entitlement like you you guys you guys
you have to understand what this really
means and what this is this is to push
aside
everything that we need to look for in
order to get people truly healed in the
future and just throw it away and push
it aside that's what this is so somebody
and people can hang their hat
now on this new Theory this popular
Trend that's on the rise is the concern
that certain foods are high in lectin
and therefore have a negative effect on
the health you have to understand that
for decades there have been chronically
sick people and for decades to come
there will be chronically sick people
please know that there's going to be
chronically sick people for decades and
decades to come without the right
information not because of lectin when
someone knows what's wrong with her or
his body knows what's causing a symptom
or condition and knows how to heal it
she or he can heal it over dozens of
years I've witnessed tens of thousands
of people do just this you guys recover
their health even from the most
devastating conditions these recoveries
had nothing to do with lectin
concern I've witnessed tens of thousands
of people healing and recovering
throughout the 35 more than 35 years I
have helped people with devastating
conditions and these
recoveries had nothing to do with
lectin we can't live in a bubble where
we believe that the that nobody got
better from what ailed them until the
lectin trend just came along until the
lectin train Trend just just came along
choo choo into
the you know right down the
tracks we can't just put a blind eye
that people never healed from chronic
illness before the lectin trend came
along the promoters of lectin literature
and Studies have been completely in the
dark about the thousands and thousands
of people who've healed without their
trendy misinformation about
lectin it's as if it's if it it's as if
they've ignored people's healing because
it didn't fit into their box of what
they
believed it didn't fit into their trendy
box and whatever their belief system was
so they just ignored the amount of
people that have
healed without any electing concern or
fear along the
way right they pretend that no one has
ever healed from chronic illness at all
in fact you can just bring somebody to
some of these lectin people and say well
this person healed from chronic illness
doing this and they won't even
care that won't even even be thrown into
a study it won't even be thrown into a
possibility of checking a study it won't
meaning to actually to actually be used
as leverage it won't even be thrown it
that person would be crazy if they
healed that means they were never sick
they were crazy that's what that meant
that's what that means unless it falls
into lectin and our lectin studies and
our lectin propaganda and our lectin
literature unless you were part of the
whole lectin thing you never healed from
your chronic illness they pretend no one
has ever healed from chronic illness so
that they can build the lectin Empire
you don't think there's a lectin Empire
there's lectin Empires out there
building see all you're going to hear it
is the next few three four five years
non-stop Le and Le is all you're going
to hear and guess what sure people can
remove processed foods with lectin in
them people can remove processed foods
people can go on trendy high fat high
protein diets with no sugar in them for
a little while and if they really
weren't that sick and didn't have too
many problems and has few sniffles and
maybe nak in a pain they'll probably
feel better but you take people that
have real neurological mystery
conditions by the millions that are out
there and you want to play that game
they don't get better they end up going
around looking around another place to
heal going around looking around for
another place to heal and keep on going
around yep whether it's lime disease
whether it's real ra whether it's you
know Hashimoto whether it's just they
keep on going around cuz the Hashimoto
creeps back in when you're on those
high-fat diets those there's trendy
high-fat diets that are anti- sugar and
it creeps back in and they come back
around again three more years later
they're sick again five more years later
they're sick again where's the lectin
going to get you there then you it goes
on and on and on and on this is a prime
example like I said before I repeat it
again of entitled ignorance the problem
with lectin concern is that it removes
foods that would actually stop the
viruses and the other pathogens in your
body that truly cause symptoms and
disease did you hear that did you hear
that the problem is with the lectin
concern is that it removes bodies that
would actually heal you because they
stop viruses and pathogens they have
other things in
them these Foods might not be able to
park a car good and they might spread a
bad rumor like how bad a tomato is it
might spread because it's a night shade
oh oh it might spread a
rumor but it could actually heal you and
stop
viruses it might not be able to park its
car good that rumor might go around and
ruin all of its good just like it did
that Mom where all the good she's ever
done is thrown out the window thrown out
the window because someone didn't like
the way she parked her car they watched
it they watched it and then they texted
somebody and spread a rumor
saying this mom is no good as a person
and it ran around town somehow and
nobody knew how it really developed and
where it came
from well that's the whole lectin thing
that's like a
tomato or a potato which stops
viruses being blamed for all the real
good it does because it actually stops
real disease the real chronic illness
that's out there it actually stops it
because because just like the potato it
has high amounts of available Eline a
kind that no other food actually Harbors
or has that actually stops the Epstein
bar virus from causing chronic fatigue
fibromyalgia Hashimoto thyroiditis and
multiple sclerosis and the list goes on
the list goes
on but it's going to be packaged as a
bad food for somebody to hang their hat
on because it's an easy cell cuz people
be like oh oh carbohydrate that's bad oh
oh potato that's bad wait a minute sweet
potato oh you got to look out
out you got to look out and it's an easy
cell because we're suckers in the end
we're all suckers because it's easy to
be a sucker when you don't know what's
going on in science and research is
keeping everybody in the dark to someone
can come along and want to hang their
hat on something and build an Empire off
it in two seconds flat and you'll be
suckered into it that'll be one more
decade
wasted so the prime example of entitled
ignorance is the problem is first of all
you don't recognize that so many people
have healed I've seen lives saved with
the potato literally saved even
recently
recently not even just years ago
recently where they couldn't eat
anything at all it was the only thing
they could eat to recover their Linings
of their intestinal tract from being
burned out by food poisoning and burned
out by other problems and adrenaline and
everything else that people don't even
understand how it works in the gut
nobody knows what goes on in the gut you
can give all the research and science
about nobody knows what's going on in
there because remember interest groups
back each study that they're looking for
and if there isn't an outcome to to
soothe the Beast of the investors to
sooe the investors you have to
understand this there's an investor
behind any
study and so if an expert gets funded to
create a study it has to have an outcome
that's positive or they will never be
invested in again you need to understand
the the this the the level of what that
is in which that is you need to know
what that is it's real and that means an
outcome's going to come out no matter
who likes it who doesn't like it as long
as it fits
in to some narrative so you need to know
this so prime example is not is for
ignoring people that have healed
removing foods that actually stop
viruses and pathogens that are being
ignored
by
arrogant people in the
industry that cause real symptoms and
disease lectin
leaders don't know about these pathogens
like Epstein bar they don't know the RO
role in causing conditions and illnesses
such as Epstein bar and the true which
is the true cause of rheumatoid
arthritis they would rather think a
potato is causing somebody's ra than
discover the truth
that the cheese or the butter or the
milk in potato mashed
potatoes is actually feeding a virus not
the potato itself they wouldn't they
don't want to know that it's actually
feeding a virus causing more
ra you take that out the butter and you
take out that you take out that lard and
grease from a hash brown and you take
out that butter from from you know off
your potato and the cheese off your
potato the very foods that feed
pathogens and you just have a steamed
potato you have a good chance to heal
your
ra because of what I was talking about
earlier about the bioavailable LI scene
involved that stops the Epstein bar
virus from causing ra first of all letin
leaders don't even know ra is caused by
Epstein bar or any kind of pathogen or
virus they think the body's attacking
itself and destroying itself and then
they think a food is causing it I can't
tell you how remedial that is I can't
tell you how basically stupid that is I
can't even tell you to where we are
today in this day and age that we would
even be there still now today that we
would even be here with that kind of
unbelievable Joker ISM like it is
incredible they'd rather believe that
autoimmune is the immune system
attacking the body's own cells and
destroying itself since they don't
understand that what the autoimmune
theory that what it really is and how
it's inaccurate they don't understand
that they have nowhere else to turn
besides blaming it on
lectin and you know how important it is
for somebody in their career to hang
their hat on something you know how
important that is it means everything it
means everything okay hang your hat on
something doesn't matter if it's going
to hurt people harm people stop people
from getting better if you can hang your
hat on something that's what matters
creates your legacy right hang your hat
on something oh that's your
legacy that's how it
works all right
and that's how people get wrapped up
into the wrong
direction believing in part that lectin
are a problem because to supposedly
confuse the body and cause it to turn
against itself so okay lectin are the
reason the body's are turning against
itself first of all the body never turns
against itself it can't turn against
itself no lectin can make the body turn
against itself nor can anything else
make the body turn against
itself a virus actually infects the
body creating the inflammation your body
creates an
antibody whether it's discovered or Not
by research and science because there's
so many different antibodies that not
not even discovered that the body
creates to go after the pathogen and
destroy it but only the pathogen itself
this is Advanced information I'm giving
you that doesn't exist out there
Advanced information it's how I've
gotten people to heal and still get
people to heal I put it in my books I've
worked with people oneon-one for
decades and so we're still back in
stupidity land I mean I have to say I
hate saying that word but it's that
bad so they believe that the lectin are
the problem because they supposedly
confuse the body and cause it to turn
against itself while they remove the
foods that can help you heal such as
fruits and certain vegetables roots and
tubers leading you to eat more fats that
actually not only harm you but help feed
the pathogens because they put you you
on these really high-fat diets cuz
they're so sugar feared they're so s
such in fear of sugar they put you on
these high-fat
diets because they think oh wait wait a
minute this is that's what they put you
on and guess what that does it destroys
your liver it destroys your liver and
and and whether it's a they they all put
you on the high animal protein diets but
just say you want to be plant-based and
follow their law You' have to be on tons
and tons of of fats on a plant-based
diet too which doesn't help your
liver but understand this all The lectin
Advocates and leaders and study grp and
and and the people behind all the
studies all these years they're anti-
plant-based
movement I'm not anti- plant-based
movement I'm not anti- whatever animal
protein movement but I'm not anti-
plant-based movement they're an there's
a bias there's a bias nature to it all
they're anti fruit to begin
with so you have to understand EV
everybody involved in the lectin world
the anti-lectin
world everybody involved are all anti
fruit to begin with they all bought into
either the keto way or the high protein
way they're totally against all
plant-based modalities
whatsoever and they're totally against
fruit they're anti fruit to begin with
so the whole thing is built with a bias
against fruit itself do you know what
that means you know what that means when
you do a study it means you have a
belief system already set in place and
then you get funded for that belief
system so of course it's going to come
out in the way it's going to come out
because guess what it can't go any other
way especially when you don't even
believe in Fruit when you think somebody
shouldn't even be eating fruit because
of the sugar and fruit don't even
understand that fruits help heal dis
disease they help heal the liver they
help reverse disease in every way
possible that's how it
works so they end up removing the foods
that heal you sure you might get
temporarily results they take you off a
processed food because it's not lectins
and wheat it's another protein that
actually causes problems and I'll tell
you what it causes it feeds a virus
lectins don't feed viruses but certain
other types of protein and certain other
types of phytochemicals that are
actually in
wheat can feed a virus they don't even
know that they're so far removed from
even researching that because your mind
is shut and closed for so many reasons
we just talked about throughout this
whole show not even understanding that
people have healed from chronic illness
without their eltin their phony eltin
belief
systems
so they put you on these high fat diets
and they get rid of all fruit all
together together the very thing that
helps heal your liver and bring it back
and guess what's in your liver viruses
viruses that don't even know about
viruses that sit inside the liver that
the experts don't even know about that
science and research aren't even aware
about that sit there and those are the
viruses that create inflammation and
create chronic illness with all the
illnesses and autoimmune diseases that
we
have the lectin and fruits and
vegetables do not harm us I repeat the
lectin in fruits and vegetables do not
harm us please don't let any Source
confuse you into thinking that lectins
are like the toxic alkaloids produced as
a defense mechanism by some wild plant
not fit for human consumption let me go
into that a little
bit there are chotes and twigs in other
plants where if a deer takes a bite a
deer in the wild takes a bite alkaloids
will surface to repel that deer in other
animals and insects from damaging it
further I repeat
alkaloids not
lectins alkaloids because what they
throw at you they try to throw this
other bogus piece of science too they
try to say that well lectins what
happens is when you're picking your
vegetables and your
fruits and you know whether they're in
the wild or in your garden that the
plant build a defense mechanism to stop
you from eating
them that's what that's what the that's
what the argument is it's it's easy to
buy into it it's really great you know
what that's going to do it's going to
stop you from eating your fruits and
vegetables and other foods that could
really help you it's going to stop you
from doing that so then you can buy into
the whole lectin thing and you'll end up
sick anyway in 10 years because it's not
the it's not what does it and gets rid
of the viruses the very thing we talk
about in the books and here on the radio
show is to get people
better it's a sad sad day when I have to
I have to put out information to help
clear the ear the air and actually help
balance things back out again it's
amazing how things work so what happens
is is in the wild when a deer eats some
leaves off of a chute or a root that
came out of the I mean a chute that came
out of the
ground okay or it ate it ate some
leaves off of a young a
sapling it bit it bit some Twigs off of
some Maples the maple will re release an
enzyme an enzyme and an alkaloid to the
surface to protect the tree from the
deer that is not what our garden variety
vegetables and fruits and wild edibles
such as wild blueberries or other wild
herbs that we use like red clover and
everything else has that doesn't exist
for human consumption humans can eat and
choose to eat these there's a reason why
these foods are on the planet and
there's a reason why we grow them and
it's a reason why we eat them and it's
why they're here too and the fruits are
on the trees naturally and here God
given for us to actually heal and grow
and feed
ourselves it's
different because a deer and a wild
animal also has an enzyme in their mouth
that
triggers a wild twig a wild plant a
sapling like for instance an
alder or a baby maple or whatever kind
of plant or just you know a wild herb
coming out of the ground and so what
happens is when that deer comes along
and a deer bites this enzymes are
released that the enzymes come out of
the deer's mouth onto it it triggers
these alkaloids to surface that doesn't
exist with us when we grow green beans
out of our garden when we grow um
tomatoes out of our garden none of that
exists this is such a disaster of how
they can just spin everything it's
amazing just spin it all spin it all to
keep people from getting to where they
need to go and where they need to do
there are shoots and twigs and other
plants where if a deer takes a bite
alkaloids will surface to repel that
deer and other animal and insects from
damaging it further they're triggered
off by a deer's enzymes in a deer's
mouth we already don't eat those Foods
we don't eat those types of foods
they're toxic to us we already know
you're not supposed to eat the very
Foods in the wild that have these
alcohol IDs that now experts try to
trick us and say oh they're electons
this just how you can throw anything out
there anything out there you want to
confuse people believe me that's what
they do I know so you can do it you do
it you do it I watch it all day long out
there because they're backed by bias
studies interest groups interest money
investors investors somebody puts a half
a million dollars into something you
better have an outcome and the person
who who you know sold it to them to get
the money who has a belief system and
who's anti- fruit better be delivering
some kind of information to them even if
it means don't look at everything else
even it means ignore everything else
even if it means ignore how many people
have healed otherwise even if you would
ever that's how it
works so we already don't eat those
foods that are in the wild because
they're toxic to us and lectin aren't
even what makes them a problem Garden
variety fruits and veg vegetables and
even the wild plants we know to be
edible like I talked about before are in
a whole different category they're not
triggered we don't have an enzyme from a
deer inside of us a deer that and yet
they're being lumped together with
problematic alkaloid containing plants
again the lectins and the foods we eat
do not cause harm the lectins and the
foods we eat do not cause
harm there are certain proteins that
aren't in fruits and vegetables and are
in items such as da eggs and certain
grains like wheat and they do feed
pathogens and people don't understand
that part alone that part like there is
worth the price of
admission is worth the price of
admission that alone what I mean by
price of admission I mean you don't have
to pay a price I'm just saying if you're
going to go to a you know if you're
going to go out and see a a movie and
you're going to pay so much for a ticket
hopefully it's worth a price of that
ticket this alone is worth everything
knowing that there's certain proteins in
dairies Dairy and eggs and other
phytochemicals undiscovered by research
and science that feed
pathogens viruses and bacteria that are
creating the inflammation and guess what
you guys lectins aren't one of them
lectins are not one of them there are
dozens of proteins and compounds and
dairy and egg and Wheats and wheat for
experts to hang dozens and dozens of
hats on in their quest to alleviate
chronic illness and yet they try to hang
their hat on just one that's not even
the problem they try to hang their hat
on the lectin one it's utterly
ridiculous be concerned about
gluten-rich Foods absolutely and don't
be but don't be afraid about potatoes
and ripe Tomatoes I've watched them heal
the sickest people as I said before
saving even lives look out for
anti-lectin sediment and be ious about
buying into it this trendy mistake is
going to continue for quite a long time
it's here to stay because money has been
invested into
it so don't let it confuse you or
confuse the bear with healing into the
future it's another anti-f fruit
campaign you have to know that they're
going to hit the fruit in any way they
can because the minute you gain a little
power and you use the fear of The
Nightshade of the Tomato which I'm going
to talk about in a little while
minute you grab that you can then if
you're anti- fruit in general outside of
a handful of berries if you're anti
fruit in
general you can you know you you then
can use that you can wave that power
once you have people's attention you can
you can harness that power and be like
yeah well you shouldn't be eating other
fruits either because of all the sugar
and everything else and whatnot and
people be like whoa you must know what
you're talking
about so look it's another anti- fruit
campaign another bias design to stop you
from eating the fruits that heal your
body and you're
another excuse for medical research and
science is lack of knowledge about what
causes chronic
illness please don't let it Rob you or
your children of what you need to heal
along the
way see this as a beacon of light honest
to God see it as a beacon of light today
whatever you
do it's really important see it is a
beacon of light so let's talk about a
little bit more
about about about all of this are you
guys hanging are you hanging with me are
you with me you got some herbal tea with
you so I hope so I hope so okay so how
does this whole thing work in in other
ways let's talk about some other stuff
let's clear some other different things
going on with all of this um okay let's
go into the banana let's go into the
banana fruit fear people anti-lectin
people they don't like a ripe banana
because they don't like ripe bananas
because of because of sugar because
they're concerned about sugar the only
way to eat a banana is ripe you don't
want it overripe but you don't want it
under rpe it's the only way to eat one
bananas have the ability when they're in
their ripe stage to stop literally HIV
the retrovirus
HIV that's they can repel the retrovirus
HIV they also have antiviral properties
that that are incredible they've healed
kill people with colitis colitis severe
severe colitis ulcerative colitis
hemorrhaging just hemorrhaging blood
vessels bananas I've seen bananas turn
people around with colitis because
colius is viral not the body attacking
itself here's a prime example of a
mistake going on it's thrown into the
autoimmune disease category because
science research have no idea anything
about it lectin people don't know
anything about colitis they don't know
anything about any autoimmune disease
they don't the best lectin doctors don't
know anything about best lectin
scientists don't know anything about
autoimmune disease of course not if they
did they wouldn't know what it was they
don't know what it is with colitis it's
a virus and that virus sits inside the
uh colon and it sits in the Linings of
the colon and if you feed it the wrong
Foods yes it eats and they don't know
that either it eats and it eats the
wrong Foods it'll eat dairy it'll eat
eggs it'll eat like the other things I
talked about that are in wheat and other
grains and stuff like that it'll eat
that
and but when you put banana in it helps
kill off the virus antiviral properties
but lectin experts love to do the ripe
the unripe banana the green banana I
can't tell you how
destructive that is to the intestinal
tract a g solid rock hard green banana
I'm just going to tell you right now
unripe is so hard to digest so hard to
digest it's unbelievable that's that and
and but yet they like that as an option
because they're so afraid of sugar
because it hasn't it hasn't developed
its sugars yet so they like taking the
skin off don't do the don't do that
green banana thing it's a way to really
irritate your gut
Linings because that's that's what
happens when it's unripe like that you
can't do that but when it's ripe it
heals your gut Linings that's how it
works this is just just a simple mistake
already just a I mean it's not even
simple it's a ridiculous mistake already
being made out of the fruit fear out of
the fear of sugar out of the fear of
fruit causing harm it's
unbelievable bananas soothe the
intestinal tract lining they bring down
inflammation do you know how by actually
stopping pathogens that are causing
inflammation so they bring down the
inflammation I've seen bananas save
lives over the years severe Crohn's and
Colitis cases I've had to put them on
nothing but bananas and celery juice not
celery celery juice and and bananas to
recover them to stop them from getting
their intestinal tracks cut
out and save their
lives and they're living their lives
now okay but entitled arrogance in the
industries and the leading experts out
there who think lactans is the cause of
everything would even think that existed
even if it was put in front of their
face because if it didn't fit into their
reasoning no no no no the world's the
world stops for lectins it's like okay
no everybody's sick it's because of the
lectin everybody's sick that's it's
lectin that's what it is now that's what
it is
unbelievable
Tomatoes Tomatoes stop cancer banana
stop cancer too but Tomatoes stop cancer
but they just don't stop cancer they got
a vitamin C in it different than any
vitamin C there is and let me tell you
about the whole Nightshade thing to
begin with
Nightshade all that means is it may
Blossom sometimes a Nightshade May
blossom in the Night Under The
Moonlight if the moon is strong enough
and when it does that fruit Harbors a
vitamin C that's stronger than any other
vitamin C tomato vitamin C is very
powerful it stops viruses and pathogens
do you know why tomato got a bad wrap
because it was always with v
Parmesan sauce you know it was the sauce
with v parmesan it was it was the tomato
sauce on just you know wheat pasta wheat
pasta penet pasta tomato
sauce it was you know it's it's it was
it's on pizza with a gluten you a crust
filled with gluten and oil and grease
and
cheese of course no one so many people
over the years reported they reported
that they had some kind of reaction when
they had their Pizza this in the old
days they had a reaction when they had
their their their parmesan whatever that
is with the sauce and everything their
ravioli with the sauce and they the
Tomato was always blamed on it because
of a rumor spread about a tomato being a
night shade so they were like well the
cheese is in a night shade that's not a
night shade that can't be hurting you um
the Butter's not in a night shade that
can't be hurting you meanwhile those are
the things that are actually feeding the
the viruses and pathogens to create your
arthritis so but see how the bad wrap
occurred it's amazing how the bad wrap
happened so wait a minute so the the
gluten in the crust that's not a night
shade now we're all anti-gluten of
course but this is how it got the wrap
the bad wrap a fresh heirloom Ripe
Tomato is so healing when it's thrown on
top of a salad of
spinach a little bit of
avocado it's just an little squeeze of
lime or lemon it is so healing there's
nothing wrong with it and you know what
it does it stops cancers it stops
viruses it's loaded with minerals it's
got a vitamin C to reverse disease it's
good for the thyroid it's incredible for
the liver and it's good for the gut and
you don't have to do anything to that
tomato to change it prime example prime
example of how trendy traps work just
don't get sucked into them whatever you
do it's not worth it why am I fighting
for this I'm not making money off of
this it's not like I have a a lectin
supplement company where I sell lectins
and someone's anti-lectin out there with
all their literature and all the
different studies out there and now I'm
like oh I better I better clean up this
mess in order to sell my eltin
supplement because if everybody's
anti-lectin now I'm going to go out of
business what do I what am I earning
from this what am I getting from this
what am I getting from this I know what
the elcin people are getting from this
they're getting money and they got and
they got interest groups involved and
they got Investments and everything else
I know what they're getting out of it
what am I getting out of it battling it
what am I getting out of it trying to
bring you the truth what tell me what
I'm getting out of it I'm not getting
one penny out of it so what the heck let
me tell you what I'm getting out of it
I'm getting out of it because you know
when when I go to my grave down because
we you know long down the road and it's
time for me to leave here I know I did
right for the people I know I did right
you better believe it I know I had your
back I know I had your back and I still
do have your back I knew it in IND know
and and I know it and I feel it and
that's what it's about it's making sure
you protect yourself it's making sure
that whether you know it or not that one
tomato you
ate actually helped you heal whether you
know it or not I know it so and that's
what that's you know it gives me
peace so anyway okay
so
so they we're talking about just for the
record Nightshade plants like our our
vegetables and Nightshade fruits and
stuff they grow in full sun they need
full sun a tomato plant needs full I've
grown tomatoes my whole life I've grown
tomatoes I can't tell you how healing it
is little Sun gold Tomatoes my God you
know how good those are for you you know
how packed of minerals they are sun gold
did you ever see those at the farmers
market Sun gold so juicy and so sweet so
good for you
unbelievable what they do for glucose
they Stop Diabetes they heal your liver
I mean what they can do for you is
extraordinary and they're under attack
they're under attack the sun gold
sitting at the farmer's market I can't
tell you I've grown Sun Golds I've grown
all the cherry tomatoes I've grown all
the different kinds of tomatoes in my
life I've grown them because they're
good for you they're good for you so
look anti like I said anti-lectin
Advocates started hating fruit la long
ago before they even learned about
lectin so lectin experts and Advocates
didn't even know they didn't even know
about lectin they didn't even know they
just hated fruit to begin with they were
anti fruit part of that anti- fruit
movement when you listen to the fruit
fear show part of the anti-m
movement and I'm just telling you how
this stuff
happens so we're coming to the end of
the show there's more to talk about with
the Leon world because you know there's
I I know there's more to talk about um
first of all I'm going to do a gut
health show another gut health show and
talk about how leaky gut really works
how it all works and they and they're
trying to package lectin you're going to
go everywhere they can now they're going
to say lectin oh can help with the
meaning can hurt leaky gut that's not
even possible and I can't wait to go
into that when we have a
chance have you checked out the thyroid
book check it out um just came out
pretty recently actually recently it's
it's it's in it's the beginning of being
out there check it out and uh you know
you can help people there's o over a
hundred symptoms and conditions inside
that book I explain what the causes are
and they're not
lectin they're not lectin the real
causes of over a hundred different
symptoms and conditions like across the
board you got a symptom it's probably in
there and it's not Leck and caused okay
so just know that there's so many things
things people suffer with so many
different illnesses and chronic
illnesses and yes it's tricky because if
you get rid of gluten you might feel
better because guess what wheat
something in wheat like the gluten does
feed pathogens which which is why you're
not feeling good don't get that confused
with the lectin propaganda and rhetoric
that's out there now to try to rob you
of healing do not get that confused
whatever you do and that's going to be
that a big mistake in your healing
process a big mistake look it's easy to
fall prey for what's out there now with
information years ago when the internet
wasn't around very few books existed in
the health movement and I had this
Advanced information that I'm giving you
today and every day on this radio show
every time I do the radio show Advanced
information that's in my books I had
years ago same Advanced information and
I was giving it to people and guess what
they didn't have to fight through all
the garbage that's out there and now
that the garbage kept in growing growing
growing like Spirit told me it would the
fight's going to be harder and harder to
actually get people better but we can do
it I I have some faith and I have some
hope and I have some Faith peace in your
heart I love you dearly take one day at
a time don't be afraid of your fruits
your vegetables okay take one day at a
time I love you be good you know keep
your fats low your diet whether you're
vegan plant-based vegetarian or paleo or
high protein keep your or whatever
trendy diet you're on keep your fats
lower keep them lower so your liver can
heal so your liver is not being pushed
to the maxed and poisoned so you can
actually get better and then work on
bringing in more fruits vegetables leafy
greens celery juice you name it heavy
metal detox smoothie I love you guys God
bless you take care one day at a time
byebye I'm thinking about you you