hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing
information much of which is not found
anywhere else and is decades ahead of
what's out there now and that's how it
has to be in order to heal because
what's going on in the alternative
environment for medicine in the
conventional environment for medicine
isn't really healing anybody well I
can't say that entirely people get a
little bit better there are some amazing
surgeons out there too that remove
things out of people's bodies if
somebody gets an appendicitis if
somebody has an aneurysm there's
incredible surgeons so but I'm talking
about chronic illness that's where the
disaster lies it doesn't lie with with a
liver transplant we got amazing people
out there to to remove a liver put one
in I mean you know we're in a great
place uh medical science and research is
in a great place when we're doing that
kind of thing but where are we with
chronic illness it's disastrous I'm
sorry to say but disastrous and the best
information out there in the internet or
or in books or wherever you can find
isn't enough because we have 250 million
Americans alone and I'm not even talking
about global and and 250 million
Americans that are sick with symptoms
out of the over 300 million plus
Americans that we have here and that are
sick with symptoms and different
conditions many diagnosed wrong many
symptoms they don't no one
understands that's where we are with
chronic illness so does this radio show
have to be ahead of the time darn right
you better believe it has to be ahead of
the time and it has to be ahead of
everything else and it is and that's the
whole point this radio show it has clean
and pure information if you're brand new
to this in if you're brand new to this
radio show medical medium radio show and
everything else around it make sure that
you tell friends too that the
information here is not backed by agenda
driven money stuff like that all that
crazy stuff that's in the industry like
the medical lobbyists and everything
else around it that are involved with
making sure that conventional medicine
is poisoned meaning as far as for
chronic illness and alternative medicine
is poisoned for chronic illness so that
when you go and you try to find help you
get told you got Lyme disease when you
may not have Lyme disease or you get
told you have multiple sclerosis when
you don't have multiple sclerosis or you
never get told what causes anything or
it it could be anything going on tingles
and numbness aches and pains blurry eyes
brain fog confusion then you're told
it's something in your gut when that's
not really what it is it's one thing
after another you got Ser there's people
out there walking around fatigue chronic
fatigue everywhere with all kinds they
can't do anything they all kinds of
symptoms weak Limbs and frustration
anxiety depression and not getting the
answers so when it comes down to that
science is behind and studies do not the
whole thing studies and research search
don't really match up to anything with
everybody's suffering from aches and
pains joint pain nerve pain neuropathy
everything going on all of it is still a
mystery migraines headaches you name it
have I said enough and that's still a
mystery to research and science it's
still a mystery to to most professionals
so this is pretty actually all
professionals really when you think
about it unless they know what's causing
everything now the reason why I'm saying
this and being so strong about all this
all of this is because we're going into
we're going into protein is where we're
heading and before we go into protein I
just have to let everybody know that the
information here in the show isn't
because I believe in one thing or I
believe in another thing or I got some
belief system and I'm going to I'm going
to shove a whole bunch of protein crap
right down your throat a whole bunch of
protein nonsense and knowledge down your
throat maybe science and and research
believes you need this amount of protein
I'm just going to take that and just
shove that right at you no we're not
going to do that we need the truth
instead we can't get tricked and we
can't get fooled because let me tell you
something when it comes down to the
protein and the protein whole phenomenon
to the whole Obsession and everything
about protein we're getting tricked
we're getting fooled if anybody's ever
played a trick on you you didn't like it
I can guarantee you that I'm sure you
didn't but if someone plays a trick on
you and it's your whole lifetime and
your family's lifetime before you and
your mother and father's Lifetime and
your grandparents lifetime before you
and everybody else's lifetime before you
and after you your children and this the
same trick the same joke is being played
on your children and their children it's
not a good thing and the protein problem
is this very trick and that's the big
that's the deal so we're going to go
right into that we have to the
information that show is pure untampered
with it's not
supported by the thumb on the scale
research and science that forces studies
to go a certain direction to take care
of investors that put their money in it
so everybody's happy except for the
person with chronic illness well we have
nothing to do with that and thank God
and I'm so darn happy we have nothing to
do with that and that's why people are
healing check out check out medical
medium books you know my books check out
the whole thing learn and heal and it's
really important to do that so let's go
right into protein look I sound a little
extra edgy today a little extra snarky
on this but there's there's a reason for
this because protein has been like it's
like the thorn in people's sides because
the minute you follow the protein law
the law of protein you get yourself
messed up you fall into a trap you fall
into a ditch you step into a pothole you
get yourself in big trouble and you have
to know this for your own good it's
critical because you have to protect
your family you have to protect your
friends you have to protect your loved
ones you got to protect yourself
whatever you got to do and the protein
machine I call it the protein machine is
an evil evil
machine it's an evil machine that
doesn't that doesn't take hostages it's
an it's an evil machine that wants to
take people down it sounds crazy well
back in the
1930s okay the 1930s a deal was made in
the industries a deal you have no idea
about a deal that never gets surfaced it
never gets talked about and it doesn't
even get talked about with with all the
different food groups the food Wars you
got the Paleo people and the protein
eaters here you got the vegans you got
the vegetarians here and you got this
food War out there and everybody's like
trying to throw science reg garbled like
junk science just whatever it is just
throwing it back and forth you know the
Paleo people and the high protein people
are all like well you vegans you're
going to be starving and you need your
protein and where you're going to get
your protein and the vegans and the
plant-based people are all trying to
prove hey we got protein we're throwing
and you're eating all the animal meat
and that's all bad too and there's this
war going on out there and it's pretty
intense but everybody's keeping busy and
and their eye is on this protein ball
and they're passing this protein ball
back and forth back and forth some more
authors come out and write about the
same protein ball back and forth back
and forth more experts come out and talk
about it on you know whatever TV shows
back and forth and guess what you get
burned you get burned yeah that's right
you get burned and no one knows about
the deal and the deals that have been
made in the past to make sure protein
confuses the crap out of you guys that
protein confuses the heck out of you
guys so guess what you stay sick that's
right and you end up staying sick
because the minute you got your eye on
the protein ball Hey look it's all about
protein look at the back of the package
it's protein ignore what what's really
in the food ignore what can actually
cure your illness because hey no one
knows it creates chronic illness anyway
so why how would you know unless you
read the medical medium books and
everything and if you don't then you
don't know what causes any disease or
illness so there you go and so what
happens is we end up just lost in the
protein land did you get enough protein
oh I'm hungry I must need protein oh my
hair's falling out I must need protein
oh my Skin's not feeling good looking
good I must need protein Oh My Nails oh
must be protein your nails aren't strong
must be protein oh let's get let's go
and get you know let's go to a a and
they'll put all the stuff on your face
and be like oh it's going to help it's
got proteins in it oh let's wrap you up
in proteins let's do this let's do that
hair shampoo oh there's proteins in this
hair shampoo it'll help your hair get
thicker it's endless Madness and
stupidity you guys wouldn't believe it
and yeah I've been staying away from
this topic I've been staying away from
it there's a reason why because it's
that annoying it's so annoying I almost
couldn't stand to want to do this but
the problem is problem is I have to do
this I have to because if you don't have
it straight if you don't know what's
going on how are you really going to get
better when your adrenals are shot how
are you really going to get better if
you got the chronic fatigue because
you're viral how are you going to get
better if you got Twitches aches and
pain spasms Tremors okay the shakes
weakness fatigue fear chaos anxiety
depression blurriness brain fog floaters
in the eyes how are you going to get
better when you don't know anything
about those things and you're looking
for protein how are you going to get
better if you're searching for protein
to be your answer when you're walking
around sick and you go to a new doctor
and I'm not listen I'm not picking on
the doctors you know that you know that
you know how I am I know a lot of
doctors I love doctors that's not the
problem is at all it's just unique the
doctors can't help what's being taught
to them that's all it's as simple as
that it's like a whole bad school it's a
whole big bad school out there in health
and there's everybody goes to it and
files in and learns what they learn and
what they learn is old old old deals
that were made old deals that were made
hear me out hear me out okay back in the
1930s all right protein came to town it
was like Santa Claus coming to town and
this wasn't no friendly nice good Santa
Claus this was a Santa Claus with big
contracts of tons of paper tons of paper
contracts that sit in vaults that you
don't even have your hand you couldn't
even touch these contracts no way in
hell it's called grandfathered contracts
in business to make sure protein was
literally the focus in every institution
school every medical school every single
school from elementary school across the
country to everywhere possible protein
was a new word where did you get your
protein if you're going to grow and
you're going to drink some milk you're
going to get protein out of your milk
you're going to grow strong bones and
strong muscles so you better get your
protein and these deals were made they
were slimy greasy disgusting deals that
were made in the old day where money was
passed from one person to another and it
institutionalized as protein being God's
answer to everything and you know what
else was happening but 1940s early
1940s everybody was filing into doctor's
office of sick left and right for the
first time in history to this degree
where women were find in in like armies
of women were coming in with anxiety
depression for the first time in the
1940s they were coming in with mystery
symptoms like never before I've talked
to old doctors I remember in the '90s
cuz I was doing this in the 90s and I
was doing this in the 80s I was doing
this for this is what I had I didn't
start this five years ago I didn't start
this six years ago oh he's the medical
medium what he started 3 years ago no
I've been doing this forever since I've
been here and I'm going to tell you tell
you right now I talked to old doctors in
the '90s
okay back then and they were in their
'90s they had a history of knowing what
happened in
1940 okay so if someone says hey what do
you know what happened in 1940 Mr Big
medical medium I'll tell you I do know
what happened in 1940 don't tell me
different don't tell me different I do
know and I talked to a lot of old
doctors in the in back then okay and
they said they couldn't believe it it
was like they woke up in morning they
had their coffee they Dr drove to work
okay in their old the old cars the old
Buick or whatever they had they drove to
work they got there and there was a line
at the door it was that fast they said
they've never seen anything like it and
they only had a couple of fallbacks to
go on because when they looked for help
from research in science research in
science said tell them they need protein
tell them maybe they're not getting
enough protein if that doesn't work tell
them they're crazy and it's all in their
head tell all the women they're crazy
and it's all in their head and if that
doesn't work okay tell them it's
hormones because science and research is
manufacturing hormones for the first
time now we're going to need to sell
them you see what I mean we've been
duped in so many ways we've been smacked
in the heads in so many ways we don't
even know we don't even
know and meanwhile everybody was coming
in due to DDT poison mercury poisoning
heavy metal intoxification they're
coming in because of Epstein early bar
viruses were finally hitting the fan
which you got to learn about in thyroid
healing you got to read that book front
to back to really know about the Epstein
bar and and they know it's not out there
the information that's out there that's
sadly not out there yet and don't get
fooled when science when somebody puts
out a little thing and they say oh seven
seven diseases that that are linked to
Epstein bar don't get fooled by that
they're just trying to derail you once
again it's not linked it's act the EP
bar is is the cause of these diseases I
talk about all the time don't get fooled
by that information that you see
floating around that's another to try to
derail the progress that we've made you
and I have made so what happens with the
protein ball everybody's passing that
baby around now everybody's passing that
around and that thing is still in the
way that means that if you're doing
something right for yourself you're
going to end up doing something wrong
for yourself CU you're going to be
thinking protein someone's going to tell
you did you get enough protein and
you're going to derail your
process that's how it works that's how
it works so let's talk about protein and
different light I'm giving you the
history of protein with the dirty deals
the dirty deals that are made going all
the way back the old dirty deals you
better believe it going all the way back
protein has a nasty business behind it
I'm just telling you and a lot of money
to be made off of it in the past and a
hell of a lot of money is made off of it
now because it's an endless topic and no
matter you know and I'm not even going
to be able to stop it it's like the lime
disease thing the truth about Lyme
disease I talk about in book one in
medical medium book one the truth about
lme disease is in there okay about how
it was originally viral it is viral it
still is viral even though there's some
bacteria present and I talk about how
the lime labs are all messed up and
everything else and I talk about all
this stuff like it's all there if you're
getting upset and you got Lyme disease
just get the book and read it and give
it a chance so you can protect yourself
but I'm never going to be able to stop
the lime train I don't think the lime
trap that's out there there's too many
Labs too many doctors they're all
working together no one knows what's
going on and it's just too big and I
don't think I can change the course of
that one and I don't think I'll ever
change the course of the protein mistake
either but you know maybe I'm just wrong
and maybe we are going to change the
course on the protein thing finally
maybe it's possible and the same thing
with the lime thing possibly I mean we
know we've gotten thousands and tens of
thousands and tens of thousands of
people better with Lyme disease we know
that already so maybe we are changing
the course but listen to
this when it comes down to protein it's
so big it's such a big
giant that even when you hear the show
and you listen to the show and you got
the straight you got the straight and
narrow you you know what it is you know
what's going on about protein you
understand what's going on with protein
you're still going to bump into a wall
possibly because it's that riddled with
misinformation out there about protein
and there's that much protein fear and
there's that much it's in it's literally
passed down a generation now since 1930
and and you can't you can't even you
can't even get around it and so it's it
hits everybody it's like when women are
pregnant is are you getting enough
protein first of all protein isn't even
what takes care of the baby when you're
pregnant it's not even the very thing
it's minerals it's nutrients
phytochemicals and food it's
antioxidants those are the things that
develop a baby it's carbohydrates that
develop a baby it's all these other
things that develop a baby and then the
baby's liver develops its own protein
too which is the key see that's the
whole thing you need all these other
things in Foods so that your own liver
which science and research doesn't even
know about creates your proteins the
ones that the body accepts as actual
protein to do the things that science
theorizes that the body May do with
protein your liver and by the way Liver
Rescue is it's on its way it is on its
way so you got to check that out go to
Amazon and check it out I did everything
I did everything for that book I don't
even know what I didn't do I didn't put
just the kitchen sink in there I mean I
put a bathtub in there there's a bathtub
in that book it's it's it's insane it's
unbelievable okay so so that's what
happens so research and science doesn't
know what the liver does it it just
doesn't the liver has thousands of
chemicals chemical functions thousands
one of them is producing proteins so the
body can identify those proteins and use
them that's one thing okay that's where
we get our proteins the most but eating
Foods eating foods that heal and feed
the liver eating foods that take care of
us that give us all these other things
can then allow the liver to create
proteins we need undiscovered proteins
the liver creates hundreds of proteins
hundred
that have the function that function
that are used for the body to function
with and it has even nothing to do with
food or what's in
food except the right Foods the right
Foods lots of fruits and vegetables help
the liver perform its
functions so see what I mean that's how
unbel that's how butt backwards we are
that's how butt backwards we are
unbelievable and it's even more than
that there are protein sources in food
yes and they are helpful they are
helpful but there's harmful ones too and
I'm going to cover that so you guys
we're going to cover that of course you
know which ones they are I'm sure you
know so we're going to cover those
different harmful ones but there's
helpful ones the proteins and spinach
really good for us really good just make
sure it's raw spinach make sure it's not
cooked it has to be raw spinach it's a
really high protein Source Nori you know
when you have your Nori wraps your Nori
rolls the sushi rolls but the the Nori
rolls and you put whatever you you put
avocado in there and you put some
cucumber in there and some celery and a
little tomato you wrap it up and you cut
it in slices and you put it nicely on a
tray so that's that's something right
well there's lots of protein in the
norish sheet and we can't get confused
protein's not supposed to satiate hunger
the reason why we look for animal
proteins and this is an A bash on animal
protein I'm going to tell you right now
I'm going to tell you straight up right
here this isn't propaganda against
animal the animal protein War world and
this isn't propaganda against the vegan
World okay you have to understand this
for sure because a lot of people even
when I explain myself like that you
should see some people are just like oh
he's just he's he's throwing propaganda
against the vegans oh he's throwing
propaganda against the meat eaters no
I'm not I'm not at all here's how it
works there's fat that's with protein
that's how it get satiated so if you're
a vegan you're eating so many nuts and
seeds and so many cashews and it's okay
to eat some nuts and seeds it's okay to
eat eat some uh pumpkin seeds and some
flow seeds it's okay to use a little bit
of olive oil extra virgin olive oil cold
pressed it's okay and same thing with
the animal products it's okay if you
that's what you like and that's what
you're feeling good and you got no
problems and your liver's nice and
strong and you want to eat some animal
protein of some kind it's okay to have
some animal protein but remember there's
fat in these
proteins and they can't be
separated so what we get satiated on
which makes us think we need more and
more protein is we get satiated on that
fat content and guess what that fat
content that's in a ton of nuts will
kill your liver it will kill your
liver because you it's that the high fat
diet is the problem that's the problem
and no one wants to address that on any
level the high I'm not talking about the
trans fatty acids I'm not talking about
you know some some crazy fast food
restaurant that's got it's got the fryer
going with God knows what kind of Grease
is in that fryer and it's just it's
rancid and it's just it's bubbling over
and you frying crap in there and and you
know and you get pancreatitis from it
I'm not talking about those bad fats or
the the bad fats and some cupcake that's
packaged in some some brand that's
popular and mainstream that's sitting on
the shelf in the grocery store and it's
got all kinds of crazy fats that are in
there too all hidden and wound up in
there those are terrible yeah they kill
the liver yeah they make us sick I'm not
talking about those no no no no no no
way I'm talking about what happens when
you eat too much animal protein too much
too much you're eating meat for
breakfast God forbid I mean seriously
you end up getting your fatty liver you
get you'll end up with diabetes down the
road no matter what I don't care how
much exercise you're doing you'll be
like at a doctor's office be like your
A1 C's up you better cut out that one
apple you eat a day you better that must
be it it's not all the meat and chicken
you're eating and it's not all the eggs
you're eating you better cut out that
one apple that's how stupid things are I
have to say that word I can't help it
it's idiotic here's the thing here's the
thing okay same thing with the vegans
doing the plant you guys I know so many
of you guys are plant-based listen to me
I I I adore you I totally support it one
billion percent but I got a lot of
plant-based people and and they can't
eat any fruit because they're so busy
eating so much of the other stuff
they're eating two avocados three
avocados a day then they're having a
whole bunch of nuts and seeds they're
eating two tablespoons of coconut oil a
day they're putting in their smoothies a
whole like almond butter left and right
and this isn't just the plant-based
people even the people that are lowering
animal protein don't eat right so even
there you know some of the doctors out
there that are prancing around with new
ideas saying oh yeah I still eat animal
protein but you got to lower it and and
but what you got to do is still focus on
high fat lots of fats fats are good for
the brain they're good for the brain no
they're not terrible for the brain
terrifying for a brain what's not been
discovered by research and science is
people have fatty brains they have fatty
brains just like fatty liver just like
fatty liver and that's what kills people
too that's what kills people too you
know that expression Fathead yeah it's
legit it's real no one knows it or
realizes it but it's real the brain can
get fatty the brain itself the liver
gets fatty so even the fancy books that
are out there now with misinformation
left and right because of a theory or
because of a belief system that they're
going to just shove down your throat
even those that say oh but no high Fat's
still great yes you got to start lower
your animal protein but high fat you
still want more lots of avocados and you
want all these all all this almond
butter straight right into your smoothie
every morning and you don't want to eat
too much fruit stay away from those
sweet fruits it's ridiculous in fact it
set sends you down to not healing and
here's the problem if you're working on
your healing process and you're ebbing
and flowing because of the natural
healing process or because your
supplements that you're on maybe you're
on the wrong supplements or something or
maybe whatever and you start taking a
turn for a second you're going to think
it's protein you're going to instantly
blame even if you're on a good diet
you're going to blame it and that's a
whole another disaster if you're on a
good diet you're going to blame that
good diet as being a protein problem and
you're going to shuffle around to
another diet and then to another belief
system then another ideology another
you're just going to be moving and
moving around and cheating yourself at
getting better classic and I see it all
the time it's painstaking it's painful
reason why I put Liver Rescue out there
is because of this it's just because of
this reason this is one of the reasons
you need to know what's going on inside
the body and what to do including
supplements and everything around
supplements so here's the deal okay I'm
going to be straight up all right if
you're eating animal protein there's
some to avoid some you can have that
won't kill your liver and you got to do
it in moderation depending on where you
are with your sickness if you're eating
plant-based you're eating vegan there's
there's some nuts and seeds you can have
some avocado you can have some little
coconut oil you can have you can also
have that if you eat meat and you could
also have that you don't but the point
is all the fats got to come down a
little bit you got to make a conscious
effort to bring them down a little bit
bit that's the key it has nothing to do
with protein at all proteins put there
so you you don't even know how much fat
you're
eating that was one of the key things
because what happened was and just so
you know the fats the the government
standards of fats and all this you know
if you look at the stats on fats how
much fats are in the food how much fat
are in a piece of meat how much Fat's in
a piece of chicken how much Fat's in a
nuts you know they're all wrong do you
know they're all wrong every Farm is
different every single animal is
different they're completely wrong to
the degree of how much Fat's and
everything and everybody knew it at the
get-go all the way back they got you
focused on the protein so nobody eats
healthy enough and the reason why they
do that is so the industry keeps sick
people filing in left and right because
it's a massive trillion trillion dollar
machine that's grandfathered in with
contracts and deals made over centuries
and you guys are all Pawns in the game
man all Pawns in the game if you play
with the protein train if you want to
ride the protein train you're going to
be part of that whole game I'm not
trying to rhyme here it's just happening
naturally okay I'm not a rhyme I'm not a
good
rhyme so all right look the bottom line
is when you think protein you got to
instantly think of fat that's all think
of fats okay wait a minute no wait a
minute fats how much how many fats are
in my diet and you got to lower them a
little bit I don't care what illness you
have what disease what symptom you have
to lower the fats a little bit if you
want out I'm giving you a golden ticket
it's like willly Wonka's you know the
Chocolate Factory or whatever The Candy
Factory it's like you're getting the
golden ticket you're opening up that
chocolate bar which I don't want you
really eating too many chocolate bars
you open up that chocolate bar and then
gold golden ticket is there and I'm
trying to hand you that golden ticket
you can smack me in the face smack it
out smack the golden ticket out of my
hand go ahead slap it out of my hand go
ahead I'm okay with that I'm okay I've
been slapped before go ahead just smack
it out of my hand smack me in the head
if you want okay but I'm trying to hand
you I'm trying to to hand you I told you
I was a little bit a little bit a little
bit extra excited today you know I'm
trying to hand you the golden ticket you
want to call it the Golden Goose of the
golden egg I'll do that too handing you
the Golden Goose the golden egg I'm
handing you whatever it is you know and
and it's important it's important
because it can help you can save you can
make your life live longer you hear
about aging aging everybody worried
about aging I don't want to age I don't
want to age with 20-year-olds don't
really care about aging too much you
they're just too busy with everything
else right then you hit 30 and you're
like wait a minute I'm 30 oh I'm out of
my 20s and you get a little scared right
and you HS start hitting 40 you're like
oh my God I'm 40 I'm aging don't want to
age I don't want to I don't want gray
hair I don't want to age I don't want
whatever whatever I don't want my skin
to go bad I don't want to age I don't
want to get disease I don't want to
start breaking down I don't want my
bones and body to start breaking down my
muscles breaking down I don't want all
of that
happening but it will if you're focused
on protein it
will even if you're an athlete and
you're in your 50s and you're working
out and you don't seem to have a scrap
effect on your body if you're focused on
protein you can set yourself up for a
heart attack from Hell a heart attack
from hell I see it all the time I've
witnessed it all the time I've seen
people drop dead out there in the world
I talk to people and they're like I
can't believe how many people are
dropping dead joeo is dropping dead this
other person Saras Su dropped dead
they're all just they're all just
dropping dead out there heart attacks
Galore oh what were they eating I don't
know they seem to be healthy they were
exercising they were doing low carb they
were they were taking care of themselves
I don't you know the whole bit the whole
bit now In fairness to the plant-based
people and fairness to the vegans and
plant-based people okay there's a double
standard out there and I feel bad for
the plant-based people because here's
the deal all the meat eaters are allowed
to be sick because guess what out of 330
million Americans or whatever it is just
say it's 330 million Americans I I don't
know the number don't quote me on it
don't say hey we got him he doesn't even
know the number of am I'm just saying
okay I don't quote me on that there's
three 330 million Americans out of them
300 29 million
900 whatever okay whatever it is and if
you want to go percentage you know it's
99 something something per meat eaters
meat eaters okay just letting you know
and I don't mean meat any kind of animal
product theaters plant-based people it's
just a fraction you think there's a lot
of them no it's a real small just such a
small amount it's so tiny it's utterly
ridiculous and if one plant-based person
one vegan gets sick or has a symptom or
they're they're wafering back and forth
with a with a with some kind of problem
because they have a virus or something
else that has nothing to do with what
they're eating and they get they don't
feel well the meat eating world just
comes down on them it's a double
standard but we're not allowed you you
know what I mean we're not allowed and
that's the whole thing we shouldn't do
that we shouldn't be allowed to come
down on the plant-based people we we
shouldn't be
allowed to come down on the on the
plant-based people the vegan people we
shouldn't be that we shouldn't we're not
supposed to be doing that jumping on
them and we're not allowed to do that
the thing is is the vegans they're not
allowed to jump on the the the animal
protein people when they get sick
they're not they're not and you know but
the thing is is the animal people the
animal protein people they jump on them
they SC they they try to crush the
vegans and the plant-based people oh
it's because you're not getting protein
oh it's and I got to say all fairness
that's terrible that's terrible because
there isn't any vegans really it's a
small crew and vegans are only vegans
for a little while they're not vegans
for 30 40 years I mean they maybe people
are vegan for a month and then they're
off of it maybe people are vegan for a
year they're off of it there's not many
so you can't they can't be judged in all
fairness that's uncool it's uncool to be
judging that when there's or
329 million animal protein of some sort
some kind of animal protein
eaters and what about all the sickness
that's the majority of the country and
and they're all sick out of the when I
say there's 250 million Americans that
are sick that and there is I'm telling
you right now don't get confused by
television don't get confused by TV
because you see some people that look
look healthy on TV because they're hired
for a commercial or whatever it is don't
get confused by that there's over 250
million sick
Americans and you know how you got to
understand it's all the animal protein
years but I'm not just saying that's why
they're sick I'm saying and that's where
we have to clear this up right now I'm
saying it's because of the high fat diet
the high fat diets the too much fat in
the diets it's not about the animal
protein really in the end it's it's
about the fat and in the vegans when
vegans get sick they're on way too much
fat too so the small amount of vegans
it's a small crew it's a really small
crew out there you don't think it is
it's small believe me and that small
crew they they they're on high fat diets
too and they get
sick and there's both sides are looking
for
protein that's what I'm trying to say so
you got to be really careful you got to
lower the fats what does that mean if
you're plant-based you got to keep the
avocados where it's like one a day you
know maybe even a half of avocado a day
maybe it's a handful of nuts and seeds
in between and the rest lots of fruits
salads if you're if you're you know if
you do some cooked food you can do
potatoes sweet potatoes winter squash
you can do all that if you're raw you do
lot extra bananas and dates with salads
and greens and you make sure you get
your celery juice in we're going to talk
about rebuilding muscle too so just hang
in there for this ride hang in there
okay I hope this show is interesting
enough I hope it's interesting enough
cuz I I want you guys to know all this
stuff okay and if you're doing animal
protein you got to bring you can't be
eating meat three times a day I've never
seen anything good ever come out of in
all my years and I'm not anti-animal
product person and all I'm telling you
right now I'm not one and I've never
seen anything good I swear to God out of
out of eating animal protein of some
kind three times a day never seen
anything good come out of it it I I'm
telling you right now ever ever and if
you say someone lived to be 85 and ate
animal products three times a day they
would have lived to be 118 then if they
didn't because the fat shortened them to
85 and when it comes down to diseases
the very re real causes of illness and
disease that I outline in my books you
guys outline in the books which is all
the viruses which is all the heavy
metals you can't get heavy metals out of
the body in its entirety if your fats in
your diet are too high both animal
protein side and both vegan side and
plant-based side okay you can't get the
heavy metals out of the body you can't
get the viruses out of the body easily
if your fats are too high and that means
you're searching for protein and getting
yourself in trouble with fat how many
shows like doctor shows where another
guy comes on he's like here's how you do
your smoothie you put your almond butter
in there and you throw this and you
throw your just a few blueberries in
there a few cultivated blueberries in
there and you put those in there and
you're just like and you're blending up
this big fat smoothie right on one of
the doctor show and you're just like
okay let's keep on teaching people to
eat nice and lots of fats and then then
you come across and you show the table
it's like ban Meats oh which is all fat
still all fat when you think oh whole
lean proteins it's all fats or say it's
a different person coming up on some
weird doctor show and it's like oh let's
lots of nuts and see coconut oil should
be doing two tablespoons of coconut oil
and lots of tahini and everything else
because whoa you're going to need lots
of HEI for your protein and you're going
to be all these protein Powers all the
the different protein powers and you're
going to get in trouble you're going to
get in
trouble because what's really happening
is we got viruses eating people up all
the symptoms I mentioned ear early on
all the symptoms and all the diseases
Hashimoto thyroiditis multiple sclerosis
this go goes on and on and on these are
just a couple of things that I randomly
mention all the time lupus whatever and
all of them there's but tons and tons
and tons of autoimmune conditions eximus
Rises everything else all of it from all
the different UTI from all the different
migraines to everything under the sun
there's pathogens and metals behind it
and it has nothing to do with protein
God Almighty it has nothing to do with
protein that's how demented this joke
has gone too far and how demented this
joke is is and how far it's gone does
anyone know how far it's gone it is
disgusting and I'm telling you right now
it's not over I could sit here and rant
all I want on a soap box I could be like
okay step right up and just come on
here's a Golden Ticket of Truth take the
golden ticket of Truth and still
someone's going to smack it out of my
hand because you know what I can't
control the world haven't you realized
that too that you can't control the
world but you know what we can do we can
change the people around us and the
people we meet and we can change
ourselves and we can heal and help heal
others and you know what you know what
you save one person one person and that
is their world that is their world
remember that that is their world you
save one person from misinformation and
stupidity out there in the in the
industries alternative and conventional
you save one person and you save one
child you save one Grandma you save one
person you just save their world
regardless of how idiotic the world can
be that you can't control and that's the
power of what we're doing and that's the
power of what you're doing and that's
the power that's what it all
is so there's all these things that
create disease and illness and symptoms
and nobody cares nobody knows anything
about and the ones that do care say you
need more protein to fix it you believe
that do you believe that yes it's still
going on you walk in into the best
functional doctor and I love all the
functional doctors but you walk into
them and and oh I probably need new Pro
more protein and it's not their fault
God bless them because they're still
helping people in different ways all our
doctors do every last one of them still
help us in every way and they have
compassion and they care that's why they
woke up in the morning and said I'm
going to go to medical school I'm going
to go and torture myself through that
whole process and then sit in an office
somewhere why people file in when I
could be doing something else with my
life because they care because they care
so that's why it's a big deal but what
happens is we get thrown the wrong wrong
place down the we get thrown into like
hey a protein fear it's all about
protein fruit's bad fruit fear it's all
about fruit oh you know it's it's all
LEC in fear now LEC in fear listen to my
lectin show you got to list listen to my
lectin show you got to listen to it
unbelievable talking about crap people
are trying to H hang their hat on why do
I get upset about this because it
hinders your healing it slows down your
healing it's going to mess you up so
what do you eat what do you do how do
you eat I'm sure all these questions are
coming through first of all there's
plenty of protein you can't stay away
from it it's in everything you can't you
eat a potato and the bioavailable
protein just in the skin alone and
inside the potato itself is more healing
than some of the pro all the proteins
out there in the world but potatoes are
shunned that's what I'm talking about
there's there's protein and tomatoes
proteins that people don't understand
yet that science and research don't
understand because what they confuse you
with purposely is the dirty deals went
on in the 30s and the 1940s that were
married to right now and don't even know
we don't even know what we're married to
that's how sick it is and this is the
deal and these and these grandfather
laws that we're attached to that we have
no idea what they are they're geared so
we get confused that we think satiation
has something to do with protein it has
nothing to do with protein satiation
satiation has everything to do with
carbohydrate with calories and that part
is right it's calories satiate also
mineral salts satiate mineral salts and
calories satiate hear me out glucose
carbohydrate mineral salts satiate
that's what
satiates that's what that's what takes
care of hunger but they purposely
poisoned the water so that you think fat
that fat protein that protein satiates
because proteins are always they always
got fat involved with them and they
satiate and then we get confused it has
nothing to do with that and then they
throw away your potatoes they throw away
your tomatoes with hip trendy crap that
circulates just when we make progress
they throw away your fruit we finally
make progress that fruit fruit is
healing people and it really is and they
throw at another trendy person paid for
by God knows what fruit fear and do you
know all got got people that are they're
not even paid off they're just following
other people that were paid off 20 years
ago that were the that were the plants
that were the moles and they were put
into the system alternatively and
conventionally so so fruit fear went
down the line so that people who aren't
paid off go and write a book about you
know stay away from all that Sugar stay
away from all those fruits you got got
to be on your protein it's
unbelievable what's going on out
there yeah take a sigh take a sigh so
what can you eat you just can't you can
eat lots of things but you can't think
about protein as you're eating you're
going to get in trouble there's protein
and
bananas for God's sake there's protein
and bananas and a b bananas satiate they
satiate because of because of the
calories coming from the carbohydrate
and banana which is really healing which
actually kills viruses and bacteria in
the gut which actually heals Celiac
Celiac it heals IBS bananas heal Crohn's
and Colitis I've had the worst Crohn's
cases ever out there and I've dealt with
them and I've gotten people to to avoid
surgeries and everything else Under the
Sun with silly
bananas bananas even repel retroviruses
like HIV bananas repel herpetic virus
like all the H all the hhv sixs and
sevens and eights and
undiscovered and in the nines and the 10
and 11s and 12 14s and 15s that are
undiscovered by research in science and
so many herpetic mutations over 60
varieties of Epstein bar I talk about
all my books if you don't have my books
got to get the books because I don't
cover all that in these shows there's no
way I can there's no way I can if you
read it once read the book again you'll
you'll realize there's a whole bunch of
stuff you missed and and and the deal is
is that you know everything's got
proteins everything oranges have some
protein apples have have protein and
they're all proteins yeah they got them
in there and they do play some role in
the body but what really plays a role is
keeping your liver healthy so your liver
can create all the proteins you need
that's the whole point a dying liver you
age you bombard your liver with loads of
fat you bombard your brain with loads of
fat and you age oh so you hear about
science that there's fats oh the megas
are good for the brain that fats are
everything for the brain that's what you
heard let me tell you something there's
a micros opic percentage of fat in the
brain the rest is made out of glycogen
storage hardened which is which is
actually a positive thing with this
because it's hardened glycogen that's
how our brains stop atrophying and stay
alive and stay vibrant and don't shrink
when we get older it's from
carbohydrates from stored glucose in the
form of glycogen the brain is this
jellyfish of sugar with very low traces
of Omega so low and small without
because the more fat in the brain the
more the more Metals will stay in the
brain the more fat in the brain the more
the more viruses can breed in the brain
the more the more trouble the more
calcifications crystallizations in the
brain black spots white spots on the
brain lesions on the brain you name it
can
develop all of that with fatty brain
that's right you heard it here first you
heard it here first bet a whole bunch of
copycats out there in the book world are
going to want to come out with all this
stuff when you know the whole thing when
medical medium's putting out this liver
book to try to make sure that you guys
heal in every way in every capacity you
better believe a whole bunch of people
are going to try to counter it with
their their idea of what they think the
liver
does and they'll and you know what one
of those ideas is I'm going to tell you
right now the industries both
alternative and conventional think that
Fat's good for your liver even though
fatty liver is caused by Fats is that
amazing the industries right now
alternative and conventional believe
that sugar is bad for your liver and I'm
not talking about table sugar that's not
good for anybody and there's a reason it
was separated in such a way I'm talking
about the sugar that's naturally derived
but it's naturally sitting in all the
fruits and here's the thing you want to
build muscle it's not built on protein
muscle's not built on protein muscle's
built on three things hear me out here's
your golden ticket giving you the golden
ticket do you want it three things
muscle is built on mineral salts that's
one thing mineral salts lots of celery
juice whether you're working out whether
you're an athlete whether you're sick in
bed atrophying because you're so sick
you better stop the atrophying by using
celery juice mineral salts stop the
muscles from atrophying they also remove
the toxins in the way from the muscle
cell expanding and building so your
muscle tissue can build when you get
mineral salts in your muscles which is
celery juice and then you guys and then
the second thing the second thing which
is critical is carbohydrates not fats
not proteins carbohydrates fats stop you
from building muscle they stop you from
building muscle they do they do
carbohydrates carbohydrates that's what
builds muscle because guess what muscle
cells can only be built on glucose
entering into it with a nutrient because
glucose attaches to all nutrients when
you eat a banana the glucose from banana
attaches to all nutrients to drive it
into the muscle to build a muscle okay
that's the second thing and I'm being
light on this there's more I could add
the third thing is using your muscle so
if you're sick and chronically ill in
bed and all you can do is lift up a
glass you're building muscle by lifting
up a glass if you're getting enough of
the fruit in you enough of the potato in
you things that have the carbohydrate
and you're lowering your fats you know
what gets people chronically ill really
in trouble when they're in bed and all
their doctors and all their family
members like they need protein they're
waing away they're atrophying they're
sick in bed nobody knows what's wrong
with them come on maybe they got Lyme
disease maybe they got this maybe they
got that maybe got Ms whatever it is but
they're viral as heck and they're loaded
with viruses they're suffering the poor
things I've seen it for years it's
horrible and you know and then they're
being thrown fat diets lots of protein
and fat being thrown in them atrophying
them when they need to be getting on
some bananas they need to be getting on
potatoes they need to be getting on
maybe some steamed peas steamed
peas okay that's what I'm talking about
those are the things that matter and you
know why protein powders now the P
protein powders you know why
bodybuilders that eat animal protein but
they hop on a p protein powder that's
actually a carbohydrate in there that's
what gives you muscle and you know those
you know those other you know there's
other there's people that say wait a
minute if muscle doesn't get built on
protein I'm on an all protein diet I'm
on no carbohydrates how come I'm
building muscle that's because they are
on carbohydrates they're in the protein
shakes and powders they's SE sugars in
them they're hidden in there that's how
they do it they have to put sugar in
these protein powders I know this for a
fact I know this for a fact they have to
if they don't you're going to hit the
wall you're going to hit the wall it's
critical and and I'll tell you right now
the one apple you do eat every 3 days if
you're on a low carb diet and a high
protein diet the one apple you eat every
3 days is going to actually be what your
muscles are sucking up and absorbing so
you can build a
muscle and then you use your muscle you
build a muscle don't think about how
many protein grams you need a day how
many grams of protein you need a day
you're just going to get yourself in
trouble you're going to walk into walls
you're going to step on potholes and
you're going to get yourself in trouble
you just got to be eating enough fruits
and vegetables and you got to make sure
you're lowering your you're if you're
okay let's let's hit it if you're
hitting if you're doing animal proteins
do it once a day if you love animal
proteins do it once a day that's right
you're hearing it from me do it once a
day do your salmon once a day absolutely
if you like your grass-fed beef and
that's what you really feel good on do
it once a day the reason why people feel
like they need a protein a lot of times
too is if they're only eating salads
with not enough carbohydrates in them or
not enough calories in them they're
eating some salads and they're eating a
little piece of fruit here and there and
they're on this like diet or they're on
the cleanse which is amazing to help
them heal they'll feel like they're
hitting the wall and they need 4 oz
steak or 4 oz piece of chicken or a 10
oz piece of chicken because they're
looking for calories and chicken has
it's so high in calories the protein
isn't what fills you up or satiates you
I said it earlier it's the
calories it then that's what does it so
you have to bring your potatoes in your
sweet potatoes your winter squash you
have to start your your steamed brussel
sprouts you got to start bringing in
some some dense calories and you got to
be doing your spinach soups you got to
throw your spinach you know I talk about
medical median book one into the blender
and blend it up with some tomatoes and
you make yourself a nice rich spinach
soup and you got to be eating enough
fruit you got to get your papay out you
got to get your you eat a few bananas
and a few dates you'll get satiated and
you'll be able to heal if you're eating
animal protein go to one Ser if you're a
big animal protein person go to one
serving a day if you're a big vegan big
into IND plant-based and that's your
whole thing absolutely I support it go
down drop your nuts and seeds in your
oils though bring them down have a
handful here and there and make sure you
get a lot more of the fresh fruits and
vegetables do melon in the morning gets
lots of celery juice but both sides of
the aisle I swear to God both sides of
the aisle are so busy battling over the
protein war and really honestly the
plant-based people and the vegan people
they're taking the fall they take the
hit because there's not a lot of them so
as they're healing and reversing their
diseases and changing people's lives get
a whole bunch of angry I mean it's a
double standard in that it's
unbelievable what happens but both sides
of the aisle both sides of this C the
camps two camps out there Hatfields and
The McCoys both sides are playing around
with a volleyball with protein written
on it and they're both getting suckered
suckered suckered suckered it's so sad
and so so really you're only going to
hear this from me and it's the only time
you're ever going to hear hear it you're
going to hear it for me okay I talk
about it in the liver book though but
I'm saying you're only going to hear it
like this like this in this radio show
because you know what I don't want to
waste my time on the stupidity of the
protein problem it's almost nauseating
but I realize something you guys need
this information so I have to just I
just have to chill and I have to chill
and realize I just got to give you what
you need I've always lived by that I
can't stop because of protein's that
annoying I got to deliver and I got to
stay delivering and that's what the
medical medium radio show is all about
well that's what I'm about as a soul as
an individual and that's what spirit's
about is I have to follow spirit's
information because it's pure untampered
with clean source of information that
wasn't paid off by somebody somewhere
down the line and the thumb wasn't put
on some scale and it was twisted so that
our human Minds get all twisted up with
it and we don't heal and we don't get
better okay so how much protein do you
need I wouldn't even think about it it's
everywhere in every food you eat you
just think about are you getting enough
carbs are you getting enough calories
and I'm not talking about from a donut
I'm not talking about from that and I'm
going to tell you right now if you're
into eggs kill the eggs whatever you do
I should have mentioned that early on
kill the eggs the eggs are a protein
Source no matter what for vegetarians or
whoever it is vegetarians animal eaters
whatever eggs are bad they're bad they
feed every virus every disease every
bacteria that science of research
doesn't even know about or understand or
haven't even understand or discovered or
research and that are the real reasons
why you're sick it's not protein it's
because of things that
feed things like viruses and disease and
guess what too much protein and you're
worried about too much protein and you
want to eat that much protein you will
feed these viruses and eggs is one of
them you lower your animal products down
you get rid of your eggs you get rid of
your dairy products you lower things
down and you heal and the plant-based
people watch the the nuts watch the nuts
and seeds too too many I don't want to
make you paranoid have a handful here
and there but make sure you're getting
all the other things and that's critical
too that's critical but don't focus on
protein you guys try not to but you know
what I could say that a million times
and you know what I'm going get that
that golden tickets can to get smacked
out of my hand you're probably going to
smack me in the head at the same
time because it's out there to the point
where you can't even dial something in
the computer dial something how do you
like that you can't even type something
in I love you guys bless your heart I
love you ter just love you so much I
want to squeeze you and hug you and just
thank you for all that you do just God
bless you bless your hearts bless your
soul take one day at a time I'm I'm with
you 100% I'm not going to stop I'm with
you take care all right bye now see you
next show okay all
right