without right there the propolis pure
and the lemon balm why does it matter
because it does the lemon balms and
nerve Vine calms the nerves I'm under a
lot of stress are you guys under a lot
of stress the other propolis pure immune
system the ultimate immune system and
that's what I love about both of these
but I mean I take all of the Bemidji
stuff periodically at different times
but those two I don't go anywhere
without so I keep them in my car I got
them with me all the time I got them in
a bag I just make sure I go places with
them you get a free
30 bottle but you got to know
this is a large bottle these aren't the
little tincture bottles so I'm just
letting you know they're not the little
tincture bottles
these are the large bottles right here
just dropping that on you right now you
get a free 30 dollar large bottle of the
best quality lemon balm that ever
existed if you get a hundred dollars
worth of stuff at vimergy this is almost
four ounces right here so if you go to
vimergy.com uh V as in Victor I Amazon
Mary e r g y.com the best stuff out
there there is hands down you could fill
you in on why but you get the free
actually the lemon bomb right there and
you guys know I endorse these guys
because they're that incredible but
what's amazing is if you just get a
hundred dollars worth of stuff from
Bemidji you then can tack on
the lemon balm bottle right there and
then there's a Code they have never done
this before I'm telling you because
they've never done this before that's
why I'm like excited you know I love I
love when something can help people I
just told all my friends I just told my
family I'm like you don't get it when
you get your micro C and your B12 and
your zinc from Imaging and it comes out
whatever it is that comes out to a
hundred dollars tack on the four ounce
bottle of lemon balm the four ounce
bottle of lemon balm tack that right on
to your order that's free the four ounce
bottle of lemon balm you just tack that
right on they got the code right there
too so go to vimergy.com the link is in
medical medium profile right there or
the description the profile or
description depending where you are what
what uh page you're on but anyway I want
to tell you guys that I'm going to read
a little bit about the quickening so I
want to do that that's easy I spent 300
she said oh and you can just tack on
Boom hundred dollars or more you tack on
then the free four ounce bottle of lemon
balm that is sick like I don't see
companies doing that I don't see
companies doing that kind of thing I
mean it's this is really really cool
um you said beverage works like no other
it works like no other I know this
see what happens I deal with a lot of
doctors I talk to a lot of doctors I
have a lot of doctors that reach out to
me that go look aw I need to ask you
about something I need to ask you about
these patients I need to ask about you
see you know some of this
troubleshooting stuff out there what's
the best supplementation what's the best
things to use right and so I it matters
the quality it's not even just quality
it's like Supreme quality that's what
counts because everybody can just say
quality now you can put out the
shittiest crappiest piece of crap
supplement out there and call it quality
now that's how the world works right you
can put out the worst stuff the worst
quality crap and you can use the term
quality that's what supplement companies
do now they'll use oh quality our
quality is there oh sure sure there's a
lot of things that determine real true
quality one of the one of the things
that determines it is not putting in
hidden ingredients hidden ingredients in
there
like ingredients that are not disclosed
on the bottle and supplement companies
put up to 10 percent of crap inside
their supplements and they don't tell
anybody they don't disclose it or
anything that's one of the most
important things to know right there
that takes you into like what's called
real quality anyway before I start
reading about the quickening I want to
talk about that I just want it to go
over
this incredible what I call a gift
that's happening
which is amazing that beverage is doing
so if you just got on here if you get a
hundred dollars worth of products from
Bemidji
and then you can tack on an extra
product like it's a lemon balm that's
the product right vimorgy.com V is in
Victor i m ismary ergy.com
and it's at vimergy.com not on Amazon so
vimergy.com not on Amazon you can tack
on after that hundred dollars
a free 30 bottle of lemon balm right
there the nervine that's what I call it
the nerve Vine what does that mean
nervous system
nervous system calming the nervous
system and so many people are so jacked
up right now they're so stressed out
they're going through so much they're
dealing with so much crap out there and
it's critical to have that nerve Vine
for those things that people are up
against so many things that people are
up against so I wanted everybody's under
stress right now hardships losses
emotional hurt they are dealing with it
life's BS that they're handed all these
different things so it's important to
have that nerve-ind calm things down
and that's a big deal right there so I
just want to tell you about the lemon
balm the deal of imagery.com about that
like that blows my mind it just blows my
mind okay letting you know
and so it's a propolis I don't go
anywhere without these two
propolis right there now I can't say it
enough right
so the propolis pure contains over
consistently contains over well over 50
percent of active bioavailable
polyphenols like quercetin and there's
just one of them and one of the
polyphenols right it contains that
and that's incredible all on its own so
this is one incredible reason but I know
when I tell doctor friends practitioner
friends out there and they're like you
know I got patience that have this going
on that going on and and I'm like well
are you doing the propolis have you told
your patients about the propolis and
then they get the patients on the
propolis and then
just crazy stuff happens where things
are being reversed and that is critical
so immune system is I don't even call a
propolis I call it immune system uh do
you have my bottle of immune system do I
have my bottle of immune system over
there where is it where's my immune
system that's what I actually call
propolis pure because literally it's
that powerful thank you for the light
blasting I think you're welcome can't
wait to do another one soon
so I don't go anywhere without these two
lemon balm and the propolis right there
and the quality of this propolis so
let's hit that for a little bit
okay
there's no alcohol in here
but not just no alcohol
there's no alcohol now there's a reason
why I'm saying that just think about
that for a second he said no alcohol he
said no alcohol why is he saying it
twice
why is he doing that is he repeating
himself no
there's not just no alcohol in this
propolis there's no alcohol what does
that mean is it a trick question it
means there's propolises out there that
say non-alcohol
that have alcohol
because of the extraction process the
extraction process
propolis pure does not have alcohol but
for real
does not have alcohol in there
critical to know oh yeah no I found a
propolis out there they do have you it's
got no alcohol in it uh
sure
sure it doesn't have no alcohol in it
sure I believe that I don't believe that
that's the whole point that's the
difference
and that guarantee for me knowing
there's no alcohol in the process
there's no alcohol in this bottle
critical because there's alcohol in
propolises even when they say no alcohol
or no alcohol added or no alcohol
there's alcohol in there I could say it
a thousand times I'll tell you why
because it's a big deal huge huge deal
because we need a propolis without that
it makes a big difference because
without it your propolis is really
stronger that's just one aspect all in
its own and then you talk about
beverages propolis like
that's another level of quality all on
its own when you taste this it's unlike
any propolis out there I actually dare
you to get propolises but I don't want
to want you to waste money
but dare you to get propolises and then
do do the taste test you take this one
right here the propolis pure and you do
that and then you do the others and
you'll just be like what the heck is
going on
and this is my favorite supplement of
all time people ask me what is your
favorite supplement aw I get asked that
so many times just like what's your
favorite this what's your favorite that
right what's your favorite my favorite
supplement of all time hands down is
this propolis pure right here to know
that there's one made us in a specific
way it's a precious and complex
substance from nature
that offers many benefits for health
right including the immune system which
is one of the big reasons all on its own
and oral health I mean you know people
with oral health issues
so many people walk around with oral
health problems
yeah propolis is critical especially
with oral health stuff very important
all on its own
so what happens with vimergy's propolis
it's sourced from a limited number of
carefully screened beekeeping operations
that's the big difference I'm I'm just
excited today because when I found out
about the Free bottle of lemon balm with
an order of a hundred dollars and then
you tack on your lemon balm for free
when I found that out I'm like I'm gonna
talk about I can't help it that's
amazing I'm going to talk about my
favorite supplement of all time
which is the propolis
so it's from a limited number of
carefully screened beekeeping operations
and that right there changes the game
all on its own
and in and the other thing it involves a
unique purification process
that results in containing well over 50
percent of its polyphenols you gotta
understand what that is like what that
means if you're somebody that's
interested in just knowledge about
supplementation knowledge about it
this is an incredible situation right
here with the Vemma G propolis pure
if you're somebody that see you're a
knowledge Seeker like I'm seeking
knowledge
I'm telling you some really unbelievable
things right here
Source from a limited number of
carefully screened beekeeping operations
that means it's not just a [ __ ]
situation
that's out there when people slap stuff
together and stick it in bottles
that means it's far from that
and that's really important to
understand and then their purification
process allows doesn't kill the stuff
and that's another thing too propolis is
out there when they do the purification
process they kill the active ingredients
think about that right now just you guys
I'm excited because basically remember
she's giving a gift out
they're giving a thirty dollar bottle a
four ounce bottle of lemon balm for free
with a hundred dollar order at
vimorgy.com but it's fmergy.com not on
Amazon
so I want to talk about this the process
of propolis
when you when you process propolis you
kill you kill all its active ingredients
that's what happens out there
but they have a unique purification
process that results in keeping the
bioactive ingredients polyphenols well
over 50 percent strong and bioactive
critical right there stay calm says
propolis has helped my gum pain a lot
anybody with oral issues whatsoever this
is what I point to
people are worried about oral health
this is what I point to right here
this is it
Health with Haley says should you swish
the propolis in your mouth to help with
oral care or just swallow what I do is I
put it straight in my mouth and I just
let it sit there I let it move around
and sit in my mouth
a lot of people are like a lot of people
talk about things they do orally like I
do oil pulling or I do this well let me
tell you
this is a lot more beneficial than any
of that
you put propolis in your mouth before
bed
because that's what I do I put propolis
in my mouth before bed
just so you know I'm an older guy I got
all my teeth
I don't have implants in my mouth there
are no implants in my mouth
and you know I have the purple shock
therapy in the brain saver book just
letting you know the propolis shock
therapy instructions on putting it on
canker sores mouth sores this is a big
deal
and some people
you know they might have good oral
health going on where you want to keep
good oral health too
and that's a whole other level
so I'm not 20 years old I'm not 30 years
old
you know even though even though the
internet says I'm what 29 now
so Ali stare says I thought we could
just heal with food
so the question is I thought we can just
heal with food right what people are up
against and everybody's situation is
different I've seen a person just heal
with celery juice
I'm sorry but I have I have seen that
just acid reflux gone that's it I've
seen that somebody's blood pressure down
boom gone their blood pressure's down
high blood pressure's down because
celery juice right and they just did
celery juice I've seen that over and
over again out there there's a lot of
people with chronic sickness So when you
say I thought we can just heal with just
food
that is not encompassing everybody
everybody's different
everybody is different
there are people out there with a lot of
viral inflammation a lot of pathogenic
problems a lot of toxic stuff inside of
them a lot of toxic junk inside of them
a lot of different contaminations and
exposures
and a lot of different support system
issues they're struggling they don't
have a great great resources they don't
have a great support system and so when
you say I thought we only need food for
healing well who are we talking about
talking about somebody with less stress
somebody with less contamination of
toxins and exposure somebody with less
less pathogenic contamination because if
we're talking about that then maybe yeah
you can totally heal things up with just
food but then you get a whole bunch of
people they've been sick for 10 years
they've been sick for five years they're
struggling they got a lot of issues
going on they got a lot of exposure they
got a lot of situations a lot of stress
their adrenals are totally beaten down
and maxed out and they need
supplementation
you get somebody with with a real
challenging condition they need
supplementation so that's important to
know and then supplementation is a
blanket big one term what's
supplementation what are you even
talking about because there's a lot of
crap out there if you're talking about
liver you know packed in some kind of
chewable or you're talking about some
gummy are you talking you're talking
about some you know you know ABC Gummy
or whatever it is ACV gummy whatever it
is that's doesn't mean that's going to
help it's specific supplementation for
specific reasons and specific quality
all that matters it's somebody's healing
could be make or break
make or break with just a few different
things because it's Death By A Thousand
Cuts
and notice I put that term out there
Death By A Thousand Cuts when it comes
down to health issues and what happens
when we're struggling with health issues
and it's Death By A Thousand Cuts and
now I see influencers out there saying
Death By A Thousand Cuts
Death By A Thousand Cuts no mention of
medical medium death by a thousand
because of course I got to throw that in
I can't help it
but
propolis is key for the immune system
strengths if you're somebody and you're
relying on just food
well your immune system might need a lot
more than that for whatever's going on
critical to know somebody's dealing with
mouth ulcers and all kinds of issues and
Immunity problems immune system issues
that's
a whole nother thing so that's why it's
critical to know
there are tools out there so two two of
my favorite supplements I don't budge I
don't go anywhere without two of them
right here the propolis and the lemon
balm
why should I take lemon balm because I'm
under enormous stress all the time I
mean I don't know if you guys know but I
am right
people are up against hardships they're
up against stress adrenaline lowers
their immune system because they're
always getting jacked up with adrenaline
from stress
and they need immune system support and
antioxidants the polyphenols very
important all on its own
I know that there are people out there
and Chip propolis is critical critical
for the immune system and then you throw
in toxic chemicals metals that people
have bugs and flu bugs and pathogens
that are going on more things that break
down their immune system and breaks down
their immune system and breaks down
their immune system more of that and
then we're in a whole nother game
something very important to know and I
do know
but there is um there are some people
that are total you know they the total
downers about supplementation
because they don't know the difference
they don't know the difference from
garbage junk supplementation like whey
protein powder and garbage like that and
all kinds of big tablets with you know
all kinds of junk in it with a hundred
products in it they don't know the
difference from the gelatin tablets all
the junk all the whey protein powder all
the natural flavors and everything they
don't know that difference
from there to something this pure and
this unbelievable for the immune system
so what they do is because they're
ignorant of that understanding out there
not the person who has the question that
said doesn't can't we just do it with
food no not you I'm talking about the
people out there there's some
influencers out there that will say you
know you don't need supplements ever you
don't need any of that right it's sad
when they say that because what are they
talking about if somebody would have
busted up immune system someone who's
struggling and suffering somebody who
has a lot of challenges with their
immune cells
and you're like and they hear that and
they're just confused and they're like
oh okay
and then they're also not being told the
difference they're not being told the
difference from just gelatin based
garbage filled with all kinds of crap
and whey protein powder and then trendy
stuff that isn't good like charcoal
which is terrible for the for the the
intestinal tract terrible for their body
and they don't know the difference of
all the bad stuff out there the Clays
the bentonite clay the charcoal the
Pearl powder all the junk and garbage
and the trend stuff they don't know that
difference right there compared to
something that has over 50 percent of
its polyphenols bioactive quercetin
that's not dead it's alive in the
propolis pure and what that means I'm
talking about this
because these things need to be talked
about once in a while they just do they
need to be talked about once in a while
what comes down to moving the needle you
want something that helps to move the
needle you don't want to be dogging it
you don't want your health dogging it
and a lot of people they can't stay on a
good path they get thrown off all the
time thrown off the wagon all the time
by being influenced by so much crap out
there that they're being pushed off the
wagon and they don't know which way the
wind blows with their health they have
no idea what they should do they're
eating all kinds of crazy stuff they're
doing their cheat days and if that's the
case then it's critical to keep your
immune system strong if you don't know
what is going on with your health if you
don't know what's happening it's
critical to have your immune system
supported and that's a big deal anyway
two supplements before I read a little
bit about the quickening right here two
supplements that are critical and lemon
balm
and the propolis you just got on here
you guys if you buy a hundred dollars
vemergy.com these in Victor I Amazon
Mary ergy.com 100 worth of product you
can then tack on an additional
four ounce bottle of lemon balm right
here that's the nerve Vine I call
nirvine of choice the nervine
so very important too
so talk about mushrooms I like Rishi
mushroom I like chaga mushroom I like
those I don't know if you're talking
about the whack the like the the wacko
mushrooms that's another whole nother
story
but yeah
okay so you guys when I want to get like
into a calm relaxing State a calm
meditation State I take the lemon balm
that's what I do are you guys doing any
of that are you taking a little time out
do you chill out do you do a little yoga
do you do little you know breathing do
you sit somewhere in a quiet place quiet
place in the house
are you doing the collecting Stones
meditation Journey coming up we'll talk
about that in a minute too whatever it
is are you relaxing that's a great time
to take the lemon balm so that's a
fantastic moment if you're somebody
that's just chilling out
you want a little time to yourself you
want a little down time is it at the end
of the day of your crazy day is is
are you all jazzed up with anxiety are
you all jazzed up with different
problems and stuff like that through the
day
or if you're nervous it's a great calmer
to do the lemon balm so I wanted to talk
about that too because it's that nerve
Vine that's really powerful
so you guys there's so much to talk
about all right so Lev Lev says on IG I
got off my medical medium supplements
and the effects were catastrophic
such a lie that people don't need
supplements it makes or breaks for me
there's it's make or break I've talked
you know what's sad can I just say
something
if you guys are okay with this do you
guys have a second you know what's
freaking sad
is I've been talking about make or break
for years and years
from the very first book and way before
I've been talking about it's critical
that the chronically ill they don't get
swayed off their game
because it's make or break crap that
happens but it's easy to get lost
because you get okay first of all let's
go into this if there's it's no
Secret
that there's people that don't like me
out there in health the health World
they don't think I should have a space
in the health world even though they're
they're ripping off the medical medium
information daily and not citing it back
there's people out there health
influencers and so forth that don't
believe I deserve a space in the health
realm even though nobody even had an
inkling to what was wrong with anybody
just eight nine years ago when the first
book came out
even though I have 35 plus years of
experience of bringing people's lives
back and so there's people out there
that don't think I deserve any space at
all in the health scene
right they just don't like me so what
they do is they conjure up things to
break down the medical medium Community
they conjure up stuff they throw stuff
at the mm Community all the time you
don't need a supplement
you don't need to take any meanwhile
they take it behind the scenes meanwhile
the ones that are saying it the
influencers that are saying it to people
you don't need to take your your memory
you don't need to take your supplements
meanwhile they're they're taking
the Bemidji supplements behind the scene
because the intentions there are because
it's towards me right it's towards the
medical medium so you try to break down
the community this happens all the time
I see it all the time
Steph Ever After says Bemidji sups have
given me my life back B12 lemon balm
ashwagandha zinc micro C
if you get a hundred dollar order at
vimergy.com
you go to venergy.com 100 order
you get a free four ounce bottle almost
four ounce bottle of the lemon balm
right here you just have to go to
vimergy.com
get your do your 100 order or more and
then tack on an additional lemon bomb
and then hit the code that they have
there I think it's like
f-r-e-e-l-e-m I mean that you'll see the
code there
so
I want to go back to make or break I've
been talking about that for years I
remember doing a lecture
like seven eight years ago
one of my lectures I was doing is a
crowd of people and I was talking about
make or break on how every little thing
matters because it's Death By A Thousand
Cuts and every little thing matters with
your healing process this is critical I
noticed if I don't talk about this for a
while the snakes come in
and the Sharks come in
and the opportunists come in and they
come into the medical medium community
and they advertise to the medical medium
Community to death or they sit there and
they just literally talk down medical
medium and try to get them parading on
their side like come do my programs you
don't have to do that and you don't you
could eat anything you want you could
eat all the pizzas you want you can eat
all the vegan pizzas you want it doesn't
matter too restrictive you know medical
medium doesn't want you on gluten or
dairy products he's too restrictive he
doesn't want you on eggs he's too
restrictive he doesn't want you on pork
fat medical medium doesn't want you on
pork fat he's so restrictive he doesn't
want you on a stick of butter every day
so you get a heart attack he's so
restrictive anyway the point is
is that the Sharks and the stakes
Slytherin and swim into the medical mean
community and they'll say you don't need
a supplement but hey do my program and
I'm going to take my supplements
privately when nobody knows in my
kitchen at night
that's what they do the supplements that
got them better and here's another thing
a lot of people got better
a lot of people that rip try to rip
medical medium down and shade throw
shade on the medical medium in the
community they got better through the
medical medium
protocols with supplements then then
they stop citing medical medium and said
hey come over here you don't have to do
anything you don't want to do he's so
restrictive oh yeah you'll hear that
stuff all the time the wild blueberry
babe says I needed supplementation
because of the number of pathogens
toxins and poisons I've been exposed to
as well as traumas needed all the help I
can get grateful for femergy
and that takes me to another thing
yeah
that is so incredible by the way where
do I get it fearing woman says Where do
I get it the lemon balm in the other go
to vimergy.com via's in Victor I am as
in Mary e r g y.com
go there you have to order a hundred
dollars worth of stuff of supplements
that you need and then you tack on the
30 dollar
free lemon balm
it's incredible it really is
cool I love Emoji they are really Game
Changer even if you can afford just one
is great you will have healing
and that's what I mean it's
it like the propolis is critical it's
critical for me
because I put my physical body
through the mill I run it through the
mill
like seriously that's what I do okay
it's not smart
I'm not saying that it's a good idea to
do that it's not
but that's what I do to keep up with all
that I got to do I run my I burn myself
to the ground
like burn it to the ground and then
okay
I use the Vim to restore and build me
back up
so I can't hang in there for when I'm up
against massive stress writing the books
working hard doing no sleep 20 hour days
22 hour days
and that I want to keep myself strong
for I do I want to keep myself strong
so I just want to say like I said
there's a tremendous amount of fork
tongue snakes and lizards even though
you know whatever lizards are probably
friendly to a point and there's probably
some friendly snakes out there okay but
there's some snakes and lizards that
slide in
they do and they come on into the
medical medium Community because you
know what though it is too that where
they've made a name for themselves
through the medical meme community
by healing themselves with medical meme
information the books and the protocols
and then they tell everybody oh don't do
a supplement don't do this he's
restrictive oh it's a cult it's a cult
that's what it is uh really
okay you know and they'll say whatever
they're gonna say because they just want
to shade on everybody but then it chips
away at everybody and it's Death By A
Thousand Cuts because it's make or break
and as somebody just said originally
earlier they were saying
that someone persuaded them to stop
their energy supplements and then their
health went catastrophic and then they
had to go back up it's it's it's like
that out there I've seen this over and
over again meanwhile which is really
interesting there's some other
supplement companies out there that are
kind of bonding with some of the Sharks
and some of the snakes yeah because it's
a compa frequentition
it's competitive crap out there it's all
about the medical meme Community how how
to break into the medical medium
Community to sell their garbage and crap
that has a percentage of unjust of
undisclosed ingredients in it that
aren't good that has alcohol and citric
acid and all this garbage in it and
everything else it has all that stuff
and doesn't have the quality and that's
the sad part all on its own anyway I
want to read about the quickening but I
just wanted to talk about all this
I just don't want this company to
disappear someday
so I fully endorse them because this
stuff is that amazing you cannot mess
with this type of product here it
doesn't exist anywhere it will never
exist anywhere else I can honestly tell
you there's no way in hell ever there's
going to be a supplement company that's
going to duplicate this or even try the
price Point's not going to be there and
they're not going to be able to do it
I'm going to tell you right now
there's not going to be a company in the
world to actually duplicate that
propolis pure they'll never go for the
price point they'll never go for the
quality they'll never go for the
carefully screened you know screened
beekeeper operations they'll never go
for any of that they won't hands down
this is the best stuff out there lupus
free with celery three through three I
healed my frozen shoulder Frozen
shoulders awful that's awful so many
people have suffered from that I healed
my frozen shoulder with celery juice
alone but I needed vermergy for so many
other symptoms and the shock therapy
which is amazing
the shock therapies from SOC are
probably one of my favorite things
all around are the shock therapies from
SOC
I mean nobody in the health realm even
thought of anything like that no one in
the health realm anywhere
knew to do the shock Therapies
that's Testament alone
to what's so incredible about SOC and
the information
um um yep yep on YouTube I feel like mm
is the least cult anything it empowers
the individual to heal so you feel you
feel like medical medium is the least
cult like thing yep it empowers the
individual
to bring and heal themselves based on
educating customizing their own
protocols incredible the keeps on going
like that
yep
yeah it is the least culty thing out
there
I mean I won't go into it I won't go
into what's going on in the health Realm
but it's terrible and it's doggy dog
world dog eat dog world
mm shock therapies are life-saving
incredible
I just read that over there on IG okay
you guys
I just want to tell you I'm going to
read about the quickening in a second if
you've got a couple of seconds too but I
just want it to let you know can you
show a close-up please of the propolis
pure I'm not sure where you are but
there you go can you see it this way
propolis right there propolis pure I'm
reaching out
there it is
let me try it this way
trying to reach over the counter here
let's get some of this golden goodness
out
let's do it
there you go
incredible
it's gold liquid
there it is
now what I like to do is I just put it
straight in my mouth is what I normally
do but there's the golden liquid right
there
over 50 percent of its polyphenols
bioactive
which is incredible all on its own
there's the golden goodness going in
there
yeah
so I know we're hitting a lot of
different topics right here we're
talking about death by a Thousand Cuts
we're talking about make or break the
healing process talk about the Sharks
and the snakes and the lizards to
Slither into the medical meme Community
or already started there they started
out in the medical meeting Community
they got known in the medical medium
community
and then they just wanted to sell their
own stuff
right the programs or whatever it is
sell their own courses their own classes
and then they they go with that
marketing strategy which is don't ever
ever cite the medical medium be your own
thing and then they come out and they're
like don't do this don't do that he's
he's too restrictive on his Foods
yeah because I don't want people eating
pork fat
so they don't get a heart attack
all right
and the other thing too is natural
flavors just so you know about
beveraging products they don't have
what's called natural flavoring natural
flavors
organic flavoring can I just tell you
right now when you see something like
organic natural flavors or organic
flavoring or you like you call a
supplement company you're like so I saw
you got natural flavors in your
supplement
um tell me a little bit about that and
they're like oh yeah our natural flavors
are good for you they're fine they're
all natural they're even organic well
people don't realize is the MSG that's
in natural flavoring and natural flavors
out there
it's in all the supplementation out
there now vimergy won't put that garbage
inside their products the only company
that's like no right from the start the
only company that never ever had it in
there and there's supplement companies
out there that are trying to model after
vimergy right now and they used to have
natural flavors in their supplements
just so you know they used to have it in
there but no one knows about what they
used to have and then they take it out
because they're like whoa yeah we better
listen to what Memories he's doing too
we better copy cat
yeah
Janessa says propolis pure from vimergy
made my canker sores disappear in less
than 24 hours amazing when applied
directly
can I read that over and over again
because seriously Genesis probe was pure
from Bemidji that's the problem of
Bemidji made my canker sore and canker
sores I've seen be debilitating for
people disappear in less than 24 hours
amazing when applied directly
I don't know I don't have any words
because it's miraculous and incredible
and that's in medical medium tool and
technique and it it's working and works
for people
that matters
all of it does so I wanted everybody to
kind of know what's going on
and how important is
critical tools are imperative for people
with he with problems
problems with their healing process
problems with what they're going through
their bodies emotionally mentally all of
it
crispy perspective says it made mine
disappear in 48 hours definitely amazing
but you got to remember something if the
propolis cure pure is making your canker
sores disappear in 48 hours what else is
it doing for the immune system
that people don't see is happening
inside their body and you guys know I
endorse these guys one hundred thousand
percent
and for a very good reason
because when things work they work
it's just blows my mind really purple is
pure is my favorite supplement of all
time
it is that's my favorite supplement of
all time people want to know what my
favorite supplement is of all time it's
this and okay I've talked about propolis
the propolis pure a couple of times
what a couple of times over the year or
something where I mention it but I
should be talking about it every single
day
I don't but I should be because of what
it deserves
and the and the company deserves Anna
says the Amiga says
Pro Plus pure helps me heal my cuts on
my hands and lips from eczema I love all
of Energy Products that's incredible
it really is
so I wanted to talk where do you get it
please it's bemidji.com V is in Victor i
m is in Mary e r g y.com and make sure
you take advantage of imagery take
advantage of them please they're
offering a four ounce bottle of lemon
balm the other supplement I don't go
anywhere without read the instructions
on the website V as in Victor I Amazon
Mary e r g y.com read the instructions
on their website vimergy.com take
advantage of what they're offering
get that free thirty dollar bottle of
incredible nervine please get it I mean
that's the lemon balm right there I call
it the nervon
so those are the two right there and we
get a little lemon balm out and then
we're going to read about the quickening
in a second
basically
they're that imperative I use them every
day we have the collecting Stones
meditation Journey coming up it starts
on the 19th and I love these supplements
supporting me and my friends and my
family while I'm doing
the collecting Stones meditation Journey
so if anybody wants to know what aw and
his family and his friends are going to
be taking during the collecting Stones
meditation Journey it's going to be the
Bemidji lemon balm and the vemergy
propolis pure
that's what we're going to be taking
keep immune system strong and calming
the nervous system while releasing Those
Old Wounds
because those old wounds are going to
transfer into the stones
and we're going to have our Stones
they're going to transfer into the
stones I don't know if you know about
the collecting
Stones meditation Journey check it out
the link is in the description in the
profile go to medicalme.com sign up to
the collecting Stones meditation Journey
do not do not miss out on that it's for
free it's for free and you're gonna have
experiences you never expected and by
the seventh day of the collecting Stones
meditation Journey your mind's going to
be blown and you're never gonna forget
that process and you're never going to
forget what it has done for you the
collecting Stones meditation Journey
just letting you know right now how
important it is
see
vegan in autark says can I add propolis
to my running
protocol even if it's not mentioned
there
yes
ask your doctor what's right for you but
if that was me I would
I'm putting some lemon balm in here
putting lemon balm ask your doctor
what's right for you
read this supplement chapter if you get
a chance in the medical medium
new addition or the brain saver book or
the cleansed heel book but read the
supplementation chapter so you
understand you know you know what what's
amazing is that is when haters
right they'll say oh medical medium too
much supplements are you kidding if you
read the book in the in the chapter it
says start with one
two or or a few or if you're sensitive
in General on anything for any reason
whether you're chemical sensitive or
whatever it is you can read about that
in there and just do tiny drops tiny
drops
like this people need the opportunity to
go as far as they need to heal they need
the opportunity to take as many
supplements as they need to heal or
learn how to use them they need that
opportunity they also need the
opportunity to use this much see that
right there
that much three
four tiny drops look at that
if you want four tiny drops five six
tiny drops
because you can customize because it's
not one size fits all another thing that
haters like to do is will be like one
size fits all medical means one size
fits all are you kidding you can be
doing the monocleens
at the same time
you can be doing your own supplement
protocol that you customize from the
medical medium books and information you
could be doing a medical medium shock
therapy when someone else isn't what do
you mean one size fits all are you ready
for this
medical medium information and medical
medium in general talks about the food
Wars
and talks about how it's not about
animal protein or plant-based if you
want to be plant-based be plant-based if
you want to be vegan be vegan if you
want to be animal protein be animal
protein but you still have to learn why
you're sick and what to do to heal you
have to learn why you got sick and what
it takes what you need to do to heal
whether you eat animal protein whether
you're vegan or plant-based
right now some of the vegan communities
I'm not saying all of them at all
some of the vegan communities are really
really coldish some of them not all of
them there there's a couple out there
and they're like oh we hate medical
medium because he talks about you can
you can do his stuff eating an animal
protein
and they get so angry
they're angry because I'm not against
somebody eating animal protein why am I
going to be judging somebody why should
I ever judge somebody for eating animal
protein and why should I judge them for
being a vegetarian or a vegan or a
plant-based person who am I and what
right do I have to judge anybody
for what they put in their mouth life is
hard and some people say animal protein
works for them you think I have the
right to judge them and that's the whole
thing it's it's important to know like
with the mm information
you can come here and you can learn how
to heal bring in the things you need
customize your protocol the way you want
to
and move forward
with your life and not be judged you
could be a plant-based person here you
could be an animal protein person here
you can come straight out of keto animal
protein and come here straight out of
paleo animal protein and come to Medical
medium induce medical medium tools you
can incorporate medical meme tools into
whatever it is you're doing it's called
it isn't one size fits all it's called
customizing what you need really
important because everybody's different
everybody's different
critical to know
so just talking about some of the things
that are going on out there too
Jess says love your books
celery juice has helped me with my
inflammatory pots
incredible
it really is
love and healing says on IG mm info is
vast I love that I can stop searching
for answers lots of misinformation out
there so glad I'm not lost in that world
anymore and I'm so glad you're not lost
in that world anymore
because that world yes is scary and I've
seen a lot of people lost in it over the
years Lisa I was vegan and eating
healthy and got so sick now I'm vegan
medical medium style and healing and
that leads me to one other thing right
here
I love when when plant-based
medical medium Anthony William haters
there's some plant-based influencers
that hate medical medium Anthony William
out there
right and but they don't realize
something there are so many plant-based
people here in medical medium community
that were doing plant-based but we're
sick as dogs and they learned that it
took more than just being plant-based it
took being plant-based for them and then
the Learned protocols and shock
Therapies
and all kinds of different things it
took more right and then there's just
plain old raw vegan movement out there
or plain old you know plant-based raw
vegan influencers out there that that
just crap on MM say it's all like
whatever a joke say he doesn't have any
credentials I don't have any credentials
I'm not a doctor never said I was if I
had credentials I'd be flaunting the
many everywhere if I had a certificate
of being a health coach I'd be saying
yeah I also have a certificate as a
health coach why not it would probably
help me actually but I don't have any
credentials but what happens is with
there's plant-based influencers out
there that hate mm so much
because they think well they got it all
down with their plant-based thing when
they don't realize you can be
plant-based and sick
sick
real sick
so sick and then learn how to heal while
still being plant-based because medical
meme's not against plant-based Lisa says
I love the propolis so much I don't even
get sick anymore with the cold because
every time I feel something I do shock
Therapies
I love
I love my little bottle of propolis
I do I do
but I also love my little bottle of
lemon balm right here I love my little
bottle of lemon balm I do I'm hearing my
lemon bomb bottle talk to me what huh
you're gonna help me
in what way
you're gonna help calm my nerves
and help fortify my nervous system
that's amazing
medical medium shock therapies are
Beyond innovative
truly Jody Jones says the shock
therapies have literally saved my life
literally saved my life
that means everything
Shannon Shannon hake over there on
YouTube I put propolis pure on my herpes
pustules they go away within 24 hours
mind blown
drop the mic
mind blown seriously
mind blown probably says something to
tell me right here what huh
what
you're gonna help me
my immune system
oh my God that's just what I need thank
you
what I was trying to say earlier you
guys got a second
so Elaine says Elaine says I'm not a
vegan I'm a medical me I'm in medical
medium vegan
okay
Ascend says do the supplements have
alcohol as preservatives no they do not
they do not have alcohol
they never did
supplements never did have alcohol
there's a lot of plant-based people that
talk about like there's a lot of
plant-based sorry influencers
that talk about like
other kind of approaches out there I've
seen those approaches
it's 20 tincture bottles
with alcohol in them
I've seen those approaches out there
it's 20 tincture bottles of alcohol
the stuff I know and the stuff I could
say would blow your mind if you had a
chance to sit down with me and ask me
about like what's really going out there
and going down in the health movement
plant-based movement vegan movement
whatever it is
I can blow your mind
within minutes and you'll be like what
the heck I'll be like yeah did you know
that did you know that that person's
whole protocol system is all filled with
alcohol in all their bottles you know
what that's like to someone who's
chronically ill and they go and they
start Downing that much straight alcohol
breaks down their immune system anyway
so much so much to know medical medium
shock therapies are in the brain saver
protocols book if you look right here
where am I going you'll see brain saver
protocols you see that back there you
guys the shock therapies are in there
check them out when you get a chance
mind-blowing information
and I notice I notice
that out there in the health realm of
competitors what they try to say the
haters and competitors and influencers
that want to take down medical medium in
the community I noticed that they say
they say things
that they do and and they don't happen
here
they say things that they do and they
project it as if I do it or something
it's sick it's like a sickness
is that like narcissism is sick
Tara says alcohol tinctures only ruined
my gut and nervous system more as I was
desperately trying to heal that's so
important to know I'm going to read a
little bit right here the medical medium
New Edition
guys remember to sign up for the free
collecting Stones meditation Journey
check it out link is in the description
and right there the quickening
at the beginning of the book
Spirit of compassion
calls our current ERA
the quickening
never before has civilization changed at
such a fast pace
do you guys concur
technology has revolutionized virtually
everything about our lives
we live in a period of breathtaking
wonder and opportunity we do do we not
it also is an era of danger
by the time we mentally process
something that's just happened it's
already old news
we're in such a rush that we always feel
the need to be a step ahead along with
up to the minute information at our
fingertips come greater demands if you
guys have a lot of demands upon you
that's why I do
the lemon balm
and the propolis responsibilities but
get ready for this along with
responsibilities and a lot of Demands on
us there's also pitfalls
pit Falls what is that you're walking
along
and you go down walking along
pitfalls
Brit says what page are you on beginning
the book
in the quickening section right here
just stroll in right at the beginning
here
okay
I know that's quick
I'm in medical medium
so
this is an interesting information right
here too Lightning Fast advances
sometimes come at a price
unconsidered vulnerability so Lightning
Fast advancements also come with a whole
bunch of stuff
these changes affect all of humankind
and women kind especially Bears the
brunt so women kind Bears the Brunt
with so much happening with the quick
the quickening
it's women who face the greatest
expectations in our current day
no no
disrespect to men
men also face a lot of crap we know that
right
but no no disrespect just acknowledging
that right now during the quickening
women really are faced with a lot of
different expectations in the current
day
women whose bodies so often get pushed
to the brink
and chronic illness has become such a
widespread issue for women for men and
for children
if we don't interrupt the constant flow
of misinformation
then that's what medical medium
information does it breaks and
interrupts the flow of constant
misinformation out there if we don't
recognize what our four mothers and
forefathers have gone through and
redirect our course then the generations
to come will have to endure unnecessary
suffering I'm seeing it now I mean when
I go back 35 years I'm seeing how
the generations
have to endure like the new generations
suffering to keep up with The Changing
Times to survive we must learn to adapt
the only way to do that is to protect
our health
and not in just
a ridiculous way
but in a way that matters and counts
the popular approach right now in books
articles and social media and podcasts
about chronic illness is to advise
people to eliminate what are theorized
to be inflammatory foods from their
diets while making theoretical
improvements to gut health and that's as
far as it goes
the information out there doesn't
explain what actually causes autoimmune
disorders or chronic conditions or how
to rid yourself of the real root
problems that is why people stay sick I
don't care how many people have adopted
the whole inflammatory thing out there
and they talk about it on podcasts or
whatever they talk about
they still don't know the root causes
but there are genuine explanations for
the conditions that leave medical
communities
in a stagnant place and leave patience
without answers
is there such thing as that patients
yeah
sure is TJ says
so true aw I'm 59 and scary to see how
much things have changed
the illusion is that there is a movement
in the medical communities
sorry the illusion
this is an important word to just
like digest for a second the illusion
is that there is movement in medical
communities understanding of chronic
illness
I see some like seriously some some
really good doctors out there
doing a lot of stuff trying really hard
they still don't know why their patients
are sick
I hear about it all the time the reality
is that appearance of advancement often
comes from false leads and guessing
games so it's like you what happens is
when we seek help we're getting kind of
like
snowed with smoke and mirrors with
advancements in health
but really it's a lot of Flash
pomp circumstance bells and whistles
Jackie B says on YouTube this book has
changed my life
it's got the collecting Stones
meditation journey in here but there's
going to be a lot more
of that starting on the 19th you get a
video every day it's going to be
incredible
so this is important information right
now
the reality is that appearance of
advancement often comes from false leads
and guessing games and people are still
suffering
still suffering that stagnation doesn't
need to hold you back anymore there are
powerful methods to deal with the
challenges we face in this modern era
medical meme information is shaped and
changed Health all on its own just not
only in the last few decades but
specifically and especially in the last
three years last 10 years
this book is the guide to truly freeing
yourself
I've written it so you can truly heal
and keep yourself from getting sucked
into the trends and fads and mistakes
and half truths and errors and
distractions and deceptions about Health
and Wellness
Spirit of compassion has provided this
information so we can help today's
children grow into healthy adults
and here's here's what's interesting I'm
not against science not against science
and research
I'm in no way anti-science far from it
actually I don't question that the Earth
is round I hope I don't
I hope I'm not bothering anybody that
there's a lot of people that think the
Earth is flat and I don't judge them on
any level
I don't question that the Earth is round
or that the Earth is billions of years
old
or the value of the scientific method
What Spirit of compassion reveals in
this book is being read here and as a
result becoming recognized by the
scientific Community more and more each
day so here's what happens scientific
Community is poaching information that
was only published out of this book
right here and the other medical medium
books but at least science is advancing
because of this right here this book was
published
but was already written in the process
of getting printed in two thousand and
13.
if you or a loved one is sick do you
feel you have 20 or 30 or 50 years to
wait for answers very important right
there so I want to read this little
section
the word Quicken doesn't just mean
become faster
it also means spring to life
historically is referred to the first
signs of movement a fetus showed in the
womb
which is to say this time of the
quickening isn't just about life
speeding up it's also about rebirth
so even though things are going faster
than ever before with the quickening
right now and we know that I mean you
guys know just in the last three years
hasn't things gone a lot faster just in
the last four years how about the last
five years
do you think things were different 10
years ago than what they are now greatly
different in so many ways Health with
Liz good to see you this book is one of
the most precious to me because of the
Soul healing chapter I'm so grateful for
Spirit of compassion for providing this
info
thank you health with Liz
truly I respect your opinion and your
experience
and what you say
aren't we all looking for truth truth
about our world the universe truth about
ourselves about life about why we are
here about our purpose are we not
looking for truth about all of that
when we're sick we question ourselves
how many people question themselves when
they get sick
so many people do
from what we were put on Earth to do we
doubt basic truths like the body's
ability to heal because we have haven't
yet connected to what's really behind
our illnesses
we go from Doctor to doctor medical
community to medical community looking
for an answer we lose faith in life
itself and I can't stress that point
enough so many people lose faith
when they get sick
they lose faith
when we become well doubt melts away we
have energy to to to devote to our true
purpose we watch ourselves transform and
we believe in the good in life again
we get reacquainted with our path in
this world we find our way back home
with peace in our heart and soul
the truth about the world ourselves life
purpose it all comes down to healing and
the truth about healing is now in your
hands just wanted to read that to you
guys
hope I did it justice
mixed up a couple little words in there
but did my best
Gabriella says it's been crazy since
2016.
I agree
couldn't agree more
you guys sign up to the collecting
Stones meditation Journey when you get a
chance don't miss out link is in the
description link is in the profile
starts on July 19th
you're going to find your three stones
scope out the spot that you want to find
your Stones wait to July 19th to gather
your stones but if you had to gather
them beforehand I completely understand
you can sign up on the profile or go to
medicalmedium.com
you can go to medicalmedium.com and sign
up to the collecting Stones meditation
Journey it's a free Journey you won't be
disappointed
someone's looking for the code for the
Bemidji
um
foreign
ergy.com and you'll see it's there
you guys
I hope I hope you've enjoyed this
live
I'm going to take a little bit of lemon
balm right now I'm going to calm myself
down
right here
do I dare say bartender give me another
no
but I'll take another
there's no alcohol in the Bemidji
supplements
which is a miracle really and no hidden
alcohol in the Bemidji supplements
so I can't say bartender give me another
well I can still say it
I got the pure propolis pure right here
lip smacking good
you guys
I'll see you next time
God bless you truly take care of
yourselves
one day at a time pat yourself on the
back and keep a light heart please