hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who has 10 or 20 or even 30
years to wait for answers to their
illnesses cuz believe me people have
been waiting and I've seen it you've
seen it you know what I'm talking about
and it's no fun it's absolutely no fun
and we're talking about gut health today
and and the intestinal track and
understanding gut health because that's
Today's Show and I'll tell you why
that's Today's show you know I was
actually thinking we were going to do
another show and there's so many things
in different topics but gut health is
serious it's really serious and more and
more people I mean I've watched this for
decades actually but more and more
people now are just saying well you know
I can't get my gut better what do I do
and there are answers there are answers
to fixing problems there are answers to
fixing you know everything involved with
it constipation bloating gas loose
stools poor absorption you know tummy
pains strange tummy pains gastritis all
these different things we go to the
doctor for and we can't get answers and
we go to Alternative doctors we can't
get answers too we it's well you go to
Alternative doctors usually just blamed
on candida we can't just do that because
a lot of what happens is with gut health
is a lot of people they can get better
from a little while then it all comes
back or they don't get better at all or
it gets worse over time or they do get
better because they you know there's
some people that get better and they
removed you know uh gluten out of their
diet and they removed a little dairy
products out of their diet or they
cleaned it up they got rid of pastries
cookies and cakes and they did get
better but there's a lot of people that
don't and they do everything and
everything and anything to actually try
to get their guts better and look I know
how frustrating is so today's show is
gut health and we're going to talk about
this poor absorption and tummy pains and
everything around it and it's just a
sign that our guts need attention and so
this is serious we're addressing this
today because who has 10 or 20 30 years
to wait for answers for the illnesses
I've said this before I say it again
that I've seen people wait a long time
for
answers and you know when it comes down
to gut health the reason why a lot of
people don't get better is because the
information out there the newest
information out there is is has dust on
it and it's old it's old information and
you know someone was telling me the
other day they said you know you got to
you think pretty big of yourself Mr
medical medium because you're talking
about how new information and you're
talking about how new books and new
things that are coming out about gut
health you're talking about how that's
old and outdated and I'm like yeah cuz
it is it is old and outdated it's not
about you know what I believe in what I
think what it's about somebody getting
better and having the right information
so yeah I might come across sounding a
little bit arrogant someone said oh you
seem like you might be arrogant because
you got all the answers that's not it at
all spirit's got the answers and I want
you to have those answers I want you to
have those answers and I want you able
to heal and move forward because you can
you know and when I look into the latest
information it's even out there cuz
someone says hey look at this I'm like
whoo and I'm all excited and I look at
him I'm like look this stuff is ancient
history already ancient history before
it was even minted you know everything
about candida that's that's wrong
totally wrong and we're going to cover
cover candida a little bit today
everything about leaky gut totally wrong
I mean there's there's I mean I'm seeing
stuff on the scene right now about leaky
gut it was 20 years ago and it was wrong
20 years ago it was was misinformation
20 years ago look I have to find this
humorous I have to make because it's sad
it's sad because that's 20 years of
someone not getting the information they
need to get their gut better to get
their health better because it affects
their families it affects their lives it
gets in the way of everything and the
suffering occurs I have to keep a sense
of humor about it because it kills me it
kills me to watch it I've watched it in
young people I've watched it in
teenagers I've watched it in kids I've
watched it in older people I've watched
people lose their jobs I've watched
people suffer I've watched people you
know have you know difficult lives they
get divorces over it because they can't
eat anything the other person can eat
and whatnot and it causes problems I've
seen it all and so when someone says hey
you seem to be pretty arrogant no what
it is what it is is is the crap coming
out in books and information and
literature and everything else in the
best sense meaning even including all
the alternative about gut health is so
way off it's ridiculous and it's not
about me being like hey I got all the
answers it's about the TR truth it's
about what's really happening in the gut
it's about what's wrong it's about what
spirit says and it's about you getting
better cuz and the bottom line is I
don't care I don't care whose feelings I
heard out there when it comes down to
you it's it's about getting you better
it's about you having the right
information so you know I don't care if
a brand new book comes off the running
and it's about leaky gut you know and
and meanwhile when you look in it and
it's literally 20 30 years old
information is even the new information
and it is wrong right off the press and
I'm like oh here we go again here we go
again how many people are going to be
led down a path for another 10 years oh
my God and you know what that's okay
that's okay if I didn't have to see the
suffering myself that's okay if I didn't
have to see it it being real but it's
real people are going through hell and
back with their guts in testinal tracks
no one's clearing the air about it no
one is I have to do that I have to do it
I need you feeling better you need to
know what's going on and we're covering
a couple of really cool things something
that nobody knows about nobody bottom
line okay so that's what today's about
check out life-changing Foods okay so we
were doing a live webinar we got all
kinds of stuff going on so check out
life-changing Foods too um you know that
book is packed and I mean packed I mean
I I literally I basically thought I was
going to stroke out writing that book
okay right because I was taking so much
data from Spirit so much data and
information from Spirit that's never
been taught anywhere or learned or
anywhere it's not offered anywhere about
what over 50 fruits and vegetables what
they do do which I call them the holy
for these groups of fruits and
vegetables wild foods and what they do
for people what illnesses what symptoms
they take care of so when you really go
through this and you pick out the right
vac vegetable the right herb the right
spice the right wild Food For Your Right
condition and you do it in the way you
need to do it and it just comes together
it's lifechanging I also have a
fertility chapter I also have um what
not to eat chapter another one of those
where you know look out for these foods
not to eat and you name it it's packed
and you know I I had to get that
done I'm laughing because I yeah I went
through hell and back with that one but
I'm going to tell you right now it's
it's so worth it when you guys get this
in your hands um so hey lock down a copy
when you can all right so look I just
want the book in your hands it's
everything it means everything to me to
just get you guys healthy so that's why
we're doing the gut health gut health
today I want you healthy I don't care
what it takes I'm going to give you any
bit of information all the information I
can if this is first time you came on um
it started all with me at age 4 heard a
voice perfectly clear in the ear in real
time real time means someone's talking
to you in real time it's not being
channeled it's not being taken in in
other kind of you know ways it's not
being like you know Zapped into the
Consciousness there's nothing going on
like that it's someone talking to me in
real time it's a voice I heard since age
four that's where the information comes
that's how I've helped tens of thousands
of people move forward with their lives
and have changed their lives and um so
um that's how it all really began with
me and I dedicated my life into helping
people I'm going to make sure you have
the information that you need to help
your loved ones your friends the people
you care for your family members and
yourself and that's what matters the
most I don't care what else is going on
in the world it's about you feeling
better so you can live your life you
could do the things you need to do you
know I've watched it I've seen it I've
said this before I got moms telling me
they can't
believe 20 years later after they birth
their child their daughter and their
daughter you know is now 20 years old
they can't believe 20 years later the
daughter their daughter has a diagnosis
that they had they have and it's still
there's nothing new to fix it nothing
new to fix it same chronic fatigue
syndrome fibromyalgia Hashim modus
thyroiditis all the same nothing new I
and you know and and I've had people say
look I bought every book out there on
Hashimoto's I bought everything and it
doesn't even tell you what causes it
exactly exactly because there's nothing
new out there and it has to change now
it has to change and you know and I've
had moms they're crying because their
15-year-old daughter is sick with things
that she was sick with and and still
nothing's done about it and and and it
goes on and it goes on and it goes on
and you know and and it's hitting young
people
177% 17 out of 100 college
students go home leave College in the
middle of college and don't go back and
don't go back it's not because they
couldn't do the studies meaning like
it's not because they weren't brilliant
they left because they were sick 17 out
of a 100 you do the math how many
thousands of students are going to
school every year okay across this
country do the math right now 17 out of
100 then do the math what's that out of
a th000 what's that out of 10,000
they're coming home and not going back
to school because of chronic fatigue
syndrome because of Epstein bar even
though they're not being diagnosed with
Epstein bar Epstein bar is rampant and
just literally it's harming our our
youth you know and you name it and it's
is everything from fibromyalgia to
inflammation to random disorders to um
to insomnia to you name it it's
rampant and the books out there and the
information and the Articles and the
literature just isn't cutting it so we
have to do the show and and and like I
said I don't care if I'm on the edge of
stroking out getting that information
from Spirit to put in these books to get
to you guys I'm going to do it so move
on to let's move on to the the gut
health show that's where we are so
thanks for hanging in there until we get
to this point so look bloating gas
gastritis pain constant pain
constipation diarrhea you know
inflammation then there's gut health
like disorders that have our conditions
and diseases we got Celiac we got
Crohn's we got um you know IBS we got
colitis we have it all it all plays a
role in here it all does but you type in
colitis and cause unknown you what's IBS
cause unknown irritable bowel syndrome
cause unknown okay Cron's cause unknown
and and you know what's
interesting is back and I've said this
before I'm going to say it again back in
the in the80s what happened was when we
were at that crossroads where
conventional medicine was was just it
was just conventional medicine if you
were in naturopath you were just
completely thought of as just crap total
crap if you were an naturopath in 1980
okay and this was a really dangerous
time dangerous time for naturopaths
natural medicine hop you know home paths
chiropractors that thought beyond the
normal you you name it that was this was
a really bad time this was when we were
completely divided right now you have
clinics where there's conventional
doctors you got clinics where there's
natural doctors and they're all all
working together you even look at some
of the most popular clinics now it's
like they got they got a nutritionist in
there they got a naturopath in there
they they got a functional integrated a
functional medicine doctor in there and
then MDS are flipping over they're like
they're not MDS anymore they're MDS and
they're functional doctors right this
didn't exist back in the 80s it was the
Dark Ages and we might still be in the
dark ages of misinformation right now
but we're not in the dark ages of where
we were as far as collaborating and back
then I mean it was like it was insane it
was you went to the doctor you you were
told it was all in your head so if you
were a woman you went to the doctor you
told you were insane you told you were
lazy you're told you were crazy your
blood work checked out fine antiquated
antique blood work which we still use
now you told you were fine and that's it
you get you get sent home that was the
80s okay and but what happened was it
was happening in such a degree and so so
so much of that was happening the
naturopaths came on the scene I mean
they were always around but they were
really starting to come in and file out
of schools there was an explosion in
the80s and they they're filing you know
they're filing out where each state had
a few met naturopaths now which was
which was which was unbelievable in some
states in the US think about it okay and
you know the first the first naturopath
in California which I actually know
personally the first first natural path
in California you know coming out in the
late 70s early 80s and California where
you know isn't that where everything
happens first
supposingly right and so the first you
know naturopath came out but what
happened was you know naturopaths and
natural medicine need some needed
something to hold on to something to
bite their teeth into because what was
happening is there was a flood of people
flood of women like I'm sick I'm sick
you know uh uh you know I went went to
10 conventional doctors no answers that
still happens today went to 20
conventional doctors still still no
answers that still happens today though
and what happened was the candida
diagnosis was born it exploded it was an
amazing diagnosis because it was like
whoa you got some you got candida you
got candida overgrowth in your gut
that's what's going on here and what it
did was it was like it was like uh an
Awakening it was like Angels came out of
the sky and like the heavens parted and
it was like and Jesus just baby Jesus
came down I mean it was like that kind
of moment that was the kind of moment
where you know hey there is something
wrong with me and but it wasn't really
candida in the end that's why we've gone
from candida to today right now we're
going to
sibo sibo small intestinal bacteria over
sibo we're going into that land now you
know and that was the land that 30 years
ago when spirit said hey it's not
candida Spirit knew it was overgrowth of
different forms of bacteria and it
wasn't candida see Spirit was ahead of
its time 30 years so I've been able to
help people for 30 years who didn't have
to go through the candida ride which is
kill your candida kill your candida this
you know what I mean the whole bit so
and even sios miss misunderstood right
now because sio is still a
misunderstanding of what kind of
bacteria is in the gut that's causing
that over what oh what is the
proliferation of bacteria well it's
mostly strepa cacus and it's it's it's
antibiotic resistant strep sibo is a
development of strep that's been in
someone's system and they've taken
antibiotics through childhood or any
other time in their life and they fed
the strep strep got stronger then it
overgrew later and when you get older
and your immune system starts breaking
down you're not taking care of yourself
and you're stressed out the strep grows
even more proliferates even more and
that's what sibo is nobody even knows
that yet so I'm giving you Advanced
information right there all on its own
so you know the bottom line is this is
we're going to cover a few good things
we're going to talk about leaky gut
let's start with leaky gut okay we're
just going to have to do that someone
says you have leaky gut chances are you
don't have leaky gut leaky gut if you
had leaky gut you'd be in the in the
hospital with 105 temperature which
accept this and dying so you don't have
leaky gut you have to understand that
something went wrong with the whole
leaky gut Concept in fact there's even
new new information new books out now
talking about leaky gut totally totally
Antiquated
information
unbelievable yeah I mean it's been
superseded it's it it's just
unbelievable and so leaky gut isn't just
this this whole thing where you got you
got this permeability happening where
where all this debris and stuff is going
through the intestinal lining and gases
are going through the intestinal lining
that's not really what it is first of
first of all if you had diverticulitis
diverticulosis and it got even to the
point where something escaped to the
other side we're talking 104 temperature
we're talking emergency
crisis so not even people that have
eruptions in their colon where they have
Diverticulitis and eruptions have leaky
gut it would have to go even past that
situation
ation see that's that's how it works
this is where it's so misinformed on
leaky gut I I I don't mean to be a pain
in the butt about at all I don't it's
just that what am I supposed to do just
go along with it and not give you guys
the right information to heal I I don't
get it so it's so the deal is look so if
you've been diagnosed with leaky gut
that chances are you don't have leaky
gut it's not what's happening do you
have problems in your intestinal tract
yeah you definitely could have problems
a lot of people don't have any problems
in their intestinal tract and they they
feel sick they got fatigue they got
Epstein bar they got shingles they got
other problems they got you know other
stuff going on and it's still blamed on
leaky gut cuz you know it's it's that
kind of thing you know so you go to a
gut health doctor you're going to get
leaky gut diagnosis go to Lyme doctor
you're going to get a lime do you know
diagnosis go to Multiple Sclerosis
doctor you're going to get an MS do you
know diagnosis I mean have I said enough
does it go on and on and on so so um the
deal is with leaky gut that's not what's
happening what does happen though is our
liver okay produces less bile due to
stress due to Foods we're eating okay
especially if we're eating lots of high
fat densed foods or we're eating foods
that have lots of fat and sugar combined
like like a chocolate cake which has
tons of lard and then it has you know
some some it say tons of lard and then
has table sugar involved or corn syrup
involved but whatever it is that we're
eating over time it breaks down the it
breaks down the liver it gets the liver
to become more fatty more pre fatty and
it's usually due to real high intensity
of fats in in our diet for too many
years so our liver breaks down
bioproduction
minimizes okay so so that minimizes
hydrochloric acid minimizes hydrochloric
acid is a blend of seven acids
undiscovered by science today you want
to know you want to know the future I'm
going to tell you some of the future to
begin with like I said hydrochloric acid
isn't one acid that's not one acid in
the stomach it's a blend of seven they
just have not been able to single it out
yet and figure it out and like I've said
before we don't know what happens to
food when it drops into the stomach yeah
there's absorption yeah there's
digestion there's a simulation let me
tell you something God only knows what
happens the minute food enters that
stomach I promise see that that's a
thousand years from now we're going to
know exactly how everything works but
the bottom line is um the bile gets you
know less production of bile from the
liver liver gets pre- fatty liver as
time goes on okay and as all this is
happening your hydrochloric acid breaks
down so you get low HCL so that's
breaking down when that's breaking down
then um food doesn't digest well and it
starts to rot and it gets down into the
intestinal tract and it starts to rot
when it starts to rot it produces
ammonia ammonia ammonia is a is
basically an agent that can move through
any part of the
body it can move through muscle so it
has nothing to do with leaky gut it can
move through
organs ammonia can move through an organ
like a ghost moves through a house and
goes through the
wall okay you can have a perfectly sound
amazing intestinal
lining that doesn't have one callus on
it not one pup not one callus not one
hole from a bacterial infection from 30
years ago not one anything wrong with it
and ammonia will move through your
intestinal track just like a ghost moves
through a wall if you believe in ghosts
of course you know some somebody out
there might not believe in ghosts so I
don't want to you know insult anybody or
whatever I'm just
saying and and so it's the same kind of
thing that occurs so it and it moves
through organs that ammonia it moves
through
muscle it there's nothing that stops IT
from going right through the human
body and then out of the human body
ammonia just comes right through the
skin the skin doesn't even stop it it
just leaks right out of the skin has
nothing to do with leaky gut on any
level on any level it's called ammonia
permeability ammonia permability is a
word that's in my book that Spirit came
up with for me to teach people so it's
our word over here and it's called
ammonia permeability and it's from
ammonia leaking through the entire
body and and that's just the bottom line
that's how it works so that's that's
what occurs now that's not leaky gut on
any level on any way because this
doesn't mean you're going to feel sick
ammonia
permeability doesn't make you tired
doesn't make you
sick and it doesn't hurt you it's other
things that happen in the gut that have
nothing to do with candida or leaky gut
that end up hurting you it's that break
it's that breakdown of the liver meaning
the liver being stagnant sluggish it's
food not breaking
down okay it's food not breaking down
and rotting and then starting to feed
STP starting to feed eoli starting to
feed seiff starting to feed Mera I mean
we get exposed to all this stuff you
know you just visit a friend in a
hospital and and you know I mean
anything's possible it's like one two
three just like that and so that's what
happens is food just starts to feed
things now if the food is not good food
like it's food that I tell people to
avoid like eggs then it feeds something
worse feeds viruses such as like Epstein
bar shingles colitis is caused by the
shingles that's the shingles virus on
the inside of the lining of the the
intestinal tract causing colitis and it
feeds off of eggs it feeds off of dairy
products it feeds off of gluten one
thing you're going to get out of the
show is you're not going to get like oh
yeah like you know anti-inflam Foods um
you know autoimmune Foods yeah just stay
away from the gluten stay away from this
mot toxins and this and that you're
going to get you're going to get
information about what foods feeding
what causing what illness and what
disease that's what you're going to get
you're not going to get that anywhere
else unless they're listening to this
show and and and adopting it so the the
eggs will feed the shingles virus in the
intestinal tract you won't hear that
anybody anywhere else it'll feed the in
the shingles and intestinal tract cause
an inflammation and eruption of blood
vessels that's what's happening there so
it's it's other things that are you know
worse mean when you have when you have
viruses inside of us certain bacteria
inside of us never mind candida candida
is there to try to protect you it sits
there did you know this that without
candida we die how about that one
without having candida in our system we
actually die that's what happens an
overgrowth of candida is because it's
protecting you candida is literally
trying to absorb
absorb and eat stuff and eat food and
debris to take it away from something
worse in the body candida is trying to
save your life by gobbling up whatever
it can it gobble up that chocolate cake
because it does candida doesn't want
that chocolate cake getting to Coline
strepa cacus getting to you know getting
to the shingles getting to over 60 VAR
of Zep bar hhb6 hhb1 hhv1 hhb2 I could
go on and on forever cyeg CMV and so
what happens is that candida is sitting
there protecting your life that's what
it does that's not even the issue so
these are such critical pieces of
information I forgot to tell you put on
your seat belts I forgot to tell you
guys you got to guys got to fasten your
seat belts so I'll even put mine on
okay right so we'll get the seat belts
on so anyway we got other things that's
a leaky gut confusion I'm talking about
Hydrochloric acid we we have
hydrochloric acid problems where they
break down the seven aets that are that
are just considered one because science
hasn't funded got the funds or or got to
the point of Medical Research Medical
Science to figure out the seven
different assets that are the blend in
there I'm going tell you one other thing
too the scien is not know we're born
with this like type of hair microscopic
furry hair on the inside of her
intestinal tracts and the inside of her
guts they're to Heart Harper good
bacteria like elevated biotics like
we're going to talk about in a little
while they're there to hold all the good
bacteria so that bad bacteria can't get
into Spate Linings and start creating
Diverticulitis and so forth and
everything but the problem is we lose
this hair really fast years ago hundreds
of years ago we didn't lose it fast it
stayed with us now because of
antibiotics it just burns right off of
the inside of the intestin track and
colon I mean kids are given antibiotics
with their first deer infection instead
of other things being figured out and
you know it just starts right from the
beginning lots of antibiotics it just
wipes out this intestinal tract lining
this this microscopic fur that's on the
lining of the intestinal tracts and by
the time we get into our teenager Years
and we're eating you know we're eating
all the fun stuff like Twinkies and
everything else and you name it and it
just between that and antibiotics it
just just wipes right out and now we
just basically have a bare colon and
bare intestinal
tract and that you know and that
information you can you can only find
here the problem is with that you get
calluses and then you got all these
other bacteria then you get more
antibiotics and then you get more
problems and you know then you're eating
poorly the liver breaks down you're
gaining weight all kinds of problems are
happening and this is what goes
wrong gastritis is
bacterial so when someone has gastritis
so they have a lot of gas that's not
fungus that's not yeast that's not
candida that's bacteria that's bacteria
overgrowth that's what that is um and so
that's what gastritis is so it's another
thing to understand so inflammation in
the intestinal tract inflammation like
IBS in irritable vowel syndrome okay
that's that's that's a another great one
because you know I talk about I laugh
about that it's like oh you got IBS well
what's IBS
you know and and so yeah we the whole
thing with that is inflammation is
caused by a lot of things it's caused
mostly by bacteria a breakdown of like I
said the liver the hydrochloric acid
food not breaking down okay and and it
rotting in the intestinal tract feeding
different types of bacteria we also pick
up a lot of different kinds of bacteria
chronically or constantly we're eating
in restaurants we get it everywhere so
we have to be careful in how we're
eating um you know a restaurant you know
I try to eat as many fresh fruits and
vegetables as I can you know that's what
I that's what I like to do because I got
spirit in my ear telling me that you
know we we we're only here so long you
got to get as many meals as you can in
you that are good and spirit's always
pushing me to do the fresh fruits fresh
vegetables that's what I'm always being
pushed to do uh but when I'm at a
restaurant you know what I do is I order
cooked food that comes really hot like
like hot F you know fresh fruits and
vegetables that became hot like hot
vegetables that's what I order because
you know I don't want to get any
contamination I don't want to get
cross-contamination from you know
somebody at the sink in the kitchen so
I'm careful because you can pick up a
whole multiple different varieties of
bacteria in your journey of eating out
and doing things I'm not trying to put
fear in you but make sure you're kind of
cautious make sure your food comes hot
that matters
um it matters greatly a lot of people
have a whole bunch of low levels of food
poisoning in their system all through
their life it builds up it reeks Havoc
it breaks down a lining of the
intestinal tract and so forth they have
antibiotics in and out of it all we get
a lot of gut
damage and this is what occurs creates a
lot of inflammation different pathogens
creates different inflammation we have
viruses in the intestinal tract causes
different inflammation and then then
there's things like gin bar uh inflaming
the SP spleen and liver and then causing
digestive trouble because your liver is
inflamed your spleen inflamed because
you have a little bit of epine bar and
so then it gets confused and we think
that's our intestinal track another
thing is there's viruses like the
shingles that make the nerve sensitive
makes all the nerves in the body
sensitive so here's something here's a
nugget right here that's so important
there's people out there that think they
can't digest
anything they think they can't digest
any food but that's not accurate that's
not true it's just that they're feeling
the food move through them are you one
of those people because you feel the
food moving through you because all your
nerve endings all your neurological all
the nervous central nervous system the
vagus nerve the frenic nerves they're
wired to your colon your dadum your
intestinal tract so your whole your
stomach all that has nerves going to it
all these hot nerves and if you've been
viral different varieties of Epstein bar
you've been viral with with different
varieties of shingles if you a sensitive
person from a lot of heavy metals from
um from your nervous system being
sensitive because of a lot of heavy
metals toxic heavy metals what's going
to happen is when you eat your the food
is going to rub the lining of your
intestinal tract and colon as
peristaltic action is happening and when
that happens you guys you're going to
feel like oh I just I'm not digesting
this I don't know what I'm eating that's
you know feeling good and then what's
going to happen is you're going to stay
away from a salad you're going to stay
away from something like that that rubs
along the sides you're going to stay
away from that and then you're just
going to have like oh the only thing I
can have is an egg an egg seems to work
I don't feel any pain when I eat an egg
meanwhile the egg is feeding more
inflammation and more nerve problems and
more issues but yet it feels good going
down I had people telling me that
they'll be like well you know the only
thing I could eat is an egg the reason
why is the egg turns into a liquid like
a liquid glue that just sits in the
middle it doesn't rub the intestinal
walls or the Linings it doesn't rub the
sides so you don't feel it but if you
eat some butterleaf lettuce or you eat a
Roma piece of lettuce or you eat an
apple that pecon that that stuff is
going to go and and start doing some
healing and it's going to rub the lining
of the intestinal tract it's going to
rub the lining of the stomach it's going
to rub everything and if you have
sensitive nervous system you're going to
be like oh I didn't digest this oh I
can't digest this that's how confusing
it is so if you're pushed into a corner
where you feel like you can only eat
like a piece of cheese and an egg or all
you can eat is just this one piece of
chicken and you're one of those people
that I feel bad when you get pushed into
that try to try to break out of that box
have a little bit of avocado you know it
it will rub a little bit as it goes down
because it's got fiber in it and Pulp
but it's not going to it's not going to
you know rub all so much where it's it's
getting you upset try to do a little bit
of some you know some boiled potato and
try to get that in there you there's
different things you can do some sweet
potato some butternut squash um you can
try different things that won't be so
you know they won't rub as they go down
to try to graduate you out of that
sensitive nervous systems are a big part
of our digestive like cry out our
digestive pain and suffering that a lot
of people have it's nerve sensitivities
it's vagus nerve sensitivities going
right to the intestinal tract it's
frenic nerve sensitivities going right
into the intestinal tract so much of
this is these nerve sensitive
sensitivities from being viral
neurological symptoms for being vibral
when someone someone has
fibromyalgia even they they with what
they don't know so if you have
fibromyalgia what you don't know if you
have a bad case of it the nerves are not
just in other parts of the joints or
other parts of your shoulders or your
arms these nerves they hurt in the
intestinal tract so when you eat you're
like I don't know what to eat I ate that
it doesn't feel good I had a date it
doesn't feel good I had this but I can
eat an egg and that feels
good so it's it's important to know and
fibro caused by Epstein bar of course um
my brought that to the world's attention
quite a while ago and and uh and it's
getting around so finally people are
learning um so look back to candida if
if you were diagnosed with candida don't
go hog while crazy trying to kill your
candida whatever you do instead take
Foods away from whatever bacteria is
causing your real inflammation that's
another thing too take Foods away take
the dairy take the eggs out take all the
gluten out I'm sure you've taken grains
out we're going to going to do a show
just on grains though we're going to do
a show just on grains that one will come
up you guys got to hear that one it's
really cool cuz I'm not against all
grains so um but when you're dealing
with you know intestinal INF
inflammation and you're worried you
think it's candida you got to bring in
some fruit you got to bring in some
papaya we got to talk about all this so
we're going to we're going to go into a
lot of this
so key key things take-home things we
got to build up your hydrochloric acid
we got to get your liver stronger we got
to get your bioproduction up to par and
we got to get the right
probiotics the right probiotics I'm
going to offer later on in the show two
probiotic companies that I think are
okay okay that I think are fine but what
I really like I really like is elevated
biotics elevated biotics is a term from
Spirit um to help the world to help you
get better if there was a time in your
life where you actually ate a piece of
kale picked out of the garden it could
have been 20 years ago the bacteria on
that kale which is an elevated
microorganism is still in you today
keeping you
alive okay it's not the microorganisms
that are in soil born microorganisms
those are weak those are weak that's
outdated
information I'm just for warning you it
look you don't want to live in the past
you don't want a car without the
headrest from 1950 so when someone Nails
you in the back they slam you in the
back your neck goes back you have no
head headrest on the car and your neck
your neck snaps you don't want that kind
of car you don't want that kind of seat
you don't want a car without airbags
today driving around but that's what
it's like with this with with you know
with the information with microorganisms
right now the best newest stuff coming
out is is outdated was outdated to begin
with soil born microorganisms are not
the ones that give us what we need okay
they're helpful if they're not harmful
they're helpful because they keep the
plant healthy down below but they can't
handle the sun they can't handle the
wind they can't handle the rain they
can't handle anything they hide they
hide in the soil and they're not that
strong when we consume them if they
happen to be on our produce and we
consume you know we consume a little bit
of dirt it's not going to hurt us but it
dies off quickly in the stomach with our
own hydrochloric acid there's a
microorganism called elevated biotic it
sits on the leaves it sits on the
raspberry you just picked it sits on the
strawberry you just picked it's loaded
on there and it handles the wind the
rain it handles the radiation falling
out of the sky it handles the chemicals
dropping out of the
sky it handles you know pollution it
handles trucks with diesel fume spewing
out of it driving by and it stays alive
it sits there on a Raspberry someone
told me hey I used to pick blackberries
20 years ago I found them on the side of
a road was that okay and I was picking
black yeah elevated biotics are on there
microor microorganisms that are sitting
on that Berry they go deep down into the
Elum they're the only bugs that go down
into the Elum down in there and Nestle
in there and create B12 and save our
butts so when you go to the farmer
market go to the organic you know
Farmers Market you get some kale you
don't have to you just give it a gentle
rinse if you see dirt on it you rinse
off the dirt and you know the elevated
biotics will be on there if you have a
if you don't have a garden and you got a
little pot and you got parsley and you
stick it on the patio it'll collect
elevated
biotics apple apple from an orchard
elevated biotics if you can only do it
once a year it helps you do it twice a
year helps more that's the probiotic
that's a probiotic that keeps us alive
that's Advanced
information I have to I have to harp on
that advanced information thing in case
we got new new people on board too you
guys if you're new this is your first
show and you just need to know where
we're coming from here at this show and
just I just hope you stay with us and
learn and learn and help people so just
stay with us and we move forward
together and I got respect for everybody
in the audience everybody listening you
I stand behind you I just want you
feeling better and I just hope you stay
with us and you know we just learn
together we grow grow move forward um so
it's those elevated biotics that are
amazing they will bottle these up down
the road when they when they learn about
them and they discover them so I don't
know when that's going to be I don't
know but you can't wait those 30 years I
can't wait okay so let's get the
elevated biotics in us now those are the
ones that stop disease those are the
ones that stop cancers in our intestinal
tracts those are the ones that stop scar
tissue in our intestinal tract and
that's another thing I want to talk
about scar tissue is rampant in our
intestinal tracts it's not leaky gut
syndrome it's Scar Tissue Scar Tissue
caused by antibiotics burning our
Linings Scar Tissue caused by bacteria
Scar Tissue caused by pollutants and
heavy metals toxic heavy metals and
that's that's what it's about there
that's what it's about let's talk about
some things we can do for all this okay
we're going to need another gut health
show I can tell already because we're
moving we're moving through this so
far H foods for gut health celery juice
just go to my Instagram you'll see
people drinking celery juice you guys
know you're probably listening that they
in Instagram all the time you're doing
the celery juice and you're rebuilding
your hydrochloric acid you're rebuilding
your gut health you're getting out of
that whole fear of candida that
misrepresentation of candida and
misrepresentation of leaky gut I mean
freedom is nice man freedom is nice and
you know it's it's important it's
important because when you start looking
at some of that Antiquated information
out there and some of the antique stuff
and you like oh my God I was there it's
great to be here it feels good I feel
the same way you guys do trust me I'm
because I'm because I'm just glad I'm
with spirit I feel the same way I'm
honored and and I just I'm just great I
meaning it feels great to have it the
information for all of us me me included
so celery juice 16 ounces of celery
juice every morning once a day you can
turn your gut problems around
hydrochloric acid builds up your liver
starts to back down
meaning it starts to calm down if it's
overheated if it's inflamed it starts to
get better if you're an acupuncturist
and you just believe in in acupuncture
you know I love all forms of medicine
that are alternative and even
conventional um many of them
conventional but if you're an
acupuncturist you you always find that
liver heat in your patients I bet you
know what I mean so you probably see all
that liver heat in them because you're
using your intuition you're popping
needles into them and you're like whoa
this liver is a mess well the celery
juice make sure your clients are on
celery juice if it goes against a belief
system just try to work it in somehow
try to work it in but you'll get your
your patients with all those liver
problems better because I know
acupuncturist they talk to me all the
time about they say well you wouldn't
believe the liver problems I see Anthony
I go yeah use some celery juice aloe
water aloe water that's a big deal so
you blend aloe in a blender look for
different recipes I got them everywhere
I think they're you know go to Medical
medium.com go to my blog and you'll find
it it's really
important so aloe water Alo is an
anti-inflammatory because it's antiviral
antibacterial it goes into the
intestinal lining and it only starts
going after that bad bacteria that sibo
bacteria that IBS bacteria all of it so
you want you want your Alo okay it
lowers the bad acids acid
reflux is because hydrochloric acid one
the seven blend is gone and what took
over is acids produced by
bacteria and viruses and that's what
acid reflux is it's actually bacteria
produced I mean acids produced bad acids
produced by bacteria and that's that's
what it is so you want to get the celery
juice in there you want to get the aloe
water in there every day to start
knocking down that bad bacteria you want
to get papaya in you papaya papaya it is
it's a Saving Grace I've seen it save
people's lives with colitis with Crohn
with um IBS with intestinal chronic
gastritis chronic inflammation papaya is
amazing it helps soothes the nerves if
you got viral neurological problems with
your intestinal tract that I was talking
about early earlier soothes the nerves
wild blueberries they feed all good
bacteria they feed elevated biotic
bacteria it feeds off of that that's
like that's like milk of the gods to the
bacteria that's keeping us alive so
that's important and I wanted to tell
you about the elevated biotics they sit
in the Elum and they produce B12 B12
that's bioidentical to us that our body
uses to stop methylation problems to
stop stop our methylation issues that we
have and that's what the elevated
biotics really does okay so um if look
if the a lot of if I've gone too fast on
the show cuz I'm talking so fast just go
back to the show listen to it again
you'll probably be able to pick nuggets
out of it so you know please go back to
it if you can um
oranges oranges are incredible for the
intestinal tract the bioflavonoids the
pith all of that oranges are amazing
they move through the intestinal track
they collect bad bacteria and they feed
good bacteria and they move through and
they help us heal vitamins helps her
intestinal tract heal that's important
um the calcium and oranges is important
spinach raw spinach incredible if you
eat a lot of raw spinach you'll see your
skin starting to turn color the beta
carotenes are so powerful in spinach
that your skin starts to turn starts to
turn healthy colors healthy colors from
spinach should eat a lot of spinach
incredible for the intestinal tract
lettuce red leaf lettuce butterleaf
green leaf green leaf Roma amazing and
but you might be one of those I met ion
that feels like you can't digest lettuce
because you got nerve issues but no
one's giving you that information
doctors don't know practitioners don't
know sensitive nervous system so you
think you can't digest lettuce start
with a little butterleaf lettuce so it
doesn't rub so much on the lining so you
feel it and um Sprouts incredible
different Sprouts amazing you know why
elevated biotics grow on sprouts so if
you don't have your own garden you can't
get to an orchard and and the fall to
pick an apple to bite right out of an
apple if you can't get to a farmer's
market then you grow your own Sprouts
right on your kitchen table it will
collect elevated biotics it's a miracle
process that that's involved with God
that's involved with the universe if you
don't believe in God then the universe
if you don't believe in the universe
then the light but it's just it's it's
in it's involved with the the holy
Powers you know the holy
Source um and then uh sweet potato
incredible for the liver incredible for
the incredible for the intestinal tract
fresh mint added to smoothies salads or
make a mint tea peppermint
tea That's what I'm drinking right now
that's what you hear me sipping
peppermint tea that's incredible for you
for the for the digestive tract very
important um Ginger get some ginger tea
going I think that's what I'm going to
do later on some ginger tea top
supplements for guts health gut health
um there's a company called Enz Meda so
enzima probo you know we we list these
things also on our um on the website so
it's easy access um I like vimergy okay
vimergy v m e RG y um I like the barley
grass juice powder I find that's great
for the intestinal tract I have a little
every day I also like the chaga mushroom
powder they have because I like that for
my liver because it helps get the liver
in shape which is part of the gut health
problem part of the bile problem so
that's cool cat's claw licorice root
these are great for killing off bacteria
and viruses in the intestinal tract cats
claw and licorice root incredible really
really do help it helps move people
forward okay liquid B12 the one that I
talk about all the time the adinos silab
balamin you only heard that here when I
started the show and that was what a
year plus ago a year and a half ago
whatever it is is now a year and few
months and you're only going to hear it
here I've been teaching about that for
years that's the only one that matters
is that adoil methyl com combination so
make sure that's happening uh magnesium
golden seal periodically using golden
seal if you think you have some type of
bug in your intestinal tract use a
little golden seal don't do diet diet
Tous Earth particles it's horrible don't
do dious earth particles can read about
it in the medical medium book if you
want to know more about that that um I'm
sure somebody's upset about that but the
point is it's just it's not good it
isn't uh with intestinal tracts it gets
it's really hard on the lining so these
are some of the things we're talking
about um that are really important and
you could do this every day lemon water
it's incredible for your liver every
morning squeeze that lemon right into a
glass of water drink it 16
ounces all these things matter to
getting your gut health back stay off of
eggs stay off of soy stay off of dairy
products stay off of canola oil canola
oil it reaks havoc on the gut
lining reaks
Havoc totally does I just heard someone
just told me the other day they've been
listening to um this this new guy on the
scene with um this new guy in the scene
with gut health and seem like it was
Advanced information they got into it
and then they the person was
recommending canola oil they were saying
non GMO canol canola oil but they're
recommending canola oil I couldn't
believe my ears my ears
exploded because canola oil feeds every
manner of ill in the intestinal tract it
WS Havoc it destroys children's
intestinal tracts it feeds every type of
bacteria everything wrong it elevates
your candida because your candida is
trying to save your life so it's eating
up all the canola oil it's really a it's
just a hot mess so just stay away from
that canola oil okay so the bottom line
is you know what to do you know where to
go and we got a we got a great start
remember to go to my website
medicalmedium.com you can get the free
healing path make sure you do that just
download it simple as that check out my
lifechanging Foods book I did everything
I could to get that to you guys to get
the information to you guys you should
have seen me I was up all night many
nights getting information from Spirit
about what asparagus does about what
nettle Leaf does about what the wild
blueberry does about what what these
things what diseases what conditions
what illnesses these things conquer and
what's really in them that science
doesn't even know about don't miss out
on that get a copy and lock one down so
you have it when it comes out so you're
not waiting because not waiting or
something later on um I just want
everybody to have the information they
need because it's about you healing it's
about you getting better you know for
years I've had to hear stories of people
and and what they've gone through and it
kills me to know that they just didn't
have the information that they could
have had earlier on I have people here
now 35 years later 30 years later in
their 80s in their 70s in their 90s
feeling better than they did 30 years
ago when I freed them from the Lyme
disease trap when I freed them with
Spirits information from the lime trap
when I freed them from the trap of of of
misdiagnosis of of Ms and fibro and what
things really were and what the needed
to do and it pains me to know that we're
still in this place I'm just one guy and
I need your help I need your help
getting the information out there I need
your help too I really do I need your
help with all of it because there's
nothing worse than seeing everybody not
have information till this day in
2016 it's beyond me so let's do it
together I love you I got this gift
because it needed to be for you guys
it's not for me this gift wasn't for me
in any way shape or form hasn't done
much really for me on any level besides
at least know that it's helping you and
that's what what matters to me blessings
I love you I stand behind you it's not
your fault I believe in you
bye-bye