hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who is 10 or 20 or 30 years
to wait for answers to their illnesses
to their
symptoms and life is precious I mean you
know that uh I know that you know that
we know that there's no time to spare so
let's let get into the healing now
Today's Show is part two of the
addiction series we can call it a series
I guess but it's part two okay so and
that means if you're you know into the
show I mean you you need to you need to
get the other show or or or listen to
the other show is what I'm saying got to
go back if you missed it last week but
this is part two of addiction the reason
why it's part two is because even though
we did practically a full hour on
information about addictions and and
being addicted and in the whole bit even
though we did that um there's so much to
cover there really is to do it justice
look any show I've ever done probably
needs four shows four shows for that
topic and I do one show and they say hey
look we're going to do another one
another day down the road and it's true
because I I have done started to do a
couple of shows and and getting into
them more uh topics that we've done in
the older shows and getting into getting
into it more with more information about
it all so that's true but addiction is
the kind of thing where it just felt
look I I feel the addiction of wanting
to get part two done of getting the
information out now and not
waiting uh um four months or six months
or eight months or a year something like
that whatever it is you know hey it's
like an addiction to do this show no I'm
just kidding there but you know what I
mean I have to get this done so we have
that information in our hands because
when it comes down to addiction it's no
joke I mean look the smallest addictions
and I said this before in the in in the
last show the smallest ones can be
really hard and there's a lot of
different small ones but there's some
really heavy duty big ones and there's
nothing wrong with you know catching the
small ones seeing seeing them sometimes
for what they are because it can stop us
from getting into a big one you know
some of the things that I offer um in
the last show and this show help us
battle you know and get help us battle
that addiction or it's going to help us
break away from not getting in trouble
deeper into an addiction that's a whole
another thing because here's here's the
here's how it works with addictions it
takes everything you got anything you
can get everywhere you can get it
percentage wise 5% support here 5%
support here 5% support here because it
matters it could stop you from going
back to a drug
rehab and it it can it can because if
you don't have that support the problem
is when we're deep into addictions or we
have small addictions whatever it could
be there's this breaking point and we
just break we're just like okay that's
it you know that's that's the point I've
seen it for years for with people and
they break and they fall victim you know
they fall into it and if there was just
5% more of support in this area or this
area or something they're eating that
could
actually you know throw off that
addiction just enough where they have
enough Inner Strength or spiritually
speaking just enough spiritually just
there for them a little bit of spiritual
wisdom something that gives the other 8%
other 2% other 9% and stops The Fallout
and stops The Fallout so from the nasty
happening where oh my God now back into
this whole addictive behavior again and
I can't seem to swim out of it every
little bit counts in part one I covered
a lot of stuff on on these two big
groups one is
adrenaline okay and the other one
glucose the reason why when you're aware
of glucose deficiencies and I talked
about that part one when you're aware of
glucose deficiencies you can literally
stop yourself from falling into whatever
addiction you might be heading into
whatever might be and if you're aware of
how adrenaline plays the role or plays a
role into addiction you can be aware of
it and be like whoa wait a minute I'm
getting an adrenaline high right now and
that adrenaline high is leading me to oh
G to grab some drug or grab that alcohol
or grab that candy whatever it may be so
this is really an important show um hey
you know and and on on another note by
the way hey go to my website
medicalmedium.com check out everything
that's happening there download the
healing path what are you waiting for
seriously if you don't know anything
about it download that and start getting
into it because you're going to get a
lot of help in fact if you have any kind
of addictive behavior in your in your
past or in your life or in your future
that you think you could have or
addiction you know going on in your life
or you know someone or some family
member anything download the healing
path it's free it's free that's what it
is it's been free always was always will
be there's no charge on it it's free and
it's an intense it's basically like an
intense course but it's it's it's going
to help you move forward okay and so
that's something also Instagram we put
stories everybody's stories on Instagram
you know it's not just the Instagram
where you get this little pick and it's
cute and it's a couple words you know we
have a we have some of those too and
there's nothing wrong with that because
if you only have two seconds and you're
flipping through social media and you're
like oh yeah that's cute oh that's great
or whatever it is fine but what we do on
Instagram is we put stories okay they
they people struggles what they've gone
through their healing process them
getting better what's going on with the
you know the medical medium books how
people are into the medical medium books
and how they're changing people's lives
you might be one of them you might know
just by you know hearing this and being
like hey I'm one of them and if you're
not there yet you'll get there one step
at a time well actually it's three steps
up to two steps back okay three steps up
two steps back that means that's the
healing process because when you're
healing your body's doing all kinds of
miraculous things all kinds of
phytochemicals are moving through your
body and all kinds of different healing
energies are happening within the body
and your immune systems recalibrating
constantly as you defeat defeat the
Epstein bar viruses you beat down some
kind of bacteria as you beat down some
other toxin or some other viral
component and that's how the body
mysteriously Works always remember
that's a three steps up two steps back
um a little bit about me I was given a
gift uh at since I was and not a not a
little Christmas present not a birthday
present wasn't given that kind it was
wrapped with a bow and it was had paper
and it was for my birthday no it was
given a gift um from God um of of
hearing a voice perfectly clear someone
said to me well are you hearing God no
I'm not um I wish I was you've read my
first book I wanted to talk to God so
bad and hear God but instead I was
hearing what um what has been introduced
to me since a child as Spirit of the
most high and spirit I call Spirit was
speaking to me at age four told me my
grandmother had lung cancer when nobody
knew and and ever since then it's it was
every single day after that I had the
sight to see and hear what was happening
with People's Health but in in book one
in the first chapter origins of the
medical medium I talk about you know my
struggle with hearing the voice and
wanting to cut out that voice get
getting rid of that voice because I hear
it from the outside of the body not the
in in inside so I have no control the
voice is just always there as if
someone's talking to you uh perfectly
clear and hearing that voice you know
was always telling me what people's
struggles and their conditions and
what's happening with what's going on in
their Li lives and it was tiring it was
tiring as a child and I could honestly
say sometimes it still beats me down to
today so I I stay out of crowds as much
as I can but what I will tell you though
is I wanted to talk directly to God I
you know I I wanted to cut out the
middleman which was spirit and I wanted
God to speak to me and hear God
perfectly clear and you know and even
though I was told by spirit that the
gift obviously came from God I couldn't
hear God and that was really difficult
really difficult I'm telling telling you
a little bit about my gift um because a
well first of all I don't really talk
about it that much or go into detail too
many times but I'm talking because look
you know when we're in addictions and
we're deep into addictions and we feel
hopeless and we feel lost oh I realize
having a voice talk to you could be a
great way to pull you out of it and
that's true and that's true and I and
and but with when it comes down to
addictions having information can
replace sometimes not having that voice
so I might have been given a gift that
tells me hey don't eat that Anthony
don't do this it doesn't mean I I won't
though I've been known to to especially
as a child known to go against spirit
and do what I wanted to do you know make
my way espe ly through a teenager and um
but but regardless you know I still have
that voice that says don't do that
that's stupid
don't don't do that that's not g to help
you and but what happens is that uh when
we when we go through life we don't have
that voice it's hard to get it so we
seek it through counselors and you know
helpers in different ways and and you
know spiritual support in different ways
and we we seek it in these different
ways and you know it can be re really
helpful and you know and and so much but
but more than that because a lot of
people they they tend to you know they
tend to shy away from um help with their
addictions we know that they tend to
turn away from it I you might know you
might have done that you might have
known someone who who's done that and
you know when it happens sometimes
information you hear from other sources
and in other books or any sources can
can stick and resonate and hold and hold
true and that information kind of
replaces that inability to hear a voice
perfectly clear in the ear like I do and
so that's why this is important this is
really important to know information to
be armed with it to have a shield of
with it a shield of it
to to protect you to help protect you no
matter what no matter what illness as
well illness disease symptom whatever's
happening whatever diagnosis you've had
regardless it's good to have information
it can sometimes and many times be that
freeing moment be that
voice and it matters you know and look
I've been getting I've been the
messenger of information from Spirit and
providing that for everybody so so we
can all get a a a piece of spirit the
the spirit that I hear you know we all
have spirit in us we all have you know
we all have that that will to survive we
all have connection spiritually in
different ways and we all have our
connection to God but in the way I hear
it I like to offer that in any way I can
um the healing path is one way the radio
shows are another and the books of
course and anything I can do
um for everybody so so that's what it's
about so that's why we're here so I want
to go now into we're going to go now
into the whole heaviness of this the
lightness of it you name it that's where
we're starting now um so that's the plan
okay so I talked about adrenaline a lot
in the last show in part one and but
what I didn't Express or tell you is
that adrenaline itself is highly
addictive it is a drug it is such a drug
and so when we do things that are
adrenaline induced we get just as
addicted and sometimes more addicted to
the adren adrenaline
surges more so than the substance more
so than the candy more so than the
alcohol more so than the cigarettes more
so than the coffee coffee
yeah that's right coffee all right more
so than you know the
chocolate and I'm going to talk about
chocolate in a positive way a little bit
too not in just a negative way by saying
look you know it could be a an addiction
I just know so many people with nervous
system issues neurological symptoms and
neurological problems that if they eat
chocolate they get they literally
they're shaking they're shaking cuz
chocolate is is so neuro based I mean
it's B basically it's basically got some
neurotoxins in it as many health
benefits as it has in it it's got
neurotoxins in it I always say look if
you're really healthy and you feel great
and you don't have any confusion and you
don't have any brain fog and you don't
have any neurological shakes and you
don't have any Tremors and you don't
have any neurological pains and aches
and pains and stuff you could yeah I eat
chocolate it's got some health benefits
I'm sure packed in there but if you're
anywhere neurologically speaking at all
I would probably stay away from it now
the one thing I like about chocolate is
um for real addicts that are on opiates
and they're they're stuck you know
they're they're stuck on oxies or
they're see with a prescription or
whether that's street drugs or whatever
it is and they're really in deep and
whatever kind of drugs they're doing um
you know prescription nonprescription
whatever is going on um what happens is
chocolate can be really helpful it could
be one of that 5% 5% tool that I'm
talking about CU you need all these
different percentages that 5% tool to
actually stop you from caving on an
opioid caving on you know a drug caving
on a you know street drug pharmaceutical
whatever and of course you need the
rehab when you're in when you're in on
the drugs really heavy you need the
rehabs we know that you need to seek out
rehab you need to seek out support you
need family members supporting you we
know the whole thing you guys know about
it probably through experiences or just
anything you've read or learned or seen
even on television but and and you know
I've seen I've seen people I've worked
with people in some dire situations and
a secret one of the secret weapons if
someone's actually dry you know they're
actually dry they're off the wagget I
mean they're on the wagon however you
want to say and they're
clean chocolate can be helpful
periodically it can be a way to curve or
or stop someone from going onto back
onto a a heavy drug or heavy addiction
so that's the one positive thing I
really like about chocolate I remember
back 25 years ago in my office 25 years
ago in my office okay I had a stack of
chocolate bars the dark stuff you know
just it had sugar in it had the cane
sugar was like 69% or something or 70%
right caca the whole bid and it was
wasn't a raw chocolate it was a cooked
chocolate it was a bar all right and I
had these bars because Spirit taught me
that these chocolate bars can save
someone's life if it's the right person
at the right time that's what I was told
by spirit all right so those chocolate
bars were off limits to all the sick
people that came into my office to see
me every day 25 years ago okay that were
lined up and I mean they were lined up I
was working seven days a week s days a
week and I was working for free by the
way free I never charged I never charged
until a dear close friend said you're
going to starve to death okay I had no
car insurance I lost my car because I
wouldn't charge I had to live in the
office and I refused to charge but I was
dissolving because I couldn't even get
food or pay a bill and I
remember so you know 25 years ago I had
people lined up and they were coming in
droves and if if anybody had a symptom
that was neurological in any way whether
it's depression or anxiety or aches and
pains the whole bit those big stack of
chocolate bars they were off limit off
limits that's right because that was
just going to neurotoxic break them down
make them sicker eventually even if they
got a high off of it and they felt a
little better but let me tell you
something okay I remember a
19-year-old uh boy came in with his
mother and father all right and he was
addicted to street drugs he was addicted
to you know some kind of oxy or
something like that I don't know what it
was back then I think but it was
definitely an opioid it was it could
have been you know could have been one
of it was one of those and he was
addicted severely they went in and out
of rehab in and out of rehab constantly
the whole bit and he wasn't he wasn't
surviving this they came in out of
despera trity all right and spirit said
immediately the chocolate bars the
chocolate bars I said
ah these were big they weren't like the
kind you get in the you know the health
food store they you know the ones that
are only like 6 inches or 8 inches long
this was the big one it was like a foot
long kind of like the foot long hot
dogs you know it was like six or eight
inches you know wide or whatever it was
one of these and it was high quality
stuff and and you know had them stacked
I pulled the chocolate bar off the off
the thing and I said this is going to be
your weapon that's what I said I said
spirit says this is going to be your
weapon and the parents looked at me and
they said we're open to it because we're
desperate we've we've been through hell
and back we're losing our lives because
of this and because our son is losing
his life and he said yeah I said I said
you're you're you're you're weaning down
off your drugs you know you're working
with your your doctors on that you're
working on that whole thing I said but I
want you I want when you feel like
you're going insane and you're and
you're really struggling through that
weaning process at different times I
want you to start eating a hunk of this
chocolate and I don't mean like a little
bite I mean a hunk of this
chocolate you know I remember he he
looked at me I said look have a little
piece now I opened it up broke off a
piece and he and he was eating and he
said this is really good this is really
good and he smiled and his and and his
parents said it was the first time he
smiled in years couldn't even get a
smile out of him the first time he
smiled his name was Cole so Cole started
eating a piece and he smiled and he
looked at me and he said you know what
this this this can work I said you feel
it can work he said this can work and
the parents said I've never heard him
even say anything like that ever
throughout this whole Str process and he
said this could work and guess what it
did he was clean in fact he literally
weaned off rapidly off of the off the uh
the opioids with with the doctor rapidly
okay not only that but he was knowing
how to self-medicate with the chocolate
he was free from it his drug addiction
in 3 weeks three weeks never touched it
again again how do I know I stayed in
contact with them for years years after
that one reason why is because they
helped me out too is the parents said
why are you in this office here with you
know not able to eat not able to do
anything you helped us for free and they
were like we're just going to give you
some little donations here at the start
just so you can get some car insurance
just so you could drive I said well
driving doesn't really work for me that
great anyway because I hear Spirit as
I'm going down the street and spirit's
telling me as I'm at a stoplight what's
wrong with everybody in the left side of
me and the right side of me or in front
of me so you know but either way you
know so it was one of these things where
they said well you're going to have to
you're going to have to get something
something donations or something for
what you're doing and so you know it
kind of moved forward in my life from
there that's just just filling in that
blank if you're curious but the point is
is Cole survived he survived Spirit told
me when he walked in he wasn't going to
make it if if if they left that day
unsatisfied or confused or uncertain or
not wanting to comply or whatever okay
spirit said he's not going to make it I
had that hanging over my head and this
is 25 years ago had it hanging over my
head like a lot of things that hung over
my head with knowing too much but the
point is
is that chocolate saved his life saved
his life so as much as you see I don't
really talk about chocolate too much I
have one recipe in life-changing Foods
where there's a little bit chocolate
involved I think it's a pomegranate
recipe I don't know if you guys know it
and stuff like that and fine I think you
know I support it it's okay I have it in
the book but I'm saying if you know if
you really feel sick and you got a lot
of problems keep it minimum don't do a
lot of it you could do like the
pomegranate recipe or something or do
something once in a while don't tank it
every day or don't have it you know like
five times a week but addiction wise for
espcially coming off the heavy stuff
they heavy drugs the stuff that seems
inconceivable to break for so many
reasons more than one two three four
five reasons so many the chocolate can
be a savior in certain situation you see
that's my love hate with it but I'm just
letting you know that's why you know
certain things that's why people say to
me hey don't you love don't you love uh
don't you love this diet don't you love
this diet don't you love this diet it's
like yeah but if you got something wrong
with you not going to be good if you you
know if you got a kidney disease you
should not be eating steak or you will
die early bottom line bottom line I was
taught that by Spirit if you got a
kidney disease you got a kidney issue
you should not eat chicken or steak or
any Animal product you have to be 100%
plant-based if you have a kidney problem
on any level you have to be 100%
plant-based or you will may you may not
not make it with a kidney disease bad
kidney disease you have to back down the
animal products with kidney diseases
Spirit taught me that a long time ago so
it's not about what diet to choose it's
what's right when you're dealing with
stuff if you're suffering from viral
issues like Epstein bar anything like
that you don't want to feed the virus
why do you think I always say don't have
eggs don't have dairy don't have eggs
don't have dairy because you'll feed a
virus and stay sick because it's not
because I hate eggs that much you guys
know my history I wanted to run an egg
Shack when I was a child you know flip
flipping you know flipping omelets all
right but you know my dream never came
true I had to stick with this instead so
the bottom line is is that you know it's
about what's right for you at the time
and whether I you know like chocolate or
not at the time I knew when to take that
bar off the shelf for Cole to save his
life his spirit said that will be
medicine for his situation um so a
little bit about that just just know you
guys hanging in there get your feet seat
bels on I don't even think you even put
your seat bels on yet we got a little
ways to go um so addictions to Salt
isn't that interesting do you know
anybody that's like hey I'm addicted to
Salt I got this salt thing where can't
get enough salt can't get enough salt
okay because the reason why is because
neurotransmitters run on sodium this
doesn't mean you got to go and start
tanking down salt every day this doesn't
mean I just gave you the salt Freedom
key all right that's not what that means
I don't mind a little Himalayan rock
salt or Mountain salt or something like
that that's on your food or high quality
sea salt I get it you know Salt's okay
and and it is okay the neurotransmitters
which are talked about in part one which
get get interference from heavy metals
which cause like bulimia which cause
like anorexia you know things like that
those the heavy metals that get in the
way of like like the whole B addiction
that whole you know feeling like that I
talked about feeling that you have to
relieve yourself of every content in
your stomach the minute you eat because
what's happening there is that what
starts that what starts something like
that is the toxic heavy metals in the
brain Mercury being the number one so
when Mercury interferes with
neurotransmitters in in a certain part
of the brain it actually causes a
bulimic condition and then even if those
heavy metals are removed or something
Alters where you outgrow it brain tissue
develops you know say you're in your
youth you're you're a teenager and
you're having bulimia or something like
that volic condition what happens is
that even if your brain tissue outows
heavy metal and you get by you bypass
that you're going to be addicted to your
own adrenaline the reason why the
vomiting thing is so hard to break with
the Bing conditions the reason why is
back to what I was saying before the
adrenaline itself the adrenaline surge
you get before you vomit you can get
addicted to it's euphoric I talked about
in part one it's absolutely euphoric and
because it's euphoric it's like a a drug
all in its own in fact a powerful drug
never underestimate the power of this
drug The Surge of adrenaline that occurs
and so our addiction to Adrenaline can
happen with so many different illnesses
and I know some of you are thinking oh
that's well that's sounds crazy you know
I know someone who's who's who's bulimic
and it's because they were abused or
were yeah no of course but but it's but
that's a trigger the abuse is a trigger
you know a mental thing going on work
you're under mental abuse and whatever
it could be your sexually Abus abused
anything going on yeah that's that's a
severe trigger which then causes that
that neurological problem which you you
you you vomit but the adrenaline itself
afterwards becomes the weapon it becomes
the addiction and that's why people
struggle with that it's it's the same
thing with uh varieties of anorexia what
happens is there's an adrenaline surgent
occurs when you look at food especially
if you have if you've been abused about
food or something has happened about
food and you know you're sitting at a
table and food gets put in front of you
your adrenaline starts surging and that
adrenaline becomes your food becomes the
drug so you don't need to eat so you
literally lose your appetite immediately
because adrenaline is surging through
your system at a high rate and no one
talks about this this is information
that's never been out there anywhere it
doesn't exist it's like most of the
information that that we talk about on
the show so if your first time on the
show realize you're going to hear stuff
you're never going to hear anybody else
anywhere else um and uh and there's a
reason for that lots of reasons if you
don't know anything about me look into
me um and uh so so okay so I wanted to
cover that a little bit deeper such a
serious situation and and so the key is
is when
someone's um getting older and they
realize they got the the condition where
the Bic or anorexic anorexic condition
of any kind what happens is and I say
any kind because there's different
varieties there's no there's no one
variety of these so many different
varieties for for many reasons knowing
knowing that there's an adrenaline
addiction can save someone's life can
save someone's life remember how I said
at the beginning here you may not have
the this the voice that I hear perfectly
clear on the outside of the ear in real
time you may not have that option okay
because it just doesn't exist you may
not have the option so how about getting
the information from that voice that can
save your life or save someone's life or
somebody you know it it matters that's
what I was saying earlier so so the deal
is is that back to mineral salts with
this mineral salts play a role in in
Breaking adrenaline addictions so so
what happens is we get people that are
addicted to Salt because they're using
the adrenals too much and doesn't mean
they have
something like
anorexia or they have lmia or they have
um you know they're addicted to
something else whatever it it just means
that if they have that salt thing going
on they could get more addict addictive
in different ways for different reasons
the assault addiction is a sign that
your body's craving your
neurotransmitters are craving lots and
lots of mineral
salts and mineral salts do protect the
adrenals in ways that are unbelievable
so it's it's it's about the big time a
big part of the adrenals why do you
think I offer the adrenal snacks the
adrenal snacks a celery stick right and
so that's why we offer those adrenal
snacks like celery stick one date so
it's potassium in the date it's
micromineral sodiums in the celery
combined to the
neurotransmitter okay but not only to
the neurotransmitter to the
adrenal and um and they protect us
protecting our adrenals is a big part of
breaking addictions cuz when you don't
protect the adrenals the addictions can
come on like a like a lion like a tiger
like like a monster tigers and lions are
monsters you know what I mean like a
Monster can just come on like that and
so we have to protect we have to so back
to eating every hour hour and a half
small meals if we can eating small meals
small meals and they matter um these
little snacks all through the day celery
stick uh date okay um some berries uh
cucumber sizes um you know anything like
that I could you could look up all my my
my snacks that that I offer in so many
different ways including the blog and
everything um so mineral salts are
needed someone has the salt addiction
they're desperately needing mineral
salts to the brain into the
adrenals all right where can you get
those mineral salts too spinach leafy
greens spinach especially spinach celery
especially celery which is an herb but
spinach leafy green the sodium content
in spinach is the kind that really works
versus getting the hit from that that
Himalayan salt or or that fake salt in
junk food you know or road salt in junk
junk food those don't really cut
meaning they don't get to the neuron
they don't get to that neuron where the
electrical pulse impulse runs through it
like I explained part one and so so it's
always important to understand that um
you need real mineral salts from the
celery by the way the mineral salts and
celery are undiscovered before you all
of a sudden say oh we know sodium is in
in celery it's salty it's it's science
already has it no science doesn't sorry
they don't okay they know there's sodium
in celery they don't know it's comprised
of micromineral salt different sodiums
different variety of sodiums that aren't
even labeled listed in science and
research under the lab because nobody
cares no one wants to learn meaning and
no one it's there's not like tons of
funding going in to figure out what's
inside celery I promise you that there
isn't hundreds of millions of dollars
going into celery all right to figure
out what's in it all right but it's got
these micromineral salts comprise
subgroups com I even talk about it in
life-changing Foods a little bit um so
pick up life-changing foods you can even
get more obviously more
information um so all right let's go
let's keep on going through this so
sodium addiction because your
neurotransmitters need the salt your
adrenals need the salt well the
micromineral salts okay and then sugar
addiction because your brain needs the
glucose and your liver needs the glucose
all right and so we're going to cross
that threshold a little bit more today
on the sugar
addiction how do you stay addicted to
Sugar you meaning addicted to bad sugar
how do you stay addicted to bad sugar by
having bad fat mixed with it ice cream
that right there will will make sure
that no glucose gets to your brain and
liver you'll starve your brain and liver
and because of the fats in the ice cream
will stop that sugar that glucose from
getting into the brain and the liver see
what happens is the wrong fats and too
much
fat stops sugar from going to where it
needs to go into cells into muscles into
the heart into the brain into the liver
no one talks about that out there it's
like it's like disheartening it's all
about high fat high fat high fat high
fat no sugar high fat no sugar that's
ridiculous in a million ways I can't
even tell you guys I'm not talking about
um you know Silly lowfat diets I'm
talking about the right kind of fats the
right amounts depending on what's going
on with you depending on what's
Happening and if you got a sugar
addiction if you need you know if if you
feel like you you're on sweets all the
time you're missing glycogen and glucose
to the brain you're missing which which
all this leads to addictions sugar
addictions because you want more and
more of the bad sugar cuz the sugar
won't go in the right place so you going
more and more Donuts more and more
uh cookies more and more danishes more
and more Bagels more and more I don't
know whatever just whatever what kind of
what kind of candy do you guys like kind
of sugar do you guys like it's got to be
switched over to dates it's got to be
switched over to fruits it's got to be
switched over to raw honey sugars that
are the healthy sugars okay the healthy
sugars for sure maybe some Fuji apples
maybe some braver and apples uh maybe
some galala apples um you know maybe
some arom apples if you can find them
somewhere in an orchard somewhere else
at the end of the year but but the point
is is that the right kind of sugar can
get to the brain and stop sugar
addictions but it needs to make sure
that you're not eating the wrong kind of
fats too high in fat that you're not
like filled with with with nothing but
too many uh of the wrong omegas the
Omega-3s are really important and
getting them in the right sources are
critical when it comes down to making
sure sugar absorbs the correct way so
let's go over some of the right fats
hemp seeds that's the right kind of fat
but you don't want a whole full bag of
hemp seeds a day cuz then it's going to
be so much fat or you don't want a big
container of hemp butter it's going to
be so much fat it's going to stop the
right kind of sugar from getting to the
brain and restoring the brain so you
don't fall into any kind of addiction I
don't care what the addiction is you
could fall into it you see and making
sure the right kind of sugar gets into
the liver that then what I mean by Sugar
I mean glucose sto restoring glycogen
deposits restoring carbohydrate deposits
in the brain and in in the liver now I'm
touching upon a lot of this in this
little area because I know on part one
when I said the brain is made out of
carbohydrates I meant it it is but
there's going to be a lot there's going
to be an anger Fest because of that
because right now there's misinformation
the brain is all fat the whole thing on
the brain being filled with fat is is
complete misinformation and a total
misconception there are micro deposits
of fats in the brain that are Omega-3s
but here's the thing not just
Omega-3s okay
oils that aren't even on record one of
the oils on record in the brain is
swalling okay that's one of the oils on
record in science and research that's in
the brain is squalling all right that's
a micro that's a micro fat micro fat the
brain isn't made of fat or filled with
fat it's got these really tiny
little micro omegas hidden in certain
areas of the brain undiscovered by
science and research squalene is one of
them but that is discovered that is
discovered by science and research thank
God okay because it gives us hope but
there's all kinds of subgroups of these
Omega-3s guess where you get them
watermelon seeds when you eat your
watermelon you bite your seed and you
chew it up that's where you get it you
ready hem seeds all right and you ready
butterleaf lettuce butterleaf
lettuce in butterleaf lettuce there's
these micro fats and the there's these
Omega-3s that that do go to the brain
it's not a hunk of fat or it's not fats
it's different it's like a micro Omega
that's got a viscosity that's so thin
that it won't even constitute as a fat
or seem it or or be like it and it's not
a lot of it not a lot of it even really
small amounts that get into the brain
all right and blackberry seeds the seeds
of a Blackberry tomato seeds when you
eat your tomato there's seeds in the
tomato that seed has an omega-3
undocumented by research in science by
food research and Science and any kind
of research in science and that's the
kind that goes to the brain in said
people are loading up on all this bad
fat all kinds of crappy fat everywhere
and I'm just talking about fried grease
and all that I'm talking about what
people think is healthy fat they got it
stacked to the brim they're being told
it's healthy and they're losing the
glucose reserves in their brain and it
could set you up for some serious
Alzheimer's but not just that addictions
if you're trying to break any kind of
addiction
you don't want your diet so high in fat
so I'm giving you detailed information
so that you're not leaving here confused
thinking ah the guy he's got a different
belief on whatever no fat whole world
says fat every doctor says it now
whatever no no this is this is about
knowing what's what's right yeah and I
have the right to say that because of my
source other than that I wouldn't have
the right to say that I'd be just
swimming on the internet looking for
misinformation being like well I don't
know I guess I'll follow this but I'm
lucky I'm blessed and that blessing that
I have I want to share with you bottom
line so you understand so what that
means is that so whether you're you know
eating a meat eating diet or just a
straight vegetarian diet or vegan diet
whatever it is keep the fats low for
bringing more butter lettuce mashe MH I
talked about it in the last episode um
get some watermelon seeds you know
they're out there you can buy them and
eat them you know have them in the
watermelon some hemp seeds sesame seeds
have a little bit of it you some sesame
seeds some tahini make sure these are
mixed in whatever diet You' got so if
you're eating turkey make sure you also
have some of these things mixed in if
you're not eating any kind of animal
product make sure you got you know these
in there which you probably most likely
do because you got more room for it but
so that's and and what does this play
like a role in where and how I'll tell
you it plays a role by halting
addictions when you get enough glucose
to the brain and and the liver your
liver is not going to be starving for it
your brain's not going to be starving
for it and you're not going to go into
deep into addictions of all kinds and
you're also going to have protection
against adrenaline surges that can get
you addicted to anything addicted to
literally
anything okay very important to know
very important to know and you don't
want to be addicted to Danger okay I I I
I recently told a story about when I was
in my childhood on my street and
everybody looked at me because they knew
I would do things a little bit more
daring because I heard a voice and the
voice The Voice made me kind of what
would be um you know not unstop
stoppable but indestructible or whatever
it is and you know I was considered
superhero in my childhood because of
what the voice would say like like
diagnosing uh a friend's mom of diabetes
or whatever it was and and what what
happened is because that I also felt
like I can do anything so I would do
things that were dared devilish dared
devilish but I found during those
Daredevil causes um going against Spirit
of course I found that the adrenaline
ride in it D like Daredevil anything
jumping on a bungee cord I mean with a
bungee cord attached to you which I've
never done but anything like that you
can get addicted to Adrenaline and then
okay fine what does that mean that means
you might all of a sudden SE drinking
too much coffee and never be able to
break it you might be you might be you
know um you know doing some kind of uh
amphetamine that's prescription you
can't break it you might be able to you
might not be able to break a sugar bad
sugar diet you might not not even to
break a whatever and so whatever that is
cigarettes and so forth I want to tell
you a little cigarette pack trick
cigarette I call it the cigarette pack
trick I think I might even talked about
in one of the episodes possibly going uh
going all the way back last here maybe
maybe longer um one way to to to can
give you some information on how to
break cigarettes first of all the reason
why you're smoking cigarettes is because
cigarettes activate adrenaline they shut
off your
appetite um they they you know you ever
hear about hey when people get off of
cigarettes they get off the nicotine
they start eating more have you been
through that in your life that's because
um the adrenaline surges are calming
down you're not you're not getting that
adrenaline amped up
so one way and here another reason why
people get addicted to smoking isn't
just because of nicotine being a drug um
it's
because cigarettes make you alkaline for
a quick second a hot second they make
you alkaline so for like 30 seconds you
get an alkaline hit you get alkaline
like it's this this this super sonic
wave of bam you're
alkaline and that happens when you smoke
cigarettes
and then it goes o way acidic so you
need another you need another cigarette
and boom to get the alkaline hit then
you go way acidic then boom you get the
alkaline hit then you go away acidic and
um because the coal that's
burning when when it's in
between of being fresh tobacco and then
burnt tobacco a chemical compound
develops in between that nobody knows
about once again undiscovered by
research science that becomes so
alkaline so alkaline it's off the chart
it's this one split
0.00000000 Point whatever 1% of time
that this chemical ignites but it
ignites between the fresh tobacco and
the burning tobacco and right when it
poofs right when it ignites right there
you end up getting it into the system
and it is more powerful than 10 million
tons of nicotine that's being you know
that's being exagger exag I'm
exaggerating on that of course whatever
um but it's so amped up and it gives you
an alkaline hit to the
brain not into the lung to the brain
right away and that's out what you're
hooked on nobody knows nobody know they
think it's nicotine nicotine is just an
aspect of it it's this alkaline hit
that's what it is and so so when you
know when that's occurring it's hard to
break break it also you got the
adrenaline rush cuz every time you go
into your pack of cigarettes and you're
about to pull out a smoke a Sig your
adrenaline starts running and if it's
held back from you a little longer your
adrenaline runs more and if you can't
get to your break time at work go
outside and you know wherever you're
working whether it's you know a store or
factory or whatever you do in your life
whatever and you want to get a break or
you work in a hotel and you want to step
out in the back of the hotel or a
restaurant you want to get a cigarette
and you miss that break and you got to
wait for the next break your adrenaline
starts running more and more and more
and you won't even want food your
adrenaline's pumping through your veins
remember I told you about the two big
groups in part one if you haven't heard
part one you got to hear part one you
got to find part one I'm I'm I'm asking
you find part
one after this after this one um so what
happens is that two groups is that group
is adrenaline the other one's glucose so
you're sitting there and you're waiting
and adrenaline's running more and more
as soon as you get that cigarette out
your adrenaline's fired up and running
and then you get the hit and then boom
you're alkaline for 30 seconds that's
what happens of course you'll have also
a nicotine with TR withdrawal off of
nicotine that is real but it's only part
of it you guys part of it so what's a
good cigarette trick here's what you got
to do here's where I like chocolate once
again good old chocolate Spirit taught
me this trick for people okay all right
so you got two packs of cigarettes you
empty one of them so you empty one of
the packs so it's empty well you should
empty the other pack too because you're
only going to put 10 cigarettes in that
pack not 20 so you're going to put 10
cigarettes back in that pack the other
pack that you emptied completely you're
going to fill with little pieces of
chocolate the little pieces little
pieces from the little chocolate bar not
the big one I talked about earlier
you're going to fill that with little
pieces of chocolate you're going to
stock it okay and what you're going to
do is you're going to have every time
you get that adrenaline surge that
adrenaline surge is coming on like babbe
that adrenaline surge is is coming on
and and you know it and it's break time
and you're about to have your cigarette
or whatever it is you pull out a piece
of chocolate out of the the empty pack
that that was filled with chocolate
pieces it even soaks up some of that
nicotine believe it or not cuz nicotine
is is
aromatic and and soaks up some of that
tobacco everything else so that the
chocolate pieces and if you do this
ahead of time your chocolate pieces will
soak up a good aroma of cigarettes by
the way so you pop one or two little
pieces in your
mouth and you don't chew them up and
swallow them right away you leave them
in your mouth as long as they can until
they melt until they take their time
it's all the way to the bank you do that
all right and then the next time you
have a cigarette out of your 10 your 10
cigarette pack and you break down you
cut your cigarettes down in half you cut
them down in half you could do five
cigarettes you could be whatever daring
level you think you are start at 15
cigarettes whatever you might be doing
and you keep both packs on you another
secret weapon is never smoke
inside smoke outside always smoke
outside but that's not all only smoke
when you're
walking if you can try that one it's a
Sure Shot way to quit only smoke while
walking you'll take less drags and
you'll get less you know addictive
nicotine like we're talking about and
other stuff going on it's all going to
be calming down a bit because you're
gonna be walking you're going to be
walking off your smoking habit because
it's hard to smoke while walking it's
harder versus just standing there or
being outside so that's another
technique is you have to do the walking
while smoking thing and what you can do
is get more oxygen in you because you're
walking and yeah so that's the other
trick plus with the the you know the
packs so these are the two you know two
very powerful ways you do them combined
then yeah you got it in the bag you'll
quit smoking your adrenaline will
eventually Cal down because when you're
taking that
walk and you're smoking less cigarette
you're ad Dre adrenaline that's pumping
you're not just standing there while
adrenaline is pumping making you a
victim making you prey whatever it is
you know you you what what happens is
your adrenaline is being used as you're
walking you're using it up you're going
to be less
addicted on all levels so that's the
that's the cigarette technique cigarette
pack trick so you know that make sure
you tuck that one in for somebody you
know that smokes because you don't smoke
I know you don't smoke well I'm sure
some of you do but hey but maybe you
know someone that does all right so
that's a whole another thing right there
covered the mineral salts covered the
sweet brain stuff a little bit very
important cover the eating every two
hours to hour and a half that can help
stop any addiction any percentage you
get out of the show any trick or any
piece of information that's powerful
okay it's powerful I'm going to go
through one thing spiritually for just a
few seconds there's also spiritual
energy that's at hand with addictions
okay you know I hate going into this
land too much but we have angels and
those angels are there for us and we
need to call upon them and I don't hate
going into the angel thing I love it we
know because you know there's angel I
have two Angel chapters in you know in
my books I have an angel chapter in book
one book two uh life-changing angels I
just you know we just you guys know
about now which are really incredible to
have on your side especially even with
with eating problems or
anything but there's also negative
energies out there there's just negative
energy out there I'll just simplify it
those negative energies love addictions
love people that are trapped in
addictions be aware that there's just
psychic energy out there that there's
psychic energy out there that that that
just that just magnetically likes to be
involved with
addictions okay there's something that
um that you know how the alcohol is
called spirits you probably heard that
before but guess who started that one I
started that one 30 years ago 30 years
ago I started that one that one came
from me if you ever I always say there's
stuff that has gone around and come
around and it came from me real early on
I could even prove that one I have that
one in writing 30 years ago and what
happens is that that whole Spirit thing
involved with Spirits with alcohol why
we call them Spirits or why they've been
called spirits is for that reason
because Spirits do or an energy does
come around when we're trashing
ourselves in any way possible whatever
that might be I mean even if it's on the
most mildest level so just be aware that
you want to cut out that negativity you
want to cut out those negative energies
you don't want to let them feed off of
your addictions too as well whatever
that might be so I just wanted to pop
that at you one last second while we're
finishing up this show isn't this fun so
look um and and yesterday we talked
about you know some stress as well we
know it's Planet stress come on I got to
be honest um Planet stress is what it is
I can't be ignoring that fact planet
Earth is a beautiful place without a
doubt but because things have changed
throughout the ages in so many ways that
govern the way the world works it's it's
it's pretty stressful we know that but
we have to realize that yeah the stress
does play a massive role and anything
we've gone through the hardships the
losses and I understand and I'm behind
you 100% they play a role but let's
strengthen ourselves let's get the armor
on let's take all this information
anything you can from the show I'm going
to stick by you we're going to do the
show and we're going to keep on doing it
we're going to keep on doing it and I
stand behind you guys I love you you
know I do and you know I'm here and I'm
here I'm going to give you everything I
got I don't care I don't care what it
takes I'm going to make sure I I get
that information in the books and the
whole bit I love you dearly take care
everyone and hey on to the next show
I'll see you then bless you God bless
you