PID all kinds of different conditions
urinary tract infections are on the rise
up up up up they're not going down down
down UTI are going up up and away the
problem is with UTI they're not just
going up they're going chronically crazy
where women are
suffering
incredible suffering we're talking about
devastating suffering because of UTI
chronic I that don't want to go anywhere
because guess what the bacteria became
super bacteria it is now a super bug
that's what's happening so so many
people are dealing dealing with chronic
UTI they can't get past them they can't
move forward it's just tormenting them
and it doesn't go away same thing with
pelvic inflammatory disease that too
just keeps on tormenting women in such
ways that is
undescribable because words don't match
the suffering they are suffering with so
we're going into that UTI bladder
infections kidney infections right
urinary tract infections yeast
infections yeast infections
interesting yeast yeast yeast so funny
thing about well it's nothing funny
about it but the funny thing about yeast
infections is it's not the yeast is not
the real problem it is bacteria area
that's Underneath It All the yeast just
the immune system is so challenged in
that area that the that yeast just grows
because it's growing because there's so
much of an immune suppressive um
situation happening in the bladder area
the vaginal area all of that that the
yeast just tends to explode but it's
exploding because the bacteria is
thriving and taking over we're talking
about strep we're talking about bacteria
we're talking about super bugs a little
bit we're going into that we're talking
about UTI we're going to talk about
solutions for UTI as well so that's
going to be really helpful for a lot of
people that are dealing with UTI you
don't want to miss this episode this is
an important one I'm even reading a
little bit out of Liver Rescue a little
bit out of cleanse to heal don't miss
this do you know anybody struggling or
suffering with UTI or have a history of
UTI and now they have acne now they got
sibo years later they get sibo now they
get PID now they got acne again then
they got an ear infection then they got
a sore throat and a strep throat problem
M yeah exactly strep strap strap strap
strap strap strap exactly sibo they
never talk about what bacteria it is
that creates small intestinal bacterial
overgrowth but it's strep our good old
friend strep hey strep how are you fine
doing okay living in everybody's
lymphatic vessels living in everybody's
pores living in everybody's throats
living in everybody's butts yep you got
it that's what happens strep is always
hanging around people's anuses it's
hanging around the rectums all the time
that's where strep loves to be it's
around everybody's throat it's in their
mouth every day people have more than
one variety two variety they'll have
three variety four variety five variety
six variety seven variety they'll have
10 varieties of strep some dormant some
lowkey some much more serious creating
everything from acne to sty yep sty
thrush all that thrush on their tongue
just causing problems so that's the
whole thing there we're going into strep
and we're going into UTI but let's hit
the UTI problem because that is critical
because I'm seeing it more and more
years ago I didn't see it like it was
today you'd have that antibiotic
resistant UTI you'd have that out there
I saw it out there okay but now it's
unlike it's ever been it's never been to
this degree I called it though and I saw
I've written about it that these bugs
would actually take off to such a degree
where they'd be antibiotic resistant but
not just Mera not talking about Mera I'm
talking about plain old Jan
strep not Mera this is important to know
this is a really good episode and we're
going to talk about Solutions too which
are critical um let's get into it a
little bit the antibiotic dilemma do you
guys uh love antibiotics antibiotics are
the leading treatment for
UTI antibiotics are the leading
treatments for UTI you know what that
means that means decade after decade of
bugs that are actually becoming
immune to the
antibiotic it's how it works and then
that bug spreads to another person and
so that person receives that bug and
then now they have an antibiotic
resistant bug they get sick and then
they go to the doctor the doctor gives
them an antibiotic again and now their
bug is in them that's already antibiotic
resistant is now even becoming more
antibiotic
resistant and
the and then it keeps on going on and on
and on and on so that's what's
happening it's not like the old
days and then the antibiotic kills the
weakest bacteria but the strong survives
so let's do this
okay I prepared for this one here we go
okay you got a bacterium right here you
got a bacterium right here got a
bacterium right here and a bacterium
right here and I'll even put another one
right here and one more right here so
these are
bacteria okay so here we are take a look
you guys these are inside the bladder or
the kidneys so let's make a bladder
here okay there we are we got a bladder
right and in that bladder is a whole
bunch of bacteria and strep bacteria is
what it is okay so antibiotics are used
all of a sudden boom we take an
antibiotic the antibiotic is coming
through right now here it goes there it
is the antibiotic coming
through there we go can't really see
this good but there it is Boom the
antibiotic came through then now we get
some dead
bacteria this one explodes Boom the
antibiotic killed
it boom Another One explodes boom
Another One
explodes interesting this one just gets
maed that bacterium gets maed this one
just gets
weakened am I yelling this one gets
weakened okay okay this one doesn't get
harmed at
all all right we got a weakened
bacterium we got a maed bacterium
damaged but they survive they survive
and they provide information now against
that
antibiotic they hold the key to survival
against the antibiotic that was given to
them think about that right now right
and then you got one that survived it
completely that also holds information
but it's completely unharmed in fact it
seemed to do good with the antibiotic
that one little bug right there drank
those
antibiotics consumed them it didn't hurt
them and now this one bug right here is
getting
stronger nice and strong now now it's a
nice strong bacterium you see this the
maed ones not as strong but they provide
information and they stay alive is what
they do they too survive it and they're
a they survive it in the aftermath
they're still hanging around okay and
then another one too at the same time
still survived it and it's it's there
right so now you got three bacterium but
three different bacterium same bacteria
but three different experiences three
different strengths and three different
injuries one not injured two one maed
one injured there's a problem with that
though because then as it's producing
more bacteria is being produced okay
which happens more and more
bacteria is being
produced right here's your bacteria
right
here and these bacteria are getting
stronger and producing the weak
ones okay want to be as strong as the
strong one so the weak ones become even
stronger than the original strong one
that wasn't even affected by the
original back antibiotic okay this is
important the weaker
ones gain strength the ones that were
maimed and injured by the an antibiotic
keep that in mind they were maimed and
injured at and they
now okay they strengthen they rise above
it they gather information from their
injuries they learn how to not get
injured again by the antibiotic they
become stronger than the one that
survived completely without injury at
all and that's a problem all on its own
okay so now you have very strong
bacteria here's the thing
they get stronger they get stronger and
then all
right and then a new infection
occurs they get stronger they override
the immune system of the person drops
exactly the immune system
drops there's another bladder right
there okay so white blood
cells for some reason aren't as strong
in that person their own white blood
cells aren't doing the jobs they need to
do they get triggered they get exposures
something happens there and then the
bacteria rise up and get stronger and
now we have a new infection they
reproduce I'm going to make a whole
bunch of them here if you guys with me
you're following me right now okay and
then the new antibiotic comes through
they're sick again and then a new wave
of antibiotic comes through they're at
the doctor's office they got a new
UTI and then boom here comes the
antibiotic it's rushing
through
okay and what happens is all these new
bacteria
right they don't budge everybody's happy
they're stronger they supersede the
antibiotic and then the doctor gets
pissed the patients gets the patient
gets pissed stays sick the doctor's
pissed and then they change up the
antibiotic get ready for this the new
antibiotic gets then prescribed so here
comes the new antibiotic coming through
and this is what sucks right here really
sucks it comes
through and then it mimes
and injures a whole bunch of them that's
right this one gets maimed this one gets
injured this one gets maimed this one
gets injured this one gets almost killed
completely this one just gets slightly
injured this one never gets touched okay
that's
fine here's the problem now we got a
whole bunch of brand new
streps and those brand new bacterium
strep
bacterium have
information and survived a new
antibiotic that is not good they
survived a new
antibiotic they're still alive now they
have information from the original
antibiotic how to survive survival
instincts in the bacteria and now they
got new information from the new
antibiotic survival mechanisms kick in
in that bacteria the
bacteria does not want to lose so it's
going to now
supersede and then boom the next phase
happens okay you got a patient that's
getting a little better again the
patient's getting a little bit
better I really can't stand this
whiteboard
yep all right new bacteria it's
reproducing
here we
go once again immune system drops in the
patient the patient was getting
better a month later two months later at
some point okay there's the bladder
again I'm just doing a bladder you do
kidneys you can do you know urethras
whatever
so all
right playing around markers here so we
got a new bacteria
this bacteria has information from two
antibiotics it has survived two
antibiotics yes it has indeed and it has
survived the person's immune
system that's the whole point it
survived their immune system and it
survived the antibiotic involved in
their immune system okay both with the
immune system working on that working
with that antibiotic and both with that
antibiotic okay so get ready for this
person get sick again they got another
UTI it's pretty darn serious they're in
pain they got a fever they don't know if
they got kidney infections bladder
infections and here we go there might be
some blood in the urine
right goes to the doctor doctor
prescribes an antibiotic the same one
that they used last time so you fill
your prescription now you're taking it
antibiotic runs through the body it's
triggering the immune system immune
cells you're trying to work with it it's
trying to work with everything it's
going
through okay and this time now with this
new
antibiotic it's only killing off this
one only killing off that one only
killing off that one that one that one
that one but this one right here is just
injured that one's injured that one's
injured that's one's injured injured
maed and we got the whole thing over
again all the maed and injured ones say
I'm not going to do this anymore I'm not
going to let this antibiotic this new
antibiotic rule the roost and clean us
out we have to Rise Above This and we
have to get stronger and then what
happens is the new reproduction of that
of that bacterium is even stronger so
that the next phase of the antibiotic on
the fourth round which happens all the
time and sometimes it's a sixth round
sometimes it's a seven another one's
prescribed here we
go and now none of the bacteria are
budging at all got a fever there's blood
in the
urine kidneys are inflamed they have to
give steroids out now so now it's
steroids plus the new antibiotics so
here we go doctors's got to play the
game again and here it
comes right now it's time
to
use now it's time to use the new
antibiotic all right so we got this
bacteria that bacteria that bacteria
that one right there that one right
there there we go here's all the
bacteria yep we got another bladder
we'll just do bladder here we go there's
the
bladder now the doctor has to bring in
the super antibiotic one with a lot of
side effects one that causes a lot of
problems one that also says a lot of
terrible thing things on the side effect
package the little roll out and here we
go here it
comes boom boom boom boom boom boom bo
boom I'm taking my
antibiotic
right the super
antibiotic the Super One a change
up
okay injures this guy kills off this guy
mes this guy injures this guy kills off
this guy doesn't even touch that guy
that guy and that guy now you got three
guys here not even being touched by the
super
antibiotic but you still got injured but
not dead
bacteria injured but not dead bacteria
you got some dead
bacteria but too many
injured too many
injured and too many maimed but still
survived and others that didn't even get
affected and then we got a big problem
so now they reproduce
again after the Super antibiotic went
through they reproduce this time we're
in trouble now big trouble here we we
are because they use the super
antibiotic again and then they have that
running through and now these
bacteria they have messaging they Cod it
they have information they're
superpowered they do not not give up at
this point they have information of four
to five different
antibiotics and they don't want to budge
anymore they put their foot down they're
done that means they don't budge so then
the doctor has to run another
antibiotic brings that one
through and now the patient is just
chronically sick chronically suffering
and chronically sick a super buug has
been
born the patient has the Super buug
whether it's a male
female the patient has a super buug and
then the patient has a
relationship or the patient is a chef
working in a restaurant who cuts their
finger and then bleeds on three
different meals that you can't really
tell because a lot of chefs they wear
the black gloves they put the black
gloves on they throw a bandage on put a
black glove on there's still blood
everywhere and they get working really
quick they wipe their hands and or it's
a relationship sexual interactions of
some kind and then that super bug now
gets transferred onto someone else with
all this information and all this
messaging and that information or the
shopping
cart shopping cart's a big one I've been
saying this for decades you guys heard
me say it years ago before c came around
the shopping cart is a big one okay lots
of different bacteria on there lots of
strep lots of Staff lots of C diffs L
lots of Mera lots of other stuff too but
the strep is just crazy on the shopping
cart handles crazy that's how much is on
there okay so with that if they swabbed
if they did a swab in a p tree dish if
they did that like off the shopping cart
handles you wouldn't believe what would
grow wouldn't believe it so you're
sitting there with a shopping cart
handle you're not using handy wipes
you're not doing an alcohol handy wipe
across the handle you're you don't
you're you're not thinking about
anything you don't care about anything
maybe you're just somebody that thinks
that your immune system will get
stronger because of it and you won't
have to worry because hey who cares I
can just eat bugs and have bugs all over
my skin it's just all that whole thing
that philosophy you know that philosophy
right it makes you stronger you become
immune to it or something like that
that's not true that's not how it works
the more exposure you get to these bugs
the more exposure you get the more bugs
you get the more problems than you have
and then that it doesn't work that way
where we're just all of a sudden hey I'm
immune to everything and that's what I
want all these bugs no it does not work
like that tell that to someone who got
you know Herpes Simplex 2 tell that to
someone who's got something else that
they caught from somebody it doesn't
make you stronger it's not how it works
it's a hassle it's all a hassle so then
that strep then that super bug gets into
somebody else through a shopping cart H
handle through a public bathroom off the
toilet seat off the dispenser whatever
it is
and they get it and they get the bug
that's superpowered it is a super
version of itself it already knows all
the
antibiotics it already knows about them
all that means when you come down with
something or you get sick or something
happens and now you got a UTI whatever
it may be you go to the doctor and the
process starts all over again but the
doctor starts giving you that first
round of antibiotics and it won't budge
so easy especially if you have a comprom
rised immune system and you're already
struggling with something it won't
budge and they're just like why do you
have these UTI all of a sudden or say
you know someone has someone has sex
with somebody else and you know is
unprotective even if it's even if it's
protected sex it's still easy to
transfer these like these um these
streps and this bacteria and all a
sudden now there's a new UTI somebody
has that never had before and now but
it's an anti-resistant it's a what is it
antibiotic resistant is what I mean
version of itself that has all this
information that's coded that's got all
this Intel that survived all these
antibiotics that knows them well so now
we have another person with a super bug
and just as Grim as it sounds it's not
Grim when you know how to heal and use
tools and that's the thing about medical
medium information it's the one place
where people that are the sickest come
to find answers and it's not all that
biohack [ __ ] out there that's going
on it's real it's the real deal it's
real answers real information on how to
heal what to do and that's medical
medium information and that's how it's
always been people can be jealous out
there and they can rip it apart or say
what they want about it it Stills the
most people healed in the world to the
most chronic conditions and this is why
knowing about this information not just
biohacking crap on social and just this
this this and try this it's for people
who have been there and done that
they're seasoned and they know so what
happens is there is hope so when these
super bugs the super strep gets to
somebody else and they're fighting these
these battling these UTI and it seems
hopeless there are women out there with
chronic UTI every day of their lives
going into overactive
bladder going into chronic UTI
overactive bladder pain in their kidneys
pain in their back PB and then it tack
on acne and sore throats and sibo
because they all get a sibo diagnosis
eventually tuck on to all all those in
there and they're living with these
Super Bug streps it's happening more and
more out there and there are more people
living with this than ever before now
there is an up surge that's getting out
of control a serious upsurge and that
upsurge is not going to stop it's going
to keep on going unless people know how
to arm themselves and take care of
themselves and know how to fight feed
their body what they need do the right
things giving their bodies what their
need so they can they can beat this
Super Bug stuff down because it's no
joke right now cuz people are passing
these along and it's out of control
people need the right information
there's cleanse the heel right here in
front of me and in cleanse the heel it
got pelvic inflammatory disease right
and even you know PID right and even
prostatitis got that there too and I'm
talking about bladder infections UTI all
of that in here so it's cleanse to heal
people need this book they need the
information I have Liver Rescue in front
of me right here I want to read a little
bit about this for a couple of minutes
if you guys don't
mind the story of
strep is what I was just telling you
guys that's the story of strep right now
in this modern day what people are
dealing with and how bad it is okay most
people strep starts in childhood they
get the ear infections to get the strep
throat the sore throats it starts
earlier on it strep passed down from the
parents a lot of times and it's strep
that's passed down to the parents and
then the children the B the children
have it and the children pass it to each
other in
school and so it's it's strep being
passed around everywhere that's what it
is but that could be fine in some ways
but in others it's antibiotic resistance
STP that's being passed around going to
each person then that takes us to the
next level of understanding which I want
to go to
now which is the immune system okay
that's the next thing every time SHP
enters into somebody and battles our
immune cells and it survives so anytime
SHP enters into each person and it goes
into war with our immune cells right
here goes into war every time that
happens and there's a battle and the
strep survives it has information so
when that strep is passed on to another
person it's not just
antibiotics it's also relationships with
the immune system of the person it was
in this whole time so then when that STP
gets passed on to somebody else it's
getting passed on to somebody else with
information on that person's immune
system information of how it survived
the battle with that person's white
count
and so when that strep is in the new
person the strep now has a way to beat
immune systems it goes into another
person another person's immune system
goes up against it there it goes it's in
battle the the bacteria survives why do
you think people keep on getting acne
all over again they still have some
strep surviving what do you think they
keep on getting the UTI over again the
bladder infections the overactive
bladder right that one to OAB they keep
on getting these things and then the
thigh and then the sore throats and then
the strep throat periodically and then
the earaches and ear infections or they
get exposed to new strains and that's
another story and we'll go into that too
the strep has information of the
person's immune system information of
the antibiotics the other person took
they take it to the next person the next
person's immune cells go against it they
go into battle what survives is Boom the
bacteria again some of it survives it
gets passed on to a new person with now
immune system information from two
others now here's where it gets really
intense that
bacteria can go through a 100 people and
gather information from their immune
systems of that 100
people that's how super bugs are made
it's not just the antibiotic over
usage and then the UN and then not being
taught how to heal and get rid of the
bacteria
naturally it's also information from
each person's immune cells to each
person and that bug becomes one
Unstoppable brutal bug and that's why
there are women out there young women in
their 20s and in their early 30s that
are in years on a daily basis and they
are so sick and they have so much
UTI chronic UTI going on they have so
much overactive badder UTI kidney
infection sore throats molay tired
fatigue everything else Under the Sun
with it and they're suffering and
they're bleeding they're on antibiotics
again their stomach's being ripped a
shreds from the
antibiotics then they get their sibo
diagnoses and it's all around the same
old thing more antibiotics for that and
they're suffering
and then
because they got a strep inside of them
that could have been through a hundred
people that was passed on to them one
way or another and that strep is smart
it's smart it knows the immune cell
information from dozens of people it
knows the antibiotic information from
dozens of people and it carries it with
it and we have to know how to destroy
that bacteria and how to kill it and
what to use that it is not immune to
because that's the key right medical
medum information is always about the
cause because guess what they didn't
know strep was a UTI problem they didn't
know strep was other problems they knew
about strep throat but they didn't know
strep created acne they didn't know it
created sty did they didn't know it
created UTI by the way that's medical
medium
information but it does it's just coming
out people are poaching it and it's
going out there and it's just getting
out there every day just like you guys
are probably seeing because I know you
guys are telling me you see it every day
we see it every
day but the point is is that bacteria we
have to learn how to kill it you have to
identify it and know there's a cause
behind your PID there's a cause behind
your
UTI there's a cause Behind these
things and there's a way to kill and
destroy kill and destroy the
bacteria even bacterium that is
antibiotic resistant and knows a crap
ton of people's immune systems that
understands all these people's immune
systems that that bacteria was in all
this
time understands it is an expert at
immune systems because that's what the
bacteria becomes it becomes an expert at
everybody's white count immune cells all
of it it knows it all it's been in too
many people it hasn't been destroyed and
it's gotten stronger and stronger now
it's a super bug and that's where it's
at and that's happening now every day
and we think these super bugs are bad
now wait till the next round of UTI 10
years from
now and all the young men and women it's
going to be like nobody's ever seen ever
seen it's going to be that bad it's
going to be bleeding is normal
constantly bleeding catheters constantly
on catheters that's another thing too so
the UTI are getting to a point where all
these young women are are literally
living with
catheters that's how bad it
is and so we have to be mindful and
understand that there is a way to beat
it and there is a way to do we're going
to talk about that in a little bit but I
want to read a little if I
can okay maybe most people strep starts
in childhood maybe even pass down from a
parent at conception yes a newborn can
enter the world at strep already in her
or his
system a child can also get strep from
daycare or school and it's easily passed
from child to child it really is as well
as adult to adult because strep is a
type of bacterium antibiotics do seem
like the obvious choice to treat it but
here's the crucial point that I talked
about to know about strep long ago
before antibiotic Revolution before
antibiotics long ago you guys this is
really interesting right here before the
antibiotic was born long
ago strep used to be one strain of
bacterium strep was one strain of
bacterium which takes us to this next
part right here and now this is really
important okay this is
important very
important I'm going to bring this around
for a second
okay all right so
five antibiotics ago 10 antibiotics ago
10 different people ago the bacteria
look like
this right but then it changes a new
strain is is is created along
with the superbug power it alters and
turns into a different bug now we have
the old
strain that's way in the past and it's
and other people we got the new
strain and there it
is right there that new
strain becomes another new strain
eventually another new strain another
new strain but here's the thing if you
pass on this strain that it became to
another person through sex or through
drinking from somebody's glass or from
being in a bar and eating something or
whatever you're doing in a restaurant or
on a shopping cart in a shopping cart or
in a public bathroom or so many other
ways you can do
this if you pass on that strep bacteria
to somebody in that in that strain to
them they'll have that
strain and they may keep that strain but
it'll be that strain okay these in this
person can still alter and become a new
strain in a few years that new strain
can be passed on to another person and
then they'll have that
strain
see that's how it
works men can get UTI too and they do
but they don't have a cycle men do not
have
menstruation they do not have a cycle so
they don't have the immune system
lowering thing that happens so what
happens is when a woman goes for
menstration and she has her cycle her
monthly cycle immune system drops and
80% of our immune system goes to the
reproductive system that's medical medum
information 20% stays around the body
for the rest of the body the
reproductive system is the number one
Focus that time a month where it's the
number one Focus for the immune system
think about that right so because of
that the immune system is so focused
around the reproductive
system okay that it's easy to catch
strap
orally very easy to catch it orally or
in the eyes where the immune system
isn't there to destroy it right off the
running so if there's some kind of
relationship or a shopping cart like I
said or a public bathroom and something
goes in the eye or something gets in the
mouth whatever it is during the cycle
80% of the immune system isn't around
the mouth it's not there so for a woman
it's not here it's down here so the
strep can easily start its it's
beginning in the mouth in the throat and
the so for so forth in that area so that
happens too all right let's go into just
a little
bit all right here's the crucial point
to know about strep long ago before the
antibiotic Revolution I'm reading out of
Liver Rescue if you guys never seen
these books you don't know about these
books you should get both of them go to
Amazon get both be the best thing you
ever did become an expert about your own
health learn how to
heal become a true expert a true expert
not a
biohacker SHP is not and never was a
super buug in the past so strep was
never a super buug it's not designed to
be a Super Bug originally it was never
meant to be one we are forcing it to
become a super buug
okay it's much more forgiving strep than
ever than anything else was okay and
it's original state going back many
years ago it was much more forgiving
it's a forgiving
bacterium it's not as unforgiving as
merca it's not as unforgiving as Mera so
that is something to understand cith and
Mera can be even much more brutal much
more brutal of a superbug stre still
even with its worst superbug mentality
whatever it's more superbug
creation it doesn't hold the power as
like Mera and what MCA can turn into
some kind of flesh eating bacterium that
just becomes a super super bug so I want
that clear so people
know so if they got strep and they're
living with strep they're living with
all these symptoms you can turn it in it
can turn naturally into a Super Bug over
time because it's force-fed the
antibiotics it's force fed
in the way I was saying all those things
but it won't get to like a Mera level at
merca's worst so the different varieties
of Mera there's all these different
varieties of Mera did you know there's
thousands of varieties of Mera and some
of the top tier varieties of Mera that
are just like God awful and they kill
people is what they do and they give
them sepsis and then they die they like
the top tier of the worst shp's not
there so I wanted that to be
clear but SHP is no longer one strain I
want to go back to that a little bit
it's no longer one
strain there are so many varieties of
strep at this point over the
decades strep being a victim of
antibiotics it found a way to survive to
adapt adaptation didn't just mean
getting stronger it meant mutating and
spawning different strains and varieties
and that's what strep does it's the
ultimate like spawner of new varieties
of bacteria all strep all the same
family but it's the ultimate see heal
with Mariana says over there on IG I
healed my UTI back in 2002 with the
herbs and supplements you recommend in
cleanse the heel book amazing is it
2020 let see what it is um healing with
Victoria I used to be on an antibiotic
once once a month for UTI I haven't
needed them in four years thanks to your
protocols thanks to you and so because
medical M information destroys UTI just
destroys them so one thing about mm info
if you know how to use it and you use it
right you can annihilate so many
different strep
conditions Shamrock over there in IG
this was me with IC whoa I see for 20
years of extreme bladder pain until I
found medical meum information thank you
aw
incredible
incredible over here Heidi on IG before
medical medium I had chronic strap
throat utti and kidney infections I now
have no pain and haven't had to run to
the doctor in many years this info Works
quote from you amazing and I will add to
that quote from you it does work it does
work it does it has a track record of
working that's the power of it you know
biohackers an informationist messing
around all these different things out
there on social can do that for people
this information does and that's why I'm
a messenger of s so's information
because it saves lives Maria over there
on YouTube great topic I used to get UTI
all the time and they are so painful
it's much better thanks to aw and S so
incredible let's go into a little bit of
protocol talk a little bit too let's
just double check we covered some stuff
right here let's talk about like the
different strains a little bit longer
the spa the different strains I want to
go into that over there on YouTube
wondering wishing good to see you
antibiotics used to be the go-to for our
family after medical meeting protocols
viy zinc micro Ginger turmeric shots
cat's claw well I love that cat's claw I
love that cat's claw in celery juice no
more we are free from the constant
doctor appointments thanks s so and
medical
medium it's going to get me
emotional the because you know when you
heal it is everything Maria over there
on YouTube great topic I used to get UTI
oh I saw that one already great Chrissy
over there and I think um twitch Stitch
Chrissy I was in tears every time I had
a UTI I can't imagine the amount of
people that are going through it and
they go through it on levels that are
just devastating it's become like Super
Bug now level and it's brutal and so
many people suffer from it their guts
get ripped to shreds from all the
antibiotics they have to take they're on
steroids almost all the time and it's
brutal along the way strep got
classified as having a group a and a
group b yeah the medical world now
identifies strep all the way through
Group
H Group H though as you read about in
the acne chapter cuz acne is Strep
caused by the way you guys it is it's
medical medum info but it's strep caused
that the population carries there are
also strains within the known groups
that are yet un that are yet
unidentified and undocumented so here's
how medicine
works medical research and science works
like this they've classified some of the
bacterium the strains but they haven't
classified all of them haven't even
scratched the surface so the bacteria
out there that they haven't even
documented classified got their hands on
or anything like that and that's the
scary thing it's even
scarier yep even a gifted and talented
lab technician discovered that even if a
gifted and talented lab technician
discovered that there were more strains
and groups of strep that weren't
currently known the Breakthrough would
go unrecognized the scientists would not
be able to find funding for this area of
critical medical importance because
right now funding is too tied up in
misled areas like how genes relate to
disease so yeah you guys let's go into
this a little bit now some protocol
stuff I'm in cleans to heal if you don't
have the book I feel bad for
you get the book get the book get the
book I mean you don't have to spend a
$5,000 program on how to walk Barefoot
on your on your lawn
you can do that but it won't make your
UTI go away keep that in mind you can do
earth and you can do like you can would
not wear shoes and you can watch the
sunrise in the morning and you can angle
your bed a certain way in your room the
way the sunrises and sun sun sets but
none of that's going to get rid of
somebody's de debilitating acne sty UTI
bladder infections kidney infections
P it's just not going to happen
hardcore stuff that has to work then you
can do all that stuff for fun the other
stuff I was mentioning okay danan 144 on
IG I was in so much pain for nine months
with interstial cystis celery juice
saved my
life yeah and that's why when someone
says celery juice sucks or celery juice
isn't what it is or something out there
that's it's actually such a disservice
to the chronically ill it's so sad when
celery juice literally has turned lives
around saved lives yeah I know all right
let's go into it pelvic inflammatory
disease PID right here talks about UTI
it's in here right here cleanse the
heel all right the true cause bacterial
infection of one or more strains from
over 50 groups of
strep there are different levels of
PID it's like different levels of UTI
different levels to all the different
things different levels to
sibo incredible okay so let's go into
the protocol right starts out
interesting fresh celery
juice I still have some left right
here if you guys want any I still got
some right here we're in aw's kitchen
so fresh celery juice it says work up to
32 oz daily and cleanse the heel work up
to 32 o daily I did my celery juice and
it didn't work I did my Celler use and
it didn't work I was doing 4 ounces it
says work up to 32 o what page and Maria
says what page 537 and cleanse the heel
so page
537 get your book
out
okay second thing in here aloe
vera aloe vera for UTI for
PID for overactive bladder too aloe vera
two or more inches of fresh gel skin
removed two or more inches of fresh gel
skin
removed all right what's the next thing
on the list barleygrass juice
powder another thing on the list cat's
claw very interesting cat's claw
critical for
UTI critical for
PID critical for men that are having
prostatitis right there cat's claw it's
a big one you'll hear more about cats
claw every day out there and more about
cats claw every day it's the medical
medium information that got that out
there catclaw was around it's been
around obviously but using it for the
things that it's being used for for
protocol false is medical medium
information originally for cat's claw
curcumin and there you go that's another
one de Manos yeah de Manos is
great but you need more than deos if
someone's dealing with UTI and pib and
some of the things I'm talking about
here you need more than de Manos de
Manos is in here it's part of the
protocol and sometimes you'll hear out
there like a practitioner or somebody
will say de Manos use that for your UTI
it's like okay but what about about the
golden
seal what about the cat's claw where's
that what about the celery juice de
Manos Dem Manos drink cranberry juice
drink cranberry juice that's great and
all that's great but guess what it's not
enough for the kind of UTI that are
happening out there every day right now
no way it's not enough but it is when
it's compiled with other things it helps
right right
and the books have the amounts to C but
you customize I talk about the amounts
in here but you
customize over there n g Elena I had
several severe PID which went to left
kidney too o I was told I need
hysterectomy and will be disabled heal
that with mm now all I need is to heal G
AOS or it says GBS AOS
all right ibrite it's another one right
there golden
seal golden
seal
UTI golden
seal why do I do
that people just they get lost they
don't hear something they don't know
they get a UTI next month don't even
remember so I'm hoping if you're one of
those people you'll be able to save
yourself
UTI golden
seal so I talk about here dosages
everything okay remember the quality of
supplements matter so check out medical
mem information but the quality of the
supplements
matter critical I talk about that in the
supplements chapter in cleanse the heel
make sure you look at that really
important another one
strep UTI PID overactive bladder all
these lemon
bomb UTI lemon bomb okay ready UTI
licorice
root licorice root ETI nettle
Leaf
incredible and there's more in here too
that you can play with cust cize
yourself it's here the information that
s SOC brought to us to save people's
lives I get it fun you know surfing the
net surfing
social whoa let me cold plunge you know
whoa let me walk Barefoot it's all great
whatever cold punching is not good it's
not good for people chronically sick all
that stuff but either
way I'm talking about fixing problems
and that's the key and that's what the
medical medium information does fixes
problems keep that in mind Amy over
there on IG friend with
Ms was on
Walker only 30 years old drank fresh
celery juice daily and could walk again
after about four
weeks I love you guys incredible oh
gotta tell you one thing though medican
podcast at Apple podcast mercury in fish
and fish oil don't miss it mercury in
fish and fish oil where does the Mercury
go where does the Mercury go do not miss
the medical be podcast at Apple podcast
you guys if you subscribe to it on
Apple and you're not getting the you
know notifications check anyway check
the podcast so you can see the new
episodes you may not be getting notified
I see this happening just a whole bunch
of people so check out the medical Me
podcast at Apple podcast mercury and
fish and fish oil where does the Mercury
go get on the medical medium newsletter
too so you can learn about what's
happening because I am going to be
somewhere in
person I'm going to be somewhere in
person earlier this year I'm letting you
know this year so I'm going to be like a
little later this year I'm going to be
in person I'm going to sign some book if
you got if you got an old medical medium
book bring it up to me bring it up to me
I'll sign it I'm letting you know okay
definitely I'm really excited about that
I'm just trying to figure out the
logistics to to really know exactly
where I'm going to be but it's going to
be LA and then the location I'm working
out the logistics on the location I'm
hoping I see you guys there if not maybe
another time in the world I don't know I
never did a book signing it's the first
official book signing ever in the
history of all the medical medium books
and um so I mean you might want to be
there and bring your book so I can sign
it join the medical medium
telegram as well I might leave a message
tonight and I fact I think I will leave
a message tonight on
telegram okay and join the Instagram
broadcast channel I'm going to leave
something there too have you actually
joined the the broadcast channel okay
it's called the mm inside scoop mm
inside scoop the medical medium
broadcasting channel I'm going to leave
a little message on there and I'm going
to leave a telegram God
willing God willing I will leave a
telegram you guys I love you much and
thanks for being here today I can't wait
to see