UTI PID all kinds of different
conditions urinary tract infections are
on the rise up up up up they're not
going down down down UTI are going up up
and away the problem is with UTI they're
not just going up they're going
chronically crazy where women are
suffering
incredible suffering we're talking about
devast dating suffering because of UTI
chronic UTI that don't want to go
anywhere because guess what the bacteria
became super bacteria it is now a super
bug that's what's happening so so many
people are dealing dealing with chronic
UTI they can't get past them they can't
move forward it's just tormenting them
and it doesn't go away same thing with
pelvic inflammatory disease that too
just keeps on tormenting women in such
ways that is
undescribable because words don't match
the suffering they are suffering with so
we're going into that UTI bladder
infections kidney infections right
urinary tract infections yeast
infections yeast infections
interesting yeast yeast yeast so funny
thing about well it's nothing funny
about it but the funny thing about yeast
infections is it's not the yeast is not
the real problem it is
bacteria that's Underneath It All the
yeast just the immune system is so
challenged in that area that the the
yeast just grows because it's growing
because there's so much of an immune
suppressive um situation happening in
the bladder area the vaginal area all of
that that the yeast just tends to
explode but it's exploding because the
bacteria is thriving and taking over
we're talking about rep we're talking
about bacteria we're talking about super
bugs a little bit we're going into that
and we're talking about UTI we're going
to talk about solutions for UTI as well
so that's going to be really helpful for
a lot of people that are dealing with
UTI you don't want to miss this episode
this is an important one I'm even
reading a little bit out of Liver Rescue
a little bit out of cleanse the heel
don't miss this do you know anybody
struggling or suffering with UTI or have
a history of UTI and now they have acne
now they got sibo here's later they get
sibo now they get PID now they got acne
again then they got an ear infection
then they got a sore throat and a strep
throat
problem yeah exactly strep strep strep
strep strep strep strep exactly sio they
never talk about what bacteria it is
that creates small intestinal bacterial
overgrowth but it's STP our good old
friend strep hey strep how are you fine
doing okay living in everybody body's
lymphatic vessels living in everybody's
pores living in everybody's throats
living in everybody's buts yep you got
it that's what happens strep is always
hanging around people's anuses it's
hanging around the rectums all the time
that's where strep loves to be it's
around everybody's throat it's in their
mouth every day people have more than
one variety two variety have three
variety four variety five variety six
variety seven variety they'll have 10
varieties of strep some dormant some
lowkey some much more serious creating
everything from acne to
sty yep sty thrush all that thrush on
their tongue just causing problems so
that's the whole thing there we're going
into strep and we're going into UTI but
let's hit the UTI problem because that
is critical because I'm seeing it more
and more years ago I didn't see it like
it was today you'd have that antibiotic
resistant UTI you'd have that out there
I saw it out there okay but now it's
unlike it's ever been it's never been to
this degree I called it though and I saw
it I've written about it that these bugs
would actually take off to such a degree
where they'd be antibiotic resistant but
not just Mera not talking about Mera
I'm talking about plain old Jane strep
not MCA this is important to know this
is a really good episode and we're going
to talk about Solutions too which are
critical um let's get into it a little
bit the antibiotic dilemma do you guys
uh love antibiotics antibiotics are the
leading treatment for
UTI antibiotics are the leading
treatments for UTI you know that means
that means decade after decade of bugs
that are actually becoming
immune to the
antibiotic it's how it works and then
that bug spreads to another person and
so that person receives that bug and
then now they have an antibiotic
resistant bug they get sick and then
they go to the doctor the doctor gives
them an anti biotic again and now their
bug is in them that's already antibiotic
resistant is now even becoming more
antibiotic
resistant and
the and then it keeps on going on and on
and on and on so that's what's
happening it's not like the old
days and then the antibiotic kills the
weakest bacteria but the Strong Survive
so let's do this
okay I was prepared for this one here we
go okay you got a bacterium right here
you got a bacterium right here got a
bacterium right here and a bacterium
right here and I'll even put another one
right here and one more right here so
these are bacteria okay so here we are
take a look you guys these are inside
the bladder or the kidneys so let's make
a bladder here
okay there we are we got a
bladder right and in that bladder is a
whole bunch of bacteria and strep
bacteria is what it is okay so
antibiotics are used all of a sudden
boom we take an antibiotic the
antibiotic is coming through right now
here it goes there it is the antibiotic
coming
through there we go
can't really see this good but there it
is Boom the antibiotic came through then
now we get some dead
bacteria this one explodes Boom the
antibiotic killed
it boom Another One explodes boom
Another One
explodes interesting this one just gets
maed that bacterium gets maimed this one
just gets
weakened am I yelling this one gets
weakened okay this one doesn't get
harmed at
all all right we got a weakened
bacterium we got a maed bacterium
damaged but they survive they survive
and they provide information now against
that
antibiotic they hold the key to survival
against the antibiotic that was given to
them think about that right now right
and then you got one that survived it
completely that also holds information
but it's completely unharmed in fact it
seemed to do good with the antibiotic
that one little bug right there drank
those
antibiotics consumed them it didn't hurt
them and now this one bug right here is
getting stronger
nice and strong now now it's a nice
strong bacterium you see this the maed
ones not as strong but they provide
information and they stay alive is what
they do they too survive it and they're
a they survive it and the aftermath
they're still hanging around okay and
then another one too at the same time
still survived it and it's it's there
right so now you got three bacterium but
three different bacter iums same
bacteria but three different experiences
three different strengths and three
different
injuries one not injured two one mimed
one injured there's a problem with that
though because then as it's producing
more bacteria is being produced okay
which happens more and more
bacteria is being
produced right here's your bacteria
right
here and these bacteria are getting
stronger and producing the weak
ones okay want to be as strong as the
strong one so the weak ones become even
stronger than the original strong one
that wasn't even affected by the
original back antibiotic okay this is
important the weaker
ones gain strength the ones that were
maimed and injured by the an antibiotic
keep that in mind they were maimed and
injured and they
now okay they strengthen they rise above
it they gather information from their
injuries they learn how to not get
injured again by the antibiotic they
become stronger than the one that
survived completely without injury at
all and that's a problem all on its own
okay so now you have very strong
bacteria here's the thing they get
stronger they get stronger and
then all
right and then a new infection
occurs they get stronger they override
the immune system of the person drops
exactly the immune system
drops there's another bladder right
there okay so white blood
cells for some reason aren't as strong
in that person their own white blood
cells aren't doing the jobs they need to
do they get triggered they get exposures
something happens there and then the
bacteria rise up and get stronger and
now we have a new infection they
reproduce I'm going to make a whole
bunch of them here if you guys with me
you're following me right now
okay and then the new antibiotic comes
through they're sick again and then a
new wave of antibiotic comes through
they're at the doctor's office they got
a new
UTI and then boom here comes the
antibiotic it's rushing
through
okay and what happens is all these new
bacteria
right they don't budge everybody's happy
they're stronger they supersede the
antibiotic and then the doctor gets
pissed the patients gets the patient
gets pissed stays sick the doctor's
pissed and then they change up the
antibiotic get ready for this the new
antibiotic gets then prescribed so here
comes the new antibiotic coming through
and this is what sucks right here really
sucks it's comes
through and then it mimes and injures a
whole bunch of them that's right this
one gets maed this one gets injured this
one gets almost killed completely this
one just gets slightly injured this one
never gets touched okay that's
fine here's the problem now we got a
whole bunch of brand new streps
and those brand new bacterium strep
bacterium have
information and survived a new
antibiotic that is not good they
survived a new
antibiotic they're still alive now they
have information from the original
antibiotic how to survive survival
instincts in the bacteria and now they
got new information from the new
antibiotic survival mechanis organisms
kick in in that bacteria the
bacteria does not want to lose so it's
going to now
supersede and then boom the next phase
happens okay you got a patient that's
getting a little better again the
patient's getting a little bit
better I really can't stand this
whiteboard
yep all right new bacteria it's
reproducing here we
go once again immune system drops in the
patient the patient was getting
better a month later two months later at
some point okay there's the bladder
again I'm just doing a bladder you do
kidneys you can do you know urethras
whatever
so all
right playing around mark ERS here so we
got a new
bacteria this bacteria has information
from two
antibiotics it has survived two
antibiotics yes it has indeed and it has
survived the person's immune
system that's the whole point it
survived their immune system and it
survived the antibiotic involved in
their immune system okay both with the
immune system working on that working
with that antibiotic and both with with
that antibiotic okay so get ready for
this person gets sick again they got
another eiti it's pretty darn serious
they're in pain they got a fever they
don't know if they got kidney infections
bladder
infections and here we go there might be
some blood in the urine
right goes to the doctor doctor
prescribes an antibiotic the same one
that they used last time so you fill
your prescription now you're taking it
antibiotic runs through the body it's
triggering the immune system immune
cells you're trying to work with it it's
trying to work with everything it's
going
through okay and this time now with this
new
antibiotic it's only killing off this
one only killing off that one only
killing off that one that one that one
that one but this one right here is just
injured that one's injured that one's
injured that's one's injured injured
maimed and we get the whole thing over
again all the maed and injured ones say
I'm not going to do this anymore I'm not
going to let this antibiotic this new
antibiotic rule the roost and clean us
out we have to Rise Above This and we
have to get
stronger and then what happens is the
new reproduction of that of that
bacterium is even stronger so that the
next phase of the antibiotic on the
fourth r which happens all the time and
sometimes it's a sixth round and
sometimes it's a seventh another one's
prescribed here we
go and now none of the bacteria are
budging at all got a fever there's blood
in the
urine kidneys are inflamed they have to
give steroids out now so now it's
steroids plus the new antibiotic so here
we go doctor's got to play the game
again and here it
comes all right now it's
time to
use now it's time to use the new
antibiotic all right so we got this
bacteria that bacteria that bacteria
that one right there that one right
there here we go here's all the
bacteria yep we got another bladder
we'll just do bladder here we go there's
the
bladder now the doctor has to bring in
the super antibiotic one with a lot of
side effects one that causes a lot of
problems one that also says a lot of
terrible thing things on the side effect
package the little roll out and here we
go here it
comes boom boom boom bo bo I'm taking my
antibiotic
right the super antibiotic
the Super One a change
up
okay injures this guy kills off this guy
mimes this guy injures this guy kills
off this guy doesn't even touch that guy
that guy and that guy now you got three
guys here not even being touched by the
super
antibiotic but you still got injured but
not dead
bacteria injured but not dead bacteria
you got some dead
bacteria but too many
injured too many
injured and too many maimed but still
survived and others that didn't even get
affected and then we got a big problem
so now they reproduce
again after the Super antibiotic went
through they reproduce this time we're
in trouble now big trouble here we are
because they use the super antibiotic
again and then they have that running
through and now these
bacteria they are messaging they Cod it
they have information they're
superpowered they do not not give up at
this point they have information of four
to five different
antibiotics
and they don't want to budge anymore
they put their foot down they're done
that means they don't budge so then the
doctor has to run another
antibiotic brings that one
through and now the patient is just
chronically sick chronically suffering
and chronically sick a super buug has
been
born the patient has the
superbug whether it's a male
female the patient has a superbug and
then the patient has a
relationship or the patient is a chef
working in a restaurant who cuts their
finger and then bleeds on three
different meals that you can't really
tell because a lot of the chefs they we
the black gloves they put the black
gloves on they throw a bandage on put a
black glove on there's still blood
everywhere and get working really quick
they wipe their hands and or it's a
relationship sexual interactions of some
kind and then that super bug now gets
transferred onto someone else with all
this information and all this messaging
and that information or the shopping
cart shopping cart's a big one I've been
saying this for decades you guys heard
me say it years ago before c came around
the shopping cart is a big one okay lots
of different back bacteria on there lots
of strep lots of Staff lots of Cs L lots
of Mera lots of other stuff too but the
strep is just crazy on the shopping cart
handles crazy that's how much is on
there okay so with that if they swabbed
if they did a swab in a p tree dish if
they did that with off the shopping cart
handles you wouldn't believe what would
grow wouldn't believe it so you're
sitting there with a shopping cart
handle you're not using handy wipes
you're not doing an alcohol handy wipe
across the handle you're you don't
you're you're not thinking about
anything you don't care about anything
maybe you're just somebody that thinks
that your immune system will get
stronger because of it you won't have to
worry because hey who cares I can just
eat bugs and have bugs all over my skin
it's just all that whole thing that
philosophy that philosophy right it
makes you stronger you become immune to
it or something like that that's not
true that's not how it works the more
exposure you get to these bugs the more
exposure you get the more bugs you get
the more problems you have and then that
it doesn't work that way where we're
just all of a sudden hey I'm immune to
everything and that's what I want all
these bugs no it does not work like that
tell that to someone who got you know
Herpes Simplex 2 tell that to someone
who's got something else that they
caught from somebody it doesn't make you
stronger it's not how it works it's a
hassle it's all a hassle so then that
strep then that super bug gets into
somebody else through a shopping cart H
handle through a public bathroom off the
toilet seat off the dispenser whatever
it is and they get it and they get the
bug that's superpowered it is a super
version of itself it already knows all
the
antibiotics it already knows about them
all that means when you come down with
something or you get sick or something
happens and now you got a UTI whatever
it may be you go to the doctor and the
process starts all over again but the
doctor starts giving you that first
round of antibiotics and it won't budge
so easy especially if you have a
compromised immune system and you're
already struggling with something it
won't
budge and they're just like why do you
have these UTI all of a sudden or say
you know someone has someone has sex
with somebody else and you know it's
unprotective even if it's even if it's
protected sex it's still easy to
transfer these like these um these
streps and this bacteria and all a
sudden now there's a new UTI somebody
has that never had before
and now but it's an anti-resistant it's
a what is it antibiotic resistant is
what I mean version of itself that has
all this information that's coded that's
got all this Intel that survived all
these antibiotics that knows them well
so now we have another person with a
super bug and just as Grim as it sounds
it's not Grim when you know how to heal
and use tools and that's the thing about
medical medium information it's the one
place where people that are the sickest
come to find answers and it's not all
that biohack [ __ ] out there that's
going on it's real it's the real deal
it's real answers real information on
how to heal what to do and that's
medical medium information and that's
how it's always been people can be
jealous out there and they can rip it
apart or say what they want about it it
Stills the most people healed in the
world to the most chronic conditions and
this is why knowing about this
information not just biohacking crap on
social and just this this this and try
this it's for people who have been there
and done that they're seasoned and they
know so what happens is there is hope so
when these super bugs the super strap
gets to somebody else and they're
fighting these these battling these UTI
and it seems hopeless there are women
out there with chronic UTI every day of
their lives going into overactive
bladder going into chronic UTI
overactive bladder pain in their kidneys
pain in their back p and then it attack
on acne and sore throats and sio because
they all get a sibo diagnosis eventually
tack on to all all those in there and
they're living with these Super Bug
streps it's happening more and more out
there and there are more people living
with this than ever before now there is
an
upsurge that's getting out of control a
serious upsurge and that
upsurge is not going to stop it's going
to keep on going unless people know how
to arm themselves and take care of
themselves and know how to fight feed
their bodies what they need do the right
things giving their bodies what their
need so they can they can beat this
Super Bug stuff down because it's no
joke right now cuz people are passing
these along and it's out of control
people need the right information
there's cleanse the heel right here in
front of me and in cleanse the heel I
got pelvic inflammatory disease right
and even you know PID right and even
prostatis got that there too I'm talking
about bladder infections UTI all of that
in here so it's cleanse to heal people
need this book they need the
information I have Liver Rescue in front
of me right here I want to read a little
bit about this for a couple of minutes
if you guys don't
mind the story of
strep is what I was just telling you
guys that's the story of strep right now
in this modern day what people are
dealing with and how bad it is okay most
people stress starts in childhood they
get the ear infections they get the
strep throat the sore throats it starts
earlier on it strep passed down from the
parents a lot of times and it's strep
that's passed down to the parents and
then the children the B the children
have it and the children pass it to each
other in
school and so it's it's strep being
passed around everywhere that's what it
is but that could be fine in some ways
but in others it's antibiotic resist
resistance STP that's being passed
around going to each person and that
takes us to the next level of
understanding which I want to go to
now which is the immune system okay
that's the next thing every time SHP
enters into somebody and battles our
immune cells and it survives so anytime
SHP enters into each person and it goes
into war with our immune cells right
here goes into war every time that
happens and there's a
battle and the strep survives it has
information so when that strep is passed
onto another person it's not just
antibiotics it's also relationships with
the immune system of the person it was
in this whole time so then when that STP
gets passed on to somebody else it's
getting passed on to somebody else with
information on that person's immune
system information of how it survived
the battle with that person's white
count and so when that strep is in the
new person the strep now has a way to
beat immune systems it goes into another
person another person's immune system
goes up against it there it goes it's in
battle the the bacteria survives why do
you think people keep on getting acne
all over again you still have some strep
surviving why do you think they keep on
getting the UTI over again the bladder
infections the
overactive ladder right that one too OAB
they keep on getting these things and
then the thigh and then the sore throats
and then the strep throat periodically
and then the ear aches and ear
infections or they get exposed to new
strains and that's another story and
we'll go into that too the strep has
information of the person's immune
system information of the antibiotics
the other person took they take it to
the next person the next person's immune
cells go against it they go into battle
what survives is Boom the bacteria again
some of it survives it gets passed on to
a new person with now immune system
information from two others now here's
where it gets really
intense that
bacteria can go through a 100 people and
gather information from their immune
systems of that 100
people that's how super bugs are made
it's not just the antibiotic over
usage and then the UN and then not being
taught how to heal and get rid of the
bacteria
naturally it's also information from
each person's immune cells to each
person and that bug becomes one
Unstoppable brutal bug and that's why
there are women out there young women in
their 20s and in their early 30s that
are in tears on a daily basis and they
are so sick and they have so much
UTI chronic UTI going on they have so
much overactive bladder UTI kidney
infection sore throats molay tired
fatigue everything else Under the Sun
with it and they're suffering and
they're bleeding they're on antibiotics
again their stomach's being ripped to
shreds from the
antibiotics then they get their sibo
diagnosis and it's all around the same
old thing more antibiotics for that and
they're
suffering and then
because they got a strep inside of them
that could have been through a hundred
people that was passed on to them one
way or another and that strep is smart
it's smart it knows the immune cell
information from dozens of people it
knows the antibiotic information from
dozens of people and it carries it with
it and we have to know how to destroy
that bacteria and how to kill it and
what to use that it is not immune to
because that's the key right medical
medium information is always about the
cause cuz guess what they didn't know
strep was a UTI problem they didn't know
strep was other problems they knew about
strep throat but they didn't know strep
created acne they didn't know it created
sty did they didn't know it created UTI
by the way that's medical medium
information but it does it's just coming
out people are poaching it and it's
going out there and it's just getting
out there every day just like you guys
are probably seeing because I know you
guys are telling me you see it every day
we see it every
day but the point is is that bacteria we
have to learn how to kill it you have to
identify it and know there's a cause
behind your PID there's a cause behind
your
UTI there's a cause Behind these
things and there's a way to kill and
destroy kill and destroy the
bacteria even bacterium that is
antibiotic resistant and knows a crap
ton of people's immune systems that
understands all these people's immune
systems that that bacteria was in all
this
time understands it is it expert at
immune systems because that's what the
bacteria becomes it becomes an expert at
everybody's white count immune cells all
of it it knows it all it's been in too
many people it hasn't been destroyed and
it's gotten stronger and stronger now
it's a super bug and that's where it's
at and that's happening now every day
and we think these super bugs are bad
now wait till the next round of UTI 10
years from
now and all the young men and women it's
going to be like nobody's ever seen ever
seen it's going to be that bad it's
going to be bleeding as normal
constantly bleeding catheters constantly
on catheters that's another thing too so
the UTI are getting to a point where all
these young women are are literally
living with
catheters that's how bad it
is and so we have to be mindful and
understand that there is a way to beat
it and there is a way to do we're going
to talk about that in a little bit but I
want to read a little if I
can okay maybe most people strep starts
in childhood maybe even pass down from a
parent at conception yes a new born can
enter the world with strep already in
her or his
system a child can also get strep from
daycare or school and it's easily passed
from child to
child it really is as well as adult to
adult because strep is a type of
bacterium antibiotics do seem like the
obvious choice to treat it but here's
the crucial point that I talked about to
know about strep long ago before
antibiotic Revolution before antibiotics
long ago you guys this is really
interesting right here before the
antibiotic was born long
ago strep used to be one strain of
bacterium strep was one strain of
bacterium which takes us to this next
part right here now this is really
important okay this is
important very
important going to bring this around for
a second
okay all right
so five antibiotics ago 10 antibiotics
ago 10 different people ago the bacteria
look like
this right but then it changes a new
strain is is is created along
with the superbug power it alters and
turns into a different bug now we have
the old strain
that's way in the past and it's in other
people we got the new
strain and there it
is right there that new
strain becomes another new strain
eventually another new strain another
new strain but here's the thing if you
pass on this strain that it became to
another person through sex or through
drinking from somebody's glass or from
being in a bar and eating something or
whatever you're doing in a restaurant or
on a shopping cart in a shopping cart or
in a public bathroom or so many other
ways you can do
this if you pass on that strep bacteria
to somebody in that in that strain to
them they'll have that
strain and they may keep that strain but
it'll be that strain okay these in this
person can still alter and become a new
strain in a few few years that new
strain can be passed on to another
person and then they'll have that
strain
see that's how it
works men can get UTI too and they do
but they don't have a cycle men do not
have
menstration they do not have a cycle so
they don't have the immune system
lowering thing that happens so what
happens is when a woman goes through
menstruation and she has her cycle her
monthly cycle her immune system drops
and 80% of her immune system goes to the
reproductive system that's medical me
information 20% stays around the body
for the rest of the body the
reproductive system is the number one
Focus that time of month where it's the
number one Focus for the immune system
think about that right so because of
that the immune system is so focused
around the reproductive
system okay that it's easy to catch STP
orally very easy to catch it orally or
in the eyes where the immune system
isn't there to destroy it right off the
running so if there's some kind of
relationship or a shopping cart like I
said or a public bathroom and something
goes in the eye or something gets in the
mouth whatever it is during the cycle
80% of the immune system isn't around
the mouth it's not there so for a woman
it's not here it's down here so the
strep can easily start its its beginning
in the mouth in the throat and the so
for so forth in that area so that
happens too all right let's go into just
a little
bit all right here's the crucial point
to know about strep long ago before the
antibiotic Revolution I'm reading out of
Liver Rescue if you guys never seen
these books you don't know about these
books you should get both of them go to
Amazon get both be the best thing you
ever did become an expert about your own
health learn how to
heal become a true expert a true expert
not a
biohacker strep is not and never was a
super bug in the past so strep was never
a super buug it's not designed to be a
Super Bug originally it was never meant
to be one we are forcing it to become a
super buug
okay it's much more forgiving strep than
ever than anything else was okay in its
original state going back many years ago
it was much more forgiving it's a
forgiving
bacteria it's not as unforgiving as
merca it's not as unforgiving as Mera so
that is something to understand cith and
Mera can be even much more brutal much
more brutal of a superbug strep still
even with its worst superbug mentality
whatever it's more superbug
creation it doesn't hold the power as
like Mera and what Mera can turn into
some kind of flesh eating bacterium that
just becomes a super super bug so I want
that clear so people
know so if they got strap and they're
living with st they're living with all
these symptoms you can turn it in it can
turn naturally into a Super Bug over
time because it's force-fed the
antibiotics it's force-fed in the way I
was saying all those things but it won't
get to like a Mera level at mca's worst
so the different varieties of Mera
there's all these different varities of
Mera did you know there's thousands of
varieties of Vera and some of the top
tier varieties of Vera that are just
like God awful and they kill people is
what they do and they give them sepsis
and they die like the top tier of the
worst sh's not there so I wanted that to
be
clear but strep is no longer one strain
I want to go back to that a little bit
it's no longer one
strain there are so many varieties of
strep at this point over the
decades strep being a victim of
antibiotics it found a way to survive to
adapt adaptation didn't just mean
getting stronger it meant mut eating and
spawning different strains and varieties
and that's what strep does it's the
ultimate like spawner of new varieties
of bacteria all strep all the same
family but it's the ultimate see here
with Mariana says over there on IG I
healed my UTI back in 2002 with the
herbs and supplements you recommend in
cleanse the heal book amazing is it
2020 let see what it is um healing with
Victoria I used to be on an antibiotic
once a month for UTI I haven't needed
them in four years thanks to your
protocols thanks to you andc medical
meme information destroys UTI just
destroys them so one thing about mm info
if you know how to use it and you use it
right you can annihilate so many
different strep
conditions Shamrock over there in IG
this was me with I see whoa I see for 20
years of extreme bladder pain until I
found medical me information thank you
aw incredible
incredible over here Heidi on IG before
medical medium I had chronic strep
throat UTI and kidney infections I now
have no pain and haven't had to run to
the doctor in many years this info Works
quote from you amazing and I will add to
that quote from you it does work it does
work it does it has a track record of
working that's the power of it you no
biohackers and informationists messing
around all these different things out
there on social can do that for people
this information does and that's why I'm
a messenger of s so's information
because it saves lives Maria over there
on YouTube great topic I used to get UTI
all the time and they are so painful
it's much better thanks to aw and S so
incredible let's go into a little bit of
protocol talk a little bit too and let's
just double check we covered some stuff
right
here let's talk about like the different
strains a little bit longer the spawning
the different strains I want to go into
that over there on YouTube wondering
wishing good to see you antibiotics used
to be the go-to for our family after
medical meeting protocols viy zinc micro
Ginger turmeric shots cat's claw well I
love that cat's claw I love that cat's
claw in celery juice no more we are free
from the constant doctor appointments
thanks s so and medical
medium it's going to get me
emotional because you know when you heal
it is everything Maria over there on
YouTube great topic I used to get UTI oh
I saw that one already great Chrissy
over there and I think um twitch Stitch
Chrissy I was in tears every time I had
a UTI I can't imagine the amount of
people that are going through it and
they go through it on levels that are
just devastating it's become like the
Super Bug now level and it's brutal and
so many people suffer from it their guts
get ripped to shreds from all the
antibiotics they have to take they're on
steroids almost all the time and it's
brutal along the way strep got
classified as having a group a and a
group b yeah the medical world now
identifies strep all the way through
Group
H Group H though as you read about in
the acne chapter because acne is Strep
caused by the way you guys it is it's
medical medium info but it's strep cause
that the population carries there are
also strains within the known groups
that are yet un that are yet
unidentified and undocumented so here's
how medicine
works medical research and science works
like this they've classified some of the
bacterium the strains but they haven't
classified all of them haven't even
scratched the surface so there's
bacteria out there that they haven't
even documented classified got their
hands on or anything like that and
that's the scary thing it's even
scarier yep even a gifted and talented
lab technician discovered that even if a
gifted and talented lab technician
discovered that there were more strains
and groups of strep that weren't
currently known the Breakthrough would
go unrecognized the scientists would not
be able to find funding for this area of
critical medical importance because
right now funding is too tied up in
misled areas like how genes relate to
disease so yeah you guys let's go into
this a little bit now some protocol
stuff I'm in cleans the heal if you
don't have the book I feel bad for
you get the book get the book get the
book I mean you don't have to spend a
$5,000 program on how to walk Barefoot
on your on your lawn you can do that but
it won't make your UTI go away keep that
in mind you can do earthing and you can
do like you can not wear shoes and you
can watch the sunrise in the morning and
you can angle your bed a certain way in
your room the way the sun rises and sun
sun sets but none of that's going to get
rid of somebody's de debilitating acne
sty UTI bladder infections kidney
infections
PID
it's just not going to
happen hardcore stuff that has to work
then you can do all that stuff for fun
the other stuff I was mentioning okay
danan 144 on IG I was in so much pain
for nine months with intertial cystis
celery juice saved my
life yeah and that's why when someone
says celery juice sucks or celery juice
isn't what it is or something out there
that's it's actually such a disservice
The Chronic ill it's so sad when celery
juice literally has turned lives around
saved lives yeah I know all right let's
go into it pelvic inflammatory disease
PID right here talks about UTI it's in
here right here cleanse to
heal all right the true cause bacterial
infection of one or more strains from
over 50 groups of
strep they are different levels of PID
it's like different levels of
UTI different levels to all the
different things different levels to
sibo incredible okay so let's go into
the protocol right starts out
interesting fresh celery
juice I still have some left right
here if you guys want any I still got
some right here we're in aw's kitchen
so
fresh celery juic says work up to 32
ounces daily and cleanse to heal work up
to 32 o daily I did my celery juice and
it didn't work I did my celery juice and
it didn't work I was doing 4 ounces it
says work up to 32 o what page and Maria
says what page 537 and cleanse the heel
so page
537 get your book
out
okay second thing in here aloe
vera aloe vera for UTI for
PID for overactive bladder too aloe vera
two or more inches of fresh gel skin
removed two or more inches of fresh gel
skin
removed all right what's the next thing
on the list barleygrass juice
powder another thing on the list
cat's claw very interesting cat's claw
critical for
UTI critical for
PID critical for men that are having
prostatitis right there cat's claw it's
a big one you'll hear more about cats
claw every day out there and more about
cats claw every day it's the medical
medium information that got that out
there catclaw was around it's been
around obviously but using for the
things that it's being used for for
protocols is medical medium information
originally for cats claw
curcumin and there you go that's another
one de Manos yeah de Manos is
great but you need more than Dem Manos
if someone's dealing with UTI and PB and
some of the things I'm talking about
here you need more than de Manos de
Manos is in here it's part of the
protocol and sometimes you'll hear out
there like a practitioner or somebody
will say de Manos use that for your UTI
it's like okay but what about the golden
seal what about the cat's claw where's
that what about the celery juice de
Manos de Manos drink cranberry juice
drink cranberry juice that's great and
all that's great but guess what it's not
enough for the kind of UTI that are
happening out there every day right now
no way it's not enough but it is when
it's compiled with other things that
help
right right and the books have the
amounts to C but you customize I talk
about the amounts in here but you
customized over there on G Elena I had
several severe PID which went to left
kidney too o I was told I need
hysterctomy and will be disabled heal
that with mm now all I need is to heal G
AOS
or it says GBS
ALS all right ibrite it's another one
right there golden
seal golden
seal
UTI golden
seal why do I do
that people just they get lost they
don't hear something they don't know
they get a UTI next month don't even
remember
so I'm hoping if you're one of those
people you'll be able to save yourself
UTI golden
seal so I talk about here dosages
everything okay remember the quality of
supplements matter so check out medical
mem information but the quality of the
supplements
matter critical I talk about that in the
supplements chapter in cleanse to heal
make sure you look at that really
important
another
one strep UTI PID overactive bladder all
these lemon
bomb UTI lemon bomb okay ready UTI
licorice
root licorice root UTI nettle
Leaf
incredible and there's more in here too
that you can play with customize
yourself it's here the information that
s so brought to us to save people's
lives I get it fun you know surfing the
net surfing
social whoa let me cold plunge you know
whoa let me walk Barefoot it's all great
whatever cold plunging is not good not
good for people chronically sick all
that stuff but either way
I'm talking about fixing problems and
that's the key and that's what the
medical medium information does fixes
problems keep that in mind Amy over
there on IG friend with
Ms was on
Walker only 30 years old drank fresh
celery juice daily and could walk again
after about 4
weeks I love you guys
incredible oh got to tell you one thing
though medical podcast at Apple podcast
mercury in fish and fish oil don't miss
it mercury and fish and fish oil where
does the Mercury go where does the
Mercury go do not miss the medical be
podcast at Apple podcast you guys if you
subscribe to it on
Apple and you're not getting the you
know notifications check any way check
the podcast so you can see the new
episodes you may not be getting notified
I see this happening to a whole bunch of
people so check out the medical Me
podcast at Apple podcast mercury and
fish and fish oil where does the Mercury
go get on the medical medium newsletter
too so you can learn about what's
happening because I am going to be
somewhere in
person I'm going to be somewhere in
person earlier this year I'm letting you
know this year so I'm going to be like a
little later this year I'm going I'm
going to be in person I'm going to sign
some books if you got if you got an old
medical medium book bring it up to me
bring it up to me I'll sign it I'm
letting you know okay definitely I'm
really excited about that I'm just
trying to figure out the logistics to to
really know exactly where I'm going to
be but it's going to be LA and then the
location I'm working out the logistics
on the location I'm hoping I see you
guys there if not maybe another time in
the world I don't know I never did a
book signing it's the first official
book signing ever in the history of all
the medical medum books and um so I mean
you might want to be there and bring
your book so I can sign
it join the medical medium
telegram as well I might leave a message
tonight and I fact I think I will leave
a message tonight on
telegram okay and join the Instagram
broadcast channel I'm going to leave
something there too have you actually
joined the the broadcast channel okay
it's called the m inside scoop mm inside
scoop the medical medium broadcasting
channel I'm going to leave a little
message on there and I'm going to leave
a telegram God
willing God willing I will leave a
telegram you guys I love you much and
thanks for being here today I can't wait
to see you next
time