I recognized the medical medium. I had
read like a little blog about him and
yeah, just like a little seed was
planted. I started listening and then a
couple years later is when I started
using his tools because I got desperate
with my symptoms. I struggled with
chronic UTI for about 20 years and I was
on antibiotics every month, sometimes
every week. I probably took hundreds of
rounds of antibiotics throughout those
15 to 20 years. And it wasn't until I
found his information that I was able to
clear those on my own. And I've been UTI
free for probably three or four years
and antibiotic free for 5 years. But I
just wanted to meet Anthony and thank
him for just giving me a new life
really.
[Music]