welcome to the medical medium nighttime
routine which I'm really excited about
showing you guys because I've never done
that before where I've showed you my
nighttime routine which is cool
including some food which is really
awesome supplementation right how I take
it the whole bit but I'm going to show
you a technique I do as I'm falling
asleep
a technique I use for my immune system
so I hope you guys stick around for that
because it's really cool I haven't
showed you that technique before because
I'm trying my best I'm only human I'm
trying my best SOC gives me information
I put it in everywhere put it here there
write the podcast all that stuff I
publish it and there's so much and
there's things that I do for myself that
I've gotten into a routine doing that I
just kind of even forget to like teach
it out there because there's so many
other things I'm doing but I want to
show you this really cool technique that
I do every single night for my immune
system and so there's a spiritual
connection involved in my nighttime
routine that I want to tell you about
which is really cool so anyway I'm just
going to start right now with the subs
because before dinner
we're trying to make some Nori rolls
which is really cool I'm going to take a
few Subs I'm going to show you what I do
every night and by the way this is the
Bemidji uh supplements right here those
are the ones I take those are the ones I
support and I fully endorsed these guys
because this stuff is that incredible
and I want it to stick around so people
have the opportunity to actually have
this in their lives and I'm going to
talk about in a little while by the way
the four big reasons why this stuff is
the best of Energy company and you be
the judge you be the judge when you hear
what I have to tell you because it blows
my mind it's mind-blowing so let's get
down to it so I want to take my steps my
here's the nighttime routine it's
starting right I'm here and no I didn't
come back from the hospital just now
that's not what this is this is my
pajamas so I didn't just come back from
the hospital right where's my hospital
tag so anyway no these are my pajamas
man so let's get started with this this
immune system that's what I'm talking
about right now and that's what's
connected spiritually to my nighttime
routine so I want to go into that a
little bit so let me just start right so
there's some cats call I'm going to pop
some in this little shot glass right so
here it is right nighttime routine
putting some cat's claw in cat's claw
right supports the immune system I'm
gonna put some propolis in here too
which is cool about Provost I like also
just putting it straight in the mouth
it's good for oral health which is
amazing about propolis too right and
supports the immune system
here's the zinc
right thing is with zinc and I've said
this over and over again I've said this
over and over again about the zinc okay
going all the way back
it's great for every aspect of our body
zinc is one of those essential minerals
that our entire body needs right one of
the essential minerals for health so
I've been saying that about saying man
going all the way back so right here
it's immune system right zinc propolis
cat's claw okay nettle leaf now nettle
Leaf is great for a lot of things like
urinary supports urinary tract but I
like it for immune system
so that's important right there
I got the nettle Leaf going right there
okay so that's an immune system shot
right there let me get a little bit of
water so I want to take this shot it's
part of my nighttime routine right here
so I'm gonna shoot this down now
here's how it goes
now I'm going to have dinner and stuff
I'll make some Dory rolls but I'm just
kind of like jostling things around a
little bit in my routine but I want to
tell you
what happens is has that entered my body
right now
I'm connecting to it it's really
important so I'll tell you what happens
the minute that goes down and into me
right
I can feel it
because I like being in tuned
to the supplementation that I'm taking
that my body's receiving so I like to be
so in tuned that I like to Envision my
immune cells
right away when that stuff is going in
me because that's important right there
so my immune system right
so right when I take
that shot and I sent that down
I align it instantly to visualizing my
immune cells my white blood cells that's
important and then
I go about my business for the rest of
the night a little bit right winding
down I'm making my meal getting myself
ready but when I go to bed
when I go to bed and I hop in bed
right put the blanket over me
and I close my eyes I shut the light off
and close my eyes
I envision
a white blood cell
and I Envision that white blood cell
floating around
so this is the visualization I do right
so I'm seeing that white blood cell
floating around while I'm actually
getting ready to fall asleep
and I'm envisioning it right
and this is what I do every night for
years that's my immune system right
there now then
I connect to the immune
support
that I took
I connect to the propolis
I connect to the cat's claw I connect to
the zinc
I connect to the nettle leaf
right and I'm connecting to it and then
I'm seeing my white blood cells receive
that Incredible Gift
that incredible power
it's just
consuming it and I visualize this now
here's the incredible thing too and then
I visualize my white blood cells with my
eyes closed falling asleep with the
light off I envisualize right
I see the white blood cells gobbling up
toxins
gobbling up poisons and toxins that's
what I see I see it start to gobble up
those poisons and those toxins right
and that's what I do and I lay there and
I connect to my body and I connect to
the purity
of what I took
because I don't have to worry too about
stuff being in these supplements which
I'm going to talk about stuff that
shouldn't be there so I don't have to
worry about that and I'm going to talk
about that in a second as well but this
visualization
and connects to the affirmations I also
say for myself like
my white blood cells I see them
I can see them floating across my vision
my eyes closed and I can see those white
blood cells gobbling things up that
should not be inside my body toxins and
poisons because we're exposed to so many
toxins and poisons out there so I'm
watching my white blood cells eat that
up as I'm falling asleep right and then
I talk to him I talk to my immune system
I talk to my immune cells and I tell my
white blood cells
that they're doing an amazing job and I
say in an affirmation way I go
okay I go my white blood cells are
powerful they're strong
my white blood cells are unstoppable
and I'll even say you guys are
unstoppable you're powerful white blood
cells
nothing gets in your way you can you can
gobble up digest and eat up
and completely destroy toxins and
poisons and I know you're doing that and
I do the affirmations with my immune
system which is really powerful and the
affirmations with the immune system is
really powerful
watching those immune cells across my
eyes
gobbling up
all the different toxins and poisons and
I talked to my immune cells and I see
did I feed you guys
right and then I Envision that my immune
system can speak
and they're saying yes you gave us what
we needed
which is really powerful really powerful
right there so what I do is I the Lee my
nighttime routine changes
it shifts right now this is it for now
but then it shifts different
supplementation different times
different seasons different stress in my
life what kind of stress do you guys
have in your life what are you guys up
against I know that I'm up against a lot
of stress I work 22 hour days 20 hour
days 18 hour days
I worked 24-hour days sometimes which is
not really a great idea either but I do
it I got deadlines I got
responsibilities there are lots of
people relying on me so what what I do
because someone might say oh you do a
lot for your nighttime routine yeah and
I have tremendous responsibility I have
people relying on me I got the world
relying on me for getting the
information from SOC out to everybody so
that information's there and that's
always a fight and a struggle to get
that out there in the world because the
world it's how it is it's hard to get
information out there right it's a lot
of work and so all of that there's a lot
of responsibilities plus personal life
stuff right that everybody has
and so with that it changes and it Ebbs
and flows
but right now what I'm doing supporting
my immune system is one of the things
I'm doing right what I love about the
propolis
the energy propolis right is it has up
to over 50 percent
of the polyphenols right
after polyphenols are in the propolis
which is incredible one of them is
quercetin so that's actually an
acropolis which I really love right
Central it's essential in my opinion
right I take it for antioxidant support
I take it for my immune system and
here's what's cool no propylene glycol
in here and that's going to lead me to
something I want to tell you guys which
is really incredible but no propylene
glycol in here and they do a specialized
specialized process which is amazing a
pic like which is incredible what they
do as far as the pro unique
um unique purification process which
doesn't exist anywhere else from what
I've heard so it's really amazing their
stuff so I want to talk about
some cool things with this now four
reasons why support
the vimergy company right and four
reasons why I fully endorsed them and
working with them I got to tell you
one is and you be the judge to this
okay right one is
label requirements
just so you know label requirements for
supplement companies
does not require the supplement company
right to list or disclose
all the ingredients inside the bottle
I'll repeat myself right there
label requirements right for supplement
companies don't require
all the ingredients in the product to be
disclosed
just so you know
keep it in mind they can have a small
percentage
of ingredients in this supplementation
out there that they don't disclose
that you don't know about like flow
agents things like flow agents
exactly and other ingredients Bemidji
they vowed
okay they would never do that they would
never put
undisclosed hidden ingredients are
hidden flow agents or anything like that
in their products that alone right there
because I've never seen that anywhere
else in my opinion when my in my life
I've never seen it that right there is
like drop the mic it's drop the mic
because I'm about connecting to the
stuff I consume spiritually emotionally
that's what I'm about right and so when
people who know me like really dear dear
family members or friends they know that
it's all about like that spiritual
connection with everything I do right so
it's all about the purification too okay
so when I take something for my immune
for immune support right when I do that
and I'm envisioning that white blood
cell
on connecting to the Purity factor of
what I put in my body too
I'm connecting to the fact that there's
no flow agents there's no hidden
ingredients that are not being disclosed
right and so that's what I'm connecting
to when I take the memory stuff so it's
like you know what it's high time just
full endorsement boom I stand behind the
company I want people in the world to be
able to have the opportunity to have the
same opportunity that I have which is
knowing I'm getting that pureness inside
my body and then connecting to that
pureness which is which is critical for
me
right
I need to know there isn't something
hidden there isn't something tricky
going on even if it's legal even it's
legal because label requirements they
legally make it so you can hide and
disclose you don't you can hide and not
disclose certain stuff small percentage
but vimoji goes above legal requirements
and they don't put anything like that in
there that's hidden in small percentages
and they always disclose everything
that's in there that's incredible so
that's one thing by the way so be the
judge on this next one okay
be the judge on this next one this is
another connection I have spiritually to
the products for me when I know I'm
putting it in my body okay my opinion my
life my spiritual connection my soul
right listen to this one be the judge on
this one which is interesting very cheap
products have no alcohol
no alcohol no soy
contains no gluten no citric acid no
maltodextrin
no magnesium steroid no vinegar
no caffeine no natural flavors
no artificial flavors no titanium
dioxide just going to say it one more
time because it's insane
that's insane when I think about it
because
I've seen a lot of supplementation out
there in the world all right from what
I've seen
no alcohol no soy no glue no citric acid
no maltodextrin maltodextrin is almost
virtually almost in almost everything
virtually almost in everything
Healthcare and people don't know that no
magnesium steroid no vinegar no caffeine
no natural flavors natural flavors
is in virtually almost everything now
out there in one way form or another
even if it says like organic natural
flavors or natural flavors or whatever
right no artificial flavors in it no
titanium dioxide that's the second thing
be the judge on that one but let me tell
you the connection I have knowing that
when I recommend
this product line to a family member a
friend a dear loved one anybody what I
recommend it to someone that I'm not
worried because I have people I have
friends I have family contact me say hey
I'm taking this I'm taking this whatever
and I'll be like oh can you look at the
back of the bottle they said yeah it
says alcohol it says caffeine in here it
says it says um gluten in here it says
whatever you know vinegar in here it
says natural flavors in here it says
titanium dioxide in here it says
maltodextrin in there and all these
things and then I I is a Consciousness
kind of level so what happens is when
people say what do you do in your
personal life well I'm doing my
nighttime routine I'm showing you guys
but I'm telling you something that I
don't talk to people about it's it's
kind of private to me in my life
absolutely but I wanted to tell you is
there's a spiritual connection I do with
everything in my life and there is a
soul connection and a Consciousness I
have to connect with to my soul about
purify application and Purity and things
like that and so if I'm going to put
something in my body in my own my own
body and how I feel I and recommend it
to a family friend or anybody
that's the second big thing where it's
like oh my God that's incredible that
that's not going to be in here which is
unbelievable now here's the third third
incredible thing right very cheap
products
okay our third party independently
tested not just
in-house
third party independently tested that's
the kind of Integrity that alone is
insane and here's the fourth right here
's the fourth which I find just as big
as the other ones right here okay about
the vimergy products
the fourth is
if you want to start a supplement
company you can choose the lower quality
stuff
for price point I don't know if you guys
heard of anything like this but this is
how it goes you can choose the lower
quality right you can choose the lower
quality cilantro product that's at the
bottom tier
or you can choose a little higher that's
this level product mean the quality or
you can choose a higher level quality
it's going to cost more but you can
choose if your supplement company the
another level but if you're some you can
even go higher and Bemidji goes
to the best sources to the highest
quality sources they can possibly find
regardless of the cost
they go to the top tier regardless of
the cost
if that doesn't blow my mind I don't
know what does or what doesn't and you
be the judge and jury man you be the
judge and jury on that so anyway
connecting to
my body right having that connection my
Consciousness my soul my spirit my
physical body I need to know it's pure
because I could feel it if I put
something that's not so pure or not pure
in my body I'll take it right off
I'll pick it right off
and that's the thing with me and that's
how I've always been and people wonder
why do you stand behind Imaging so much
why do you always because of that reason
that's one of the big reasons right
there outside of all of them right so
immune system stuff let's go a little
bit more into that so back to the immune
system so what I do is I take vitamin C
closer to bed is what I do right so I
take a little bit of vitamin C
okay that's the micro C right there okay
if you guys just came on here I'm
talking about how I support Bemidji
fully endorse them working with them and
I'm talking about like the wise too
about what that connection is like why
why would I
because when I think about that
connection spiritually and everything
about it so when I do the visualization
technique
with my white blood cells at night and
I'm falling asleep and the lights are
out and I'm seeing
my white blood cells now if you're
somebody that has floaters in your eyes
right you've got floaters you got you
got spots and when you close your eyes
or even when they're open and you see
them right but you close your eyes
because the doctor friend was telling me
how he has these white spots that float
around when he closes his eyes right eye
floaters right so he was asking me
questions about that a doctor friend of
mine and I said if you have those for
now before you can work on getting
Rhythm if you have those for now when
you're going to bed and you shut your
eyes he goes well that's when I see him
I go to bed at night I shut my eyes and
the eye floaters are all swimming around
I said Envision that they're not eye
floaters Envision that they're your
white blood cells
that's your that's your white blood
cells Envision that see those little
floaters as your white blood cells
that's them right there your immune
cells all floating around since that's
incredible he said that's incredible and
he's doing it he's doing he says it's a
life changer game changer for him right
so I love this technique of seeing the
white blood cell and then I think about
the vitamin C
vitamin C supports a healthy immune
system vitamin C right it's hot it's
high in antioxidants right vitamin C
okay
right supports the skin it supports the
skin so you have to think about that
right
so if micro C is supporting the skin
it's supporting right your immune your
immune system healthy immune system
supports healthy immune system when
you're thinking about you're thinking of
white blood cell the white count
in that Vision spiritually when you're
falling asleep
and I fall asleep to my immune cells
receiving that vitamin C
gaining strength in my mind
Consciousness in my visual and
affirmation abilities just like you have
those and I see it gobbling up that
vitamin C and then I see those white
blood cells gobbling up anything that I
want them to gobble up anything that I'm
thinking about well I had a little
exposure got into some different toxins
then I'm seeing my white blood cells go
and grab those toxins and Gobble those
toxins up and that's what I do right
there
and that's a really big one for me of
what I do every day okay so
um I I there's so many reasons why I
love Energy Products just hear me out if
you have a second about this beverage
never uses tablets you know you guys
know tablets
tablets
tablets right because tablets have
glazes
fillers titanium dioxide colors Bemidji
uses capsules if they're not just using
liquids pure liquids you're using
capsules to get away from the tablet
that's how advanced they are it's almost
like whoa how can you how far can you go
really you know so anyway with vitamin C
which is really cool right there's
there's vitamin C out there but there's
ascorbic acid now personally in my
opinion from what I've seen people go
through with vitamin C and ascorbic acid
I've seen it bother people's stomachs
that's what I've seen I've talked to a
lot of doctors over the years and I've
had doctors tell me that their patients
stomachs were being bothered by ascorbic
acid vitamin C right and vimergy doesn't
use all that straight ascorbic acid so
that's really just awesome all in its
own so
I give you a quick rundown a couple
other things I have right here all right
so uh let me get some
get a little water in here
I'm gonna take some other things too
right first of all I'm going to take a
couple of capsules right here
uh micro C
m
set those down okay
and then um
so the whole thing with like the
spiritual connection matters to me so I
think about that with everything I take
so then when I take
some curcumin right
I think about the same thing I connect
to the turmeric rhizome right the root I
connect to it right there that's what I
do I like to I like to visualize
okay that I'm actually sending a message
to the farm where it came out of I like
to connect to the Earth it came out of I
like to make that spiritual connection
that Soul connection to that Purity
right the one thing right here
which is amazing about the curcumin
which I like when I take it right is
there's no black pepper in there because
in my opinion black pepper is an
irritant because you see people they're
like well there's black pepper in my
curcue bin right and but meanwhile you
know I got all kinds of problems my
digestive out there you'll hear that out
there I've seen it before I've had
doctor friends tell me this patients
have all kinds of Crohn's colitis and
all these different conditions they're
patients right and the doctor would be
telling me like they're on a curcumin
everything like that that'd be like as a
black pepper in that one like yeah they
said there's lots of black pepper in
there it's like you know in my opinion
you know tell a doctor friend that my
opinion for sure taking not having a
black pepper is good because it's an
irritant right and Verma G doesn't do
the whole black pepper thing which is
really cool right
curcumin turmeric
and that's there's a combination of both
in here the whole turmeric and also the
curcumin in this one great for the
immune system to support the immune
system so take one of these down
nighttime routine mm-hmm
okay
now I take Goldenseal
all the time right so I take it every
single night for my nighttime routine
golden seal speaks for itself it always
has it just speaks for itself right
there right
and of course you know the vibration the
frequency and that's another thing right
I can hold supplements
hold them in my hands you know
and I can feel the frequency and the
vibration within the supplementation and
and you you may have that too you may
have that ability too you may have that
same ability right to actually be able
to feel that vibration
to feel that energetic connection so
that's what I do with my supplements
I've had people hand me supplementation
right in my hand and be like this and
like no no it's great it's great I would
hold it and instantly going right up my
arm boom into my into my body into my
system right up to my neurons I can feel
the vibration the frequency I can
connect to that spiritual nature to that
product and I can be like no no way give
me another one to try oh I could feel it
and feel that that sensation the
difference between the spiritual nature
the difference between the purification
the energy and the frequency I can feel
it right and that's what I can do and
that's the difference like pure cilantro
right
I can feel it in the cilantro okay
and that's that's you know just like
that I can feel it in here and it should
feel the same way as pure and the
frequency to that plant I should feel
the same way when I hold
right there
right when I hold that or I hold the
propolis which is an insane frequency
for me right there so that's another one
right there I want to talk about that
for a second right
I should feel the same frequency
when you're feeling that living plant
right out of your garden when you're
feeling that live plant these are the
things I think about on my my like
moment at night that five minutes I get
that eight minutes I get at night before
bed these are the things I have to think
about all the time right it's that kind
of thing for my own life and so now I
want to just talk to you guys about my
nighttime routine but I want to tell you
it's not just about what I take it's
about everything that goes into it and
everything that goes about it like the
propolis the connection to the quality
of that propolis
which is incredible the quality that
they have like you can check
themergy.com and you check it out and
you can talk to them you'll hear they'll
tell you about how what's really going
on with this propolis right anyway I
could feel that I know that frequency
that vibration and that connection and
it's the same thing as like the gold
seal but I'm going to take some gold and
seal now because I take gold and seal
um
and here's the thing with Goldenseal
you'll know it when you taste it too
when it enters your body if you're
spiritually connected if you're
connected even if look even if maybe
your connection is buried
right
maybe it's buried but other things in
your life but it's still there
Underneath It All
that frequency that connection that
vibration your spiritual connection your
Consciousness right connecting to your
subconsciousness connection to your soul
right all of that could be suppressed
you could be somebody where it's
suppressed
but you still have it in you
but it's hard to use it
when you have products that aren't pure
right so when you're using products that
aren't pure it's hard to decipher and
weed through and navigate through those
products so if you have this vibration
the spiritual connection this energetic
connection you have the intuitive power
inside of you but it's suppressed and
it's buried
and you're then with some junky products
or some products that are low quality
and all this that have natural flavors
and all this other stuff in it right
you may not be able to fish through that
to navigate through that yet in your
life because it's suppressed right or
you may be somebody where it's not
suppressed and you have that that
intuition spot on not just intuition but
your frequency your vibration everything
is just on you're spiritually connected
all of it's on right so then you know
and that's when you know when you have
also a good goal until that's how I do
it too it's like okay well then yeah
um and you can feel it go down right
same thing with propolis right
I've tried every propolis almost every
single propolis I could ever get my
hands on out there because I've always
been a propolis fiend because of soc
telling me propolis is so important
right
and so good so I've tried so many and so
many
that say they're alcohol free but still
have propylene glycol in it it's so
confusing like the whole thing is
confusing and that's a thing like that's
what you you don't have to disclose the
tiniest bit of stuff that's out there
for so many reasons for so many people
out there but the point is is that this
right here I mean you know when you
actually use it the difference if you've
used other propolises you know the
difference right you know the difference
it's like when when you get when you get
that hit
and you taste it and the thing is is
this
that I connect to that that's my
nighttime routine it's knowing all these
things right and connecting to it which
is really really it's fun too in the
sense because you it's something that
it's just it feels so good
a licorice
so I've been taking licorice forever
it's just one of those herbs right that
I've been taking forever so I just I'm
I've Loved licorice from when I was a
child
I take it it's part of my nighttime
routine because I've been taking it my
whole life and I just love it and I've
had to deal with low quality licorice's
when I was younger I had to deal with
low quality licorice products I had to
deal with licorice types of candy that
weren't the fake candy but the real
licorice candy right I've had to deal
with those I've had to deal with all the
different forms of licorice licorice
powders
where I've had some bad licorice powders
out there throughout the years 20 30
years ago trying different licorice's
I've had licorice where there was
alcohol in it lots of alcohol in the
licorice all these things and I waited
like a lifetime for a company to step it
up to actually step it up into gear
and make a licorice that I can feel good
about taking for myself and recommend a
friend a loved one anybody and
especially someone with chronic illness
right out there in the world knowing
that when they go to their doctor they
say hey to their doctor hey Dr MD can I
take this licorice knowing that the
doctor might be like whoa that stuff
looks good but
the point is my whole life I've been
waiting for like a licorice that stood
apart that stands apart
and no no junk in it of all these
different kinds of things like you know
the whole bit and that's the key right
there like high quality so I take
licorice
myself I've been taking it my whole life
I love the taste of Licorice and when
you get a licorice
right that is pure
you can taste it so I love connection
like that connection connecting to that
taste right that vibration that
frequency because of herbs
right the whole herbal thing
the frequency the vibration of herbs
everything about it it's grown for
humankind right all of that
I connect to and I think about right
so anyway
hmm
cheers
and there's a there's a flavor of
licorice right
and I've known people who hate the
flavor of licorice
and then I say well try the Bemidji one
and see what you think they try
everything like why how come I like the
taste of licorice now right so there's
that whole thing and then there's B12
right
okay supports the nerves that's what B12
does it supports the nerves and it
supports energy because and you hear
people out there they'd be like well B12
is is great for energy and you hear
people talk about that out there right
and I'm like well
I want a B12 that I know is the best
that could be out there okay and that's
just you know in my life and everything
so I take the B12
right
we're getting through the nighttime
routine I'm gonna make some food too as
well right if you're somebody that's
saying hey ew you take a lot of stuff
well I worked a 20-hour day the other
day and the day after that was an
18-hour day and so and that's with
personalized stuff that's what regular
stress that's what people relying on me
that's trying to get the information out
to the world that's what trying to
create you know the podcast that's what
trying to do all the things that I want
to do
that's what try and do like four hours
of sleep that night you know what I mean
and here's the thing I'm not on
stimulants
so I don't choose stimulants right now
I'm going to tell you right now Heart to
Heart right now a heart to heart I do
not blame you if you have to use a
stimulant I do not judge you I do not
blame you if you have to use coffee if
you have to use matcha tea if you have
if you have to use right Kombucha Tea if
you have to use something with caffeine
in it if you're doing energy drinks if
you're doing if you have to survive by
actually doing stimulants
by having to do all the caffeine stuff
and the chocolate stuff I am not going
to say one word I am not going to
denounce it I'm not going to say look
you know why would you do that I'm not
going to judge you I'll never judge you
because guess what
there's a reason why you're using
stimulants there's a reason why and it's
not your fault
it's not your fault you're not the
reason why you're a mommy that might be
on all this caffeine while breastfeeding
or you're you're somebody that's on all
this caffeine or you're a runner and you
know you're an actual Runner out there
and you run races and you do all these
things and you're jacked up on all these
energy drinks and caffeine and
everything else that has done I'm not
saying any of that's bad bad I'm just
saying that I choose not to do it
I choose to stay off of all the
stimulants
that's what I do in my personal life
that's how I am so stimulant free but
then I want to rely on Nature's real
natural natural right energetic the
vibration of nature things that are that
are important for our bodies and our
bodies needs right the more our body
utilizes things right and so you know I
like a pure B12 like this is the
adenosilcobalamin methylcobalamin the
right balance
right so that's the one right there
so anyway you guys
just run through some of these things
right there
but I don't do caffeine and if you're
doing caffeine I don't judge you because
you might be stuck doing the caffeine
because you're trying to survive that's
what I mean I don't judge you I don't
right because I know that you might be
tired you might be fatigued you might be
having problems you might be like
energetically down you might be
struggling you might have stress you
might have losses you might have all
these different things and in the
caffeine is pushing you through and I
will never ever
ever doubt you
for who you are and why you have to use
a stimulant to survive and push through
you don't think I don't have friends
that have really hard situations where
they've had to start the stimulants all
the way from childhood you know so yeah
I totally get it
I'm all about of course getting you know
getting healthier healthier strong
strengths you don't need stimulants but
whatever that's another talk on another
day anyway what I love about the B12 is
no natural flavors
no flavors
in there if you guys just got on here
talking about why I support them regime
talking about my nighttime routine if
you just got on now I fully endorse
Bemidji because it's about high time
because I want them to be out there I
need people to know there are
opportunities where there is really
incredible stuff out there and I don't
want that to disappear someday you know
I want to give my full support and
pledge my full support to a company
that's actually doing things that I
haven't seen anybody do out there the
four incredible things I talked about
earlier so if you just got here now
watch us from the beginning and you'll
hear the four incredible things where it
is mind-blowing to what the company does
and the difference and how it works and
when you hear those you be the judge and
I'm telling you right now it's like it's
it's mind-blowing really okay so I just
want to say that right a little later
after dinner I'll show you how I take my
wind down supplements if you guys just
got here after dinner which I'm gonna
make some food I'm going to talk about
my winding down supplementation which
I'm going to show you I take and what I
visualize and what I see and all of it
so I'm excited about that right there so
and the thing is I didn't even talk
about these wind down supplements but
we'll talk about them in a little bit
and I'm excited about that so I'm going
to make some noise right here
so I like Nori's at night because it's
light I don't want a lump of lead I
don't want a big hunk of bacon or a pork
chop in my gullet what I'm trying to
fall asleep you know what I mean like I
don't want that happening you know I
mean let's look if you if you want to do
that if you want to have pork chops
before bed I'm just totally right I get
it 100 that's fine but I like something
lighter and it changes for me too it
changes this isn't the like only thing I
have every single night it's not that I
just have you know it's not that I just
have this right here where I'm having
Nori rolls and that's only it and that's
all so I eat a lot of different things
you guys have known throughout all the
time so let me just get a blade out here
all right so first of all I'm gonna chop
up a few things let me chop up a pepper
really quick I love Peppers right I love
all different kinds of peppers too okay
so this is a bell pepper right
so so what I'm doing is I'm cutting some
slices of bell pepper right here okay so
I'm going to cut a few slices
real quick here
all right
and then
I'm going to line this into the Nori
right here if you can see this right
there
okay this is really fresh and this is a
live and that's another thing too I like
doing raw dinners not like cooked
dinners too
I like cooked dinners okay don't get me
wrong but I also like raw dinners
because of the frequency all of it you
know everything about it here's an
orange right here I'm gonna moisten that
I'm gonna moisten this in a second I'm
just not going to moisten it yet because
if you moisten it too early what happens
is all of a sudden it just shrivels up
it gets all wet it falls apart right
and so that's important to know right
there
um
let's go a little bit more on this let's
do it so let's get some Tomatoes going
so I got red bell not red but I got
sorry red cherry tomatoes here I also
have these other
larger cherry tomatoes right so I'm
cutting these up a little bit I'm gonna
put some nice fresh tomatoes in this
roll up right there you can make these
as fat as you want you can make them
as skinny as you as skinny as you know
you want with these two like you can
make these rollers real big you can make
these roll ups really
thin you can do either or I love this as
a nighttime meal because of the fact
that it's all living right so I like
knowing that the food is all alive now
if you know like medical medium recipes
and everything you know we do lots of
cooked ones right we do we do um lots of
raw ones you have the choices you
they're there for you which is amazing
that's what's incredible about it it's
not one size fits all so that's the
incredible thing about mm info it's not
one size fits all and I'll give you an
example this is just one of my nighttime
routines right here this supplementation
for what's happening in my life in the
moment for what I'm going through what
I'm doing see that's why it's not one
size fits off it was one size fits all
then this would be the only thing
forever
but it's not it changes could change in
two weeks it could change in a week it
can change in like a month but it's
never one size fits all because we
change right what's happening around us
changes
which is really you know interesting
right that's just life so I'm putting
some onion right here okay I sliced it
kind of thin
so what I did
sliced it kind of thin you guys see that
right there okay
so we got that
now let's get a little bit of cilantro
in here so what I do is you can couple
of options you can cut the cilantro
chop it up right
recommend chopping it up if you want it
in a roll up
because the stems
get a little bit problematic now I'm
using which what you're seeing right
here what you're noticing is I'm using
the cilantro as a leafy green if you
guys came on here just now I talked
about some powerful reasons why I use
the beverage supplements right and and
I've been and now you know like my God
the stuff is so incredible for what
they're doing the connection that I have
with them spiritually and emotionally
and the vibrations and the frequencies
everything I talked about right
it's amazing and I love to make a
connection to my food too and that's
what we're talking about here so I'm
putting a little onion in here
right there right
there we go and well I like to connect
to the food I'm making so I think about
the onions I think about the power
onions have right because onions are
incredible for the immune system onions
are an herb and I like to remember that
see a lot of people forget that onions
or herbs and they don't make that
connections it's important to make that
connection because you're looking at
herbal medicine with an onion that's
what you're looking at you're looking at
herbal medicine with an onion so I like
having that connection to an onion like
that right which is important to me so
I'm going to put a little bit of this
orange and think about what it took for
this orange to grow so my nighttime
routine is about all these things this
is it right here it's about thinking
about this orange and then psychically
trying to connect to where this orange
came from
what tree it came off of
if I sit there in a meditation just for
one or two minutes
I can connect to the tree even if I
don't know where the tree really is but
I can connect to I can transport that
connection right that frequency and
connect to that frequency continuity I
can make continuity between the orange
and my hand and to the tree it came from
and I love to do that at night when I'm
making you know food when I'm eating the
food I'm putting a couple of drops on
here on the sheet
and I'm gonna be making a dipping sauce
any second so I'm just going to roll
this up
and then I'm gonna make a nice dipping
sauce now the dipping sauce is hot you
may not like hot stuff then keep the
heat out and that's okay so that's a
Nori roll right there that's a on the
thinner side okay all right that's on
the thinner side right there let me just
give you a little close-up on that Nori
roll on a nice plate so you can see that
close-up okay there it is wow it's
amazing great focus on that I love it so
that's the Nori roll right there that's
a thin one it's alive it's fresh it's
living it's got the orange squeezed
orange right to moisten it it's ready
let's make a dipping sauce and then
we'll make a couple more rolls
pumped up about it I really am dipping
sauce
it's gonna be an orange dipping sauce
right
don't throw around glass balls
yeah
so you know here it is cut the orange
squeeze the orange
right in I mean even
grab a little bit of a strainer really
quick squeeze that through so I'm
catching the seeds to make life easy
right here while we're live
while we're live and doing this
so I'm making this orange juice dipping
sauce
which I just absolutely adore because
I've had it so many times in my life and
I love it because it's so fresh it's so
alive and I think about the vitamin C
that's in that orange juice right
you know right that Sailors on the ocean
you heard this I talked about this in
early podcasts Sailors on the ocean if
they didn't have a lime or a lemon or an
orange and they were out there on the
water too long
the men would get scurvy right that
their immune systems would fall apart
they would just lose their vitality
right they were they could not exist on
jerky because that's what they had they
had jerkies what they had right so it
was only jerky that's all they had they
were chewing that jerky and then
they would lose
their health
because they did not have that vitamin C
which was critical so we're making a
dipping sauce right
that's looking good right there
all right
so in this dipping sauce I'm gonna put a
little bit of honey in this dipping
sauce let's go
you guys know how I feel about honey
right another thing I like to connect
you right there is the honey now I put a
decent amount in there because I'm
making this dipping sauce hot that's the
way I like it right
and
that's the way I really like it let me
mix this up right there to begin with so
I have the
um
I got the honey in here with the orange
juice let me just mix this up right
there you go
get that moving in there
so this is a sweet and hot sauce
I love it at night it's got the glucose
from the orange juice it's got the
glucose incredible glucose from the raw
honey which is incredible on its own
right you're talking about the glucose
and then you're talking about
phytochemical compounds in the honey you
guys probably heard my podcast right the
raw honey podcast episode
Right medical meeting podcasts at Apple
podcast
okay so I don't know if you've if you've
heard that
all right mixing that up a little bit
now I need the heat
so I need some peppers
oh
got my Peppers right here whoa here we
are I keep them in my pajama pocket
the only thing is if you fall asleep
with them all in your pajama pocket
right
and
I don't know they just find their way in
the bed and then you got these really
blazing hot peppers you're kind of like
rolling around in the sheets with I
don't know if that's a good idea I don't
know why you're dead asleep I really am
not sure if that's a good idea so maybe
I shouldn't keep them in my pajama
pocket but I usually do right
all right hot peppers right there these
are cayennes I'm going to show you I'm
gonna do a little cut on these cayennes
look at that right so I'm gonna do a
little bit of a
now keep in mind do not rub your eyes
man I'm telling you right now be careful
what you rub you rub your eyes you rub
your face you rub your cheek whatever it
is you got to be careful because these
suckers they get on the fingers they're
hot I see people they you know like they
get in trouble with these they just do
right so let's get this into my sauce
right like look see I'm putting my
finger on the knife you see how I did
that right now it wouldn't be spot to be
like oh okay um hey guys yeah hold on
here I'm fixing my
foreign
fixing my eyeliner
fixing my false eyelashes right now so
just bear ah so you you just don't want
to do that
okay so be careful okay
so I'm gonna mix these hot this hot
pepper in here look at that that is the
dipping sauce right there look at that
nice little close-up on there nice
little Focus if we can get it so here's
what I do okay I don't eat just one of
these you might be like oh yeah that's
not gonna get me far what is he just
eating one of these and that's it
and and you're right like no I'm not
eating just one of those
I'm gonna I make them a bunch of them at
night right I do
and it's an experience when you're
connecting to the frequency of the food
you guys can use your psychic powers you
guys can use your psychic ability you
can use your intuition you could use all
of it and you can connect to the the
tree that orange came from I know I can
I know you can you can connect to the
different things so anyway you got
options here I don't like doing big ones
like this you see this right here okay
that's four right five whatever watch
this right so
check this out right I like making them
like that right
look at that
some might bite the dust totally some
might totally bite the dust but that's
all right right
if you guys just came on here nighttime
routine watch this video from the start
there's mind-blowing information about
why you know our immune system and
everything and all this stuff that's
here man wait wait do you hear it
so you got your plate right here you can
use a small plate use a big plate
whatever but this is a bigger plate
because what I usually do is a lot more
than these but I'm putting them on here
hopefully they don't fall apart on me
here in front of you guys when you guys
aren't watching they come out so good
but when you guys are watching why do
they come out all tore up and crap
that's what I want to know like what's
what's jinxing me on this right here man
it's like when I'm making myself they
don't look like like this when I
make them myself they actually look like
incredible when I'm alone and I'm making
them alone they look amazing
like really I don't know when I'm being
watched or something like that is there
something that changes it because that
one's like terrible man
you know so let's make another one
let's make another one so I want to make
one more here and we'll and we'll just
you know we'll cut through this so if
you guys just came on here I'm making
some Nori rolls part of my nighttime
routine right here okay
here we go
squeezing a little orange on the I could
eat 10 of these I could eat 10 of these
if you guys just got on here hang on
because we're going to talk about my
sleepy sleepy relax
committed stress reducing part of my
nighttime routine and it's coming up I
just want to make another one of these
really quick let's use red bell pepper
how about that
let's try that
let's knock that stem off boom
take that core out boom let's make it
fast
real fast
right
you guys are looking on their pajamas
and you think I just got out of the
hospital I didn't these are my pajamas
man
okay
my Hospital Band still on no I clipped
it off I'm just kidding
all right so I got some red bell pepper
in there I got some white like the
Dahlia onion right sweet onion how about
that and you know you can even put Apple
in here
now I like munching on apples throughout
the night if I'm working I love apples
at my desk apples are part of my
nighttime routine I love an Apple at
night always do it doesn't have to go
into a Nori roll right I'm putting Apple
pieces in the Nori roll but you don't
have to do that you can just have app I
like Apple's plain right not just an
adorable but I like them plain I love it
just a plain Apple you get in touch with
that Apple you know that flavor of that
apple right
I put some apple in there let's put some
cilantro in here now I'm going to chop
them you don't have to chop up the
cilantro you can keep it like this if
you don't mind I like chopping it up I
also like it like that too boom let's
roll it up
I can't wait to taste that dipping sauce
that's gonna be insane right I'm gonna
put a little bit of orange juice right
on the edge here check it out you see
that right on the edge boom you don't
need a mat
you don't need a sushi mat you don't you
know I see people they pull out the
sushi mat and they're trying to roll
that thing up right they have the thing
in there trying to roll it up in their
Sushi mat and if things just like all
crazy and stuff and they're like
GMAT I'm like dude what are you doing
you can roll a billion of these without
the mat you know you don't need the mat
right so let's slice these up who am I
saying that right when I just made the
worst one over there
so maybe I do need the map you guys
think I need the map
if you guys weren't watching I didn't
need the mat
right
let me pop these on here right here okay
maybe it's because I'm rushing I'm
relaxing when I do it alone chilling out
okay there we go right I got some noise
right there
I don't know why they look so
today all right let's go let's get one
in here that's what the hot sauce okay
um
oh my God
[Music]
I'm gonna use something to drink
wait
hold on
oh my God
hold on I'm just gonna torture myself
one more time
okay
that is hot that's really hot let me
tell you something
delegate your sinuses to run
um
that's medicine right there
that's all I could say that's medicine
um
just so you know
I grew these Peppers right
should I grew these peppers
amazing cayennes I love growing my own
peppers hot peppers and then I love
connecting with them they're grown for
me right they're grown for what my body
needs because a plant can actually
detect what your body needs when you're
growing it yourself so you're sitting
here you're watering it
you grab a couple of caterpillars off
the plant
you you pluck a couple of leaves that
are kind of like a little dried up and
you just you nurture that plant you take
care of that plant and that plant knows
you it knows you it knows you're going
to consume the food it knows you're in
touch with it it knows who you are
plants know who we are when we're
nurturing that plant that plant's
receiving that nurturing it's receiving
that information
it's receiving that vibration that
frequency it's receiving all that and
then we're connecting that's how it
works I'm gonna have one more of these
and I'm gonna do my time T real quick
remember one more if you guys
come on
what's insane
hmm
I usually go back to work after there
but since I'm not working
since I'm not working tonight I'm just
talking to you guys which is really fun
I'm going to show you my sleeping
routine really quick but let's just make
some time tea really quick got a cup
right here boom
need some time got some time right here
time that came out of my garden right
I'm going to put this time right in that
cup that's how I'm going to do it
okay
now you can do a couple different things
if you want honey in here
I can put a little honey in here if you
want honey in your time tea take the
time out first right
put the honey in
okay
nice
I think someone said way too much honey
someone just complained
instead I used way too much honey
SOC just told me somebody's freaking out
about how much honey I just used
well I'm sorry I hope I didn't offend
you
listen to my last one of my last
podcasts that I just did like the raw
honey podcast
check it out when you can listen to it
and and recommended podcast at Apple
podcast check it out when you get a
chance anyway I put the honey in here
let's get the hot water in
nice
I know someone's upset about how much
honey I put in I'm not trying to get you
upset
I want you happy
and I just want to put a little bit more
honey in there not to make you upset
don't get upset stop getting upset
I'm going to mix that honey up in that
because that's glucose right there for
my brain If you hear the Honey episode
you'll know what I'm talking about right
I don't run on caffeine I don't run on
stimulants I run on glucose because my
neurons need the glucose they need it
because they're firing like crazy
because of all the because of all the
information I have to receive from SOC I
have a very unfun job of receiving that
information and then trying to put that
information into words as a messenger
for everybody else I got some incredible
time tea going right there take a look
close like that and you can take a look
this way too
right here I'm gonna sip it
oh my God so delicious too so let's talk
about the winding down part of my
routine my nighttime routine where I'm
winding down because God knows I need to
kind of that winding down moment because
so much is going on so much information
is going on so I start with lemon balm
right there so make sure I get my lemon
balm in me okay it's a commentative
that's what I love about it right and
when it's high quality in my opinion man
when it's pure like this there's a whole
different frequency so it's a
commentative right it's for the nerves
for stress relaxation so I like to send
that down
boom that's down right there okay so
let's get some Gaba going
how about that
a little bit of Gaba going
right
so here we are
Gaba counters excess brain stimulation
so think about that I mean in your life
how much excess brain stimulation do you
have
you know ask your doctor what's right
for you whatever but I have a lot of
excess brain stimulation too much from
everything that's going on from hearing
SOC from living my life having all the
responsibilities from doing all the work
right so a lot of stimulation right
there
hmm
send that Gaba down right there next
magnesium
right helps with muscles that's the
whole thing too magnesium helps with
muscles
okay I love it for the nervous system
too it's another thing too all right
magnesium Down the Hatch and then
right before I go to bed this is how I
do it okay you ask your doctor what's
right for you and all that but how I do
it is I take my melatonin right before I
turn off the light and go to bed
foreign