we're talking about bowel obstruction
something that's happening every day to
a lot of people we're going to go into
why it's happening what the mystery is
and i'm making
garden potato dish right on top of it
which is really fun
so i got some onions grew those out of
the garden which is really awesome
potatoes growing out of the garden
dirt's still on them so i gotta give
them a quick rinse is what i'm gonna do
good to see you guys i thought i would
come on
see how everybody's doing we're talking
about a couple of different things to
talk about bowel obstructions i don't
know if you guys are seeing it a lot of
people are getting belly aches
they're getting pain and cramping
many are going to the emergency room
they're vomiting they're having problems
and then they're being told you got a
bowel obstruction get ready for surgery
they stick a pipe down your throat then
you got a pipe in your stomach and
they're sucking air out is what they're
doing so you sit in the hospital bed for
a day you sit in a hospital bed for two
days while you got a pipe down your
throat sitting in your stomach and the
pipe is sucking up air
and you're being told we're gonna run
another mri cat scan we're going to run
another test right here and we're going
to see how that obstruction is doing and
you're like oh my god they say your
obstruction is still there so we have to
do emergency surgery and you go and you
get a big part of the colon cut out and
you get that cut out and everything and
then they put you back together and they
sew you up they you're in the hospital
bed and like okay your bowel
obstruction's better now and what's
happening is it's not about obstruction
maybe some people
are getting bowel obstructions out there
because they do but there's this wave a
wave of chronic bowel obstructions
hospitals are getting filled with people
running in getting bowel obstructions
and it's not happening so this is so
that's you sharon lee norton says that's
me thank you for covering this topic
absolutely this is a really important
topic we're going to talk about real
bowel obstructions too but these are the
mysterious
bowel obstructions people are getting
diagnosed with that aren't real bowel
obstructions because it's a bug going
around and it's a bug that go is going
around right now people had the bug two
weeks later after the bug boom they get
hit with this bowel obstruction they're
at the emergency room so we're gonna
cover it in detail but i gotta get my
food going
so i'm gonna make a potato dish just
something quick thrown together this is
really cool i got these patty pans right
here out of the garden which is really
exciting you guys good to see you guys
coming on here so i got these these are
straight out of the garden have you guys
grown these before these are so fun to
grow they grow so quick the plants get
so strong right
and then these patty pans are so fun to
pick so great look at that is that crazy
i mean the way they look right love
growing every year for years i've been
growing those for so long now i love it
we're gonna throw that in the pan too
onions like i said they came out of the
garden i cured them right so they're not
that they're not fresh out of the garden
they're actually cured they've been
sitting around for a while right you got
to watch out they don't mold up you got
to know how to cure them okay cilantro
out of the garden too how exciting is
that right
and then the potatoes i showed you and
i'm going to show you again we're going
to do a little rinse and wash good to
see you guys coming on here and
peppers
hot peppers out of the garden now these
are green right so i picked these early
so i usually like to leave them red
because green peppers are not ripe and
that's what gives people trouble unripe
peppers right unripe ones and i talk
about that all the time
but
these are
that see how it's almost turning red and
i'll show you some close-ups in a little
bit too i'll tell you why i picked them
green to begin with which is pretty
funny because i don't usually do that i
picked them green for a reason
because i had a bunny rabbit that was
going after all the peppers and i was
like how's that how's that possible
because those are hot but you know
squirrels and bunny rabbits were really
hungry
so we're live right now you guys we're
live and i'm excited so let me just cook
a little bit we're going to talk about
bowel obstructions as well
and we're going to do a little demo
about that talk about the gut a little
bit too
so let's get going let's get some onions
right here so i'm going to cut some
onions right now
i love when onions come out of the
garden it's really
exciting everything that comes out of
the garden always seems like it tastes
the best right
so that's that's what it always seems
like i'm going to put the garbage can
right here too so i can drop some in
there
and i like to save all that too and
throw it in a pile and
make some future dirt right
so what i'm doing is i'm just getting a
couple of onions
ready here
good to see you guys coming on
so we're live right now
i'm excited making a garden
vegetable potato dish
why not
kind of excited about that right i got
the pan on right there it's getting hot
peeling back some onions and we're going
to talk about bowel obstructions at the
same time a lot of people have
chronic bowel obstructions because they
have crohn's colitis they have difficult
with their intestinal tract because
difficulties with their intestinal tract
because
they're inflamed so inside their
intestinal tract they're inflamed so as
the food is moving through their
intestinal tract they're having many
obstructions all the time
there's a lot of people that have to
live with that and they have to go
through that
okay and then there's that random acute
bowel obstruction right it's acute it's
random
okay
and we have those two out there people
do get about obstruction i'm going to
talk about a couple of stories about
that how serious this could be and then
there's this mystery about obstruction
that's not about obstruction that's
happening after someone gets a bug so
they're getting a bug that bug either
gets diagnosed as the flu it gets
diagnosed as the c word it gets
diagnosed as
something like that or a stomach bug or
diagnosed as food poisoning
right and then everything's fine it goes
away a couple weeks later all is fine
they're back to work they're back to
life and then they get stomach pain
and then they're like vomiting
something's wrong they go to the
emergency room and they're like bowel
obstruction we're live right now at
medicalmedium.com so check this out you
guys i'm streaming this live right now
at
medicalmedium.com
my website so you guys got to check that
out when you get a chance that i'm
streaming this on the website how cool
is that i'm really excited about
we're tick-tock live right now to you
guys just so you know
nick lewis on facebook good to see you
youtube or nicholas on youtube right
denise ron here right
lovely leaf leafy greens is on there
from youtube
so let's just cut up some onions let's
get them in the pan the pan's getting
hot right
is plant-based butter okay that's a
question we could talk about that later
too so we're on getter we're on youtube
we're on rumble
we're on facebook
we're on tick-tock
i mean we're all over the place we're on
twitch
don't get me started with twitch
right let's just get these in the pan
i mean look i haven't been on here in a
while
so
i'll keep it cool i'll keep it up upkeep
control keep that control
because i don't want to start doing the
twitch dance right now
i want to get this meal going really
so i'm cutting some onions came fresh
out of the garden
at one point and then i cured these
they've been sitting around for a while
good to see you guys david witchen you
want to see the twitch dance
okay melissa do potatoes become toxic
when they start to turn green
yeah don't eat them when they're green
that's not a good idea don't eat them
when they're green if it's all you got
it's the only food you have you can peel
back some of the green or all the green
you see right but i don't eat cream
potatoes
so a lot of fruits and vegetables that
if you know that that become toxic
for a lot of different reasons
just like when you have meat meat
becomes toxic when it's when it's brown
you know when meat turns brown you know
what they do they coat the meat
they coat beef with a chemical right a
sulfur chemical and that sulfur chemical
keeps it from turning brown in the store
that's just really that's that's that's
not good
that's not good let's get some uh
everything has the potential of having a
problem right
so you got to know
know what to do when to do whatever
thrown some onions in the pan let's get
this cooking
jennifer says when in doubt throw it out
on facebook right there
guys we're live right now
i'm gonna put another onion in here
one more let's do that
let's get another onion going
guys we're talking about bowel
obstructions i want to do a little demo
real quick too
about it
right
so the emergency rooms
for the last six to eight weeks
have been filling up with a lot of these
mysterious bowel obstruction cases
it's usually a couple of weeks after
they were sick
with a cold a flu
or the seed
right
and then they get better they're moving
forward and all of a sudden they get
this bowel obstruction because
that bug they had
created
inflammation
in the colon
not allowing food to get through so easy
but yet it's not a bowel obstruction
it's just an inflamed area
and then what they do is they stick a
pipe
down your throat
another thing this bug is doing is
creating a neurological spasm
a vagus nerve spasm
in the intestinal tract locking it up
causing paralysis of the intestinal
tract so it's not really technically
about obstruction there's a temporary
paralysis and inflammation
that's happening
and then what the sad part is if they
don't have a good doctor if they don't
have a good health practitioner that's
looking out for them they'll go and get
the surgery
they'll get thrown into the surgery so
there's thousands of people across this
country right now and also other places
around the world
that are getting bowel surgery and
getting a piece of their colon removed
for no reason because they don't know it
at the emergency room and at the
hospitals they don't know that this is a
bug going around
causing temporary paralysis of
the colon
and it's been being misdiagnosed as
about structure now don't get this
confused with real bowel obstructions
people can have a real bowel obstruction
i've seen it happen throughout the years
finally he is back on right then over
there on youtube
so i'm gonna get some more stuff cooking
in here let's do let's get potatoes in
there now and give this potato rinse now
this is a
that's a garden potato right there let's
see if we can take a look at it maybe
even get close up that's a garden potato
right there you guys
i'm actually proud of that potato
because like i've never grown a potato
that big in my life out of all the
potatoes i've grown right i've grown
potatoes and they're really tiny and
they weren't supposed to be tiny but
this one's like unbelievably big it's
like it's crazy i'm just gonna pop it in
here and get a little water on it if you
guys don't mind i'm gonna rinse off the
dirt
it's got all the garden dirt on there
that's huge right kim you see that isn't
that crazy that's actually huge
so i got some onions frying up in the
pan right now yeah that was like crazy
right congratulations thank you i'm
honored
thank you charlie i'm totally honored
right there that you actually
congratulated me on that that's really
nice of you
so i just washed off this potato
there we go
and that's a red potato right you guys
not a sweet potato you know it's not a
sweet potato it's a red potato let's cut
it in half
let's hope it's okay inside right not
bad it actually is we'll get a close-up
too on that in a second just get these
onions okay there we go guys that's the
potato right there
a big old red potato right
so let's chop it up let's get it on this
pan
so i'm gonna do
i'm doing some smaller pieces i'm not
doing big hunks i'm doing kind of
smaller pieces like thinner pieces
i want this to cook pretty quick
you know too big and hunky they're not
going to cook that quick you guys know
you have experience with this too you
guys ever do them in the pan like this
right
medical medium style or maybe your style
the way you do it in the pan how about
your style right
okay
if you guys just got on here live we're
talking about bowel obstructions listen
if you have crohn's colitis
celiac crohn's colitis if you have any
kind of ibs if you have narrowing if you
have inflammation and swelling if you
have pockets if you have
mega colon if you have something you've
been diagnosed diverticulitis
inflammation diverticulosis whatever you
could always get a small obstruction
temporary
obstruction a lot of people take
laxatives right we're talking about
a mysterious obstruction
all right
we got this pan going right
here and i'm going to throw some squash
in here now too some patty pants let's
do that good to see you guys but glad
i'm glad i'm here with you
it's exciting so i'm going to cut this
patty pan in half like this
have you guys seen these
right patty pan squash
i'm gonna give this the same kind of
thing
just chop it up in pieces
like
this i'm going to do it that way too
it's nice squares in here
and you can take like these the butts on
these are softer than other types of
squashes so if you want to keep that
butt in there you can same with the stem
that stem will cook if you cook it good
now if you're not going to cook these
long you want to take this little butt
out right here if you're not going to
cook if you're not going to cook that
long so take a look you guys see this
you want to get these
out of here if you're not going to cook
it that long and thoroughly right you
want to take those out because they're
kind of hard
and you've got teeth problems or
you got somebody got a relative or
somebody or a friend that comes over and
they just had dental work done and they
got two crowns all redone and everything
and you leave that in there
you never know right
so i'm gonna cut this patty pan in half
like that
right
this is great
i'm going to put the lid on that too in
a moment we're going to let that cook
down look at that
i only put one potato in there
but it was one big potato so
i mean you can do three potatoes in
there you can do four you can do as many
potatoes as you want in your dish you
can make it the way you want it right
this is kind of a medley of stuff
all right
let me
do this make sure this is high on
maximum
put this lid on top let that steam up
and cook let's get down to it we're
going to throw some peppers in there in
a little while
and the cilantro we're going to throw on
last which is really exciting we'll do
that too
so let's get into it a little bit you
guys just got here talking about bowel
obstructions there's mysterious bowel
obstructions happening everywhere
hospitals are getting filled with people
so let's go into this
i have
personally saved
a couple of people
you know old friends been friends with
for many years
got a hold of me and said i'm in the
hospital right now i gotta pipe down my
throat
in my stomach
they said i got a bowel obstruction but
i've never had a problem like that
before
okay so here we go
so there's a new bug that's been going
on it's out there it's been happening
for about two months now a little bit
over two months i think it's gonna
eventually get to the tail end pretty
soon it's a lot of different bugs
floating around right now a lot of
different flues so forth and all that
right and seas and all that so there's a
lot of that happening out there so
but there's there's one of the bugs
that's out there right now it gets into
people they often have congestion they
have congestion they have the sinus
problems right they have a fever they
don't feel good well i got the flu maybe
one one time to get diagnosed with oh
it's the c or oh it's the flu or doctor
says it's a cold or feels like a cold
then it goes away right
they get it to go away a weekly meeting
goes away naturally whatever maybe
they're doing some natural stuff to help
it whatever it is and eventually they're
fine they're out of the woods okay i got
over that that's great and all of a
sudden oh my god
oh my god what is this what is this
and they're either vomiting or they're
just in severe intestinal tract pain
cramping in the gut and they don't
understand what it is is this
appendicitis what is this and they go to
the emergency room
right they get to the emergency room
and then the doctor says we think it's
an obstruction we're going to do a test
and they get a test they get the cat
scan they get or an mri usually it's a
cat scan with this and that's one of the
tests they do well your cat scan shows
that you have an obstruction well i
don't i don't know why i've never had a
problem i didn't eat anything crazy
what's going on here where you got an
obstruction is what they say and this is
what's happening all in these hospitals
all in this country and around the world
are saying this doctor's like you got
ma'am you got an obstruction and in the
next room you sir you got an obstruction
i actually talked to somebody recently
an emergency room doctor who's a friend
of mine that said literally three rooms
like one room over here that's an
obstruction another person was diagnosed
with obstruction three rooms down and
then one room and then they you know
another room and then they rush them up
and there and they get them ready so
what they do is
they they get told they got this
obstruction they get a pipe down their
throat right
and the pipe is to suck air out or any
contents in the stomach so that's what
they're doing so they put the pipe down
the pipe goes down into the stomach and
then the pipe is sitting there vacuuming
it's vacuuming so now you're in bed and
you're stuck and you're like what is
this i never had this problem before i'm
told i have an obstruction and thinking
you got a pipe and it's down it's
sitting inside your stomach right here
and it's dry it's sucking air and it's
sucking air and that's what's happening
stellini says are these vegetables from
your garden yes they are they actually
are from my garden which is such a
blessing truly
um
all right so let's go into this the pipe
sits in the stomach and you sit there
for a day or two while they run you
through tests and what they tell you is
you're gonna need surgery because we see
the obstruction it's on the test it's on
the scan but what they're seeing is a
lock up yeah it's not an obstruction but
they're seeing fecal matter in an area
that had that has temporary paralysis
that's what they're seeing all right
from for all these random cases all
these random mystery cases it's not
somebody who's who's known to have
obstructions throughout their life
they've had multiple surgeries they've
got a tremendous amount of scar tissue
when they get obstructions periodically
you know that's different or someone who
gets a kink someone who actually gets a
kink in the intestinal tract where they
actually get a kink and when that kink
happens
then they're in trouble and they have to
get surgery if it can't work itself out
they need to get surgery now that's
different now that happens out there i
see a lot of people get kinks in their
colon they get kinks in their small
intestinal tract
and
that's what goes on right but this is
different this is temporary paralysis of
a certain area of the colon or
intestinal tract because the nerves
going to that stop working because the
bug that's going around in the last
couple of months
is seizing up the nerve
in that area
and then inflammation also occurs in
that area too the bug can do two things
it attacks the nerves in that area or
inflames that area of the intestinal
tract and then that swelling happens
just enough swelling along with
paralysis that food's not moving through
too easy
but the symptom isn't just because of
that the symptom is it's it's a delayed
reaction this bug has
elizabeth says it was all viral yeah
it is it's happening out there all the
time so really they're having a viral
infection
viral infection causing temporary
paralysis
of the intestinal tract or
colon okay
and then they're getting diagnosed
misdiagnosed with bowel obstruction and
they're getting their colons removed now
here's the thing after somebody that had
a c-section so say you're a woman you
had your you had a c-section
and you know that's that's
that you know during your pregnancy you
have the c-section if that happened
they'll blame the scar tissue from your
c-section as this bowel obstruction say
you're somebody that had a hernia
surgery so if anybody had any kind of
hernia surgery regardless of the hernia
surgery wherever it is if it was a
hernia to the left it was a herniated to
the right if it was a hernia in the
middle wherever the hernia was
if they did a previous hernia surgery
they'll then tell the the
patient
that the scar tissue from the hernia
surgery they had 20 years ago over here
is why they have a bowel obstruction
over here that's what they're told
they're told the bowel obstruction is
because of scar tissue from a hernia
surgery that's somewhere else now i'm
seeing this out there
happening where people had okay yeah i
had a hernia 30 years ago they'll say to
the doctor and they'll say well that
hernia scar tissue down here is the
reason why you have bowel obstruction
over here so we're going to need surgery
now and get that bowel obstruction fixed
so that's what's going on right now i'm
just going to move
this guy over a little bit and just make
sure this is cooking up
so i put the lid on the pan
it gets the moisture from the squash is
actually
moving helping everything stay moist so
nothing's burning in the pan the onion
the moisture from the onion is actually
helping too
and then i have that potato that garden
potato with this garden squash garden
onions i have it all
in the process of kind of steaming up
and cooking i have this little portable
burner i got it on maximum right now
now there are people that actually have
crohn's colitis they have
large amounts of inflammation inside the
intestinal tract and inside the colon
and so they have a narrowing
and if they eat something problematic
you can have a problem i remember a long
time ago
a doctor sent a patient to me
that had that type of inflammation that
type of swelling inside the intestinal
tract
and the patient
already had a surgery
the surgery happened because
they had
a cheeseburger at a cookout
really tough meat in the cheeseburger
that's what they said it was a big large
cheeseburger at a cookout this is an
anti-animal protein anti-vegan that's
not what this is about i'm just giving
you guys this person's experience right
and
she said that
she had the burger and then that night
she had the vomiting she had
the pain and she had a real obstruction
that meat was stuck so it was stuck the
gristle and the beef and the gristle and
that it wasn't really a soft beef
it wasn't tender and that gristle and
that beef it just all kind of locked up
by a spot that the person was already
inflamed and so that became a real
obstruction so they had to get surgery
so they had to get a piece of the colon
cut out they had to get the obstruction
fixed right they had to get the
the obstruction removed and so
i've known many stories over the years
that are something similar to this but
this is different
than what's happening right now
so
here's the interesting thing you think
that this would set off an alarm out
there so people would know so they're
they're not getting their colons
intestinal tracts being cut out right
now for no reason with a misdiagnosis of
bowel obstruction when really it's left
over from a viral infection
creating temporary paralysis
of a colon in small intestinal tract you
think that the alarm would get set off
like don't you think it would be a
little suspicious now every single
hospital has people pouring in with the
bowel obstruction diagnosis
meanwhile they're lining up colon
surgeons and they're just
just cutting people's colons out
for this mysterious bowel obstruction
problem you think they would kind of put
two and two together and be like whoa
something's wrong here
why is everybody having a bowel
obstruction how come the hospital had 30
bowel obstructions just last night how
come this hospital down the road had
another 10 how about this hospital over
here shouldn't they communicate with
each other no they don't and this is how
medicine works these days and always has
in the past no communication doesn't
matter what happens to people and who
cares
that's how it's always been in medicine
in the world of medicine so
so right now people are getting for no
reason their bowels cut out
from a viral infection that's just
creating temporary paralysis and
inflammation in the colon and small
intestinal tract now with that being
said if you're somebody though
right that you have a lot of intestinal
tract problems and you're and you've
been known to have severe constipation
from blockages
that could be an entirely different
story if you're somebody that's known to
have in your life
severe constipation
to the point where you don't go to
bathroom for a week or so and it gets
blocked up and you have obstructions of
fecal matter that's different and you're
usually taking laxatives or taking
prescription laxatives and you're
dealing with lots of doctor visits
that's a different story than someone
who hasn't had any problems at all with
any of this and that's what's happening
the hospitals are being being filled up
all around this country and around the
world with people coming in that never
had a problem at all of their intestinal
tract or colon or any issues to that
degree maybe they had a little bit of
bloating maybe they have a little
digestive weakness maybe they have
something else going on right or
something like h pylori or whatever it
is
but they never had something serious and
then they get this bowel obstruction a
couple of weeks two three weeks later or
one week later after they had a cold
and that cold was a virus that virus
going around wasn't a cold per se
um
arlene says my daughter that has celiac
ended up in the emergency room with this
throwing up well that's what it is they
end up in the emergency room throwing up
that's how it works
and as they're in the emergency throwing
up
right now what the standard protocol in
the emergency room is they admit you
into the hospital they stick a pipe down
your throat into your stomach and they
just suck up and vacuum any contact
contents and any air for the next two
days while they prep you for surgery
so you're going to take a look here
michelle l good to see you why do
stomach nerves affect nerves in my feet
though
well you know the problem is with nerves
is they tend to all somewhat connect to
each other no matter what and they all
end up in the central nervous system
which is your brain so in the end they
all have the same root going to the
brain to one way or another
so all nerves connect to another nerve
which connects to another nerve that
ends up somewhere finding its way to the
brain
and that's why because you know if you
have other nerve sensitivities from
inflammation in other areas like some
type of neuropathy or any kind of nerve
sensations nerve nerve damage nerve
issues of any kind or just inflamed
nerves from neurotoxins and stuff like
that anytime your nerves get inflamed
other nerves can hurt too in other
places it's very difficult for a lot of
people that deal with it i want to show
you right here close up on this dish
right here to you guys so what i'm doing
is i'm cooking these garden potatoes
right patty pan squash onions
i'm gonna throw a pepper in there a
little bit i want to keep on steaming
this up a little bit too get it going
got got it on high heat
talking about bowel obstructions
rosita when i eat potatoes
i need potatoes my belly swells i have
ulcerative colitis right so what i tell
people
and i talk to doctors a lot helping them
with their patients is
that
what's on the potato like what's on it
was it sour cream was it mayonnaise
was it oil was it any kind of fat like
an oil-based fat was it with
an animal fat
was it with any kind of animal fat did
it have lard on it was it fried
did it have any kind of other oil or fat
in there so that's another thing too to
keep did have milk cheese butter did it
have cream
did your potato have milk cheese butter
cream or anything like that
right
did it have any of that going on because
that's what makes it really hard did you
have your potato with
bread
which was gluten-based bread did you
have anything like that too what did you
eat that day as well so what did you eat
that day as well so all kinds of things
matter
ulcerative colitis
ulcerative colitis right means you have
problems with a lot of foods too so it's
not just potato so if you eat potato
and your
belly swells
but the belly could be swelling for the
thing you ate that morning or the thing
you ate the day before or two to three
days before someone can have a piece of
gluten bread
a week before and get swelling a week
later because the gluten stays in the
system and then it feeds all the
critters so so that's what happens milk
cheese butter
eggs any of that will stay in the
intestinal tract long term
and then will feed
any kind of critter you got going on e
coli salmonella
right h pylori c diff streptococcus
so these critters
right they sit inside the intestinal
tract they sit inside the colon
and when we have ulcerative
colitis you guys know if you know
if you know medical medium information
ulcerative colitis is what critter like
what bug is the bug with ulcerative
colitis that bug is shingles virus the
shingles virus is inside the colon if
you have ulcerative colitis
it's inflaming the colon and that's why
the blood vessels break and the bleeding
occurs the rupturing of the blood
vessels occur it's from the shingles
virus right here so the shingles virus
sits inside the colon
okay makes a camp there for many years
and that becomes ulcerative colitis so
the shingles virus if you guys know
medical medium information shingles
virus loves what milk cheese butter
even some soy
likes you know soy can feed it milk
cheese butter and gluten
right you can learn about colitis in
here how many of you guys have the
cleanse to heal book here it is right
here christine asks this how long will
this paralysis last
will it do away on its own yes it does
do away on its own
it does
um
so i don't know if you guys have seen
these
these are the manuscripts i know you
guys already probably pre-ordered it
it's the brainsaver book
right
these two books are coming out in just a
few months just letting you know it's
amazon.com us that's the brainsaver
protocols that's the brainsaver right
here book right here two incredible
books
they're over 600 pages each
and they're packed with information
that's mind-blowing over 300 symptoms
conditions i haven't talked about the
books in a while and i still want to
talk about them in more detail
eventually as you know as we get get to
get through but
check out the brainsaver books when you
get a chance
those books right there will blow your
mind
you'll have more information that's
mind-blowing it'll be really insane
christina s says how long will this
paralysis last would go away in its own
was the question before
yes tense the lat tends to last
for a couple of days
some people it lasts for a day
some people it's two days some people
it's three days
and then it starts to ease off and you
start to recover
you know and you and what a lot of
people do they'll sit in the hospital if
they have a smart doctor the doctor
would be like well you know what we're
not going to cut that person's colon out
we're going to just give it time and
then they watch the symptoms they watch
if the if the patient is feeling better
they watch as the patient's in less pain
they'll take the patient off of pain
medication
and they'll say well how are you feeling
today i know one person specifically
said you know what i'm out of here i was
in there with the pipe down into my
stomach i was in there for a day and i
started feeling better and i wanted out
and they just ripped the pipe out
and they took the wipe out and they said
i need out of here
and but yet they were getting prepped
for surgery they were actually getting
prepped for surgery
which they didn't need
so yes it tends to move on its own get
this little critter off of here for now
i want to chop up a pepper
out of the garden here art says all the
starch of the potatoes and squash in
that dish you're cooking doesn't that
promote feed yeast and fungal overgrowth
well the information that you have that
it does is misinformation so milk cheese
butter eggs
gluten feed all manners of bugs
and here's the funny thing you're you're
actually using medical medium
information by saying that
no one knew anything fed off of anything
that's medical medium information
so
nobody thought bugs feed nobody believed
viruses feed off of anything they still
don't science still doesn't but that's
medical medium information there's no
science study that shows bugs actually
feeding
off of a potato because there never was
there never will be a bug can't feed off
of a potato but a bug can feed off of
gluten but they don't have any tests
showing that out there studies showing
that either because it's medical medium
information
so what you're saying is doesn't that
starch feed
any kind of bugs like yeast and fungus
and stuff and other things and what
you're saying is i'm going to tell you
medical medium
i'm going to ask you a question you know
that is your information medical medium
because nobody knew anything fed on
anything
so you heard it from somewhere else that
started from somewhere else i heard from
somewhere else and they twisted it up
and now they now they're saying that
that will feed on this one it doesn't
feed on this
the whole concept
of critters feeding
on a food or eating is medical medium
information
but i appreciate the question it's fun
to watch your own information
come back to you
it comes back to you
skewed
twisted up but it still comes back right
it still comes back to me which is fun
to see it come back
but it's sad at the same time because
you see that information come back
twist it up
it's like twisted up and used against
the very
foods you're making right so here i am
the guy that put the information out
there about how all these bugs feed on
stuff feed on food and they actually eat
right so that's medical beam information
i go into great depths about that in the
brain saver books
and here i am right
being told by someone how
isn't that going to feed bugs
yeah being the person that put the
information out there to begin with i'm
not going to be serving you guys a meal
that will feed the bugs
michelle elle said this information
saved so many lives aw thank you
but
but anyway i'm happy you're asking that
question by the way does it feed
anything so let's talk about that
if you eat gluten gluten will feed those
bugs nobody knew that you guys have to
remember
all the eat better authors or eat better
books and eat better doctors and all
that
all they knew was to eat better and they
they only believed that processed food
would give you heart disease
cardiovascular problems that's that's
all that they had right
medical medium information
brought the truth out that gluten
actually feeds bugs it'll feed viruses
and pathogens and bacteria
and same thing with virus you know same
thing like
so
and medical medium information goes back
decades
goes back decades
nobody knew gluten fed anything only
medical medium information talked about
that
and
so with that
it's like what does what does these
bacteria and microbes that are not
beneficial what do they feed off of milk
cheese butter
they feed off of eggs
they feed off of corn too you got to be
really careful now listen if you guys
are growing some fresh organic corn out
of your own garden or you go to a
farmer's market and you get some fresh
organic corn right
somewhere
you can have some right you can have
some if you're not suffering with a lot
of different conditions if you don't
have chronic illness or something you're
not dealing with a lot of chronic
illness which so many people i see out
there have you can do some fresh corn
right out of farmer's market just
beautiful corn that's organic and you
want to eat it raw right off the cob or
you want to steam it and have it that
way that's not the end of the world but
don't do corn products if you're
somebody that's really has any kind of
autoimmune condition any kind of issue
on any level don't do any kind of like
cornstarch and corn products and
and you know
all that stuff cornbread and everything
else
sierra vasati says is the vacuum of the
stomach needed for the person to improve
or can a protocol be done at home versus
the er yes protocol can be done always
ask your doctor so sarah make sure you
talk to your doctor
but yes if it was me i would try to do a
protocol at home and i would try to
avoid the the vacuum pipe going down
through my stomach because into your
stomach because i know that that
wouldn't be what you needed
they do that
because they're trying to get air out
right
is what they're doing
but being that it's not a true
obstruction and just a paralysis you
don't need the pipe but always ask your
doctor no matter what whatever condition
you're in right so i'm i got a pepper in
here i'm going to put cilantro in here
that's going to be the last thing to top
it off and we're going to do that in a
minute so let me just get this back on
top
someone's asking on youtube new era okay
please tell about inflammation of the
thyroid
please now please tell i got a whole
book on it
groundbreaking at the time talking about
the epstein-barr virus creating thyroid
problems original medical medium
information you know it's hard when you
sound like a broken record when you put
this stuff out for the first time out in
the world that epstein-barr creates
thyroiditis and then years later
science of research is like we think
epstein-barr is now linked to the
thyroid really where'd you get it
there's no study out there
you got it from the medical medium book
millions of copies sold right here
they're back dating too now so they're
tricking people out they're back dating
stuff that's what they do
it's amazing what the medical industry
will do they'll do anything to try to
prove that they were smart when
that doesn't that's not the case
thyroid healing book has saved a lot of
lives around the world guys got to check
it out when you get a chance um
amazon.com if you're talking about
thyroiditis divert inflammation any of
that it's an incredible book it's helped
out so many people you guys know about
liver rescue
liver rescue is a book to read too check
that out when you get a chance
all the books and then the brain saver
books that are coming out this year
you guys when you read this
your mind is going to be
blown like
it's like blown
guys making a garden vegetable dish
right here it's over 300 symptoms
conditions in the brain saver book
mental health
okay
so incredible then there's two books
so
you got to get both you got to order
both
two over 600 page books
check them out amazon.com
right when you get a chance and barnes
and noble check them out you can order
them off barnes and noble as well
okay it was supposed to be one book
but it was a 1400 page book and my
publisher said
how are we to print that it's not
possible so we turned it into two books
it's incredible over a hundred over a
hundred recipes for the brain
300 symptoms conditions and protocols
it's
these are insane books man adele says my
mind is blown with all your books
incredible i'm just glad you're here
thank you and
thank you for being here check out those
brand saver books you guys when you get
a chance
you know
remember if you pre-order it now
you don't get charged for it until the
book is shipped till the books are
shipped you don't get charged for it
and you get the lower price in the end
right the link is in the profile right
there on tick tock link is in the
description you guys
so i think your dish is coming to a
point we talked about bowel obstructions
a little bit now we're going to just
chop up some cilantro and throw it in
here so we'll do that we'll get close up
on the cilantro real quick too
yep
chop up some cilantro
i like to throw it on at the end
so it's kind of nice and green and
fluffy and fresh
right
pop open the lid
get our cilantro in
okay i'm gonna
move this around
there we go got the fresh cilantro in
there
garden potato
we got the patty pan squash and the
onion now you can season it any way you
want
right
let's plate it up you guys
let's do
that i'm hungry
and you guys you know what
i'm going live
on instagram tick tock
and telegram
in just a little while
so hope you guys stick around
that's the dish right here
i'll give you a close-up on the dish
you guys can see right
all right we're going live i'm going to
have you guys live again it's just going
to be a couple of minutes just let me
straight out in the kitchen i'm going to
make this dish all over again
planta says
pianist daniel fritzen says no it isn't
medical medium information we did know
that sugar for example feeds candida
35 plus years of medical medium
information and work we didn't know that
that was lectures
working on over 250 000 individuals
doctors practitioners the health
movement was this big 35 years ago
and nobody knew anything ate anything so
pianist not true and guess what to prove
that medical medium information was the
first to say gluten actually fed a bug
and there's no study showing
anywhere anyhow that any of that eats
anything so there's no study showing
that then where would have where would
have somebody where would somebody have
gotten the information
okay we'll go into detail about it in
the next live coming up
and i can't wait it's going to be fun
we'll cover that too we're going to
cover that into detail you guys i still
have more here i got it right here
you can even put some fresh stuff on top
like this
you can do garlic in this dish you can
do anything you want
and i'm gonna get a fork out real quick
and we're going to be live in just a few
minutes we're going to do it all over
again
garden potato that's insane that red
potato
patty pan squash
wow
guess what that pepper that pepper is
really hot if you guys don't like that
spicy don't put a hot pepper in there
off the chart
yeah
out of control
hey guys you guys i love you
i'm gonna go live again a little bit
i'll catch you