are you guys Blown Away
I can't get out of this chapter you're
in flame cranial nerves
I mean like
never mind the blood draw information in
here with the protocols never mind
like a brain shot therapies which are
saving people's lives right now
I can't even get out of your inflamed
cranial nerves chapter chapter six in
brain saver page 97 I'm going to read a
little bit more about it I can't even
get out of there
you know what I think about it I don't
even know what to say anymore is it just
me
is this just me or are you guys like are
you guys reading the information in
these in these books
it's like it's every second
it's I mean it's crazy and it's every
line
I mean I'm not kidding I mean you like
is it planet Mars do you guys have these
wait for real
I'm not kidding like if you guys you see
this little fancy stand I have right
here it's really cool check it out I can
put the book right here
makes it easy so I'm not having to like
do this every second like I don't know
wander around the room with it
check this out right
I mean I'm in brain saver
and I'm just blown away so let's talk
about your in you ready okay this is
cool on its own your inflamed cranial
nerves
doctors don't even know their patients
cranial nerves are inflamed do you see
just that line alone is mind-blowing
you can see 10 Specialists 10
neurologists 10 internists
10 GPS
and they still won't know your problem
is because of your inflamed cranial
nerves that's how freaking Advanced the
information is in these books
if you guys don't know the brain saver
books get it right now 40 off amazon.com
us don't delay
get the books
because
they're that incredible seriously
so all right
and I'm not even talking about
everything that's in these books you
guys like pages and pages of knowledge
right Linda
she helped with Liz the whole book is
incredible thank you Liz I really
appreciate it and thank you for all that
you're doing out there spreading the
word all of that
so let me just go into this a little bit
I'll just I'll just start anywhere
That's The Power of this right here you
can just start anywhere inflammation of
the cranial nerves play a large role in
chronic mystery illness and guess what
in the 35 years of me getting
information out there
couldn't find a doctor that could ever
know that
that inflammation of the cranial nerves
plays a large role in chronic mystery
illness you'll never hear that out of
anyone that's how advanced this
information is like boom
what page am I on Lisa Marie page 97
chapter 6. I am at your service you're
in flame cranial nerves I am going to
read a little bit to you guys if you
guys are okay to hear it
or if you're available
is everybody available here
as I always say as I always say
mystery illness misrealness which is
99.9 of all chronic mystery illness duh
it's a much broader category than anyone
realizes we think that if a condition
has a name this part here blows me away
you can talk to like health
professionals and they won't even get
this you can say it over and over to
them and they won't even understand what
you're even saying I I know I've dealt
with this before check this out
we think of that ready
we think that if a condition has a name
your lupus your fibromyalgia your
Hashimoto's thyroiditis list goes on on
whatever
such as anxiety fatigue pots vertigo
Bells Palsy neuropathy ocular migraines
then it must not be a mystery to the
medical research and science group
because it has a name it doesn't have
it's not a mystery anymore that's the
biggest confusion out there you can be a
doctor go to medical school come out of
medical school know that a condition has
a name get a blood test for somebody's
thyroid or whatever and then now you got
a name for the thyroid problem
but you don't have anything else it's
still a mystery 100 percent a mystery
hi vegan Allison
I see you said hi Emma I see your
comments a lot on YouTube you know it's
still a mystery
that's the whole point
so if we think fatigue pots vertigo
Bell's Palsy neuropathy or ocular
migraines and it must not be a mystery
and more problem solved you guys you
have an ocular migraine problem solved
do you guys have pots problem solved if
you guys get a vertigo diagnosis problem
solved right there's no mystery anymore
think about that that's how absurd it
all is when you think about it this
piece of information alone is a game
changer in medical research and science
right is your problem solved because
you've got uh Bell's Palsy or fatigue
diagnosis is your it's still a mystery
anyone who has struggled with any
chronic health issue knows that this
isn't how it works you guys know that
this isn't how it works if you get a
lupus diagnosis an ALS diagnosis
anything else whatever whatever
diagnosis pepper seed good to see you
whatever it is
it's still a mystery anyone who has
struggled in chronic health issues you
guys if you just came on your inflamed
cranial nerves we're talking about a
crate this is something you don't want
to miss I'm going to tell you right now
this is a live that's very important
because we're talking about cranial
nerve inflammation and it's such a
problem it's why almost everybody has a
symptom think about that if you don't
have the brain saver books please
please check them out go to the
bookstore amazon.com us is 40 author 600
page Bibles of information
and you know go to the library get it
for free if you don't have the 26
dollars
it costs way more to print and ship and
get these babies out there in the world
this is literally a work of love
and compassion for the world that that's
what this is
Jesse Lane awesome new live
dude thank you for being here man and
you're on YouTube I saw
all right
being handed a label for your set of
symptoms isn't the same as receiving
answers about why those symptoms are
interrupting your life in the first
place getting a label doesn't mean jack
you got a label you go home with a label
great
you got a label now
but it doesn't mean enough
it doesn't mean Jack
it doesn't the whole point is
you can have a label like depression but
you ain't gonna get better unless you
know what's wrong with the real cause is
whether you're living with a diagnosis a
misdiagnosis or a non-diagnosis there
are answers to be found in getting to
know your brain stem
your brain stem and your cranial nerves
this is what it's about right here the
cranial nerves I mean the whole these
two books alone and what's in here like
I said I can't even get out of chapter
six like I'm stuck in chapter six
because it's that there's so much
information but there's so much
information in every line of the book
you can just open it up
I got a doctor friend that opened up the
book was like
what
it's like it literally it's every line
okay cranial nerve answers your cranial
nerves include your vagus nerves
trigeminal nerves facial nerves
among many others your cranial nerves
extend out of your brain stem so
your cranial nerves extend out of your
brain stem
and when they get inflamed
all the crap goes down
doctor after doctor after doctor when
those nerves coming out of the brain
stem get inflamed it's doctor it's
functional doctor it's natural doctor
it's conventional doctor it's every
doctor
your cranial nerves extend out of your
brain stem and many symptoms of chronic
illness derived from these cranial
nerves if a cranial nerve is inflamed in
any way
check this out
inflamed in any way
because of viral neurotoxins doctors
don't know about I'm not trying to be
you know mean
it's going to say some other word I'm
glad I didn't say it right I'm not
trying to be a jerk
I'm just saying they don't know about
neurotoxins they don't know about what's
even in here this is so Advanced when
you even think about it
Erica Erica Hey on YouTube
labels are meant to shut us up like we
should be satisfied with the diagnosis
100 correct that's what I've been saying
right you've read the books it's
supposed to shut you up
it's like shut up here's your here's
your label and shut up get out of here
now take this drug and get out of here
call us if you have another problem what
it didn't go away
if a cranial nerve is inflamed in any
way because listen to this because of
viral neurotoxins which none of the
doctors knew about unless they got
medical medium books then they know
about viral neurotoxins because you guys
that didn't exist there was no such
thing as a viral neurotoxin until the
medical medium books came out so when
you hear a functional doctor even
mention it now it duh where did it come
from published material
plagiarizing anyone chemical poisons and
toxins such as toxic heavy metals nobody
knew toxic heavy metals and get on and
inflame a cranial nerve nobody knew that
or even physical injury then symptoms
can occur your cranial nerves are also
affected by what's going on with your
neurons so what's going on with your
neurons if there's something wrong with
your neurons in here right here you guys
it's going to affect your cranial nerves
if you just got on here and you're like
what's he talking about cranial nerves
dude I'm talking about everything I'm
talking about so many symptoms
conditions when you deal with cranial
nerve problems
this is information I'm freely just
giving out and talking about this is a
free class right here
most advanced Medical information out
there
and my door is open
come on in
and learn
if you guys just got here
brain saver brain saver protocols right
there 40 off amazon.com us ridiculous
price
26.29 dollars
heck I saw it on Amazon on on the book
page for when you go to brain saver I
saw you can buy brain saver brain saver
protocols and cleanse the heel for 73
dollars it costs 73 dollars it cost more
than 73 dollars to even like put one of
these books out print it and get it out
I just couldn't believe it
there's a lot of things I can't believe
these days
can't believe a lot of things
you know
can't believe how messed up the world is
how people don't have answers out there
how I just I can't believe a lot of
things
symptoms can occur from compromised
contaminated neurons so if you've got
some contaminated neurons symptoms can
occur you ready for this because the
brain is sending skewed altered or
Twisted messages to the brain stem
and then to the cranial nerves if you
have a nerve problem a message is coming
out of here
and then out of your think about if you
have a nerve if you have a neuron issue
sorry you guys if you have a neuron
issue the message is going to get
twisted distorted and skewed as it
leaves the neuron goes right into the
brain stem and then out your cranial
nerves and that's why we're like short
circuiting we're like sick go into
another doctor sick
whoa
Jess selane thank you Anthony
I am having three to four brain shots
every day awesome man so proud of you
seriously
from the brain saver books love them
notice they also help with external
relationships amazing
the thing is with these brain shot
therapies Jess is that they're
miraculous it's information from above I
got warned by SOC that they're going to
do all kinds of things for people not
just what's directed in the book they
have that kind of power
to have that kind of power
viral nerve and brain stem inflammation
so we're talking about
brain stem inflammation
we're talking about cranial nerve
problems
so what does this mean
let's put it in a nutshell
ready
oh feel good
it's got weird tingles and numbness on
my neck and my nose
my forehead always feels tight
I got blurry vision but the eye doctor
says I'm fine
I got ticks and spasms all in my face
I got crazy brain fog and all kinds of
problems my ear hurts really bad I don't
know why my jaw hurts but my dentist
already removed like two teeth and my
jaw still hurts I don't know what this
mystery jaw pain is
whatever's going on
we're talking about viral nerve and
brain stem inflammation that's just a
fraction of the symptoms conditions if
you guys just got here make sure you get
these books brain saver brain saver
protocols
do yourself a favor
be prepared though
your mind's going to be blown
like
for real
most people with chronic illness don't
have physical injuries directly to their
cranial nerves that's true
not everybody got into a real serious
car accident their head went through a
windshield not everybody had that happen
most people with chronic illness don't
have any direct injuries to the cranial
nerves
but here's what they do have here's what
everybody's walking around with chronic
viral infections such as Epstein-Barr
virus that's the big one right there
right that that mm info put out there
shingles so many people walk around with
shingles
and then shingles there's all kinds of
crazy stuff you guys know because I'm
the one who put the information out of
what shingles does herpes simplex one
Herpes Simplex 2 was cold sore viruses
hit the cranial nerves every time
causing problems those cold sore viruses
hit the cranial nerves
Jackie B the brain saver books have
reawakened me to Healing that is
incredible I didn't realize how many
problems I had until I started to feel
better just a few weeks ago by doing the
brain shots
spread the wisdom around tell people you
have to see these books and try these
brain shots
you can put out a miracle
but yet
not a lot of people know about it yet
it's crazy
Isabelle Brown the Sleep restore shot is
amazing that's incredible I mean in time
people will finally get to these books
but like I said I was naive when I was
young and I always thought that once you
have this miraculous answer like these
books do you think the whole world is
gonna just do it if I saw the other day
someone was like yeah I'm in the vegan
I'm in the vegan movement and a bunch of
My Vegan friends we don't we don't need
medical medium
do you know when you get sick you will
when you get sick you will
when you go to 10 doctors you will need
medical medium books
you will
and the answers will be here for free go
to the library
you know what's going to be on my
gravestone my headstone
everything was for free go to the
library that'll be on my gravestone
but really you know
I don't know I just hope a rocket ship
lands and
I just cop on the rocket ship and take
off and never come back I'd rather do
that
all right let's go stop being silly here
Carolyn
I could not find any doctor nor a
neurologist that really understood the
vagus nerve they don't know much about
it they don't no matter how much
symptoms you have or details you give
them they just don't know what to do
about it correct they didn't years ago
when I taught about all this stuff they
don't now
and they're knocking in the future
and if anybody does squeak a peep in the
future it came from the medical medium
books it just did I'm not trying to act
like a jerk it just did it's a fact am I
not allowed to state that
that's where it came from
as you'll read more in detail soon this
viral inflammation can occur in the
brain stem so what what I mean there's
so much information here I'm just
fooling around as far as this little
part I'm talking about viral
inflammation right
the viruses getting into the brain get
the neurotoxins affecting the brain stem
neurotoxins affecting neurons and then
short-circuit messages come out of your
cranial nerves
herpes simplex one the cold sore
everybody has oh it's just a cold sore
yeah but it can give you a lot of
trouble all through the years if you
don't know how to work on healing it
the information's here to help us heal
Uma did you like that one the rocket
ship okay
when someone's cranial nerves have been
temporarily injured for example when
someone sustains a head injury so if
someone actually sustains a real head
injury
of any kind those cranial nerves won't
heal so easily if the person has a
chronic viral infection did you know
I've seen people and I've taught doctors
this I've seen people that get a mild
concussion they go into their car
they open their car door
they go down to grab something
and then they lift their heads up and
they bang the back of their head right
on the car door jamb and they're like
crap oh my God it's just been my head on
the car door jamb and they got a mild
concussion
it should heal perfectly fine
but if they have low grade viral
problems chronic low-grade viral
problems it may not heal so fine so
check this out and nobody knows this out
there
every two lines is packed
when someone's cranial nerves have been
temporarily injured for example when
someone sustains a head injury of any
kind those cranial nerves won't heal so
easily if the person has a chronic viral
infection at the same time every line
has info here
I've seen this over and over again with
people if your viral load is up there
if you've got the viral load simplex one
Simplex 2 maybe Epstein-Barr
cytomegalovirus maybe hhv6 shingles all
the different rides whatever someone has
and you bang your head your head may
take more time to heal than somebody
else
injury to a cranial nerve causes tiny
fibrous root hairs to fray on the area
of the nerve that was injured if a
low-grade viral infection such as
epstein-bar shingles or herpes simplexes
occurring the virus can attach itself to
the cranial nerves that are frayed the
hairs that are afraid now that's way
ahead of research and science right
there we're talking they'll never go
there I mean 100 years maybe maybe even
longer or never tiny root hairs Fray
when we have injured cranial nerves so
then if you have a low-grade viral
infection like Epstein-Barr a virus can
literally cling onto a root hair that is
on the cranial nerve and hence we can
have all these symptoms
man they'll never get there
the virus can station itself in the
injured part of the nerve and live there
like lice you don't you ever see lice
right did anybody ever have lice lice on
your hair
do you ever have that before
a friend of mine got lice and he's like
what should I do shave my whole head I'm
like no don't change your whole head we
can we can figure out how to get rid of
lice that's not a problem
friend of mine started shaving half
their head like I think I got to shave
my head and shaving half his head I said
that was stupid why would you do that
over lice
there's a comet healing healing apps uh
I got inflamed cranial nerves and the
protocol in the new book has helped me a
lot already incredible
isn't it isn't it wonderful to know what
you have wrong
like if I ever got sick I want to know
what's wrong with me
if I ever get sick I want to know what's
wrong
of course sfc will tell me but the point
is that's me but say it was somebody
else if I ever got sick
I would want to know what was wrong
that's all
we're live on medicalmedium.com
if you're having Tech issues on any of
these other apps platforms please go to
medicalmedium.com news flash news flash
news flash medical meeting.com if you're
having a problem
you guys because I'm streaming live live
on medicalmedium.com Christy says I was
so excited to see intracranial
hypertension in the book
my sister was labeled years ago with
that thank you that's incredible I'm
really happy that you have this
information seriously
okay there's so much to go and there's
so much to talk about here let's just
pop in anywhere
untangling the Mysteries can we talk
about that for a second you guys one
reason why cranial nerve symptoms are so
mysterious and misleading to medical
research in science is that someone can
have a little bit of everything
and don't never know
foreign
a person could have contamination or
inflammation in a group of neurons in
the brain from a source such as toxic
heavy metals viral neurotoxins which are
toxins from viruses MSG scented candles
fragrances air fresheners carpet and
clothing chemicals tattoos I'm not
ranking on tattoos
every time I say the word tattoo people
want to kill me that's it I've noticed
out there it's the craziest thing I've
ever seen
I'm not ranking at on tattoos I'm just
saying
that
the metal in tattoos and there's no such
thing
as vegan ink without metal the reason
why you can see the color of the tattoo
through the skin is because light is
hitting the metal and reflecting
it all has metal in it that's not what
I'm here to talk about today though I'm
just saying
that a person could have contamination
or inflammation from a group in a group
of neurons from all kinds of things have
toxic heavy metals
right from you know viral neurotoxes MSG
sent to candles fragrances air freshers
carpet clothing chemicals tattoos a
source of toxic heavy metal
contamination or caffeine injuries too
caffeine injuries that's another thing
people want to beat me to death about is
caffeine
at the same time they could have
inflammation in the lower middle or
upper brain stem caused by viral
neurotoxins
for other problems toxic heavy metals
and so forth the people can have a lot
of things they can have brain stem
issues and sorry some dust going in
there some brain stem issues and
they can have also other problems too
like toxic heavy metals and all kinds of
different contaminants and all kinds of
everything else in here
people can have more than one thing
wrong
everybody is different and I talk about
that in brain saver books
everybody is different
you can have one person you can have one
problem and this other problem another
person can have this other problem this
problem that's what these books are here
for to help you find out what's what and
what's whatever right
got a dry throat so I gotta drink a
little water
thing is before this I've been talking
all morning since about six o'clock this
morning so someone just needs to tell me
to shut up and be quiet and then
because literally I don't think I've
stopped yet today
all right
let's go into another little part here a
vagus nerve can be inflamed at the
bottom in the abdomen
so your Vegas nerve can be inflamed down
here in the abdomen
one of the vagus nerves can be inflamed
down here in the abdomen think about
this
and in the middle in the chest and yet
be inflamed higher up at the brainstep
so here's the thing you can have
somebody can have inflammation of the
vagus nerves down low they can have
inflammation of the vagus nerves up in
the middle somewhere in the chest they
can have inflammation of the Vegas
nerves up in the brain stem think about
that and the doctor will never know
there's no MRI there's no brain scan
there's no nothing no one will ever ever
know
Lorraine L I didn't realize how
difficult my thoughts were until taking
the obsessive thought shifter less
catastrophic thinking
less ruminating
less focus on the past calmer more
peaceful that's incredible Lorraine and
any piece you can get makes me really
happy
Becky says what's the brain shots celery
juices
[Music]
uh
brain shots
my God
what's the brain shots
I just did a 10 day with you guys 10 day
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge
I think I said brain shots a thousand
billion times
okay to answer that question
enough with the drama over here
it's in brain saver books it's a miracle
tool
I'm just gonna say everybody heard this
a thousand times from me be prepared
because it hits you and it works and it
catches you off guard because it's so
powerful
you can do the challenge on your own at
medicalmedium.com how insane is that go
to medicalme.com and guess what press a
bunch of buttons and you don't have to
buy it
go to medicalme.com is for free a 10-day
brain
Savor brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge for free just go there and hit
some buttons and it's all for free
all right
someone could have more inflammation in
a particular region of the brain skewing
neuron messages to the brain stem and
nerves
which is really interesting too for
example someone could have more
inflammation in the left hemisphere of
the brain or the right hemisphere of the
brain or in the frontal lobe or
occipital lobe or temporal lobe or
Thalamus or cerebellum if inflammation
is in an endocrine gland
hypothalamus pineal gland pituitary
gland didn't that can put pressure on a
just adjacent brain tissue squeezing the
neurons in that neighboring brain tissue
and affecting the messages the neurons
sent to the brain stem and nerves
this is way too advanced for the Mayo
Clinic this is way too advanced for the
Cleveland Clinic this is way too
advanced for all of them if you ever
talk to those doctors because I've
talked to a bunch of them over the years
this stuff right here is so over their
head they just don't even know there's
like well what's your symptom
um let's look at our cookbook here of
crap and see if we can give you way too
advanced for Harvard
way too advanced for Harvard Medical all
of this
like if you like way too advanced
all of this information is over the
heads of all the doctors in Harvard all
of this like I'm not trying to just be a
pain I'm just saying it's a fact this
would blow their mind they wouldn't know
what to do with it it's way too advanced
they'd be like wait a minute what
symptoms of cranial nerve inflammation
yeah
oh wait here's a good line the precise
locations of inflammation varies from
person to person and can even vary for
one person over time the majority of the
time it's inflammation that you can't
detect in a medical test
the location where inflammation is
occurring along specific cranial nerves
determines the type of symptoms someone
experiences such as tingles and numbness
aches and pain stiffness Burning
Sensations where in the body those
symptoms occur such as the tongue gums
the jaw temples back of the neck between
the eyes back of the head top of the
head chest or stomach and what body
functions they affect such as swallowing
peristaltic action or the from the
intestinal tract
mysterious cranial nerve symptoms also
include blurred vision trouble focusing
the eyes and usual movement of the
eyeballs including difficulty with
muscles around the eyes visual
disturbances jaw pain burning tongue
neck pain head pain migraines face
vibrating head vibrating ear popping
body buzzing humming pulsating
Sensations in the head burning hot
feeling with no fever how many times
have I talked to people who've had that
balance issues dizziness feelings of
electrical shock in the head where it's
like
loss of the ability to swallow slurred
speech
loss of hearing drooping face we know
that loss of movement of the face pain
in various areas of the face feeling
like they have a crooked jaw pulling
sensation on their face nose eyes or
forehead twitching that's erratic and
shifts all around their head and face
nausea teeth grinding teeth grinding
I'll say it twice tooth pain gum pain
difficulty chewing loss of smell loss of
taste and mystery twitches and itches or
rashes that don't go away with
scratching without rashes these and
other symptoms of cranial nerve
inflammation can either be caused by
inflammation somewhere along the cranial
nerve or by inflammation in the brain
stem or cranial nerves are attached they
won't know this anywhere this is so
Advanced this book I can't even get out
of cranial nerve inflammation chapter
chapter six I'm on page 100. Rina
I was like oh my God after seeing
stomach flipping in your book
just flipping right
who knows anything about that out there
thank you for finding it in here thought
it was something only I have and you
said it is connected with the Vegas Turf
correct I also suffered
I also suffered two quite bad vertigos
in the past vagus nerve again so it
makes so much sense it is the vagus
nerve correct Arena it's the vagus
nerves
negus nerves
all right so there's a little paragraph
here called vagus nerve insights let's
talk about that a little bit there's so
much information here
what you'll hear called the vagus nerve
is not just one thick nerve that runs
from one end to the other in a perfect
line
check this out
the vagus nerves are a larger pair of
nerves plural
not singular
plural
they deserves are a larger pair of
nerves that leave the head region and
travel down to the Torso the vagus nerve
size
that's a word right there very
interesting the vagus nerves
size
and reach
make them more complex than shorter
cranial nerves which is why they deserve
special attention here which is what
we're going to give them because we got
some killer stuff in here about the
vagus nerve
Cornelius says my GP told me that it's
impossible that I have so many different
symptoms so I stopped talking about my
symptoms to her I would just mention one
or two symptoms at a time
you can have a hundred symptoms
the reason for medical medium books and
information is to give people a way out
it's for people who have been there done
that tried everything they're seasoned
they know what's up that's why when you
get somebody that that sees one of these
free open classes and they come in and
they're just like
um I'm just looking for some apple cider
vinegar gummies and some collagen powder
and what's he talking about and it's
like you just
you know it's like the Matrix thing all
over again
this is really Advanced information for
people who have been there done that
they came from hell and back they fought
their way out they fought their way to
stay alive and survive all that crap
they went through no one knows what it's
like to be in their shoes mm info is for
really for the sick people who chronic
Leo who need the information
says I can't believe I'm still alive
with all the crap I have inside me and
what I've been exposed to the body is so
amazing it is amazing ensues
when you give your body the answers and
the things it needs and the resources
just so many incredible things can
happen the brain shot therapy therapies
alone right
so here's a section of the book called
the vagus nerve Grapevine
we think of the vagus nerve structure as
a grapevine
like the other cranial nerves
sorry we can think
we can think so I crack myself up when I
read out loud because I'll miss a word
we can think of the Vegas therm
structure as a grapevine like the other
cranial nerves the vagus nerve Grapevine
is split in two as it leaves the brain
stem there's two vagus nerves coming out
of that brain stem
with those two main Vines branching off
on their own Pathways one vagus nerve
vine branch could be inflamed while the
other vagus nerve is not
this is a critical part of the human
design
however you believe we were designed
if you believe
we were a starfish
crawled out of the ocean
came a monkey and then a human fine
that's our design if you believe
God designed us
fine if you believe
we were designed by alien technology
five if you believe
we were designed
by a meteorite just hit the planet and
we just kind of all just started to
develop whatever it is that you believe
right
we still were designed in such a way
that's just unbelievable absolutely
incredible
one Vegas third vine branch could be
inflamed where the other one may not be
inflamed this is the human design and
this is what's incredible about the
human design I'll tell you why because
what that means is you got a chance
you got a chance this is a critical part
of the human design that protects us it
protects us it means that if one of the
vagus nerves is completely inflamed or
damaged there may still be a chance of
survival while the other vagus nerve
shares its functions that means our
vagus nerves are talking to each other
baby and what they're doing is they're
trying to help each other two Vegas
nerves for the price of one see
everybody has two biggest nerves for the
price of one
so the point is though if you have one
injured vagus nerve
you got a chance
because the other one that may not be as
injured is doing its thing it's doing
all its messaging and hard work and even
communicating with the damaged one the
injured one or infected one
how incredible
who even knew that
oh they didn't it's in here
and getting out of the world now
medical research and science haven't yet
discovered all aspects of the vagus
nerves that's to say the least there are
still new discoveries to be had
one future Discovery is vagus nerve
regeneration vnr
that is certain parts of the vagus
nerves can regenerate and regrow
themselves if the conditions are right
did you guys hear that
what
like I can't get out of this chapter
they haven't discovered this yet
it's a discovery they haven't discovered
yet
it's in the brain saver book
from Spirit of compassion
the prophecies in here are insane
when you think about how incredible this
is
I mean that's a prophecy right there all
on its own
one future Discovery let's visit medical
research and science haven't yet
discovered all aspects of the vagus
nerves
there are still new discoveries to be
had now remember sitting there at my
desk
and spirit of compassion was giving me
this piece of information and I I was
just like what
one future discovery that medical
research and science haven't discovered
yet keep that in mind is vagus nerve
regeneration called vnr
Spirit of fashion is even prophesizing
and putting the the letters is V the
acumen vnr
what
yes
once you read these books you can't go
back it's like a friend of mine picked
up an old eat better book from another
author in health you know like
well-known author in health
and
he said it was like a joke after reading
into the brain saver books and going
back he said he couldn't believe it he
just threw it out
because he couldn't believe how remedial
was how literally how advanced these are
and helpful and what these have compare
that but it's like with that the medical
mean books in general
one future Discovery is Vegas nerve
regeneration vnr that is certain parts
of the vagus nerves can regenerate and
regrow themselves if the conditions are
right medical research and science don't
know this but this is a future Discovery
down the road
this is a prophecy medical research and
science will also discover that the
anatomy of the vagus nerves is not
definitive
oh my God
the vagus nerves are not designed the
same way in every person for example the
Vegas their branches don't completely
connect in the Torso for everybody
are you kidding me
in some people the two Vine branches
merely cross over and touch each other
not actually connect is it just me that
thinks this information is that
incredible
the vagus nerves also vary in length in
each person the discovery is going to be
forced upon the medical industry check
this out you guys do too and I told you
this the other day when I read this line
due to robotic surgeries where robots
programmed to perform surgery end up
injuring patients they're going to
discover that everybody's vagus nerves
are different because of robotic
injuries in surgeries
because you're gonna dial in Vegas nerve
being just one way in women
and men and what they're gonna do is
someone's going to get a robotic surgery
because they're already doing that and
the knife on the robot and I'm not doing
the robot dance is gonna cut the
machines the robot those kinds they're
gonna go and it's gonna cut somebody's
Vegas they're right in half
and then science of research are going
to have to realize that all vagus nerves
aren't the same
first
the discovery is going to be forced upon
the medical industry due to robotic
surgeries where robots programmed to
perform surgery end up injuring patients
vagus nerves because the calculations
are so unpredictable from person to
person but they're only going to learn
that when they do the robotic surgeries
that they're building now
medical communities are going to start
finding out that the vagus nerves length
growth size and directions of travel are
not as cookie cutter as previously
assumed
Echoes on and on and on the book's
packed I'm reading out a brain saver 40
off amazon.com
right now us but just know this and be
prepared
there's answers not only in these books
but
it's an Awakening
and Beyond Awakening
there are Therapies in these books
medical medium shock therapies are
just incredible in these books
brain shot therapy is incredible that's
a different therapy right there
Dana amazing information on Blown Away
on YouTube thank you for being here
the vagus nerves are made up of tiny
strands and strings of nerve cells that
run through the length of the nerves the
vagus nerve is not just one solid nerve
like medical research and science
believe
but by the way you guys look out for
imposters
you guys on telegram there's like a
bunch of imposters they're saying it's
me they're messaging I don't private
message anybody whatever direct message
everybody I don't do that but there's
these imposters they'll direct message
you they'll private message you whatever
it is and they'll just be like
they'll just want to get a combo going
with you and they're still say it's
Anthony William it's not it's not me
on telegram I'm seeing a bunch of it
lately
and they'll say hey I do consultations
no I don't do consultations so the
imposters did they do all that
just look out
I don't want anybody to get hurt by an
imposter
because of the vagus nerve size and
reach when inflammation occurs in the
brain stem that affects the vagus nerve
Grapevine the vagus nerve can exhibit a
wide range of symptoms and this is why
people
can have a hundred symptoms and the
doctors just they don't even know what
to do about they won't even believe you
you can't have too many symptoms it's
like you said earlier there's no way you
can have that many symptoms no one can
have 100 symptoms or 50 symptoms or 30
symptoms there's no way it must be all
in your head you're a hypochondriac
really because of the size and the
differences and the shapes of the vagus
nerves people could have multiple
symptoms
and doctors not realize this
you guys anyway
check out the brand saver books I can go
on for hours to chap this chapter alone
I can do multiple courses and classes
that can last a year
with just this chapter alone cranial
nerve inflammation
but it's free and I'm not going to do
that
get the books go Library get it for free
if you don't have 26 bucks
but really incredible asks you know you
guys
ask your friends what they're
experiencing ask for family members are
they experiencing the brain shot therapy
what kind of results they had tell them
they can post about it do reels about it
right and share their stories about it
and tag at Medical medium hashtag
medical medium so I can see it and make
sure that I can post it and stuff so let
us know how the brain shot therapies are
working for you and your friends and
family and if you can leave some reviews
Amazon.com or whatever the bookstores
you're getting them from and or just
amazon.com screen please do it let me
know how the books are going what's
happening experiences all of it and
clean your books if you want they may
come dirty greasy and you can clean them
with a hand towel it's a little bit of
soap a little water or handy wipe and
you can clean off the grease from the
conveyor belt at Amazon.com or other
places and because people get the book
and they think they bought a used book
but no they're all pristine and they're
all nice and brand new you name it
incredible
and the books are here for us
here's a quote at the beginning of brain
saver
here in these words you join a healing
movement
a community all over the world of
millions of people who are using medical
medium information to get their lives
back
this guidebook is Your Story of Survival
your story of discovering what was wrong
all along
and how to free yourself from it
it is your story of relief healing and
triumphs
these living words will always be here
for you for the rest of your life
they will be
you guys spend incredible live today
keep an eye on medicalmedium.com
I'm updating
I'm enhancing all of it that website
free everything there's no pay firewalls
I like to say firewalls because those
pay firewalls will burn you
they'll burp
s out there there's no pay walls
there's no nothing like that
subscription subscription fees nothing
I'm updating and adding free resources
to medicalme.com we have another
challenge coming up get ready get on
medical medium newsletter at
medicalmean.com we have another
challenge coming up I just want to be
helpful in every way possible check out
medicalmeeting podcasts at Apple podcast
check out the light infusion meditation
that came out of this book
incredible
Buzzy says the adrenaline stabilizer is
my favorite I've been taking one day one
a day at least each day since the 10-day
challenge they are addictive that's an
incredible brain shot therapy
to stabilizer anyway guys check out the
books 300 symptoms conditions answers to
them protocols heavy metal detox
cleanses seven of them Karina says
Anthony had the guilt and shame shot
and feel everything burning
away feels so free incredible they're
that powerful I love you guys
and I can't wait to see you next time
it's been an incredible moment to spend
with you guys and go through the books
I'm gonna give reading again right when
we hang up here I'm going to keep on
reading because I can't even get out of
that chapter my mind gets blown
and then maybe I will I will make a
brain shot therapy
all right you guys
bless your heart take care