[Music]
anyway we're talking about neurological
symptoms people in the health movement
never ever connected the dots between a
symptom being neurological if you're
somebody that's experienced enough in
the last 10 years 15 years maybe you've
been sick 20 years in your life and
you've been sick with different
neurological symptoms you probably went
through the whole guessing games Channel
seeing a lot of different professionals
and health professionals a lot of
different doctors and as it's happening
none of them knew that your symptom was
actually neurological so what is missed
in the health world is Vagas nerve
issues medical me information brought
into town years ago was that nerves
swell nerves actually swell they become
inflamed there's a reason why they
become
mysteriously inflamed and that's
viruses viruses such as Epstein bar
being one of the leaders everybody's got
Epstein bar at this point in the world
and these viruses release something I
call a neurotoxin it's when the virus
eats something it really likes and then
pees and poos waste out of the virus
that floats around your body and is
highly highly allergenic to the Vegas
nerves right there one of the most
important things you can learn to
empower
yourself