live on youtube making the spinach soup
a
powerful healing tool from the medical
medium new edition
now you might be thinking i don't need
any spinach soup
doesn't sound that fun doesn't sound
that great but it's one of the most
powerful tools in the bunch of tools
and it's helped a lot of people heal and
i'm going to cover why it's important so
in a little bit i'm going to talk about
the stomach and what the spinach soup
does in your stomach how your stomach
lands
have to recover and repair so you can
have hydrochloric acid so you can break
down digest your proteins
have good digestive system good good gut
health austin good to see you
glad we're on here also talking about
science a little bit
science says if science says then hey
we're supposed to believe it right
um pia hi from the uk great glad you're
here i'm honored
fantastic good to see you guys coming on
um so
spinach soup is something that is really
healing on the intestinal lining
it's healing for the brain it's an
important
important uh basically recipe if you
want to call it i call it a healing tool
for the brain
mineral salts electrolytes these things
are critical
so and someone's got the brain fog
someone has bloating cramping
digestive problems and a lot of people
have
ammonia that builds up in their gut and
builds up in their gut and builds up
their guts
causes more and more trouble and that
ammonia can seep into the mouth and
people get the bad breath
proteins and fats rot in the in the
digestive
cavity right and people get in trouble
so the spinach soup is one of these
healing tools what i like about the
spinach soup is people that have
fibromyalgia
cfs the brain fog anxiety depression
uh anything like gout i mean any kind of
condition really the spinach soup is
really powerful it's
people with kidney disease kidney
problems i love the spinach soup for
that too
very healing so uh anyway guys great
mandy says is there any good guides for
people with
mthfr problems um well
the books have that information so liver
rescue talks about
mthfr gene mutation right here so you
can learn about it
and all the books the medical media
books talk about that we'll talk about
that in cleansing heal here's a great
one too
so you can learn about that and the sad
thing is
is that with the mthf mthfr gene
mutation
uh diagnoses what people don't realize
it's there's no gene mutation so
we get tricked we get full we get duped
that's how it's done
so that test when you when you get the
mthfr gene mutation test that's just an
inflammatory marker
they actually don't find a gene that's
mutated so it's it's important to know
that
so i mean if you want to know if you
need to
and i try to tell this to anybody if you
need to believe you have a gene mutation
and that's something that feels good
like hey that's my problem
that's why i'm sick that's why i have a
problem if that's what you need
to sleep at night then then that's okay
let it be a gene mutation
all right but if you're if you're
looking for
an answer if you're looking for the
truth if you're looking for
really fixing these problems you'll
learn from medical medium information
which
is information it's teaching doctors all
around the world
you'll learn that the gene mutation
isn't really what it is
that's why okay when people get rid of
their inf
inflammation and they're doing medical
medium information they're getting rid
of that inflammation and they're doing
medical medium
information right what happens is their
gene mutation goes away
it disappears so now they're at their
doctor's office whatever they get the
blood work
and the results come back and it's like
um
your gene mutation and we don't know how
this happened but your gene mutation
went away
it's gone and medical medium
people people who are doing medical
medium information learning how to heal
through the book's information
they hear this all the time i've been
hearing this for years
so even before the publication of this
this first
book this is the new edition right here
but the publication of the first book
with mthfr gene mutation
the test was always just an inflammatory
marker but you're going to be
misled and you're going to be led to
believe that you actually have a gene
mutation they're like oh my god
my son has a gene mutation my daughter
has a gene mutation
my mom has a gene mutation and that's
what you're gonna be told right
so you're gonna be thinking all that so
now you're walking around like wow my
genes are messed up
i got you know a messed up gene
i got a gene that's like denatured i got
a gene that mutated you know it's like
my
g mutated you see how what a screw up
this is in the industry
and so but really what it is
it's like a c-reactive protein test it's
like in
an anti-nuclear antigen test it's like
it's a psa test it's it's it's an
inflammation marker
that's all it is for some reason
pseudoscience
pseudoscience slipped in the door on
that one
and made that one made everybody think
that you
have a gene that mutated
see the big mistake right there and so
and genes that mutate don't ever
research in science don't ever change
that means you have this mutated gene
forever
for for a lifetime right then why
does everybody's gene mutations go
away the mth mthfr gene mutation go away
when they're doing medical medium
information
they're really doing it they're doing
their 32 ounces they're doing their
spinach soup
they're doing their heavy metal detox
smoothie right and they're
you're doing all these tools and their
gene mutation disappears it's not
supposed to disappear
it can't disappear once you have a
mutated gene
then that's what you have till the day
you die nothing changes that right
and because it was never a mutated gene
lorraine el says so much trickery the
trickery is unbelievable
the trickery is unbelievable and to the
degree people don't even
really realize so you're going to go to
the doctor you're going to go to your
function medical
functional medicine doctor and he's
going to draw a whole bunch of blood
he only needs this much for your gene
mutation test
okay you're ready for this all right he
only needs that much for your gene
mutation test
that's all he needs right but he's going
to take
seven vials out of your daughter and out
of your son
14 vials out of your son or daughter
okay or
he or she's gonna take five seven vials
10 vials 14 vials right
and you're going to get all your little
tests and they only need that much blood
so here they are they weaken your immune
system weaken your immune system they
take
tons of blood tons when it's adding up
all the different labs um you should
listen to the
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
and listen to the blood draw episode
but there's so much trickery in the
system
from the blood draw you're losing your
immune system during the blood draw
okay so they take all your blood so your
child children's blood just out the
window
it's oh your children's blood is it's
useless
it's disposable your children's blood is
just
dispensable it's it's just it's not
important
your the blood in your children is not
important you could just remove a ton of
it and just get rid of it throw it out
the lab only needs this much blab only
needs this much
but we're going to make sure we take all
the blood out of your children
that's what the system does okay and
they throw it all away
like they they train you because science
says
they train you to believe that your
children's blood is disposable
disposable that's what they train you to
believe
it's brainwashing so they brainwash
that's what they do
that's what they do and
i mean i mean it's crazy how it works
they the way they do that
they want you to believe
hold on guys i gotta take the phone call
hello yeah this is brainwashed
uh yeah this is yeah yeah no i'm
brainwashed
yes yeah my middle name is brainwashed
uh-huh yeah no they taught me that my
my children's blood is disposable
uh-huh just can throw it away every time
yeah
no i took them in for a blood work the
other day they just took
eight vials from my son 12 vials for my
daughter
they're checking for a g-mutation test
and some other things too i forgot what
the doctor wanted to do
yeah yeah i'm brainwashed uh-huh we're
brainwashed
yeah yeah what it is yeah
no my my children's blood is disposable
they taught me that you can just throw
it all away
just throw all their blood away oh don't
worry
my children can make new blood oh yeah
they're bones their bones can just keep
on producing more cbc
yeah so the doctor can yeah so they they
can the blood lab can vamp it all away
and take more and more and more
no it's not precious no my children's
blood is not precious
no not at all they can remove all they
want
uh-huh 14 20 vials of my children's
blood
it's not important no no they said it's
no big deal just give the child a little
juice
uh-huh they just said give my daughter a
cookie
yep give my daughter a cookie that's
what they said
and they took all this blood for some
reason i i guess their blood just
doesn't matter much it's not even
precious
nope ah they can just make new blood all
the time oh i accidentally hung up on
you are you there
you there
um anyway the system's broken it's
broken
broken broken broken back
okay when we walk around like it's not
broken it's perfect because science says
our st the system's not broken it's
actually perfect we're brainwashed we're
brainwashed
science says all right and we're we
don't think the system's broken right
meanwhile science doesn't know why
anybody's sick
they just don't know why anybody's sick
fibromyalgia they don't know why
they think it's overactive nerves right
it's chronic fatigue syndrome they don't
know why they never did
okay multiple sclerosis they still don't
know why unless they take
medical medium information and publish
it which they've done
but signs of research in a on a whole
doesn't know what what's going on they
think it's your genes
your body attacking itself or it's maybe
hormones maybe
they don't know why anybody's sick right
so
it's kind of the system's so broken
and the only way you're gonna even know
this is if you've been sick but i get it
i get it i get it i get it
i get it if you don't know you're sick
right
you know then then you know here's
another thing too this is really
important to know you'll see people out
there they're not really sick
they got little things real little
things and that's fine that's great
right
little things wrong and they go to their
doctor and everything and they think
they just got it all under control
because
they're getting rid of some processed
food they're taking a few
pills a few different things they're
taking a couple of supplements
and they think that they think they got
it going down
right they're okay they got it in
control and they haven't those
people i notice they're just sold on
anything science says they're also sold
on just you know they're sold on the
balance or moderation thing
they're sold on a lot of different
theories right but the point is is until
you
get that you cross that line and you're
really sick
and you're really sick and you're like
okay now i'm not functioning
my anxiety's crippling you know my pain
in my body's hurting really bad
now i'm in a place where oh my god this
is so difficult what do i do
then you realize that science doesn't
have it down
you got to go searching now and then
you're not as now you're at a specialist
and now
you find out the system is so broken you
end up on the doorstep of a
mthfrg mutation doctor or a lyme doctor
if if if if a doctor is totally into
mthfr gene mutation you're going to get
that label boom
mthfr gene mutation right here here's
the factory let's put it on your back
right
and if you go to a lime doctor boom lime
stamp on your back
there you go out the door you got lyme
disease that's how it's done right
or if you go to an ms doctor it's like
boom it's ms multiple sclerosis
that's your tag you get on your back
right and you might get
a combination of you might get a
doctor's like well could these multiple
sclerosis
hmm it could be could be lyme disease
we're going to take check all that out
could be oh you also have the
mthfr g mutation too and you get wrapped
up into this
still no answers but you kind of leave
thinking you got some answers like
you're getting you're getting a car
you're leaving your doctor's office like
yeah i think i got some answers they're
checking for lyme disease
that's what they're doing they're
checking for lyme i kind of feel
comfortable with that
i think i got lyme disease that's an
answer i finally got an
answer here i'm comfortable with mtf
mthfr gene mutation
i think i finally got an answer to why
i'm fatigued and i'm bloated and don't
feel good and i got heart palpitations
and i got anxiety yeah yeah it's mthfr
gene mutation that's what it is
i'm comfortable i'm leaving the doctor's
office i'm driving right
or hey no oh my god i think it could be
multiple sclerosis symptoms but at least
i got an answer to why i got the
numbness on the side of my body and the
tingles
and and then all the fatigue and aches
and pains and it's supposed to be like
you get this answer but the answer
in the end means nothing means nothing
because you're scammed left and right
and this scamming
is is it's incidious it's it's actually
like incredulous
it's the scamming is such a
such a smoking mirror and
that's that's what's going on out there
you know mthfr gene mutation is
epstein-barr
i'm just going to tell you right now
i've seen bar releases all of this
poison in your liver right
this is mthfrg mutation if you really
want to know okay
and i wrote this in the books right and
that's your liver that's the epstein bar
the epson bar hides out in the liver
that's where it hides right
it hides out in the liver it's peaking
its head right there hey guys
got the epsilon bar right it likes to
hide inside your liver
okay i try to make learning fun you guys
bear with me right
and what it does is it builds up all of
this viral
toxin byproduct corpses
viral byproduct dead viruses
right viral casings that end up the
casings for what lime
lyme doctors believe are spirochetes
spirochetes the whole if you guys know
anything about lyme disease
right well they saw the spirochetes um
the doctors saw the spirochete somewhere
that's shell casings of the epstein-barr
virus
that's what that is right so the epstein
bar is behind
so many of these chronic conditions and
with mthfr gene mutation what the
epstein bar does
it releases all of this gunk and crap it
builds up in your liver
and then it puffs out of the liver puff
powder you ever step on that mushroom
that's like it's like uh
it's kind of like it looks like a circle
and it's on the ground
do you ever go into nature and you step
on it when you step on it it puffs
and what's puffing is all those spores
it's a type of it's a type of fungus
that grows on the ground right in nature
right and that's what happens your liver
puffs all of this viral toxin right
now you're going to doctor to doctor now
what that's junk does that comes out of
the liver from the epstein-barr virus
it raises your inflammatory markers
so it doesn't matter who you're at so
i'm going to head to the lyme doctor
the lyme guy well his lyme tests are
inflammatory markers there's no borrelia
he finds there's nobody bartonella they
don't find that
lyme lab i know i've talked to all kinds
of lab technicians in
lime labs and everywhere else right and
they even reached out to me and they
said how did you know we don't actually
have had lime
lab people reach out to me and say how
did you know
because it's private information how did
you know
that we don't see the bacteria we place
the bacteria's name
on the test we see elevated inflammation
and then since we're a lime lab we
put lyme bacteria what we think is
theoretically
right there okay now here's the other
thing mthfr gene mutation
they're not finding a mutated gene
doesn't that hurt
like why are they screwing us over then
like why isn't the doctor informed
because they they're just seeing
elevated inflammation
just from from the viral issue
from the viral issue right that's how
it's done so then you're leaving
the doctor's office you're driving home
and you got an answer
okay me and my kids all got mthfr gene
mutation
no you and your kids all got
epstein-barr
and maybe it won't matter then until you
guys get really sick like
really sick and then that's when it
matters
then it's like what the heck is going on
is my gene mutation out of control like
what's going on here
important to know all this is important
to know
giving you guys like i'm giving you guys
information that
if if if i opened up a school these
would be courses
and you'd be paying five thousand
dollars ten thousand dollars of course
but i don't do that i want it for i want
to give it to you for free
but i know that a lot of people once you
give everything for free
they kind of discard it because they
need to pay for something
it's interesting how the human i hear i
keep on hearing this they're like
aw why aren't you charging thousands of
dollars for the information
volumes you give out because then people
will take you know though maybe they'll
take it more serious i'm like no no no
don't insult
don't insult the people i'm helping
because they know how serious this
information is
and they don't need to pay ten thousand
dollars for a course to actually know
how serious
this is um anyway guys so
we're covering a lot of cool topics
right now and it kind of borderlines the
whole science sets
okay like science says
your genes are screwed up science says
your body's attacking itself
science says idiopathic
cause unknown and what i wrote in the
medical medium book one originally
basically science is trying to call you
an idiot you go there with your symptoms
and the reason why they did the
idiopathic thing
really is just because before they came
came up with the idiopathic thing with
all your aches and pains and tingles and
numbness and everything else
before you what they used to say what
they used to say is you're crazy
you know so
it's really it's really kind of what
they've always done but
this information is so it's so um it's
so incredibly important
so is is hemochromatosis real gene
real gene mutation just gas no it's not
it's viral
it's viral that's a viral issue right
see what they need to do is here's what
science is going to do science is going
to convince you
everyone eventually your genes are just
screwed up it protects science it's that
it's an incredible way to never
do science studies on things that matter
right because they can cast it all as
jeans
it's your genes that's it no we don't
need to take
500 billion dollars and put it into why
your children is
your child's really sick we don't need
to do that
we are going to take 500 billion because
we got all these grants from massive
corporations
we're going to take 500 billion dollars
and we're going to just study your genes
that's what they do i'm giving you
double meaning here
get ready for this double meaning
because all medical medium information
does have hidden double meanings in
there
right we're gonna get we're gonna ask
from big huge corporations so we don't
have to
and then we're going to take we're going
to ask them you give us 250 million
you give us another medical research we
want another 250 million
we want another 500 million from you and
then we're going to take our 500 billion
dollars
and instead of helping children really
helping moms
find out why they're fatigued why
children are sick with eczema
why people are suffering why children
have autism why children have adhd
why all these problems right instead of
solving any of them we're going to take
500 million dollar science
and we're going to study your genes and
it ain't for pretty reasons
it's not for cute fluffy pretty
reasons and we're gonna study your genes
never tell you
never find out what's really wrong with
you but we're gonna tell you so we can
say next time you come to the doctor
we're gonna be
at your jeans and some of the tricks are
like the mthfr gene mutation
all the different genes genie fits your
jeans jeans jeans
look you don't have to you don't have to
like me
you don't have to like the way i look
you don't have to like the way i talk
right but keep an open mind on what i'm
saying
because this is really important
information
i'm going to make some spinach soup you
guys got a lot of stuff to talk about
that's medical medium new addition
um gene mutation tests
they don't even need that they don't
even need that
forensics forensics
okay like on a murder scene a murder
scene
forensics needs a 30-year
40 year old drop of blood on a pair of
jeans
okay desiccated blood
right a pin up
on the tip of a pin you couldn't even
see it on here
on somebody's genes 40 years ago
to determine dna and other things right
but they need 14 vials from your baby
to do a little gene mutation test and
some nutritional deficiency tests
and a little bit of cbc they'll take 14
vials from somebody's baby
it there's such a break in the system
it's
almost it's almost unbelievable you know
why we
don't you know why we don't understand
it
do you know why we don't get it or
understand it do you know why
we can't this
phone thing's really driving me crazy
now you guys
brainwashed huh
yeah yeah i'm brainwashed uh-huh yeah
they brainwashed me
uh-huh yeah they brainwa paddle
uh-huh i'm part of the paddle what's
paddle
that's people that are cattle hurting
to the brainwashing clinic sheeple
we're all sheeple then we just heard we
just heard to the
we heard to the brainwashing clinic yep
that's what we do uh-huh we're gonna be
taught that it's our genes
but they're gonna take 500 billion more
dollars and they're going to study our
genes
they're never going to tell us huh
yeah we're brainwashed uh-huh yeah i
believe them
i believe them where's your study uh-huh
yeah where's your study i did they
trained us to say where's your study
did you know that when i'm on social
media brainwashed when i'm on social
media i type in where's your study
when i'm on social media i type in
where's your science report
yeah we're brainwashed i'm sick i don't
feel good
the doctor says it's my genes uh-huh
they've done it 10 trillion dollars in
medical testing
out there in the world and they can't
even give you anything but it's your
genes
uh-huh but i think that's perfectly fine
because i'm brainwashed
i gotta go i'm gonna make some spinach
soup
make some spinach soup you guys uh
stephanie what about someone who has
high histamines
and a lot of free radicals what causes
all of this in
my blood test well first of all
that's dirty liver that's dirty liver
it's really simple dirty liver liver
stagnant and sluggish filled with lots
of different toxins that's what that is
histamines elevating means pathogen
toxins
streptococcus that's one of them um
viruses shingles epstein-barr cold sores
the cold sore virus hides out inside the
liver
it's in the liver when you see somebody
with a cold sore
you're all you have to you you can learn
right now
someone's got a cold sore that virus
doesn't just live where the cold sore
comes out in the moment right
where you can catch it you give them a
kiss and now you got it
it could come out a year later it can
come out a week later but now you got
the
the simplex one right that virus lives
inside the liver
if you see that on someone it's in the
liver and
same thing with shingles it's inside the
liver same thing with with
with any bug if you had the chicken pox
when you were a child the chickenpox
virus lives inside your liver they live
in there live in there live in there
build up all this toxic sludge toxic
sludge and then the sludge starts coming
out
if you got high histamines you'll end up
getting an mthfr gene mutation diagnosis
eventually too
because it's all the same thing it's all
that gunk coming out of the liver
then you gotta clean and learn how to
clean up the liver and lower the fat so
spinach soup is a great way to do it
let's go into that a little bit
um i'm gonna get the cbc off of here
right
good to see you guys coming on i want to
be as helpful as possible
today that's what i want to do
oh wow i have the chickenpox at h5
michelle it sits inside the liver
doesn't go away it's in everybody
elena how you doing anthony i used to
have herpes on my lips
once in once and a half a year
or so but after after baby delivery my
herpes
moved now i have it on my face
or inside my nose very painful well what
happens is that
when i talk about this many times you
guys i've talked about this a lot of
times right
um the
i was going to go grab something i don't
know what it is but it's okay i
the when when you when you're pregnant
your immune system drops by 50
that's what happens so when you're
pregnant your immune system drops by 50
for women men's immune system stays
always even keel they can burn it to the
ground but it burns to the ground
evenly it burns to the ground really
evenly is what it does right
little women but women's reproductive
systems
are different they require the immune
system to be
all there so when you're pregnant
50 of your immune system protects the
baby
when you're pregnant right when you're
having
a cycle okay your immune system protects
your reproductive system too
when you're delivering the baby 90
of your entire immune system goes to
protecting your baby during delivery
so then that simplex which your immune
system had under control
it had that simplex under control right
your immune system had it totally under
control and then
what happened was after being pregnant
for nine months
and 50 of your immune system continually
taking care of the baby
the immune system wasn't there to keep
the simplex
intact like in and keep it cool
keep it calm keep it in check right
and then you deliver the baby and now
the immune system drops because you need
all your adrenaline to deliver the baby
now your 90 immune system is taken to
the baby while your adrenals are pumping
after after childbirth you can
women get everything hashimoto's
thyroiditis from their epstein bars
they get heart palpitations they get
arrhythmias from their epstein bars
they get fatigue from their epstein bars
they get um
you know they get herpes cold sores on
their face
their nose right on their lips
from uh from what would they bend
through they get all these different
conditions it can happen when the immune
system
lowers like that so um but i talk about
and cleanse the heal all the protocols
in there you can take it to your doctor
uh if you want but yeah
i'm gonna make some spinach soup
good to see you guys here so
this spinach soup i love it's so healing
it's so awesome
you know and let's do it
um i'm gonna have a shot of the
weinman's wild blueberry juice
because i'm needing a shot right now
i don't know if you guys got yours yet
if some of you got got yours yet
um but i told you i'm working with the
company
i'm trying to spread the word about it
i'm working with them fully gave them an
official endorsement for me and
everything
because i don't want them to stop making
this i just don't want them to stop
making this wild blueberry juice because
i know
it's a powerful tool and i don't like
i worry about losing these tools out
there
because everybody needs every edge they
can get you know
and then wild blueberry is a whole other
thing i know i talked about it before
but anyway
a little refresher there i haven't had a
shot today usually do it in the morning
and today i didn't today was one of
those days
totally one of those days so let's do
the spinach soup
um i'm gonna start by putting in some
tomatoes
if you guys don't like tomatoes or you
know you got a tomato
like you're just afraid of them or
something like that you don't have to do
tomatoes in here and just try to do more
squeezed oranges if you really want to
but tomatoes is really a good there's a
good reason it's in here
so that's about it right there take a
few more out just in case i got too many
and i'm going to put a little cilantro
in here too you don't have to put a lot
but i'm going to put some
makes a great chop up one celery stick
you can do that
i'm chopping up a celery stick it's a
big it's a pretty big celery
stick too okay
doing that too it's good to see you guys
i'm glad you're here
can you heat the spinach soup please
that's a different kind of spinach soup
this is a raw spinach soup
it's it's so delicious have you tried it
that's so good i mean
so good so i'm gonna put some spinach in
here too
let's let's get a garlic clove in here
i'm putting a little one okay
little one in here just letting you guys
know
if you guys came on here we're talking
about some powerful
topics talking about
science how broken it is when it comes
to chronic illness it's so
sad it's so broken um if you're
sensitive leave the garlic out if you
want if you don't like garlic or you're
sensitive about it right
but i'm using a tiny bit if you're
sensitive put a tiny bit in
okay ashley kevin just said she adores
the spinach soup
incredible so i'm gonna put some spinach
in here now
what i like to do is this is a smaller
blender blender it's not
it's not a real tall one so i'm gonna
add more spinach after i blend it up you
guys after i blend it up
you can do look you can steam spinach if
you really wanted to
i don't like it that i honestly i like
the raw spinach so healing for the
mineral salts
andrea when when i would eat raw soups
like this my acid reflux kicks up
is this liver and gallbladder being
sluggish
um first of all okay first for being
your own detective
one thing you want to do is make sure
were there any fats
in that raw soup were there avocado in
that raw soup
was there any oil in that raw soup first
of all i mean maybe there wasn't and
there wasn't any of that
okay andrea was there any nutritional
yeast in the diet was there any
vinegar apple cider vinegar in there a
lot of raw people they're just raw raw
and they're just doing apple cider
vinegar or whatever it is
make sure that's not going anywhere near
there so that's important all on its own
okay
and then what did you eat before the
spinach soup what did you have
during did you do the spinach soup or
dinner but you had a lot of
fat and you pushed your gallbladder to
the edge during the day
like did you have you know are you
plant-based and you had some nut butters
that day and then you had some avocado
that day and you had maybe
coconut oil that day um so that's that
all these things are important to know
and then how much spinach soup you know
sometimes you know you make a big bowl
of it and you send it down really quick
it's really a potent healing tool so you
kind of sip it and just kind of get
through and see how that's working too
it and acid reflux this is the only time
you ever had acid reflux
this is it this this is just it like no
acid reflux
on anything you can eat all week do
everything all week every day
every day all week you're doing
everything and no acid reflux and then
the spinach soup did it
so keep keep that in mind too you
probably had some acid reflux
constantly coming in and out of there so
the spinach soup is a healing tool
so now here's here's the next part
this this starves bad bacteria
so that's what this does so the medical
means spinach soup
starves bad bacteria
so you know what that means but really
starves them
strips them down breaks them down
okay so when you're and here's the other
thing
okay oh you got acid you got acid reflux
all the time andrea
so there's acid if you have acid reflux
you got the low hydrochloric acid
you got that going on right so there's
the low hcl
got some bacteria going i tell people
all the time i talk to doctors about
this all the time too
their patients they have this they have
the elevated bacteria in their gut right
and that's producing acid then they got
the stagnant sluggish liver that's
spewing out stuff
then the gallbladder spewing out all
kinds of stuff too
and the spinach soup's like the cleaner
upper it gets in there man it is
cleaning all this stuff up
i mean it's a healing tool that's doing
all this cleaning so that's
that happens right there um
let's put some orange in here okay
i think uh every time i do this on
youtube and face i'm
facebook live youtube live you guys at
the same time i want you to know
tammy o'neill says my son gave up coffee
and it helped
incredible angie what if you have a food
sensitivity to spinach
it's really good question i like that
spinach like that spinach question
well okay be your own detective you
ready i'm gonna help
i'm gonna help you be your own detective
was it when you eat the spinach all of a
sudden something crazy happens
right or is it you're at the doctor and
the doctor's like here's your food
sensitivities
we just took this much blood times 20
more
we just took 14 vials of blood from you
just to give you your food sensitivity
test
when they only need that so they just
broke down your immune system
nobody realizes this you guys if you
haven't heard the medical mean podcast
at apple podcast the blood draw okay the
blood draw bloodletting and vampirism
episode you have to hear it to protect
yourself your family and friends
okay so um back back to the food
sensitivity
or what was it just practitioners said
you're sensitive to spinach
you're sensitive to this nut you're
sensitive to
this you're sensitive to cilantro
sensitive to strawberries
sensitive to this sensitive to that
sensitive to this oh and you're
sensitive to spinach too is it that kind
of thing right
i want you to be your own detective okay
or is it like you eat it
and something goes funny which could
happen i mean i mean it could just for
anybody i mean people eat things they're
like hey i got this funny thing that
happens when i eat a piece of meat or i
got this funny thing that happens when i
eat a piece of pork
or or want to eat a leaf of lettuce
right people have these funny things
that happen
right but what is it going on like so if
if it's not something happening when you
go and you eat that piece of spinach
and it's just someone said hey this is
what comes up
if it was me i'd still be doing it
because
food sensitivity tests don't don't
really give the full picture about
really what's happening inside the body
and here's the thing this is important
too this is really important right here
critical how is it possible
everybody's a guru everybody's giving
out all kinds of advice
both medical whether it's naturopaths
functional medicine doctors
regular medical doctors health coaches
nutritionist dietitians
plain old coaches anybody trainers you
name it everybody's such an expert when
nobody knows why anybody's sick
it's incredible right think about that
so food sensitivities all got it down
but the food sensitivity doctor don't
know why anybody has chronic fatigue
syndrome multiple sclerosis
als they don't know anything they don't
know why somebody has alzheimer's
dementia
anxiety depression right the same thing
with nutritious nutritionists will give
you all this great advice
but they don't know why you got lupus
lyme disease they don't know why you
have anything
tingles aches and pains tinnitus vertigo
dizziness
they don't know why you have anything
but yet they're experts let me just
give you this nutritional plan i'm a
nutritionist and i'm going to give you
this nutritional plan
but i don't know why anybody's sick and
and so that's another thing too i'm not
saying
don't get help i want you to have your
whoever it is that you love all your
healthcare providers i want you to have
all of them
i'm just saying so we have to kind of
it's okay to question something
sometimes you know
says i eat your spinach soup every
single night amazing
josh eldridge he's an expert this man
saved my life
truly an honor brother honor honored to
have you here too
um
[Music]
truly honored to have you here
means more than you know julia you do
the same thing you act like an expert
too
ah good question and i like that one
hold on i gotta answer the phone
sorry julia
hello uh huh
yeah i heard about anthony william
yeah i heard about him he's the only guy
in our
whole history of chronic illness that
has more people better than anybody else
we've ever seen
uh-huh millions of people got their
lives back around the world we've never
seen that anywhere
uh-huh did you know that before anthony
william
everybody just was sick yeah they just
stayed sick
didn't matter where they went what they
did didn't matter what diet they chose
they stayed sick uh-huh yeah
no i know a lot of diet belief systems
out there took some of anthony williams
information now and they use it to get
their people better too but they don't
they don't claim they took it from
anthony william but thank god for
anthony william
because they have his information for 35
years now that
he's been putting out there uh-huh what
else why am i
why why am i talking about anthony
william did you know that his
information
is not biased or tainted or paid for
do you know his information comes from a
pure source since age four
that doctors use every single day when
they talk to him to try to get answers
do you know science and research is
taking anthony williams information now
they're publishing it after he published
it
yeah uh-huh did you know that he's got
the street cred
did you know he never contradicts
himself
did you know that he's the first
so-called whatever you want to call him
healer practitioner uh guru
author whatever you want to call the guy
did you know he's the first that never
contradicted himself
for 35 years of his information uh-huh
yeah isn't it amazing did you know that
science of research
has not proven any of anthony williams
information to be wrong
they've only proven it to be right
uh-huh did you know he gets it from a
source
right that's not paid for not tainted by
man
it's a pure source that comes from above
uh huh
did you know it works yeah i know
you know millions have healed around the
world
and that's never been ever seen before
in history of chronic illness
uh-huh so what makes anthony william an
expert he never went to college nope
never got a degree no no
i don't know yeah yeah all right
what okay i gotta go
um
i think we're good i think i can start
making spinach you can make it thicker
if you want by not putting as much
orange in
cat conte following everything i can
from you for weeks now
and getting better after 40 years of
dealing with ebv the issues what happens
is
what i'm saying to julia julia before
medical medium information you just
stayed sick
for 40 years people just stayed sick
that's what they do
you get sick you stay sick hashimoto's
never heals
nothing ever heals you just stayed sick
with fibro stayed sick with multiple
sclerosis that's what people did
before medical medium information came
to town foley came to town it was
already out there and i was already
getting people better
but when it really came to town millions
more millions around the world healed
but the point is is i'm not trying to
boast i'm just answering the question
that why should i listen to him
and you know what i tell people don't
listen to me you don't have to listen to
me
don't don't go where you want do what
you want and when you get so
sick and you're tired of being so sick
this maybe you'll actually do the stuff
i'm going to add some more spinach in
here
lauren says julie joseph i follow
medical medium and everything he says to
do
but recently my organic assets test
showed
oxalates getting high causing pain
so first of all the oxalate thing and
look i want you to listen to your doctor
lauren
you do what your doctor says okay you
listen to your doctor
the doctor says it's oxalates listen to
your doctor okay
but i'll tell you what i teach doctors
the old oxalate game isn't why anybody
was sick
people played with oxalates till the
blue they were blue in the face and
never got rid of their fibro or anything
else oxalates is also a theory
science research hasn't even actually
proven oxalates is an issue
so your doctor is not even working with
something that was proven yet
so okay is your doctor making up the
oxalates thing
because if he is you're talking to
somebody that's making stuff up right
so because oxalates can't be proven
science research never found
oxalates in the body causing any problem
there's never been anything that ever
showed that right
but and here's how oxalates work
people go on the oxalate train and they
go searching for oxalates
and people don't realize you can call it
oxalates you can call it anything you
want but what else is happening in your
life
what else are you doing are you doing
nutritional yeast are you doing apple
cider vinegar are you doing any caffeine
or did you have chocolate two weeks ago
because that causes body pain
caffeine so there's there's all these
things that people do
and so i want you to be your own
detective right i want you to listen to
everything your doctor says lauren i
want you to listen everything your
doctor says your doctor says oxalates
you go with the oxalates okay
but i want you to be your own detective
too and i want everybody to be on their
own detective right
now was there a new medical treatment
someone might have done was there
antibiotics someone might have taken
back
six months ago because six months later
you can get an activation of all kinds
of problems from antibiotics you've
taken six months before
was there nutritional yeast in your diet
somewhere msg it builds up it builds up
and builds up and then boom you've got
body pain
was there apple cider vinegar which
pickles the liver pickles the liver
breaks down
the stomach glands cause problems and
then boom you get pushed over
was there anything else happening too
was there high fat this medical medium
doesn't recommend high fat if you're if
you're trying to heal
was there high fat in the diet how much
avocado oils
almond butter are you doing how much of
all that are you doing
was there a new pathogen infection
that someone could have caught i'm
giving you guys all this stuff so you'd
be all your own detective right
are you looking at everything before you
go and hop on the oh it's my lectins
that i'm eating oh it's oxalates oh
was there a blood dross apparently if a
doctor's looking at your oxalates
the doctor must be taking some blood how
much blood has the doctor been taking in
the last year
because if you're getting blood draws
five vials seven vials four full vials
eight full
vials it adds up ten full vials your
immune system drops
then all of a sudden you get boom thrown
into body pain later right
and i'm not saying you know look
i'm not saying hey don't believe your
doctor you believe your doctor you do
what your doctor says
that's what i say do what your doctor
says you listen to your doctor right if
it was me
i'd be like what else is going on okay
the doctor just
three weeks ago took eight vials from me
what
i had eight vials taken six months ago
uh that's my immune system going out the
window um
i did eat some chocolate which has
caffeine in it which is really bad when
anybody's got any kind of pathogens or
any kind of other problems
i did have chocolate hmm yeah but i am
saying i'm doing everything medical
medium says
um but medical medium doesn't say
chocolate or in these other things he
also tells you don't get the blood draws
get ask your doctor to do something
different on the medical mean podcast
apple podcast all that information
but i want you to be your own detectives
out there like what else is happening
did you have some matcha tea that
caffeine will blow out your nervous
system
even if it's weeks later like what's
going on
and was there a new medical treatment at
all was there an older medical
treatment that happened a little while
back was there
um was there hot is the high fat going
on because medical medium knows that
when you're healing
if you do the high fats you're going to
eventually get yourself sick right you
got to learn how to lower the fats right
and what kind of supplements is the
person using too
is there alcohol in them is there is
there citric acid in them
is there other things in there there and
all that and do they know the protocols
they're taking right
but so it's important to know that
there's a lot of tools to get better
with medical medium
it's not it's not it's not
straightforward like
i've been doing medical medium i've done
all medical medium
really because when you really do
medical medium
you really do it you're a deep in the
mono eating cleanse
you're deep in the heavy metal detox
smoothie with the right stuff
you're deep into the anti-radiation tea
you're deep into the 369 advanced you're
deep into the protocols and dosages
of what degree of protocols and dosages
you're deep in top
you're deep into it no corn no chocolate
no caffeine no nutritional yeast no
apple cider vinegar
ah you're deep into it and your lemon
water can't be
in hot water your lemon water
can't be hot water are you doing 32
ounces of celery juice
are you doing 10 ounces of celery juice
okay
so what happens is what i love is when
people say
oh yeah no i did on medical medium or
i'm doing all medical medium
really because if i was a
you know really really hold on
hello yeah i'ma fly uh-huh
yeah i'm on the wall i'm on the wall now
what do i sound like you really want to
know
[Music]
that's annoying sorry yeah
i'ma fly him on the wall did you see
that did you see what she did
she took a supplement from from
somewhere else that she got that
has all this junk in it uh-huh do you
see that
wait what did that person tell that
person had chocolate bar
i know is that medical medium a
chocolate bar
uh-huh yep wait wait did you see that
apple cider vinegar yeah it went in a
dish they made
uh-huh i'm a fly i'm on the wall
uh-huh i'm just watching oh what else
oh that's a lot of fat medical medium
doesn't recommend any of that fat
no it's a lot of fat uh-huh every day
i know yeah well because yeah
they they do other stuff too i know they
said they only do medical medium and
they've been entrenched in it all the
way
but no there's a lot of stuff going on
there i know
i'm a fly i see a lot more things too
oh yeah the protein powder yeah look in
the cupboard
yeah there's the protein powders and the
collagen powder uh-huh
when did they try the collagen they
tried it a couple months back
i know they don't even know but collagen
actually makes people sick
they don't realize it but it's it's an
antagonistic against the immune system
uh-huh yeah they don't know they tried
the collagen powder
oh they're on bone broth yeah i saw that
i'm a fly i'm on the wall they're doing
bone broth
yeah i know it's not natural flavors in
one of the things they took i know
yeah yeah they had kale chips uh-huh
they thought they were eating healthy
there's nutritional yeast on the kale
trips
yeah on the kale chips i'm a fly i don't
speak right
uh-huh because i'm a fly because my
words aren't going to come out perfect
all the time because i'm a fly uh-huh i
gotta go
but but but all due respect
okay i tell people
you like your doctor listen to your
doctor
do what your doctor says okay
and the doctors that talk to me say i'm
gonna do a medical medium says
but you do what your doctor says all
right
did i make the spinach soup
all right put a little more spinach in
here and i'm making it nice and thick
i like it thicker
[Music]
so i'm making a spinach soup right now
hydrochloric acid is produced by your
stomach lands
michelle says processed health foods
have msg
am i yelling
so i'm making some spinach soup you guys
right here
look i just want
everybody better it's what i want
everybody better want everybody to have
a chance to heal
the details matter and it's easy to go
off
the train it's easy to go
now you're off the rails it's easy to go
off the rails because
there's sparkly glitter everywhere oh
collagen
maybe i should grab that collagen oh
apple cider vinegar i better grab that
oh wait a minute i better get some gut
health products
that can rip my guts apart and people
don't realize it
let me try another gut health product
that some
some practitioner wants it just rip your
guts apart
it's just a bunch of crap thrown in
these gut health products right
they don't know what what and why people
are sick and they throw it all in there
and they just send that down it's like
and it's easy to go off the rails
next thing you know it's colostrum
bentonite clay corella
and it's just it just could go off the
rails dr sherry green
terror davis vegans and non-vegan alike
have thyroid issues all ebv
you can be vegan you can be animal
product you can be
plant-based vegan you can be all raw
plant-based vegan
and have thyroid problems epstein-barr
but you got to know the tools to heal
i mean seriously guys you guys i want to
do this for free
like i am i want to give you
critical critical pertinent powerful
life-changing information right okay
i don't want to package it up and open
up a little school and just charge
everybody ten thousand dollars i want to
spill my
guts out right here and give it to you
for free every day
but if you don't take the golden nuggets
and you slap the golden card and take it
out of my hand
and you smack it out of my hand and you
don't
know the details it's really sad
and you don't read and study the books
it's
really sad
anyway you guys i'm heading off to ig
and tic
you're gonna be with me making some
beautiful spinach soup right here
okay and i know you can't kind of see it
but that's it it's spinach soup it's raw
spinach soup it's healing for your
stomach lens and everything else
june savage you saved my life you saved
my life man
honored honored bless your heart i'm so
glad you're here
okay glad you're here truly debbie
spinach soup is one of my favorite
recipes debbie that's incredible it's
one of mine
and i am excited i'm gonna take a spoon
out of my little drawer here and i'm
gonna have some in a couple of minutes
you guys melissa says you're amazing
please don't change please continue to
be
amazing stand for humanity you guys i'm
heading to
instagram you guys i'm gonna have a
couple more shots of this
usually just have one shot a day or two
shots a day i'm gonna have a shot
boom after this um you guys know where
to get this
link is in description it's
shop.wymans.com
um and you guys know supplements i use
and everything
um talk about the vimergy stuff all the
time i'm not sponsored by those guys but
it's incredible stuff
because here's here's the problem i keep
on having right
you know what i'm not getting better i'm
taking my lemon balm and not getting
better
like what lemon balm are you taking i i
found this in the health food store
dude there's natural flavors in there
there's there's citric acid in there
there's there's acacia gum in there
there's alcohol in there
uh corn grain alcohol yeah you're not
gonna get better and that's another
thing it's like the healing tools matter
and i've said this all the time you know
and like i take the lemon balm
every day every single day that's the
vimergy lemon balm
right and i mean that's that's the key
vimergy.com v is invictus i
am ergy dot com use the limb bomb you
want to use i'm just telling you the one
i use
and how everything all the details
matter
to push somebody over the finish line to
push them
over the finish line everything matters
are you guys i'm heading over to
instagram and tiktok
and after that i'm gonna go to 369
cleanse that's an instagram page and
then tick tock again
so i'm going to instagram twice tonight
after this but i'm heading to the main
instagram page i love you you love that
lemon balm
kelly right i mean
i have doctors asking me what do we do
about anxiety what do we do about
depression anxiety and stuff like that
like what do you do aw
i'm like well i don't have anxiety i
don't have depression thank god
and and you know but but um but that's
what i would do
and and i always tell my doctor friends
that's what i would do this lemon balm
is one of them
um hey guys love you guys