So today we're talking about how viruses
are alive and how they eat
so one thing to really understand out
there is that no one realizes out there
in the medical health world and medical
research and science the viruses
actually are alive and they actually eat
they contradict themselves out there too
big part of the medical industry is like
no viruses are dead they're dead
Alternative Health industry viruses are
dead viruses aren't even alive they're
just a strand of itself there's just a
DNA strand of itself and then there's
also but what about the flu what about
the flu the flu is probably alive right
and so there's confusion in that Arena
we're going to kind of talk up a little
bit about that but we're going to cover
how viruses are hungry
viruses eat
and viruses are alive important to know
so anyway got an announcement to make
next week doing a wild blueberry drinks
challenge which is going to be really
exciting sign up it's going to be a
two-day free Wild blueberry drinks
challenge sign up to medicalmedium.com
do the newsletter there so you can find
out what's going on and everything
because you want to download your
grocery shopping list so sign up to the
drinks challenge so you can get your
free PDF and you can sign up and get all
that figured out and get downloads your
free grocery shopping list and all that
link is in the description link is in
the profile check it out when you get a
chance so it's a two-day wild blueberry
drinks Challenge and a lot of you guys
have your juice by the way
it's I think it's like 10 off or
something like that right now they got a
sale going on and you guys got your
drinks probably you got your wild
blueberry juice you got your wild
blueberries so you're prepared if you
have it if you're not check it out okay
link is also in the description and the
profile
and so take a look when you get a chance
10 off they're running a sale on that
you guys know I work with Wyman's a
whole bit I want to keep this stuff
around but listen we have an exciting
topic today because this is important
because people's immune systems are
challenged people don't know how viruses
work all of that so we're going to cover
some cool information I'm going to read
right here out of brain saver as well
good to see you guys coming on
so do you have the books too
so let's find out what page we're on as
well so these are the two books the
brain saver books
page 49 mm school and then school going
down right now I'm just gonna say it
page 49 right here brain saver so do you
have your book
so we can read together because that's
fun I love reading with you guys
so okay so I'm reading a part right here
page 49 in brain saver living hungry
viruses this section is mind blowing it
really is this is a powerful piece of
information right here so let me start
for the record viruses are living
important to know they are alive give
you a little bit of an example when
someone gets herpes simplex right so if
someone has a cold sore
and you kiss the person and they have
the cold sore
you then can get the cold sore not
because the virus is dead if you get the
cold sore because the virus is actually
living it's alive it's inside the body
it's in the sore it's in the saliva in
that moment it's there okay so viruses
are actually alive this is how cold
sores herpes simplex one get trans
minute to another person then that's how
it's done it's because it is alive drink
out of somebody's glass and they just
shrank out of it whatever and then you
you could be a year you get it later a
year and it comes out but it could also
come out pretty quick and that happens
too depending on the variety of the
Simplex in the cold sore virus as well
but anyway let's go into this a little
bit for the record viruses are living
check this out in the publicly known
Arena of science
there is a battle about whether viruses
are dead or alive
no one can agree
so in that public medical research and
science Arena no one can agree and
neither side has proven facts
either side they don't have proven facts
they cannot show it they cannot say no
I'm going to show you the viruses alive
and the other then the other side I'm
going to show you the virus is dead and
they still can't even show each other
which is really incredible all on its
own here is a pillar of Truth
viruses are alive viruses are cells not
a strand of something not something
that's dead
and viruses eat
and they love food one of the favorite
food viruses love is this food I'm
holding in my hand right here that's one
of its most favorite foods we'll talk
about that too you guys recognize those
right here crack one of these open
get it in a pan get it cooking all right
I want to protect my eggs right here I
want to keep them here some baby chicks
are going to hatch
and I got to get them underneath the
heat lamp so they stay warm so they
hatch later on
okay
for a virus to live long enough inside
the human body to create a chronic
symptom or condition that's right
do you have a chronic symptom
do you have a chronic condition
fibromyalgia
R.A Hashimoto's
psoriatic arthritis
symptoms in general
all kinds of different neurological
symptoms
do you have one of those
for a virus to live long enough inside
the human body to create a chronic
symptom or condition it has to be able
to find food to sustain itself
the virus has to be able to find
something to eat in order to stay alive
inside your body
it can't just live inside your body
and just live there forever
it needs a food source whether an old
Well Spring of food inside your body
meaning inside your liver or something
you got something camped out in here for
many years but it needs something or a
new food you just ate that day it needs
food in order to sustain itself to stay
alive inside our body
it has to be able to find a food source
to sustain itself
if you guys wonder what I'm reading page
49 mm school going down right now got
the brain saver book Brain saver
protocols book right there having some
fun today
yeah
a virus does not have a mouth now this
little virus here in my hand has a mouth
right there and two eyes
and some teeth and a nose now viruses do
not have a mouth important to know
so a virus does not have a mouth and if
it's in okay sir as if it's an animal or
a human eating
instead a virus absorbs fuel
through its viral cell membrane
so it has absorption strength
that's what a virus does it gets food
through its membrane
to eat
a viral cell creates a vacuum effect now
medical research inside doesn't know
this
so this is all advanced information
about viruses and how they eat right
here in brain saver so if you're new to
Medical medium information you might be
like oh great where did you research
that
oh God this guy's pretty cool where did
he research that I want to know where
that research paper is he must have done
his research
it's information that's unknown to
medical research and science to all the
clinics to all the universities they
don't know this
they know now a couple years they'll
publish a paper
plagiarizing this probably and not
saving it they've done it already in
different ways
so this is important to know right here
the viral cell has this vacuum effect
temporarily drawing in water
this is just unbelievable actually right
here
within the blood it draws water from
your blood into the viral cell
that's what it does creates a vacuum
effect and draws water into its cell
and then
right
in that water is viral fuel
and that's the next part so say you got
egg particles
that have been broken down by your
digestion
that entered the bloodstream up the
hepatocortal vein
got into your main Highway
got into your bloodstream
and those egg particles
are floating around throughout the body
well the viral cell creates a vacuum
effect temporarily drawing in water
within the blood that's filled with egg
particles I'm just using egg as an
example it's not the only thing viruses
love to eat
and here's the cool part
it draws in this water filled with viral
fuel like egg particles or some other
food
through any area of the viral cell
membrane
so it's not like it has a mouth or it
only vacuums it up through one aspect of
the cell membrane the virus actually
absorbs the food through any part of the
cell membrane so it absorbs that water
from your bloodstream with that fuel in
it and it enters into the cell at any
place around the cell so any part of the
viral cell
and then immediately excreting that
fluid
through any other part of the cell
membrane
so here's the other thing so it can
actually excrete that fluid
if a virus is highly active like simplex
one we've got a cold sore Simplex 2
right you got a blister somewhere a
genital area
you got that you're active it's active
or you got mono or you got an
Epstein-Barr that's out and about and
it's doing its thing or you're about to
come down with the shingles virus
because the shingles is inside of you
people spread the shingles virus all the
time to other people it's really easy to
do or hhv6 or hhv7 or any of the number
of Epstein-Barr viruses
the virus is highly active it will need
to feed on viral fuel on an hour hourly
basis
so viruses don't intermittent fast
that's an important thing to know
viruses are not on the intermittent
fasting diet
viruses need to feed every single hour
when they're active
so
Michelle L hey like ourselves absorb
stuff very similar
if a virus is highly active it will need
a feed every hour if the virus is
inactive or even dormant it will need to
feed on viral fuel on a weekly to
monthly basis
Lulu says what do you mean vacuum effect
the virus can actually distort its
cell-like body and create a vacuum
effect drawing water from your
bloodstream through the membrane of the
virus into the virus itself and then
excreting that water back out but
leaving
bits and pieces of particles behind a
food that it likes
viruses do like dairy products viruses
like eggs viruses like gluten and you
might say oh he's talking about gluten
I'm sure there's tons of research on
that there isn't
they didn't know until the medically in
books that pathogens feed on gluten
itself and that's where the problem
really lies that's why someone can eat
gluten their whole life and not have a
problem
because the pathogens are either not
inside their body or they don't have
enough pathogens or the right kind of
pathogens they don't have viruses and
the viruses aren't feeding on that
gluten somebody else could have two or
three Epstein bars a shingles virus hb6
they can have herpes simplex one and
when they eat gluten
the viruses go to town and feed on that
gluten
and that's why a person that's 16 17 18
20 years old 25 years old can have a
problem with gluten and then that 80
year old guy down the road doesn't have
a problem with food
and the Doom says I saw one of the
podcast doctors talking about thick
blood today
hmm wonder where that one key got that
one
yeah that's actually real pleasure
plagiarism at its best right there
ah What a Wonderful World it is
okay let's move on a little bit good
stuff in here Tammy says virus draws in
water dot dot dot
is that one of the reasons people with
virus can feel dehydrated it's it's not
one of the reasons why usually people
are just chronically dehydrated Tammy
and thanks for the question it's really
cool it's a great question you're over
there on Facebook awesome
if the virus is inactive like I said it
could take a week to do a feeding it
could take a month to do a feeding if
the virus is really dormant and inactive
the virus has an ability to expel almost
all fluid out of its cell structure so
it can then be refilled and new fluid
that Harbors the viral fuel how insane
is that
let's see
which page are you reading over there on
YouTube I'm reading page 49 doing a
little mm spool for the moment just fun
stuff
we got brain saver you there's two books
right you know about that brand saber
protocols get them at amazon.com us
they're over 40 off right now I was like
oh my God amazon.com us
and they're just they're they're heavy
books just forewarning I saw somebody
did complain and I felt bad because they
were like oh my God like when they got
it delivered to them they're like I
didn't know these books were that big
that failed I mean
the information is so vast and insane in
these books
Maria says can Gloria chlorine dioxide
work to kill the viruses if you look in
the brain saver you'll see I talk about
chlorine dioxide
and I talk about how it doesn't work
check it out it's in here
all right
but it took about like the information
and protocols in the books
if you're concerned about that
so the virus has an ability to expel
almost all fluid out of its cell
structure
so it can then be refilled with new
fluid that Harbors viral fuel so you
ready for this
the buyers
can squeeze out all fluid out of itself
and then vacuum up a whole new batch
of water from your bloodstream filled
with more viral fuel
when the virus is active and feeding
regularly its viral cells are
continually excreting all of their
contents through their cell membranes so
here's where we get in trouble
here's where we get in trouble it's one
of the places
and before I move on that I want to say
one other thing too
eggs are not the only thing they eat so
I want to make that clear eggs are not
the only thing viruses eat virus swims
in your body
it just loves those eggs
all right
viruses love toxic heavy metals they
love dairy products they love gluten
they love lots of things I've talked
about this in all of the eight medical
medium books
on the medical mean book series
when the virus is active in feeding on a
regular basis check this out you guys
this is this is all like
what huh
I mean it's incredible really I mean
when I was getting the information on
this alone I was just like oh my God
this is like mind-blowing
so when a virus is feeding a lot because
it's really highly active
its viral cells are continually
excreting right all of their contents
through the cell membranes making
someone who has the viral infection
experience heightened symptoms
so here's how it works
I'm just going to give you a quick
rundown on some symptoms right now I
mean there's 300 symptoms and conditions
in these books
I mean check them out when you can you
can go to amazon.com and get them over
40 off but check this out or for library
for free go to the library for free
so when somebody has a viral infection
they don't know they have that their
doctor can't tell them their doctor's
not telling them they're going from
Doctor to doctor to doctor they're
looking for answers they're going to
neurologists and Specialists and
internists they don't know why their jaw
pain that's mysterious
their neck pain that's mysterious
they're burning skin feeling
they're vibrating their body vibrating
they're tremors
their ticks and their spasms
they're ringing in the ears they're
vertigo and dizziness
feeling like they're on a boat
right they're popping and buzzing in the
ears
right they're burning gums burning
tongue
pain everywhere they're trigeminal
neuralgia their back pain that's a
mystery their feet pain that's a mystery
they're restless leg syndrome you guys
like right all these symptoms and these
are just some they're tingles throughout
their body that's mysterious Tangles on
their nose their face
all these different symptoms they don't
realize are viral they don't know that
and the doctor doesn't know that if you
hear that on on a podcast somewhere of a
doctor talk about it it's published
medical meme info and nobody knew any of
this
Tiffany Scott says Anthony I have sent
you messages about my story healing
whoa your bronchitis and I never heard
back I'm Healed oh my God incredible
incredible
I might not have seen them I mean
I'm not trying to like say anything
but a lot of stuff is hidden
like there's a lot of glitches on IG and
other platforms and it's a lot of stuff
that I never see
and there's a lot of stuff you guys
never see too which is just it's sad
okay you ready you guys
the reason why I was saying the problem
is if the virus is really active and
it's feeding a lot and it's eating a lot
and it's on a regular basis that means
when the virus takes in the fuel
into the virus
eats it and then excretes it's excreting
a neurotoxin so now the virus is
excreting byproduct out of it which
could be neurotoxins of all kinds of
varieties depending on what the virus is
feeding on
if the virus is feeding on copper so
don't drink out of the copper fasks and
don't you know don't do the whole copper
thing you got to be careful if the virus
is feeding off of copper then you're
going to be getting like all kinds of
stuff eczema psoriasis
so the virus actually fills up with all
kinds of food eats it and then excretes
it on a regular basis
and here's the deal that toxic stuff
that the virus is excreting you guys
circulates in the bloodstream and lands
on nerves and now you've got vagus
nerves that are inflamed because you're
really highly active with the low-grade
or higher grade viral infection so now
you got nerve problems
you got the vertigo you got the
dizziness you got the ringing in the
ears the tinnitus you've got all the
different aches and pains the burning
skin you got the Restless Leg Syndrome I
could go on and on and on
and then you're going to get all kinds
of diagnoses oh wait the doctor thinks I
have Lupus the doctor thinks I have MS
and doctor thinks I just have five row
the doctor thinks I'm crazy you're just
gonna it's gonna be all these different
things
that's what happens when the bug is
gobbling up and excreting and excreting
the publicly known medical industry
is completely unaware that viruses eat
that's a medical medium
and medical medium science piece of
information
a publicly known medical industry is
completely unaware you guys that viruses
eat
they have not seen it studied it written
a paper on it
it is medical medium information a
viruses eat the classified get ready for
this the classified medical industry
knows
classified medical industry
knows because the classified medical
industry feeds viruses and breeds them
Harvard wherever medical universities
clinics
everywhere around the world
don't know viruses eat they have no clue
and no idea all the doctors they Stamp
Out have no idea viruses eat
but classified medical research in
science which is completely a different
world and separated it's separated
completely from all public university
medical research and science to
Everything Medical Schools it's
completely separated
and the classified medical industry
knows
that viruses actually eat because the
classified medical industry
feeds the viruses and then breeds them
keeps them alive in their labs and uses
viruses food of choice preferably raw
egg
iron
and Mercury
that piece of information you're
learning right here
is mind-blowing
go to medicalmedium.com if you're having
trouble watching this episode on social
media head to medicalmedium.com because
I'm streaming this episode right now
live I'm live right there on medical
medium.com it's so cool and our little
reminders we keep on reading this
mind-blowing information
from brain saver
a little reminder that we have a two-day
wild blueberry drinks challenge coming
up next week be prepared have your wild
blueberry juice ready it's on sale at
wymans.com check out the link it's in
the description but most importantly go
to
medicalmedium.com and
make sure you download that information
get your free PDF on your grocery
shopping list and everything else that
you might need for the drinks challenge
because it's going to be really fun and
we're gonna make a lot of drinks
I'm excited
but I'm really stuck on this piece of
information right here like I'm stuck on
this like this is insane
check this out
okay
the classified medical industry knows
because classified medical industry
feeds a virus but check this out they
feed them a preferable food that the
viruses love
which is eggs
iron
know why people are they have all that
different iron deficiencies it's all
mystery to medical research and science
why they have iron deficiencies
whether anemia and all that is happening
and it's happening rampantly right now
viruses feed on iron inside the person's
blood making them anemic so it's
mysterious
to the doctors in public medical
research and science
and of course Mercury that's another one
too other Foods the classified medical
industry feeds viruses to keep them
alive are gluten
which nobody knows that
Dairy nobody knows that and GMO medical
grade corn
so the classified medical industry
sometimes uses GMO medical grade corn to
feed the bugs they breed raise
in labs
here's another interesting part right
here I mean do you guys have the books
I'm on page 49.
one of the problems of the publicly
known medical industry when it comes to
viruses is that it's so underfunded in
this area so you got to keep in mind too
the reason why public medical research
science doesn't know anything about
viruses is because it's underfunded
that's why
no one can find the truth even if they
want to
unless they grab a medical medium book
so they hash out theories that are all
on paper because they're not allowed to
study viruses adequately so just so you
know publicly known medical research and
science are not allowed to study viruses
they're allowed to talk viruses and talk
virus theories they're not allowed to
study them
Never mind take a virus of choice and
look at it under a microscope so
publicly known medical research in
science are not allowed to take viruses
study them under a microscope
and figure out how they work
it's not allowed in the public medical
research and science Arena
virologists are not allowed to do that
they're allowed to be a virologist but
they're not allowed to do that
very few doctors are scientists that get
authorization check this out
very few doctors here in the public
medical research and science Arena
get authorization
from
The Wizard of Oz
and the outcomes are always vague
obscure and inconclusive so if
a medical doctor does want to study
viruses very few in the world in the
public medical research and science
Arena are allowed to look at a virus and
their conclusions are always vague and
obscure
inconclusive
so the publicly known medical industry
stays stuck in its war with itself over
whether viruses are just a dead strand
of RNA and protein
or they're alive
[Music]
many medical professionals believe
viruses are only alive if they're an
influenza
flu strain
so keep that in mind that's the only
time it's allowed
and Epstein-Barr is not alive to the
medical research at Science World uh
yeah shingles is not alive uh nothing's
alive
not even simplex one is alive nothing's
alive in the world of medical research
and science
but many many medical professionals
believe viruses are alive only
the ones that do believe they're alive
only believe influences alive
and even then it remains questionable
because of this ongoing internal War
you're not allowed to look at the
influenza influenza under the microscope
as a doctor
granted or funded to do so so you really
don't know if the flu is actually alive
or not
you guys following me on this stuff the
publicly known medical industry has to
work with theories kind of like
astronomers do
as an astronomer you go to bed at night
dreaming about what you might discover
behind the stars with your telescope
right so if you're into the stars and
you go to school to be an astronomer
you basically just go to bed at night
wondering what's behind those Stars
the same thing as a virologist in the
publicly known medical industry you go
to bed at night dreaming that someday
you may get funded
and truly discover what a virus does
so if you want to grow up someday and
become a virologist
you're going to be going to bed every
night wondering what a virus really does
and in hopes that maybe you get funded
to get a chance to look at a virus
if you're lucky and if you do
inconclusive that's what your study
paper will say
I wonder why
and then you're gonna and then you're in
bed at night wondering as a virologist
is a virus even alive or not maybe it's
an RNA DNA strand
in the meantime you keep yourself busy
in your career attending meetings and
medical com you know conventions and
reading other colleagues theoretical
papers
and you listen to that Lucky Devil who
was funded briefly who's up on the stage
at a convention talking about their
theory of what they think they
discovered that's the Grim reality of
the publicly known medical industry
you guys were reading right here at
brain saver
we got the brain saver books right here
we're doing a little virus talk if you
guys don't mind it's pretty cool I mean
I love this information when I receive
the information I was so like oh my God
this is unbelievable the information's
incredible
that's my opinion you might have a
different opinion you're like well I
don't know
the classified medical industry is a
whole other game
uh oh
they know that viruses eat
they do
SOC has told me they do
they feed the viruses
uh-huh they do
they grow viruses
proliferate viruses and altar viruses
and every now and then one escapes the
lab
this is what the classified medical
industry has been doing for over a
hundred years now since the Spanish Flu
was released in 1918.
this is what classified medical research
and science has been doing for over a
hundred years now
the classified medical industry knows
more about viruses much more than the
publicly known medical industry which is
your doctor at the doctor's office your
scientists at the science lab
your University Medical you know
researcher whatever they don't know
remember this
I repeat remember this
viruses are alive
viruses eat
and viruses are a single cell
that is viruses are single cell living
microorganisms
while it's always possible through a
mutation change a mutated change
for them to become multi-cell living
microorganisms
we'll talk here about single cells
because as time check goes by and
they're messed with anything's possible
the most appropriate term for these
single cell microorganisms is viral cell
that's the most appropriate term for
what's ailing people
as we get into the details of how
viruses inflame the central nervous
system and cause life-altering symptoms
and conditions in the process because
you guys that's what's happening right
now you've got a whole world of sick
people developing they're developing
with neurological symptoms
the brain saver books are here for that
right
but this is what everybody's
experiencing and living with
that's how it's going now
the reality that viruses are hungry
living microorganisms will be
foundational knowledge
in the future if they're going to save
people
from pain and suffering
so I got a little bit more to read if
you guys are up for it I just want to
give you a little 4-1-1 making an
announcement and I made an announcement
I'm excited for the two day free Wild
blueberry challenge but it's a drink
challenge which is really cool and
that's going to be fun I'm going to make
all these different drinks and since the
holidays are happening it might be
really fun and you get to stay away from
alcohol yeah you might not want to stay
away from alcohol because you might like
alcohol you might be somebody who likes
alcohol and I get it but like it'd be
nice to give your body a break and maybe
do a whole bunch of drinks that don't
have alcohol in them and instead are
really high in antioxidants really high
in antioxidants that would be really
cool
go to medicalme.com and you will see or
Link in the description Link in the
profile
definitely download your free grocery
shopping list get on the medical medium
newsletter
brain cells are highly vulnerable
so that's the thing with brain cells
they're different than other cells
inside our body other cells are inside
our body
are not as vulnerable
brain cells have to be pure and clean
unlike the liver which is meant to be a
filter for the body so your liver cells
are meant to be a filter for your body I
hope this doesn't fall out
these cells are tougher
these cells are meant to handle some
dirt
that's what your cells in your liver are
meant to do they're meant to handle some
dirt
and some grime
okay
but your brain cells
much more fragile
they're designed to just be pure and
clean
and that's the difference so when it
comes down to brain cells they have to
be pure and clean
it can't be dirty cells your liver
has dirty cells
now you don't want your liver saturated
with so much gunking problems and
everything you want to know the medical
meme information to clean up your liver
because you clean up your liver you
clean up your brain because that means
less stuff gets in the brain so let's
get into that
unlike the liver which is meant to be a
filter for the body the brain is never
meant to be a physical filter but guess
what you guys ADHD
depersonalization brain fog
focus and concentration issues
depression anxiety
100 other different symptoms
our brain becomes the filter
so our brain
is bringing in it doesn't want to bring
in but it ends up bringing in
our body brings brings in lots of toxins
and poisons that get to the brain cells
and the brain cells aren't pure and
clean anymore they get heavy metals in
them and so many other different toxins
and poisons that we talk about all the
time and we talk about in the brain
saver books
just mind-blowing information
your brain should never be a filter in
this scent in this sense
toxins your brain should only be a
filter in the sense of processing
information
that's when your brain is a filter when
it's processing information
but your brain is not supposed to be a
physical filter
for air fresheners scented handles
detergents that have all kinds of
chemicals in them
right Chemtrails falling out of the sky
toxic heavy metals that are in all kinds
of pharmaceuticals you name it it's not
supposed to be a filter for that but
your brain ends up becoming a filter for
all that stuff and all that chunk
it should only ever be a filter the
sense of processing information
receiving Communications
Karen asks what book is this one page 50
of brain saver
check it out it's for over 40 amazon.com
us buy both books here what book is aw
referencing Pamela Miller I'm in brain
saver
you guys have the book right
our brain should only be a filter for
processing information you guys
receiving Communications from another
source or another human being that's
when our brain becomes a filter
the brain houses a complex spiritual
Network
it also houses a complex physical
which requires absolute
Purity to the highest degree
it can't be that expired piece of fish
at the market with the fog glazing over
its eyes and an odor coming off of it
because the fish had become a filter for
a polluted ocean loaded with dioxins
Mercury nuclear waste petrochemicals and
sewage filled and pharmaceuticals
see
Maria says
LMAO so laughing my ass off
obviously
she says but the fact that he thinks
that the Spanish Flu really existed
laughing my ass off makes me think
you know like why I want to laugh my ass
off right now whatever wherever you got
the information that the Spanish Flu
didn't exist
makes me laugh my ass off
because then that means that wherever
you got that information
they're not really an intelligent source
and I guess I shouldn't be laughing my
ass off I should be
more like being sad
and saying that's sad that's sad kind of
breaks my heart a little bit
because that means there's a lot of
people out there it's a lot of stupid
information
and you're sitting there laughing at
like
incredible Advance information that's
already saved lives the medical medium
book series right and you're sitting
there laughing and that's cool and all
because I think that's kind of funny
that you're laughing because anytime
someone laughs I kind of laugh anyway
I'm like oh you're laughing at that okay
but whatever but I can tell you this
and I'm just just being honest okay
viruses are alive
viruses eat classified medical research
and science raised
the Spanish Flu they raised that variety
of influenza in a lab
and they released it
and that's why it killed that many
people on the planet
it was engineered and it did exist and
people did die in 1918.
and it is what it is
but I get it if you don't believe that I
hope you stay around anyway hang out
have some fun
and we'll still talk cool stuff here
all right
but listen I hope you actually learned
the good information and then
so you have that
the brain houses a complex spiritual
Network it also houses a complex
physical Network
I wonder what Dr Nesbitt would say about
that comment
which requires absolute Purity to the
highest degree it can't be that expired
piece official I was talking about
I get it to try and discount all the
people who've lost their lives is really
sad trying to rewrite histories another
thing too because what I've seen out
there is people
constantly rewrite history
and then discount all the suffering that
happened right is that what's going to
happen now oh my God
is that where we're going
all the people with neurological
symptoms that are like bedridden on
mattress Island right now you know how
many people have neurological fatigue
they can't even function
there's just like suffering the worst
Panic the worst anxiety they can't even
function they're wasting away
is it all in their head too
should I be laughing my ass off at them
is that what I should be doing should I
laugh my ass off at like all the people
that are suffering and sick with
neurological problems
no
duh
all right
let's move on ready we can't look at her
brain and know if our brain is going bad
from cologne perfume
scented candles air fresheners and toxic
heavy metals when our brains starts to
develop problems we don't see a symptom
or experience a condition quite yet so
what happens is our brain ends up taking
all these metals and all these different
chemicals and all these different toxins
and all the pharmaceutical pollution
right our brain takes it all in and
absorbs it all in you guys but we don't
really know anything yet we don't know
anything yet we don't really
experiencing really anything yet it
takes time for those cells to really get
soaked up and get those toxins and
poison soaked up
when our brain starts to develop
problems we don't see a symptom or
experience a condition quite yet we
can't open our skull
like an egg
take a look inside
and take a sniff to find out if it's
gone rotten like a piece of fish has
gone rotten
can't use visual clues or our sense of
smell
like we can with that egg or a piece of
fish that rotten egg to determine if our
brain is getting toxic or dirty you
can't crack somebody's head open like an
egg sniff it and be like oh it's rotten
in there
only when we start to develop symptoms
from a brain that's been suffering for
weeks or months or years do we start to
get a clue about what's going on inside
but I got a message for the person who
was talking about the Spanish Flu always
remember okay and this is just
being honest and I'm trying to listen to
Spirit of compassion because he said to
me
he said
be nice aw don't get sarcastic
don't get defensive and stick up for the
information
Spirit of compassion said just tell her
if she gets really sick down the road
take the medical medium books to your
doctor or practitioner have them help
you through it
but the information is for
that person down the road
so let's keep on going a little bit
Kimberly Kobe says which juicer is best
all-around celery at all
hmm
[Music]
the mm-1500 which does a whole bunch of
stuff
I talked all about it and the mm-900
which is an incredible juicer and it
saves money
you guys know the whole thing it saves
money for real incredible juicers
but it has to be the mm-1500 or the
mm-900 can't be just any juicer and you
will be surprised it'll be so great
you'll save money in the whole bit I
endorse them and just told you guys all
about them and everything
all right
what's he talking about celery juice
okay let's go no but I appreciate you
asking that anyway and I'm not making
fun of you on any level it's just that I
always tell you guys I always get
punished
for when I bring out the juicer a whole
bunch of people attack me and say there
he is with his juicer it's like oh my
God it's like they can't tell you how
many people DM and everything else and
ask like where's the best juicer or how
do I juice celery where's the juicer
sale like I get asked it 100 times and
then I go like three four months without
even mentioning the juicer and then
the community buys a juicer that doesn't
save the money out there and they're
spending all this money on produce and
going broke and it's the saddest thing
I've ever seen so now I have to talk
about it more in order to make sure if
people don't get ripped off
all right
see guys we're talking about some really
cool information right here I'm really
excited about this
Jennifer Leonard says it's okay aw
remember there's a lot of people still
hearing about you for the first time
you're right Jennifer you're right
you're right and that is so cool and
you're on Facebook that is so cool to
say because I'm going to tell you right
now that why that's so cool because
that's why I repeat myself
so many people punish me for re they
scold me and scold me for repeating
myself and and the reason why I do that
is because of the new people coming on
board
only when we start to develop symptoms
from a brain that's been suffering for
weeks or months or years do we start to
get a clue about what's going on inside
and the clue you guys is not in medical
research and science I have not seen it
so many people suffering with symptoms
conditions and they still don't know
what's going inside the brain the brain
saver books are actually able to clear
that up which is really important and do
you have the brain Jennifer do you have
the brain saver books
right here
if you don't have the 26 dollars because
they're over 40 off on Amazon go to the
library and get them for free everybody
if you go to the library and get them
for free I used to go to I haven't this
year been able to do this but I used to
load up a van and I used to drop books
off at libraries and then I would go
literally in different counties and then
in different states and I would do that
it was just exhausting and really hard
to do but go to your library ask for the
book
and try to get the book as you know from
the previous chapters the electricity of
your brain is meant to be clean
your electrical Grid in your brain
you've got a wine glass in front of the
brain here
your electrical Grid in your brain is
meant to be clean
the fluid of your brain
right the spinal fluid is meant to be
clean the blood in your brain is meant
to be clean you guys on page 51 and so
your liver your brain's best friend is
working overtime to keep poisons out of
your brain so your brain doesn't have to
become the filter and yet life here on
planet Earth doesn't work so ideally
because our livers get so overloaded
like I was telling you before our brains
get saturated with poisons from all the
areas and angles including prescription
Pharmaceuticals that are supposedly for
the brain
foreign
toxic heavy metals preservatives
chemicals caffeine and more that you'll
read about in these books
the brain is meant to be a sponge for
knowledge
so your brain is meant to be that sponge
for information and knowledge
instead it becomes a sponge for waste
as blood is pumped to the brain it is
blood that's filled with many different
toxins
the publicly known medical field doesn't
want any part in knowing this because
the last thing it needs is to learn
about the poisons that enter our brains
as you know that if the publicly known
medical research and Science World finds
out
they learn
what's poisoning our brains
that's a little crazy and a little scary
because if they learn that
they have to shut up they don't want to
learn that because they can't speak out
if they ever learn that that would
expose the crimes the neglect and the
agendas of the classified medical
industry and maybe even the wizard that
puppeteers it all
that's incredible
notably some of the poisons that get
through to the brain are viral toxins is
which why so many people are sick
they're sick to death of being sick and
they're sick
viral toxins including viral neurotoxins
remember I was talking about that
earlier viral neurotoxins from the virus
eating so what I was trying to tell you
guys is I'll make it really
easy breezy almost drop my egg
okay
the virus
inside people's bodies or viruses
whether it's Epstein bars herpes simplex
one herpes simplex 2 hhv6 shingles virus
hhv7
whether whatever varieties and strains
of them loves to feed on the food it
releases a neurotoxin that neurotoxin
goes to the brain short circuits the
brain
and makes it so we suffer and struggle
with symptoms and conditions
anybody want to have a couple eggs with
me later
crack them open or fry them up how do
you like your eggs
scrambled fried
poached
I'll make some eggs for everybody
the new people here will be like oh my
God he loves eggs this is the place to
be incredible
Egg party
okay
the virus is giving off these toxins
usually come from elsewhere in the body
they may reside in the liver lymphatic
system spleen intestinal tract
reproductive system nervous system and
even the skeletal skeletal system
I gotta learn to read better you guys
have you checked out medical meme
podcasts at Apple podcast I did swelling
episode have you heard it have you heard
the aliens podcast episode have you
heard all the different episodes of
medical meme podcast at Apple podcast
check it out when you get a chance
viruses can even Nest inside bone marrow
viruses can Nest inside somebody's bone
marrow
where many toxic heavy metals such as
mercury reside and settle this is one of
the foundations of blood cell and bone
marrow disease
mainly the viruses reside in the liver
though but they do end up in the bones
too for so many people
this is cool right here you guys check
it out as I mentioned earlier these
herpetic viruses range from Epstein-Barr
virus I was known as the Epstein-Barr
guy I was
ostracized and made fun of and
discriminated discriminated against
because I was known as the Epstein-Barr
guy and then years and years later
people are using the Epstein-Barr
information
what happened
they range from Epstein-Barr virus and
it's over 60 varieties to shingles and
it's over 30 varieties of
cytomegalovirus what
CMV and it's many varieties to multiple
varieties of human herpes 6 hhv6 to well
over a dozen varieties of herpes simplex
and a hundreds of the hhv varieties and
mutations most of which are undiscovered
by publicly known medical research and
science
classified medical research and science
let the viruses out of the running gate
publicly known medical research and
science
stumble across certain varieties of
viruses by chance like the Epstein-Barr
in the 60s
okay you guys I want to give you just a
quick rundown real fast two-day wild
blueberry drinks challenge I just want
to let everybody know it's next week
get ready for it it's free make sure you
have wild blueberry juice or you know
what you need to check out your grocery
list you can download your free pdf
grocery list so you know we're going to
be making drinks so it's gonna be really
fun holiday drinks or any kind of drinks
for any occasion but it's going to be a
great two days I'm doing six different
drinks
six different drinks I'm serious it's
going to be hilarious it's going to be
fun and I hope someone doesn't like rip
me a new one
with like the skit I do at the beginning
someone put a comment out the other day
saying
I lost all credibility because during
the wild blueberry challenge
I had baby chicks out and what else did
I have I had baby grogu out and I was
serving drinks and I was acting like I
was drunk or whatever I don't know what
they said
the point is though is that there are
people that don't like the skits but I
don't know what to do it's AWS Bar and
Grill you want me to shut down AWS I
need to ask you guys so let's do a
little poll right now okay do you want
me to shut down aw bar and grill for
good and just when I do wild blueberry
juice challenge just talk about the wild
blueberry
um here you guys it's on sale
and I'll show you how to make the drink
do you want me to do it that way or do
you guys want me to shut down aw Bar and
Grill
I'm just wondering
I don't know
I don't want to shut down ew Bar and
Grill
so yeah anyway
you guys are reading in brain save right
now no don't shut down aw Bar and Grill
one person said it no wait
Kane says love AWS Grill all right we're
not making eggs though I was kidding
around by that we're not doing that but
we will be doing the drain challenge
it's a two-day challenge it's free
download your free pdf get your free
grocery shopping list
I'm excited you guys it's next week
don't miss it I'm making six drinks
which is going to be a really fun
alcohol
no way no alcohol
Lorraine Hendricks says no no no no no
no no no no no no
Sandy says keep aw
ake
all right you got it I will okay
and the thing is you guys I can't wait
because it's gonna be fun and if you
guys make the drinks with me that's
going to be really fun
so I hope you make the drinks with me
too so I can't wait so make sure you got
what you need or whatever and we're
gonna do it that's next week we're gonna
have fun it's gonna be the free Wild
blueberry drinks challenge reading out a
brain saver right now
I just want to read a couple more
sentences check this out neurotoxins 101
so what are neurotoxins neurotoxins are
a thing produced it's a toxic waste
produced by viruses released in our
bloodstream and throughout our body
these neurotoxins land on phrenic nerves
they land on vagus nerves
they land on trigeminal nerves
have a glossal nerves
they land on all our different nerves
cranial nerves and they give us all
these mystery symptoms that can make us
feel like we're crazy
and make us really sick they could also
saturate the brain making us feel like
we have this fatigue where our legs feel
like lead and our arms feel like lead
so that's what neurotoxins can do and
they're produced from viruses like
Epstein-Barr virus hhv6 said
omegalovirus they're produced by viruses
the most common neurotoxins culprits
come from your garden variety
Epstein-Barr which everybody has
shingles everyone at this point in time
has at least one form of Epstein-Barr
and shingles living inside their body
these viruses can produce large
quantities of neurotoxins giving people
so many symptoms and conditions it's
incredible
and then because of that people end up
having so many problems but we need to
learn how to fix it how to get our
symptoms better
we need to learn what to do how to clean
up the neurotoxins how to kill off the
viruses how to beat them down how to
beat them how to clean up how to restore
our central nervous system how to make
ourselves stronger how to make our
immune system stronger all these things
matter you guys this has been incredible
check out the medical meme podcast at
Apple podcast check out the swelling
episode I did recently it's mind-blowing
information which is really incredible
right
check out the brain saver books whatever
go to the library get one for free if
you want
and make sure you're ready for that wild
blueberry drinks challenge which is
going to be fun too all on its own and
check out telegram if you haven't you
know got onto my telegram check it out
because I'm leaving messages every day
or every other day or when I can so
leaving like exclusive messages on there
which is really fun
and so
and sign up to the medical medium
newsletter so you know what's going on
okay so you get like free recipes and
you know what's happening and all this
other stuff too the medical medium
newsletter it's helping you guys
actually sign up to that as well
but thank you for being here
during this episode of viruses eat I
love you guys