so we have is the butternut squash
there's a divot in here why
because there was a pretty big hole
poked into this
i see it all the time in the market and
what people don't realize is those holes
right here's one here
those gashes
that was equipment gashes
and those gashes
there's grease on that equipment so a
little bit of grease goes into like
because i've seen all the farm equipment
i visit a lot of farms visit some
friends farms i've spent all around and
all that farm equipment there's grease
on every tractor grease on everything
and what happens is people don't realize
this so when you see when you see
injuries to things you want to cut them
out because you can have some grease
so what you want to do is carve out any
suspicious hole or
mark that's big enough you carve it out