we walk around with old hurt inside of
us from many many years ago in our lives
from betrayal broken trust not being
validated not being heard being
misunderstood being hurt by people that
we love people we don't love
relationships relationship breakups work
relationships because what we do is we
Harbor toxic baggage from wounds that
have been sitting inside of us for a
very long time inside of our soul side
of our heart inside of our spirit I'm
very happy to announce you can sign up
to the collecting Stones meditation
Journey that is going to be so profound
and so powerful it's going to blow your
mind it's going to move you forward
you're not going to experience anything
like this
it's a seven day Journey I'm going to
guide you personally through stones have
an ability to absorb but that ability is
not tapped into when you start that
Journey on the 19th something incredible
happens and a deeper connection starts
to occur when you do the collecting
Stones meditation Journey you're going
to be getting stones that are out in the
wild collect your stones on the day it
starts have an idea of where you're
going to collect your Stones maybe it's
going to be some grassy knoll somewhere
maybe it's going to be some field maybe
it's going to be some trail maybe it's
going to be a park maybe it's going to
be a beach wherever it is those stones
are going to be meant for you for this
reason for this profound way to absorb
and draw something out of you that
shouldn't be there anymore sign up and
start to think about where you're going
to get your stones
this is the summer of healing this is a
summer of healing emotionally mentally
spiritually when you're doing this
journey you're gonna feel it a deep
connection is going to grow an
unbelievably deep connection that's how
profound and that's how incredible this
journey is going to be
[Music]