Wellness reset at Cafe Gratitude this is
the kick butt Wellness reset talking
about healing the body talking about
healing the liver talking about healing
the gut it's only available for a
limited time it's at cafeic gratitude
it's a wellness reset it's Dirt Cheap
guess what I'm making on it big zero
because I just want people healing this
is a cleanse that can benefit anybody
whether you're looking to let go of a
little bit of weight or support healing
energy or simply give your body uh much
needed T up it's the celery juice heavy
metal detox smoothie it's the craving
shifter shot it's a spiced squash soup
it's the brain Soother juice it's the
healing broth soup the dream shifter
shot and you can do add-ons to this
cleanse you can do the estonians too and
you can do the massaged kale salad I
just want a healing cleanse in an
amazing place like ca gratitud so people
can heal and move forward with their
lives we've up this reset to be as easy
as possible for you you can either come
by one of our cafes and pick up a
one-day reset or you can also order a
3-day reset online and have it delivered
to your home
[Music]