ing too much were you told you're
detoxing too much do you hear out there
hey you're detoxing slow down the detox
maybe you need to slow it down we're
going to talk all about detoxing for a
little bit so I'm excited about this you
don't want to miss this episode plus
medical medium podcast at Apple podcast
I released a micro doing episode that
will blow your mind just want to give
you that quick rundown on that so don't
miss it medical Me podcast at Apple
podcast micro
doing hey man micro doing so I just want
to make sure you check it out it's a
really good episode It's really
informative powerful packed up
information we're talking about detoxing
I'm excited about this where does this
detoxing thing come from where does the
term come from what is it about so I
want to cover a couple things in the
conventional World detox meant people
going into a clinic and going through
pharmaceutical withdrawal just for the
record okay it wasn't about anything
else besides going into a clinic and
coming off of
morphine that's the term detox in the
conventional
mindset very important really important
topic here a lot of people are like I'm
detoxing too much or I'm not detoxing
enough or what's going on or my adrenals
are hurt because I'm detoxing very
important information we're covering but
the conventional World detox was going
into a clinic because you're on too much
pharmaceutical and you're coming off of
it or coming off of morphine or coming
off of oxies or coming off of something
else or even like benzo despine or
something right coming off of heavy
drugs and originally going back was
morphine that's what it was about it's
just all about morphine just letting you
know and so that's where detox comes
from on a conventional mindset on an
alternative mindset get ready for this
it's the old hygienic movement term
detoxing now I want to cover this
thoroughly this is important how did it
come about well the word detox came
about because people lived who lived in
the
cities were living in the toxic smog of
the factories and all of the toxic
surroundings and the car exhaust so what
would happen is people would be also
eating restaurant food too at the same
time and early canned and packaged food
early stuff early 1900s late 1800s old
canaries canning all the food packaged
food back then yeah and so it was all
about like lead cans and all that other
stuff so it was about toxic Lifestyles
so it was about getting out of the city
stopping partying and getting off of
recreational drugs very important to
know so in the alternative mindset
detox was all about getting away from
the fastpaced lifestyle of the day of
the 1890s and the early
1900s it was all about the early drug
movement it was all about the canned
food and it was all about the partying
and all about the MOG and the city
living and so detoxing would be get you
out of that environment in the early
1900s get you into a Country Manor
somewhere right in the Hills or
somewhere fresh air birds
chirping kind of like sanitarium kind of
like something that's a paradise nature
getting away from the toxic lifestyle of
the world the fast-paced world okay that
was also part of the alternative mind
mindset of detoxing and that even was
partly with the conventional mindset too
going back that far too a little bit but
conventional mindset mainly focused on
like getting off of morphine that was
the detox all right so let's cut into
this a little bit then the Whole Foods
you know movement just eating like
fruits and
vegetables herbs okay and getting away
from meat and this isn't a anti-meat
talk or anti- you know animal protein
talk or anything that's not what this is
at all but it was the early days the
early 1900s it was about getting away
from restaurant food and
beef and getting out of the
cities and getting into a cleaner
environment and getting off of all that
heavy animal meat okay so that was the
early alternative movement and instead
it was about eating nuts and seeds and
walnuts and almonds and cashews or
whatever you know different seeds and
all about that and sprouted grains and
it was all about getting out of the
cycle everybody was in the early 1900s
where they were eating meat and
restaurant food and were were using high
salt and we in the smog and pollution
and stress and it was about getting
somebody out the hygienic movement was
birthing and it was about getting that
person out of
that so they can actually be fre they
would they would get them off meat and
they would put them on nuts and seeds
instead of meat and this would be all
part of their
detox see so the hygienic movement was
birthed out of this
mindset and the hygienic movement was
all about your toxin sick so now you
need to
detox see where I'm going this is so
important you guys I I want you to watch
this from the beginning a couple of
times if you can this is going to answer
a billion questions I
think and but the point is is so
alternative medicine was about animal
protein was making you sick do you guys
get get my gist here I'm not saying
animal protein makes you sick when have
I ever said that that animal protein you
know medical medium's never been about
one or the other it's not has an
attacked animal meat the point is is
that the early hygienic movement was
you're sick hear me now don't miss this
point you're sick because you're eating
animal
meat and you have to get away from that
and go plant-based plant
foods and that's the hygienic movement
you are
toxic and then as the hygienic movement
grew a little a little bit more desserts
and sweets and
treats were all part of it
too so what happens is if you lived a
conventional lifestyle in the
1930s the
1940s and you weren't feeling well they
would say you need to take away all the
sweets all of the
Delicacies all of the rich
food all of the meat
Burgers they all had to go the hygienic
movement but there's something really
important to understand about this which
will blow your
mind the alternative hygienic movement
did not know why you were sick they
didn't know why someone had
Tremors they didn't know why someone
couldn't walk because they had like
wobblers they didn't know why someone
was fatigued deathly fatigued and
bedridden they didn't know why people
had all kinds of different
symptoms from severe brain fog to ticks
and spasms to aches and pains to tingles
and numbness to not being able to sleep
to everything from anxiety to depression
to trigeminal neuralgia to pain in their
jaw their neck their head everything
they did not know why anyone had any of
this this is so important the
alternative hygienic movement of Health
knew that you should detox that's they
called it they did not know why anyone
was sick they just thought it was
because you're toxic you needed to detox
that's all that's all they
knew and they only knew that up
until
until now the medical medium info about
bugs and pathogens and Epstein bars and
hhb6 is making people sick and metals
and all of that that wasn't in the
hygienic frame it wasn't in the hygienic
movement of Alternative Health at all on
any level they only thought in the let's
move pack now out of the 30 out of the
40s out of 1950s let's move up to the
80s they still believe the hygienic
movement you just toxic and you needed
to detox that's why you're sick and
bedridden that's why you're not well
that's why you got ticks and spasms
aches and pains and your body's
vibrating and got all these
problems I still did not know that there
were real reasons why people were sick
because face it everybody's toxic then
everyone is toxic you got
understand this right you mean a UPS
driver and the lawyer working at a law
firm and the waitress working at the
diner and the person checking out in the
grocery store and the person working at
this other place and the construction
guy working here and the you know the
bus driver that's working out there you
mean to tell me and the doctor that's
working here you mean to tell me they're
all not toxic they're all out there
living their life and they're living
their life toxic but they may not be
sick in the moment they may not be sick
right now they may not have a whole
bunch of symptoms you see what I'm
saying so what would happen is everybody
think about it everybody's toxic and
everybody has toxins in them but the
scale hasn't tipped yet or they haven't
gotten sick yet so back to the
alternative hygienic movement
again so the hygienic movement just
believed you were toxic and that's all
they believed that's it that you had a
detox it's a belief system it is a
belief system ingrained in early
alternative medicine please listen to
this if you can and that belief system
that was
ingrained is still floating around right
now and everybody's like your detox
Pathways your detoxing too much or you
don't know how to detox you're sick cuz
you're detoxing too heavy you're
bedridden because you're toxic in your
detox they're still passing it around
now it comes early comes from the early
1920s the early
1930s and that hygienic sense of detox
is still haunting everybody to this
day and that's the sad part confusion
with detox is probably one of the most
crazy epidemic things that's happening
right now in the health movement right
now I could just see some people
watching this right now being so irrit
irritated like wait a minute no that's
not how it is wait detox
detox because this is mind-blowing
information so let's get into it check
this
out okay everybody is
toxic everybody's got toxins in
them but one person is going to be
sitting there hurting really bad lots of
body pain lots of fatigue and another
person is not going to be sitting there
with lot of fatigue and body
pain they could be equally
toxic equally
toxic Mrs Jones is bedridden with
fatigue and brain fog can't
function Mr
Jones just as toxic is out there mowing
the
lawn that's just a fact
Jack okay everybody's toxic everybody
gets toxic everybody's eating all kinds
of [ __ ] and garbage everybody's doing
all kinds of stuff everybody's walking
around toxic but one person is bedridden
another person is really horribly sick
another person has 20 symptoms another
person has 50 symptoms and what you're
going to hear out there is you're just
going to hear detox talk and detox talk
and detox talk you're not detoxing
enough you're detoxing too much your
detox Pathways aren't working how would
you know how' you know your detox
pathways are working
nobody knows that what there's some kind
of computerized Imaging machine of some
kind that can just you could stand in
front and be like yeah see your detox
pathway is not really run uh what is
going out of your kidney huh doesn't
exist it's make believe make
believe so what's happened right now is
the term detox has been weaponized it is
weaponized and whenever something's
weaponized people are going to get hurt
they're going to get hurt they're going
to get hurt
and they are because it's a total
confused vest of the
mind and you see it every day out there
so let's go into it a little bit more
the hygienic
movement just thinks people are sick
because they need a detox that's all
it's all they think it's an old staple
it's been around and it's what you think
you go back to the 80s you're toxic you
go back to the '90s you're toxic toxic
that's why that's all it is and you need
a detox until you're
healed but what happens if you don't
heal oh you're not detoxed enough or
you're detoxing too
much nobody knows which way to go and
nobody knows which way the wind blows on
that it's Madness so let's clear the ear
a little bit and what's happening so
back to Conventional medicine and
conventional mindset detox was just
getting off of morphine
alternative and detox was just getting
off the morphine and leaving the cities
alternative movement was detox was just
getting rid of the riches and the sweets
and getting out of the Cities out of the
smog and that's it that's the reason why
you're sick you're sick because you've
eaten too much beef and you've gotten
too much beef in your
gut and you made yourself sick that is
the original
detoxification mindset there is it's
beef it's beef it's beef that's what it
is it is
1906 beef that's why you're sick baby
1910 it's beef that's why you're sick
baby 1920 beef is why you're sick and
some smog 1930 beef is why you're sick
and some smog 1940 beef again and some
smog do you
see that is how it really happened and
what goes down and has gone down
now don't take this as I'm anti- beef or
I'm anti- anything I'm just telling you
about the history because nobody knows
the history the history is critical and
the details matter with
this so then we went into the like weak
grass movement coming into the mid 70s
and early 70s where you're toxic and you
need to cleanse and you need to get on
your wheat grass and you need to get the
toxins out and that's why you're sick
and then it moved into the 80s you're
toxic because you know and you got to
get off the beef again and you got to
get off this junk and garbage in the
riches and the sweets you got to get off
of this and stop eating your chocolate
cake every day cuz you're
toxic that's where it all stems from and
comes from and it's haunted us since and
it's still haunting everybody now it's
just mindset of you're toxic you got to
detox and it's nothing but but
detox and that's the mindset coming from
the hygienic movement which has cursed
it has
cursed alternative wellness and health
it has cursed
it so there is a curse upon the health
movement and that curse will destroy and
ruin
lives 3 years from now someone gets sick
for the first time in their life and
they go into the health movement they're
on the internet and they're talking to
this person that person this doctor and
this practitioner this coach and this in
the end they're just going to get told
they're probably detoxing too heavy or
detoxing too much whether they're not
detoxing enough or something to do with
detox and they'll be
cursed good luck trying to heal good
luck let's go into it a little bit more
now all
right
okay so back in the lme disease movement
coming into the 70s and the early 80s
and this is very important to know don't
lose this information get a pen get
paper write this down this is Free by
the way I could box this up and sell it
but I want it free for
everybody back in the Lyme disease era
okay very important to know what
happened was people got sick nobody knew
why they thought it was a tickborne
illness and then they ran antibiotics
heavily into women women that already
had immune system problems and their
immune systems were breaking down and
they already were struggling physically
with their health they nuked them they
nuked thousands upon thousands of women
in the 70s and the 80s and the '90s and
they destroyed their lives they ruined
their lives they killed many of them off
they killed thousands of women off by
nuking them with antibiotics for Lyme
disease Untold
damage
Carnage because of the Lyme disease
situation where nobody knew why people
were sick they thought it was the tick
they thought that's what it was women
had all these weird symptoms
neurological symptoms and aches and
pains and they nuked them and they broke
their immune systems down and they threw
these people's lives away there are some
doctors now that are out there on the
scene including podcast doctors that
partook in this very thing in the 80s
and 90s and have blood on their
hands now what what happened out of that
was called the
herxheimer the die off you guys get
where I'm going right now the die
off so another place the detox actually
was supported through the hygienic
movement was when
basically the lime doctors were like
well I've heard detox my whole career
I've heard detox from medical clinics
getting people off of drugs I've heard
detox through alternative people talking
about how they're toxic and and they
need to cleanse and they need to get rid
of all those toxins so what I think is
happening to every time I put
antibiotics in a patient is I think
they're getting sicker because they're
having a die
off so the lme disease World which was
huge big billions of dollars of Industry
still is now they were nuking women
literally day in and day out running
powerful antibiotics throughout their
system annihilating their
bodies and then when women complain and
said I can't walk no more I can't talk I
can't think I think I'm dying they would
say it's die off you're detoxing the
lime bacteria and it's die off
so the messages were
mixed so not only do we have the early
hygienic detoxification talk from Smog
and what they said was too much
meat you also have the conventional
world with their detoxification talk of
getting off of morphine and drugs and
stuff and then you have the Lyme disease
World saying how this lime bacteria is
making women sick so when we hit them
with antibiotics the lime bacteria is
dying they're going into herxheimer's
and it's just detox do you guys see
where I'm going right
now detox has cursed so many people
literally cursed them to death you guys
have no idea what it has done and it has
destroyed lives from early on back in
the day all the way till today including
in Lyme disease and so forth it is the
curse of the alternative movement and
hell you might be fine cuz you might not
be that sick and you're just playing
around this product and that product and
you're over here playing around this and
seite and whatnot and bentonite clay and
charcoal and sow sweat off your brow and
then you got some person a woman laying
in their bed dying because they're
they're literally dying from like all
these kinds of other things I'm talking
about that were inter interwoven into
the detox talk throughout the whole
Century that has cursed people and it's
killing
people so the lime
movement
wasted tens of thousands upon thousands
of women's
lives there are thousands of graves with
women in there that died from being
bombarded through the lime
therapies no one gives a
crap no one
cares whatever because that's how this
dirty World Works anyway
so detox has grown into so many
different things throughout the course
of the hundred
years and the confusion with detox is
vast
now so let's go into a little bit
more as far as Lyme disease goes it was
the harsh antibiotic usage that was
eating away at the innards of people
that caused their symptoms to be worse
and then it was blamed on herxheimer's
which was pathogen die
off and pathogen die off took the hit
right there that was the excuse and they
used that into the they packaged it up
to the detox realm you're just detoxing
pathogen die off
right and that's why you're
suffering so let's go into a little
deeper on
this
the hygienic movement moved into the
vegan movement the vegan movement still
believes if you eat
meat that's why you're
sick the vegan movement still believes
that if you eat meat that's why you're
still sick you ever notice I never took
a stand either way did you ever notice
since the Inception of the first book to
any information I've ever given out
previous I never said that you know V
vegan vegan's the only way animal
protein animal protein's the only way
cuz it's not about these belief systems
it's really about what's wrong with a
person and why they're sick it's one
size of it's all was never medical
medium and all that proves
it but the vegans believe that beef is
why you were sick and you're toxic and
you need a detox that's what the vegans
believed all these years they stemmed it
off of the hygienic movement originally
where you were just toxic and you needed
to
detox
let's go into this a little bit deeper
now I'm going to move the chocolate cake
over
okay got a liver and a couple other
things all
right you guys I got celery juice right
here if you don't mind I'm going to take
another
sip
okay singy sweee says over there on
YouTube is that's the vegan movement I
guess I'm vegan without following the
beliefs of the movement I just thought
it was saving animals a lot of people go
vegan because they're saving animals
they
do but the majority of all vegans
plant-based people vegans whatever you
want to call them the majority of all of
them go plant-based and go vegan because
they got symptoms and they got sick
that's why they went that direction
there's a small small percentage that's
worried about animals and they stick to
that that moral grounding and they're
just like you know animals have souls
and they don't want to eat animals and
there's there's a small percentage then
they go vegan because of that but the
majority of all of them they go vegan
because they got sick or a symptom of
some kind and they went vegan because of
that so let's get into
detoxing all
right people are sick because
something's making them
sick meat is not making someone sick
I'm not pro meat I'm not anti- meat I'm
just saying meat is not making somebody
sick Mr Jones eats all the meat he wants
he's not sick Mrs Jones eats all the
meat she wants she's sick why is it Mr
Jones sick Mr Jones is sick what meat's
making M Jones sick NOP meat's Not
Making Mr Jones
sick there's people out there that are
eating all kinds of crazy stuff they're
eating all kinds of toxic stuff or what
you want to call toxic desserts and
sweets packaged food fried greasy food
and yeah eventually they'll get sick
from something and then you got somebody
who's eating very clean and they're
eating good and they're eating
everything that's coming from the best
farm and they're eating all their fruits
and vegetables and they're eating what
whatever and they're sick and they have
symptoms and they're
struggling because it's not about
detoxing it's about what's wrong with
you what is inside of you what what is
actually inside of
you and that's the key that the hygienic
movement did not know the hygienic
movement the early hygienic movement
going all the way into the modern
hygienic movement did not know people
were sick because of pathogens just
literally six seven years ago the
hygienic people right now today that are
plant-based still didn't think pathogens
had anything to do with any there is
data that I even have saved I could not
help it because I saw literally people
that were plant-based in the hygienic
movement just in 2018 saying how
pathogens did not
exist and Epstein bar was a joke and
does not exist and that you're sick
because you're toxic that's all you're
eating too much animal protein it even
CAU brought us all the way up to 2018
and 19 and it finally come 2020 when see
hit town and when SE hit town
everybody's like viral viral viral viral
what there's viruses they exist what we
have to wear masks it's viral and what
happens is that explosion all of a
sudden opened up The Floodgate so now
everybody's like oh yeah EP bar now oh
oh yeah epen
bar everybody's like oh oh yeah there's
bugs there's different bugs shingles
epine bar there's different bugs oh yeah
I didn't know the fever blister was a
virus I had no idea oh my God the fever
blister you're right I just thought you
were toxic and the hygienic movement
believed that a fever blister wasn't
viral did you know that in the 80s the
1990s the 2000s all the way to 2010 even
past that herpes simplex one was not a
virus it's believed by the plant-based
hygienic
movement and whatever gurus you call in
those movement believe that it wasn't a
virus viruses weren't real they weren't
anything you were just toxic and that's
where detox is really a poisonous thing
because it stems from such confusion and
misinformation from old belief systems
that still are there and have been
around I can promise you this if you
have a fever blister and that sucker's
popping on your lip and you go and you
kiss another person there's a very good
chance that fever blister that virus is
going to transfer onto that other
person's and they're going to have the
herpes simplex sv1 if they didn't
already have it HSV they're already
going to have
it right from that
kiss if they didn't have it
before so herpes simplex one herpes
simplex 2 are real viruses but so are
all the other viruses too and we can
catch them and transfer them in the
whole bit and it can catch up to us we
can go through our 20s and we can
actually catch three or four or six or
seven Epstein bars maybe even 20 Epstein
bars we can catch they can lay dormant
inside of us and then as we're heading
into our 30s our immune system starts to
lower we're doing things that can
trigger us maybe we're eating all the
wrong things that can trigger us meaning
they lower the immune system a little
maybe we go into some emotional stress
or hardship and all of a sudden we get
the scale tips and now we're sick and
we're like I don't know what's going on
my digestion and my floating and I'm
feeling kind of off and I don't feel
good overall and something's wrong and
what's happening is the epscene bar is
catching
up the herpy simplex one is catching up
the cyeg virus is catching up all the
metals that have been built up in your
brain and in your body are catching up
all the chemicals and all the fragrances
are catching up everything is catching
up and it's all building up but the
pathogens are the big one it determines
if someone is going to be really
struggling they're going to be bedridden
brain fogged not feeling
well the pathogens are going to be that
determination that's the big one right
there and the hygienic movement based
around the detox Theory and the belief
system that's developed all those years
doesn't even didn't even believe that a
virus had anything to do with I was
talking to guys back a decade ago
and they were just like aw I just don't
get it there are no pathogens in the
vegan in the plant-based hygienic
movement it's all about detox you just
need to detox and detox your
Pathways they were
lost they were lost now it kills them to
have to say virus kills them to have to
utter the word EBV I remember
distinctly an influencer ripping me
apart back in 201718 about epine bar
calling me the epine bar guy ripping me
apart and he was from the hygienic
movement belief system didn't even
believe the Epstein bar meanwhile the
guy probably had 10 Epstein bars lay
dormant in
him
easy so let's go into detox at another
level now it's just kind of a little bit
of an m M school today about
detoxing
so do we have to cleanse do we have to
get rid of poisons and toxins yes but
they don't take us down they don't make
us so sick we can't
function they
don't unless you're in a clinic because
you've been taking heroin for a year and
you're so jacked up on heroin you're so
jacked up that you're in this clinic and
you got to go through withdrawal that's
different that's different if you're
living your life and you got
sick detoxification isn't what is giving
you your
symptoms I've said it in medical medium
books and I've said it probably in radio
shows and so
forth that if you're highly highly toxic
and you're really really sensitive that
yes as you're cleansing you can feel
malaise a little more tired than
normal maybe a little
headachy but you won't get a massive
eruption of all kinds of rashes you
won't get like thrown where your legs
feel like cement and you're bedridden
you won't get all these ticks and spasms
and aches and pains and feeling like
you're literally dying you won't get all
of
that and and which leads to this next
next part here which is really
important when someone starts to do
something good for themselves and they
are and everything seems to be okay and
they're doing a little celery juice and
so forth and they're doing okay and all
of a sudden they get a symptom or they
don't feel
good they get
scared because someone will go you are
detoxing too fast you have to back up
and back down and back up out of that
don't do so much celery juice you're
going to have to back
out don't eat so much fruit or or greens
you're going to have to back
out somebody might be incorporating and
bringing some salads with some leafy
greens they might be doing 8 ounces of
celery
juice something's something's up on the
computer there and they might have they
might have
um a little bit of celery juice they
might be taking care of themselves they
might be taking out things like things
that they shouldn't be eating so much of
they might be removing things they might
be removing alcohol they might be
removing stuff out of their diet and
they're starting to get better and
starting to feel pretty good and they're
living their life and four months later
they start getting a symptom and they
start getting sick and then they're like
what's going on I'm doing 8 ounces of
celery juice I'm doing my leafy green
salad every day I haven't had fast food
too often I only had one chocolate dut
uh last month why am I feeling a symptom
it's what's wrong and then someone's
going to say to them on the computer or
somewhere on the Internet or on social
and they're going to say you're detoxing
too heavy you need to stop doing what
you're doing you need to get more fats
you need to get more things you want to
eat in you you're you're you're getting
emotional cuz you can't eat what you
want you feel restricted you need a stop
what you're doing you're detoxing too
much because you're getting sick cuz
you're detoxing too much of back off
back off and then the person goes oh my
God oh my God I'm scared I'm scared what
do I do and they're just like okay okay
just no I'm done with the celery juice
for now screw that medical medium you
know guy I'm done with the celery juice
I'm not going to eat so many leafy green
salads anymore and you're right let me
just order a pizza tomorrow and I am
detoxing too much I need to maybe bring
in 10 avocados or something let me slow
down the
detox but guess what they weren't
detoxing too much and their symptoms
weren't from detoxing their symptoms
were catching up because the bugs in
them and the problems in them were
overriding what they were doing what
they were doing was still not enough and
it wasn't enough to stop the trajectory
to change the trajectory of what they
where they were going to be they were on
a course of getting sick someday they
were on that roller coaster ride of
getting sick someday they were on the
train heading to the tunnel and on the
other side of that tunnel they were
going to be sick and that 8 ounces of
celery juice was keeping them stable
enough but guess what they got a little
too much exposure a few too many bugs
and they were on the way of getting sick
no matter what no matter what they were
getting sick and they were heading into
that tunnel on that
train and then somebody with a whole
detox BS from the Hy genic movement that
never knew why anyone was sick to begin
with and on no disrespect there's some
cool stuff in there like stay away from
this and that and you know in life and
stay out of the smog and make sure
you're getting clean water and clean air
and make sure you're meditating there's
nothing wrong with anything like that
but they didn't know why anybody was
sick and so then here you are with this
detox information and you end up saying
to someone you're detoxing too much stop
stop red flag red flag whatever you're
doing you better
stop and then the person
stops and then they still get sick and
still get sicker and still get sicker
and now their head is screwed up because
they were doing something good for
themselves and they were doing something
that could save them because they were
going to get sick anyway they were going
to get sick
anyway and now it's
blown you're blowing it all Sky High
that's
it what really was going on the person
was getting sicker and you weren't doing
enough you were not doing enough to
Warrant the kind of sickness you had in
your
body it wasn't about detoxing and detox
Pathways or anything like that it was
about damn you were sick and you got a
lot of bugs in you and they're
percolating and you probably got two or
three epscene bars one shingles one CMV
and probably a few other things on top
of that to
boot and HPV and who knows what else and
that's what you got going on and on top
of that you probably had exposures that
triggered you and lowered your immune
system instead of stopping you should be
moving forward even
more maybe you got a pesticide sprayed
on you outside you didn't even know it
they spray them in every Park in every
roadside they spray them everybody's
lawn around apartment buildings maybe
you've had a big drift of pesticides bug
killer and then a week later you're
getting showing signs of sickness and
somebody told you you're detoxing too
fast you better stop and now you really
got screwed because you're not going to
be able to heal
ever meanwhile what you needed to do was
not stop you needed to stay with the
good stuff and you need it
to move forward even more with
conviction to heal with faith and
determination and discipline to
heal and of course check in with your
doctors everybody should have a doctor
everybody should be asking the doctor
how many times have I held up a medical
medum book and said bring it to your
doctor
and that's what millions of people have
done over the last decade they brought
their medical medium books to their
doctors and a lot of doctors were open
to it and helpful and were impressed
with the information and liked what they
were
hearing so on the detox front Mass
confusion some people may be just sick
and some people may be really really
sick
they have old
Pharmaceuticals that have caused
damage they've
had viruses that cause
damage and when damage is done you can
be very very
ill it's not that you're
detoxing and that's why you're very
ill no one gets ill
detoxing nobody just lives their life
and they're fine and they're just
playing sports and they're on boats and
they're having fun in parks and they're
going out drinking on the weekends with
friends and having a great time nobody
gets sick because they're detoxing and
now they're
bedridden they're sick because they're
sick they're sick because they have
things wrong with them they're sick
because they're look it with exposures
and
pathogens not because they're detoxing
they're
sick and guess what guess
what there are nursing homes with people
in their 20s and 30s and 40s laying in
there sick and dying did you know
that there are parents all around the
globe with their daughters and their
sons in infirmaries dying or at home
dying with
nurses with nurses they're not
detoxing people
with all the same symptoms and
conditions out there and they're not
detoxing they're sick they're sick and
they're in
beds there are college kids that can't
finish finish
college because they became bedridden in
their junior year of college they're
sophomore year of college and their
freshman year of college and their home
with their parents thousands of them
thousands globally thousands of them
they can't function anymore they got
brain fog they got severe crippling
anxiety they can't even function in the
world they're home with Mom and
Dad they can't finish school do you know
how many women can't finish school they
can't finish get a college degree
because by their third year they got so
fatigued and fog they can't function and
actually do the
work and they're home with their parents
are they detoxing someone tell me are
they detoxing Janette says in Facebook
my neighbor just had a daughter pass in
in this condition there are thousands
Janette thousands across the globe the
us alone thousands tens of thousands of
young women and men that can't finish
school and college because they're
bedridden at home with Mom and Dad are
they detoxing I'm kind of confused I'm
scratching my head
here so they're
detoxing no they're not detoxic they're
sick and what happens is when we're sick
we need a plan we need a protocol we
need to move forward we need to learn we
need to heal and some as you're doing
that someone's going to go you're
detoxing too much you're you're way too
much and that's why you're sick and all
of a sudden it blurs the line wait a
minute was that person ever sick or were
they detoxing this whole time did they
ever get sick or were they detoxing this
whole
time because the reason why it takes
long for some people to heal is because
they were
injured when someone's liver gets really
toxic you guys and gets all these
different things in there like scar
tissue and tumors and all kinds of
things inside their
liver right
and they got an injured
liver detoxing isn't the thing that
fixes it over night the liver's sick and
it could be sick for a long time while
the person's healing while the person's
doing the right stuff to
heal it's a lot of confusion with
detoxing and it's sad because it's
growing out there I watched it years ago
and I saw what was happening years ago
and it stems from a few individuals now
too in the health movement that built
their business off of detox you hear
that business you hear that they
business
right do I sell a detoxing business no I
don't but there's a few individuals in
the health realm health professionals
that's been selling for years detoxing
businesses get it convincing people that
they're detoxing so they can take all
their alcohol herbal tinctures and such
and forth right they can take all those
things and that's been keeping the whole
detox fear and Chaos alive the detox
curse it's been haunting everybody for
over a hundred
years and that detox curse that thing's
evil because I'll tell you right now
it'll send somebody just out of healing
in in a day in a minute
because we lose faith we get insecure we
lose confidence and all you have to hear
is someone say it's really detox that's
why you're like this and then you forget
why you even got sick you didn't even
know like how did I even get sick was it
detox this whole time it's so
confusing so let's go into this part if
you got sick something
busted you're really
ill something got
broken pathogens tend to do
something pathogens tend to do something
that's what they do
okay so here's a
nerve okay there's another nerve
these are nerves it's another
nerve some nerves down here in the lower
part of your body see these
nerves
nerves all right when the nerves get
damaged by
pathogens they're injured healing
doesn't happen
overnight so when there's a
pathogen in your body and that that
pathogen eats away at a nerve that's why
people get
sick
okay what happens is put some pathogens
on the nerves you see this I'll put them
on the nerves what happens is that you
don't heal
fast maybe you're somebody and you
didn't get that sick yet maybe your
trajectory wasn't going to get that sick
maybe you have a mild upstein bar one
that just caused mono at one point and
then it's been kind of docile causing
other symptoms as you go along and then
you get the thyroid the hypothyroidism
from your mono virus theep seen bar and
you're not really that sick yet and
you're living your life and you're doing
your appointments and you're going
everywhere and you're driving around and
you're picking up your coffee and you're
getting a massage and whatever else
you're doing living your life going to
meditation going here there and you're
not that sick yet but you could be
somebody where those bugs were a lot
stronger more potent more
powerful and your immune system was
triggered enough it was beaten down with
some chemical exposure maybe some far
pharmaceutical exposure knock down your
immune system more very important point
you guys and then the bugs took off a
little bit too much and they damaged the
nerves nerve
damage okay
damage the nerves take time to heal they
may not heal in a month they may not
heal in six months but what happens is
someone can come along and be
like you're detoxing way too much that's
why you're sitting there sick no you're
sitting there
sick because you got nerve damage and
nerve damage takes time to
heal could take
years couple of years three years four
years for some people if they have the
right resources and the right things
that they're doing it could take a few
good years and then they can start
coming back somebody with severe fatigue
somebody with that was diagnosed with
multiple sclerosis somebody that was
diagnosed with ALS somebody that that
just had a lot of different Tinkles
numbness weakness of the limbs somebody
that just had crippling anxiety but the
nerves that get damage need time to heal
and when they start to heal you come
back but if you don't get that
opportunity to come back because
somebody said oh you're detoxing
detoxing stop what you're doing it's
killing you the
detoxing without that good stuff you
were doing God knows where you would be
I've seen this with hundreds of people
over the years God knows where you'd be
if you weren't doing the good stuff
you're doing but it could be blown Sky
High because we can easily poison
somebody with the detox talk I've seen
it happened for years it stems from the
hygienic movement it's been around and
that hygienic movement never knew why
anybody was sick I can tell you right
now going back 20 years ago and I'm not
going to name the
clinics but I've been friends with many
of of the people that have run and
operated clinics throughout the years
healing clinics and they didn't even
know there was anything else but detox
and they had no idea pathogens caused
any illness whatsoever I used to get
into debates all the time with like
literally directors of clinics where
they'd be like Anthony it's really just
toxins we do this you go into the sauna
here and then from the SAA you go into
this and then you go do this we have all
the weat grass here and I'd be like yeah
but there suffering with different
things inside their body like the
pathogens and the hygienic movement with
their detox BS talk has really caused a
lot of problems with people out there
and a lot of times people don't know
what they really even feel like when
they're on stimulants so people are on
so many stimulants out there in general
that when you remove all the stimulants
then you feel what you really feel which
is dragging and fatigued and tired and
that's a whole another level and when
you go to at that point you're going to
think you're detoxing too
much when you get off of stimul
stimulants people they get off their
they get off their adol they get off
their coffee they get off all their
stimulants right and they're they're off
their chocolate they're off the all the
different stimulants next to you know it
they're dragging and the depression
starts to creep up they get off all
their super fatty foods and their
stimulants and all of a sudden their
their depression starts to creep up and
they start feeling like something's
wrong and they're thinking I'm detoxing
no you're not detoxing dude you're not
detoxing you're just you were that sick
you just weren't super sick but you were
sick enough where when you got rid of
your stimulants it showcased it it
exhibited it they feel they felt what
their body really had going on and what
was really going on inside their body
their pathogens and their metals and
their old Pharmaceuticals and things
that were in there that have done damage
to nerves in their body and the
stimulants were Mass asking
it healing takes time when we've been
injured when something has injured our
nervous system our brain stem our
cranial nerves our Vagas nerves our
frenic
nerves when things injure these
things it takes time to
heal and then when somebody throws that
big old world word on everything you're
detoxing it's
detox person just got
screwed no disrespect to anybody or
anything any belief system out there or
anything like
that it's not about that
I'm just trying to give you guys the
history you come into this four years
ago two years ago there's influencers
right now that are shouting out on IG
talking so much crap that just got into
hell two years ago all they knew was cut
the carbs and eat more
protein that's all they knew stop eating
fried greasy food start working out more
and you're 22 years old you can just go
on Instagram and show how good you look
and how good you're doing and you don't
know a thing about what happened in
history and what is even going on and so
when you even utter detox pathway you
have no idea with anything about
it cold Whit spring says but doesn't
eczema and acne often get worse when you
start
detoxing what happens with eczema and
acne is a few things okay it Cycles
people with eczema and acne already
cycle into worse and less
worse ask anybody who has severe
eczema
may there's times where it cycles and
it's debilitating and then they come out
of the cycle okay they're already going
through the natural process of the bugs
moving up in strength lowering down in
strength moving up in strength lowering
down in strength and when it comes down
ex psoriasis you're going to see that
waiver but you're not going to see them
bedridden
may you know what I mean or tick and
spasms getting worse or anything else
happening to that
degree and if someone was pumped up with
steroids for a very long
time that's another thing that's very
difficult on their body's immune system
so it's coming off of all the steroids
and the steroids that are inside the
liver that plays a role with the immune
system because the the steroids hold
back the immune system's initial
reaction of exen psoriasis understand
that that's important to know that means
without the steroids their examen
psoriasis would be that
bad it would be out of control in in in
in the the probably the greatest
sense so it's a combination when you're
talking about ex psoriasis in serious
cases you're talking about the steroid
process combined very difficult because
the steroid the steroid process was
hiding and masking how bad the xamis was
so when people go off the steroids the
eczema is showcasing what it really
should be and that can be blamed on
detox like if you're doing something
good for
yourself but it's a really good question
when it comes down to eimos psoriasis
almost everybody with severe exmos
psoriasis goes on some type of biologic
some type of some type of steroid or so
forth and bend down that road and that's
controlling and masking the ecoman
psoriasis so once you start coming off
of that it just blows up because it was
hiding it was suppressing it right so
that's kind of another a whole another
angle and a lot of people it's cyclical
right with x this even when they're not
on steroids or anything like that it's
ebbing and flowing it's
awful two months later they come out
it's getting Level again who it's awful
two months later they're coming out with
it right so if you do any one thing
you're not even going to know what's
causing it at the time because you're
not going to sure you're not going to
even know where you are cyclical wise
where's the cycle where where are you
even are you a month away from it
getting worse like it usually does or
are you two months from it getting
better it it's that's another thing all
on its own but I I'll go into more
detail about exus rasis and cover
everything so so there's no
confusion Le over there on IG says aw
can you please explain why people with
thyroid adrenal issues struggle to let
go of
fat first of all when we let go of fat
we usually underc calorie
ourselves and Fat's a stimulant too so I
want to give you something little little
talk about this okay if you're on a ton
of avocado and you're on a ton of to and
you're on a ton of olive oil and you're
on a ton of olives and you're on a ton
of meat and you're on you know beef and
you're on a ton of chicken and you're
getting fat from all kinds of chocolate
and so forth and you're on lots of
chocolate and everything um what happens
is it stimulates and it causes your
adrenals to release adrenaline all the
time so you're releasing all this
adrenaline so when you come off of fat
your adrenals start to relax and then
the ad the adrenaline addiction starts
you start to feel the adrenaline
addiction the reason why people are so
so hog heavy into getting addicted to
fats to such a degree where they're
eating so much fat and everything they
have to have fat in their food they have
to have cheese they have to have all
kinds of things that are like fatty no
one wants eat a green salad that doesn't
have cheese or cheese you know squares
in it or you know something tuna in
there egg cheese right because they're
getting all that fat it's all this fat
because what that does is it stimulates
the adrenals and it makes them feel good
because they're high on adrenaline
because the adrenaline has to it has to
thin out the blood so the fats don't
cause a problem with your brain so it
has to thin out the
blood so once you come off all that fat
you're going to feel tired you're going
to feel where you used to be kind where
you sorry you're going to feel where you
should feel because that's really what
you feel like so the minute you come off
a stimulant like high fat which is
stimulant you end up feeling whoa this
is what I felt like it's a different
feeling same thing when you come off of
coffee and then you're now coffee free
you're like whoa this is what I used to
feel like or or without coffee same
thing you come off of like chocolate and
so
forth me over there on YouTube says what
about debilitating reactions to Healing
Foods
aw mean like food sensitivities and so
forth um what happens is that that's a
whole another thing I'll do a show on
that because I I want to do that
Justice I read the question because I
want to make sure I do a show on that
that's really cool because that goes
into food sensitivities and chemical
sensitivities and we need to show on all
of that
combined so back to
detoxing we have to be cautious to how
we see detoxing and understand it I'm
hoping this information that I gave you
today gives you a little bit of a window
into where it derived from why it's
still here why It's haunting
people one thing detox does is it gives
the practitioner a way
out it gives the health coach and
practitioner a way out you're not doing
better I have you on charcoal and
bentonite clay and pearl powder I have
you on sodium bicarbonate I have you on
dious Earth particles I have you on
alkaline ionizer water from kangaroo I
got you on all this stuff and you're not
feeling better um I'm a failure as a
practitioner as a health coach as a
doctor you're detoxing that's what it is
you're detoxing I read something about
it you're
detoxing it's also the way out I've
watched it be the way out for all the
lime doctors for many years I watched it
be the lot way out well no wait you're
just detoxing die off you're just just
detoxing in general that's why you're
getting worse and worse it's not
the doxy that I've been pumping in
you oh I just put whoa 10,000 milligrams
of doxy in you every single day for six
months oops it's not that that did it no
you're detoxing it's been the way out
it's this it's just it's been
weaponized so there's hundred and
hundreds and hundreds of health coaches
now thousands of them just spawning out
everywhere just boom and there's all
these people and they get people in
there and they're just like I don't know
what's wrong with these people I'm just
kind of going by the keto diet or going
by this and whatnot I'm trying to health
coach them and then you see them getting
sick and the person who's a client paid
money so they paid whatever they paid
$150 to $300 $500 and they paid this
money to talk to the health coach and a
health coach is like I think you're
detoxing that's what it is so so we got
to kind of like figure this out cuz
you're detox detoxing has been the way
out for also the practitioner now and
for the person who's a health coach it's
another reason why it's exploding out
there because people don't know why
somebody's sick they just don't have a
clue right all these people they're all
sick out there they go to the doctors
they're not happy with what their
doctors are telling them um and then
they go and they look for health coaches
and they're going to do that and they go
take they go to courses and they're
buying all these courses they're like
I'm sick I need to get better and then
they get like a moment with the guru of
the course or Guru of the coach or
whatever it is and the coach is like um
you're detoxing too
much that's another reason why it's
exploding Katrina says I confirm I had
severe psoriasis it comes in waves with
waves worse and better but in general it
became much better
on it became much better on my head
especially almost everything gone
Amazing do an
mm I think this is a big point right
here that people don't know too is H
there's another one you guys um ivy
flower says on IG can we get the
shakes when neurotoxins have the body
leave the body I shake and my teeth
chatter sometimes on the
hmds but then I feel so much better what
happens is when people's nervous systems
weaken and they're
struggling
okay anything that takes
digestion anything that takes
digestion could actually triggle trigger
mild symptoms keep this in
mind anything that triggers I'm going to
get a better white
board so everything that
triggers so can happen so say you got
some nerves right so we're going to do a
nice vegus nerve
here now there's two Vegas nerves that
come out of the
cranial the brain
stem okay we'll do some frenic nerves
again let's do some frenic
nerves I'm such an
artist all right
do some other nerves
here okay all right when we have a lot
of neurotoxins Right medical mem
information viruses that create
neurotoxins and neurotoxins are swimming
around in our body they're already
putting a damper on the nervous system
so the neurotoxins are already beating
down the nervous system okay so your
neur neurotoxins right this is
neurotoxins coming down on the nerves
right these neurotoxins already hamper
hamper the nerves the vag nerves the
frenic nerves already hamper them so any
time you
eat you're going to feel it not every
time but most of the time depending on
what time of day you're going to have
low spots with your nervous system at
different times of the day this is why
adrenal snacks and medical medium does
not do intermittent fasting this is why
medical medium information does not
withhold food from people this is why
it's not restrictive because you need to
get enough calories in and you need to
get enough snacks and stuff throughout
the day because you want to keep the the
the playing field level you want to keep
the homeostasis you guys and that
homeostasis protects you so you have
less ups and downs with a nervous system
that's already
hampered but you
eat anything depends on what time of day
it can play a role on the nervous
system because the nervous systems
already weak and
hampered takes time to
heal but if someone said well you're
detoxing better stop the hmd better stop
the heavy metal detox you're
detoxing and you get scared you stop the
hmd you stop your celery juice you stop
whatever medical mem tools there's
dozens and dozens dozens of them and you
stop them and now you're like what what
do I do
now anyway guys this concludes the first
round of detox talk we are going to do
it again sometime but I think I'm going
to talk a little bit more if you got
another
minute let's talk about new
exposures so your
gut your gut can be filled with a lot of
different stuff it can be filled with
old rancid fat that's sitting inside the
gut Linings it can be cut with
undigested protein sitting in the gut
Linings and it's all building up in
there right our guts can get toxic it
can get filled with chemicals and all
kinds of metals and everything else in
there and all this kind of
stuff okay and we can still not be
sick we can have a gut full of garbage
there are guys walking out there and
they got a gut out to here and it's hard
as a rock and you can you can literally
punch it like boom boom boom and it's
not going to actually even budge and you
can punch it and that gut's going to
just sit there like a big like rubber
ball inside the guy's gut right and the
guy's like fine he's like I go to work
every day there's nothing wrong with me
yeah the doctor says I need to lower my
cholesterol the doctor says he's worried
about my A1C he doesn't want me to get
type two diabetes but overall I'm doing
pretty pretty good I feel good and the
guy's gut is filled with [ __ ] tons of
[ __ ] and garbage
right somebody else doesn't has very
little of that in here they're eating
clean they're doing good a lot but it
also depends on exposures but if that
guy that has that hard gut that's filled
with all that garbage in there gets a
real
exposure picks up a bug something
happens could go down and it all comes
crumbling down and people who are also
taking care of themselves can also get
new exposures too that keep them down
why they're trying to heal we got to
override we got to ride those
out where do you work did they spray
something you're exposed to where do you
live did they spray something you're
exposed to it's just it's
endless there's lots of exposures
everywhere new relationships public
bathrooms everything restaurants I've
been saying this for years it's probably
the biggest bug spreading Place possible
is restaurants and hospitals right
hospitals it's it's already you know we
already know that you some but you know
you need to go to a hospital you go to a
hospital right but there's so much
exposure there too right but there's so
much exposure in
restaurants all the
same those that's a big place that's the
big big exposures they don't wash all
the stuff off all the dishes right all
the glasses and the forks I talked about
this in the brains saer book and the
chefs cut themselves continually and
then put rubber gloves on and they put
gloves on nit trial gloves on but they
got blood on everything even on the
outside of the glove because they're cut
and they're just getting it everywhere
and they put the glove on and now
they're making your food it's one of the
biggest exposure places there
is people making food they need to be
really careful even when they're home
making food for people that's how much
exposure happens out
there anyway you guys um I'm going to
let you go this was fun but we're going
to cover detox again because it really
needs like a 4H
hour
talk and these are just one you know
this is just one section of it some
things to
consider okay and uh and some things to
avoid by the
way you know some things you can't avoid
as well so some things we can avoid
which is public to toilets when we're
out we can't avoid all kinds of stuff it
just happens we get exposure that's okay
we can do things to take care of it and
move forward and
heal but either way look out for the
detox fear and Chaos it's pared by
influencer by influencer
influencer and it stems from places like
I talked about earlier all
right love you guys one day at a time