I'm back in my kitchen right here what's
in my hand do you guys have yours the
customized airan bottle right there the
heavy metal detox all inscripted in
there like that medical medium heavy
metal detox this is sitting at airwan
right now if you guys are interested in
a quick grab and go they're made fresh
every day I am back back from the
Afterparty what did you guys think about
that I'm making a healing broth right
now I'm going to read some notes as well
I'll just bring this over I'm going to
read some notes out of here which I'm
excited about
too anyway um I just want to give you a
couple different things to know one is
the pictures you know the photographs
with me at the meet and greet at aan
we're going to be putting those out
pretty soon just give us a little time
but we're my team's working on it right
now and which is really be cool once we
have them up which is really cool you
can download them like a free download
you don't have to pay for it or anything
like that which is incredible really my
team is is working hard on making them
available so I want everybody to know
and like I said you can just a free
download to get your photograph Prof it
was professionally done an incredible
photographer so it it's awesome all on
its own and we're going to send out
announcement when they're just about
ready like so look out get on the
medical medium newsletter list so you're
there so you can get the announcement
receive the newsletter that tells us
that the pictures are ready that the
pictures are ready how incredible all
right so please share your experiences
too um in the comments I'd love to know
like how you felt what happened I did
several light blasts I mean more than
several I think I did like 10 right 10
like three at a clip or four at a clip
what's going to happen here is it's
going to be long gated so the effects
from the light blast are not only going
to happen right there and then for a lot
of people but they're also going to Fan
out in your life because we did so many
of them they're going to fan out and
you're actually going to have
experiences because of those light
blasts so what was your experience how
was it how did it feel like how how does
it feel now are you back are you back
from Calabasas California where the aan
um event was the meet and greet and then
the Afterparty um down the road how
incredible was all that it was really
fun I have to say um and you know would
love to talk to you guys I'm here to
answer some questions as well and I'm
making a healing broth I love to make
healing broth after intense light blasts
like that so I love the healing broth
it's a perfect time to actually make it
hey what's going on I see you guys
coming on there which is wonderful do
you have your customized bottle did you
get it that's the medical medium heavy
metal detox bottle the aroan customized
it's in all 10 of their stores this is
it in my hand right here I didn't run it
through the dishwasher I just rinsed it
out so I wouldn't run it through the
dishwasher if it's a colle collectible
and customized bottle you can put on the
Shelf I'm doing that I have a few of
them I brought back a few of them so I'm
really excited about that so that's
right there so anyway if you don't have
one of these I mean there could be a few
of them left at one of the stores or you
know at a few the different uh airwan
stores so if you're in the area in in
California there in the LA area grab one
before they're gone cuz once the
customized bottles are gone they're
putting the heavy metal medical medium
heavy metal uh detox smoothie in a
normal aoan bottle with the tag though
with the still the cool tag but it won't
be like this so grab one if you can I
just wanted to show you guys
that please share your experiences on
how you felt with the light blast I
always want to know it's important to me
because every time we do something like
this uh spirit of compassion will turn
up the heat and bring that light blast
down and profound experiences happen not
only just there but days after so look
forward even weeks after and we're only
one week after that Awan you know event
and after party we're only one week away
I can't even believe it and I'm here I'm
back at home I'm not in California
anymore I'm back at home
Christina budman says this was the most
profound experience I've ever had it
changed me forever thank you Anthony and
S so forever grateful look that I I feel
it I can't
believe how beautiful this whole event
went it was just shocking astounding
Shen 777 over there on YouTube Hey W I
felt like I was walking on clouds and no
worries in the world felt peaceful and
Bliss out if
nowhere whoo after the light blast so
you felt Bliss out after the light blast
it was just such a beautiful experience
seriously Katherine Elizabeth very
powerful my hands were so heavy felt
moving in my spine and tugging on the
right side of my head the light blasts
are really profound and they're very
potent and the thing is when they come
down on the top of the crown of the head
and they rush through the body and
they're hitting all kinds of organs and
cells and they're hitting even the soul
because our soul is here so they're
hitting our soul they're hitting our our
our physical brain the light blast is
hitting every org every cell it's
hitting our immune system it's hitting
everything and it's dropping down
through the body it it really is a
powerful experience and a really
incredible experience um truly I mean
just remarkable everything was I'm
making a healing broth I'm going to
answer some questions to Beth Paige over
there on YouTube you made us feel like a
million dollars I tear it up on the
plane thinking about the way you
expressed yourself to us we'll never
forget it seriously I mean if you if you
want to get me choked up you're going to
get me choked up I better start cutting
an onion cuz I have onions here I better
start cutting an onions so I can mask it
how about that which I might actually do
SE hey what's happening I'm functioning
on a new level after all that light whoa
that is so nice so amazing Sally hi aw
thank you for sharing the calabases day
with all of us which you know I have to
tell you which is incredible is I
brought on a lot of people to make that
happen with the live stream wow like uh
what I mean seriously if you were not
able to make it if you weren't able to
make it you could watch the live stream
and we we put we've made it happen if
you weren't able to make it there live
but you were with us watching the live
stream of the event that was you know
what was that experience for you so
that's one thing I wanted to ask you
guys like what was the experience you
had watching the live stream in the
moment live with us getting the light
blast sharing your comments if you can
so what was your experience please share
in your in the comments if you can so
you're watching it from you know the
live stream from away from your home you
weren't in Calabasas with us you weren't
you know at the after party but you were
watching it live in the moment what was
your experience just please comment if
you can I would love to know I really
would
would and you know what we did to make
that live stream happen uh my team
worked really hard we brought in a lot
of people and that were experts at live
streaming equipment and all of it and
you know the cameras for live streaming
and they brought all that in and they
made it happen they made it happen short
notice which was you know crazy all on
its own and then the Heatwave the
Armageddon end of the world Heatwave
that came through there that alone was
unbelievable so we had we had so many
different things we had the ice packs
and we had the umbrella stands and all
of that for anybody that was waiting in
a line at the meet and greet so many
things to think about my team worked
really hard we brought in a lot of
people we worked all hard together to
make it happen it was a very special
time very special time I'm thinking
about it every day right now and um and
it's just that yeah it's in my
Consciousness subconsciousness it's in
my soul what happened and how I just
felt around everybody you know at the
meet and greet and you know and shaking
your hand getting a picture with you
which I can't wait for them to come out
I know we're it's coming soon so be on
the newsletter so you you know when the
pictures are being released with
everybody but to have a picture with you
guys and to shake your hand and talk
with you for a second I seriously say
I'm just BL away Tina abib says over
there on YouTube hi Anthony I'm working
hard to heal so I can go to the next
event yeah that's what I love to hear
seriously Beth Paige Brown over there on
YouTube I feel calm and clear no drama
inside whoa that is everything it is it
is car over there says on YouTube thank
you so much for streaming you're welcome
I I mean we made it happen it was tricky
we were on a time you know constraint we
were you know going against the clock we
were going against you know all kinds of
adversity we were going
against like all kinds of different
things the Heatwave we were we were
looking for you know the right people we
were I mean scrambling and scrambling to
make this happened I want it to be a
beautiful experience and the food tell
me about the food did you guys like the
food at the
Afterparty I was really hoping you guys
really love the food at the Afterparty
so that's one thing too so leave a
comment on that as well what did you
think about the food at the
Afterparty um I tanked it I tanked it
down so you know um and I you know I
made may have eaten it too fast but I
was hungry a lot was happening we did
the meet and greet I think I was up like
4 in the morning I think I think I want
to sleep like around 1 because of all
the work and the preparation you know
being involved with everything to make
it all happen and then I went to sleep
at 1 I my alarm clock was set for 4: I
got up at 4:00 in the
morning and I didn't even grab anything
to eat I didn't have any fruit or
anything I had just a little bit of
coconut water I think and then boom ran
to
Calabasas ran to Aran right for the meet
and greet got in there just in time I
saw everybody was there and yeah I
remember I remember I was really thirsty
I was I was doing the meet and greet and
I was really thirsty right I didn't even
have a chance to crack into an hmds the
customized bottle right there I didn't
even have a chance to crack into one
and I think somebody on my team was like
Hey W are you are you thirsty I was like
yeah yeah just grab me anything and you
know I got a coconut water and I popped
it was icy cold and I popped open the
top and I was
like just hit so good and then a little
while after that when I had a chance I
downed you know so some hm DS's and then
I was just like yeah like it was in it
was a great great feeling
um yeah so anyway I got to make healing
broth let me start working on that I
want to talk about just anything that I
I
experienced um I hope you guys had a
really good time if you were there and
like I said if you watch the live stream
you know what was your experience what
did you feel put in the comments how was
it those light blasts were
powerful and we were pushing the limit
of the light blast like Spirit of
compassion and I were pushing and my
team were pushing the limits it's like
you know what can we do another let's do
another light blast we can do another so
see can we do another and we just we
just pushed it got that light down for
everybody lifechanging light from above
and if you don't know what the light
blast is you have no idea you just got
on here and like what is he even talking
about since I was a child Spirit of
compassion started talking to me at age
4 and in that process as I was getting a
you know a little older and I was 5
years old four and a half 5 years old
Spirit was telling me about this light
and so I found a baby bird and I would
have Spirit of compassion send light
down onto that baby bird and then I
would find an injured Grasshopper And I
would have Spirit of comp that a car
like bumped into or or ran into or
something when it was hopping I remember
and I um and I saw it kind of like
bopping around on the sidewalk all kind
of injured and I would grab this
grasshopper and then Spirit of
compassion I would say send down the
light Spirit of compassion told me about
this light that Spirit of compassion can
send down so I would hold the
grasshopper in my hand and I would have
Spirit send down the light into the
grasshopper right into my hand and then
Spirit of compassion talked about about
also if Spirit of compass sends the
light into me and then out of my arms
out of my hands so that was another
thing so there's two kind of light blast
that I haven't talked about probably too
much is one is the light blast where
Spirit sends it directly on the crown of
somebody's head and it goes right
through their body right that's one
variety of light blast the other variety
of light blast is going into me and then
out my hands which is more intense for
me and the other one's intense too but
it's it's really intense when it hits me
all the time and I used to do that I
used to do that one on-one with people
back you know in my office throughout
the years when I used to help people
one-on-one before Spirit of compassion
said and everybody begged me to write
the Books and get that information
worldwide and so what would happen is
the light would go through me and out my
hands so I would use it that way and and
as a child I would do that with a
grasshopper in my hand I would do that
with an injured frog and I came across
an injured frog and I would hold the
Frog and have Spirit of compassion send
the light down uh on top of the frog is
what I would do and you know every every
single living you know creature that was
injured that I can find I would send
light down even if I wasn't able to now
hold the creature in my hand remember
there was an injured bunny that was
running around and I couldn't catch it
and I was a child and I couldn't catch
the injured bunny um still too fast but
yet one leg was injured and I would ask
Spirit of compassion to send the light
down and I would do the light blast as a
child so I would yell light light light
light and spirit of compassion would
tell me when the light was coming for
the injured Bunny with the injured leg
so the injured bunny was in a bush and
ran away and was in the bush but injured
and so I stood there and I said okay
let's do this and spirit of compassion
said okay on the count of three I'm
going to send the light down on that
Bunny and you say light you say light
and so that light came down on the bunny
in the bushes and I said light light
light and a day later the bunny's leg
was healed it was back out eating grass
and it wasn't even limping the bunny's
leg was healed and it was the same Bunny
and so it was the bunny that we saw
every morning and it was healed from
that light and that is the power of the
light blast that's I've used it my whole
life and so it was just really really a
beautiful thing to be able to do that
with everybody there at this Afterparty
such an experience for me to be able to
give that to everyone that makes me so
happy I can even do that it TR truly
does Maddie says over there in YouTube
this was lifechanging I feel as though
I've been standing taller this past week
you probably are standing taller in so
many ways including your soul is
standing taller thank you so much what a
gift thank you for being there seriously
over there on YouTube no one to you um I
felt so happy like profoundly happy the
next day after some solid years of
depression or load low mood that gave me
the push to keep going with your
information and just out from a healing
crisis whoa thank you thank you for
being there thank you for actually you
know receiving that light and anything
else and good food all of that over
there in IG the light blast was insanely
strong felt so so so much love and light
throughout my body awesome warm
Sensations and the thing is when you
feel that there in that moment you're
going to feel different Sensations as
you go along too so it's something that
keeps on going for a while and what I
did at this event at this Afterparty is
we did more than more than normal amount
of light blasts I was like okay I could
do this I could do this Spirit of
compassion said yes it's time we can do
this
and so we we we did more and so you're
going to feel like this long gated
effect like you could just be like a
week or two later even a month later
even two months later it's going to give
you like a bump up in different aspects
emotional spiritual physical it's going
to give you a bump up on all of that IGN
ignition ignition on spiritual ignition
on emotional ignition on physical like
ignition on these ignition on mental and
emotional and physical and spiritual and
that's the that's kind of like one of
its profound effects is ignition like
igniting what you have in you too and
special special you know qualities about
you and profound pieces of you and all
that from experiences you've had and
references you had and your soul
experiences from past lives all that
stuff all packed in one the light is
there to enhance and
ignite and and clear that's a whole
another thing too it's there to clear as
well so that light is there to
clear just it's just so much to talk
about Kindred solution says over there
in IG the the last Light blast had me
crying tears of joy and I felt so at
peace light and clear whoa you know what
blows me away you were there that's what
blows me away that you were there okay
that blows me away all right that I'm
communicating with you right now I'm
truly honored I can't even believe it I
feel a sense that family feeling that
sense of you know like connection you
were
there just blows me
away I was
there purely Katherine says on IG it was
a profound experience that I will never
forget I couldn't stop smiling all
weekend that is precious and Priceless
to smile and keep smiling like that that
means a lot truly Luke over there on IG
the following day I felt absolute Bliss
and freedom and live and connecting for
several hours thank you thank you thank
you can't believe Luke you were there
blows my
mind seriously blows my mind it means
the
world I mean
seriously I'm going to C up some garlic
right here we're making a healing broth
we'll still talk about the light blast a
little
bit so all through the years profound
experiences with the light blast
profound experiences all through the
years and um not just not just um I
mean
where
overnight people's bodies just changed
overnight and I have a deep respect for
Spirit of compassion and as much as I
say you you know I joke around a lot and
I I joke around a lot about being a free
spirit and um and kind of a rebel like
rebelling against Spirit when I was
younger okay and I talk about that a lot
I have um like for instance playing loud
things and loud music and stuff like
that so I don't have to hear spirit in
my right ear which takes me to another
thing I want to I want to talk about
this you'll notice and I I can't believe
it showed like it did cuz I wasn't
thinking it would and then I I I heard
somebody talking about it where when I
was doing the meet and greet and uh
people were wanted to tell me something
and they want to ask me something right
and I was there standing there I would
use my left ear to hear them so I would
use my left ear to hear the person so it
was like you know
like so great to meet you and and well
aw want to tell you something and I
would actually lean in with my left ear
because with that many people around and
everything that was going on Spirit of
compassion talks to me in my right ear
so even though I hear Spirit of
compassion in my left ear it's not like
the right ear the right ear is the
strongest point it's where I hear spirit
and it comes
through the words come through right
Spirit comes through and so when I when
I would talk to somebody somebody I
would have to lean I would try with my
right ear sometimes be like it's not
going to work there's too many people
here Spirit of compassion is talking to
me about what's happening in people
what's happening people around me people
in back of me information coming through
in that moment not sure who's who where
it's coming from each person conspir
compassions just talking so much so and
you guys know if you've listened if
you've um if you listen to the audio
books medical medium audio a audio books
or you read them so I would sit there
and have to listen with my left ear and
you see it because I watched a little
bit of the replay you know watched a
little bit of the live stream too and I
watched it I was like
oh there it is you know I'm leaning in
with my left ear I switched doing that
so I can hear the person focus on what
the person you guys were telling me so
that it wasn't getting in the way with
Spirit of compassion's information
coming to my right
ear so that was happening too
David witchin said I on YouTube I
watched the live stream for 11
hours wow Elena felt like the best day
in my life I felt loved welcomed I felt
light I felt like a part of my family it
was beautiful
magical you know I I
um yep I felt like a part of family it
was beautiful and magical that means a
lot to me right there that's why I just
wanted to read that again and it was
it's very special to me just chopping up
some garlic it's going in the healing
broth that's what I'm making right
now Jenny Jen over there on YouTube I'm
so grateful for the live stream light
blast wow what was your experience with
the live stream light
blast I've heard from people that I know
they had profound experiences with
that I'm just throwing a little bit more
garlic in here
Shen 777 over there on YouTube I was
online during the light blast and felt
super emotional and was crying because I
felt so much unconditional love and
healing power Felt So Divine thank you
so much aw and so thank you for watching
thank you for being
there throw some garlic in here I'm just
kind of peeling back the cloves a little
bit get what I call like the clove
papers when of course you're walk
welcome to put those in I don't in case
a guest is having some of the healing
broth and they're trying to pull a
garlic
paper out of their mouth right over
there in IG I went to my workout session
in yoga and I didn't have any sore or
tight muscles as I usually have nothing
is sore love it light blast thank you
then that's what I was talking about
right there like the power and the
leftover power that the light Blast has
and how it's something that it's
like it's this NeverEnding kind of like
contribution to your health it's like
each day goes by it's still there and
it's still doing little things and it's
helping the immune system and it's
helping it's helping like purify the
liver and it's helping the brain it's
helping to to loosen things that
shouldn't be in there it's helping to
you know like rewire it's helping to you
know get shed negative energy negative
energy negative you know like entities
that torment people out
there yeah I
mean people really struggle out there
with so much psychic attack the one
thing I love about the light blast is it
it
obliterates it destroys psychic attack
connections right so if you have this
this this string of energy coming from
somebody who psychically attacking you
if you have this um
this
basically this wire of negativity going
to you coming from somebody so see
somebody and even if it went to you when
it's not supposed to like there's
somebody out there hating out there
there's somebody out there that's
throwing out just just static and static
out there and you happen to be walking
by or you're in in the the wrong place
whatever at the wrong time and that
static connects to you now you're
getting psychically attacked right or
you're getting psychically attacked by
somebody somebody somebody out there the
light blast
annihilates that psychic attack
connection so everybody in there and I
should have talked about it more but you
know I was just hanging in there trying
to get those light blasts out there but
so if anybody came came into there to
that
Afterparty and they had a psychic attack
going on that day or there was a
continual on andof Psychic attack from
somebody or something from from far
away anything like that somebody in
their life maybe an old relationship
whatever it is and there's a psychic
attack going on spread of compassion
sends it light down it obliterates that
psychic attack connection boom just cuts
what people would say the cords right
slices that
string or that Essence that's connecting
it that's keeping that static connected
on somebody that's keeping them like
that so they can be mental so they can
be super emotional so they can be
doubting themselves so they can be in a
in a like a funk so they can be in a
spell spirit of compassion sends a light
light down to break that boom to shatter
that away whatever that is and to clean
that up to make sure you're clear and
you're free from Psychic attack and
that's what s so does frees people from
Psychic attack that alone is
just so important so let's get some more
garlic in
here here we
go ah the fresh smell of garlic just
garlic in a pot of water what a
beautiful smell Sophie over there on
YouTube hey Sophie it really was one of
the best days of my life thank you so
much for the effort resources and all
the energy you and your team put into
this day I feel transformed after this
day I just want to say thank you truly
thank you for being there seriously it
it warms my heart that you made it there
Sophie also says on YouTube there my
nervous system feels so much more
relaxed and stronger and my heart and
soul feel so light and bright thank you
thank you thank you aw and sfc I will
share the light forever that's
incredible I'm honored thank you for
being there seriously and you brought
your light there and that's what I
wanted to say like was was everybody
talking to other people there did you
meet people that you didn't think you
would meet did you see people there that
you didn't think you would actually
connect with and you connected were you
talking to others did you make that you
know connection with others what
happened there I wanted to ask those
questions to see if you guys had any of
those experiences
because you know that's the one thing
about the medical medum community it's
people that have you know their seasoned
they're just salt of the earth like I
said and I said that I don't use that
term lightly I never did and the people
there were that salt of the earth truly
and you know that that that really
people that like resonate to other
people with experiences and what they've
been through and all of it and they
communicate Sandra over there in IG I am
still walking on clouds after all the
experiences last
Saturday
wow so I got two kinds of garlic here
got like a purple garlic right and then
and the other variety well there's you
know that they sell in stores this isn't
for my garden right here but still
incredible
garlic
um see one
mom Hannah says over there you and your
team thought of everything from food to
ice packs to bathrooms extremely
thoughtful thank you you know that's the
thing right there right it's we want
everybody to have what they need so at
this meet and greet it's not about just
it's not just about like oh everybody
will figure something out you know like
like that's what people in the world
believe it's like no you you need to
make sure people have what they need so
the right kind of bathrooms out there
really important and I talked about that
before four but really nice bathrooms
like that's important the other thing is
the ice packs you know just having that
ice pack in your hand changes your core
temperature in your body just in your
hand you guys and when you're up against
a heat wve all you have to do is just
hold that that cold ice pack for just
even five minutes and you what happens
is you got your main arteries that go
right boom down to your hand they go
down your arm right to your hand and so
that main artery that runs right down
here okay you got your ice pack just on
there like right in your hand like that
it it's all that blood that's coming
down your main artery is picking up that
coolness bringing it back up through the
veins right all the way back to your
heart to your brain people are putting
their cold packs on the back of their
neck they're putting them on their face
they're putting them right on their
chest people were putting the cold packs
underneath their hats they were just
doing that and it dropped everybody's
core temperature while waiting out there
for a little bit it it's it's just very
very good good to do it's it was just a
beautiful thing to see everybody getting
those ice packs it was part of like we
got to make sure we you know make people
comfortable I'm going to pop some more
garlic in
here so Max Max uh Max Bond over there
on YouTube yeah it was just so amazing
even watching online thank you for
watching online seriously I also love
seeing how many medical medium people
are out there I'm not alone you are not
alone but see the industries would love
to make you feel like you're alone and
the haters would love to make you feel
like you're alone okay and that was kind
of one of the tricks that happened with
a lot of the hater you know um campaigns
that were occurring over the last couple
years is to make people feel like
they're isolated or alone or something
like that so to put out things like you
know like oh you're an M or something or
you know the game right and it makes
people feel like oh what am I doing
something bad am I doing something wrong
like what am I doing and that's what
haters do they make you feel like you
know that yeah that you're isolated that
you're the only one following medical
medium that you're the only one that
does medical medium information you know
there are millions of people that do
medical medium information around the
world in every single country around the
world doing medical medum
information and you're not
alone you know you're not and there are
people that want the heavy metal detox
smoothie in airwan they want it
everywhere and they're in all 10 stores
right now because you're not the only
one the thousands upon thousands of
people just in La alone hundreds of
thousands that use medical mum
information in LA area alone that want
this you know in the bottle so they can
buy it right away made fresh every day
you're not alone and but that's how it
works it's like
I think the haters Industries the system
just want you to feel isolated or
something alone but you're not it's a
massive Community massive community in
you know all of the United States and
all around the world and all in the
different countries so yeah Tik Tok just
restricted uh my feed for the next 10
minutes I must be talking about
something all right let's get an onion
in here
the wind must have blew somewhere in a
different
direction all right so I'm going to pop
an onion into this heing
broth so what happened with the light
blast so when I was a child my parents
would um have me in the back seat of the
car we'd be going somewhere we'd be at a
red light Spirit of compassion would
give me a lesson
a lesson as to what was going on in
somebody's body emotionally physically
in the next car so it would be at the
red light I'd be in the back seat Spirit
of compassion would say what was going
on with somebody in the car what kind of
health problem were they faced with what
kind of struggle were they faced with so
as I was in the car 10 years old 8 years
old I mean happened all the time over
and over again
uh I would ask Spirit of compassion can
we send a light blast on top of that car
so then it was the light blast kind of
like hitting cars with light so I would
be 10 years old backseat of my parents'
car and I would be like you know Spirit
send light down on that car that you
said someone was struggling so we'd be
at the red light and SS would send it
down right on top of the car roof of the
car right through the car into the
crowns of their heads and running right
through them and after a spirit of
compassion told me that this person's
struggling with a kidney problem this
person's struggling with a heart problem
this person's struggling with diabetes
this person's struggling with you know
some other issue like a liver problem
pancreas problem emotional
struggle
so the light blast became a huge part of
my ever existence and
life I used it wherever I
could I asked Spirit of compassion to
send down the
light thousands of
times thousands of times and I wonder
who did it affect who did it help I
didn't know the people that were in the
car next to me where are they now what
happened did it help them through their
life at that point
H brand says over there on YouTube the
card you gave me said you deserve to be
happy after the light blast I felt the
happiest I have ever felt now I'm
actually going to okay I'm chopping an
onion now thank God a very a very rare
occurrence you
said okay for some reason that got me
over there in
IG
um Heidi says I'm only sad I missed you
playing guitar the Almond Brothers and
Neo are favorites for me don't be
sad my monitor wasn't working I couldn't
hear my guitar one note and I couldn't
hear my voice one note because the sound
text kind of like I think messed
something up and the mic on my guitar
wasn't on so they're because when you're
out there on a stage that big and you
play you can't hear it you can't hear
one note that you're touching when
you're out there everything absorbs it
right and so there was a mic on my
guitar that was off so it wasn't
allowing anyone or or was allowing me
especially to hear what notes I was
playing and if I'm going to sing I do
need to hear the notes cuz I'm not a pro
singer you know but I do need to hear
the notes but didn't and then the other
thing happened was um my monitor was off
so I didn't hear anything I was singing
so it was like just singing to nothing
to air air you couldn't hear it you just
know you were saying the words so I was
trying to sing words didn't hear it at
all through the monitor cuz it wasn't
hooked up and I couldn't hear the guitar
basically I was just standing there like
a naked
baby throwing it all out there later on
when I watched I was like oh my God God
help
me Health with Liz over there and IG you
and the team are incredible it blew my
mind thank you so much will forever hold
it in my
heart thank you for for the live stream
Stephanie says 888 Hey Jude says thank
you so much for the live stream it meant
the world to me I loved every moment
that live stream was phenomenal to have
my
team killed themselves to make sure it
was there because you know I mean
seriously like worked really hard like I
I don't think like people know what
happens behind the
scenes but wow
behind the scenes is like oh my
God how are we going to pull this off
where are we going to get the live
stream equipment who has it in LA wait
they can't do it why right I mean it was
like one one problem needed to be solved
by the second all right let's get some
potatoes in here cuz if you're doing
healing broth I got to get these in
there
now no one to you says over there on
YouTube Just from watching it from home
I've continued to feel so much General
love my family is
amazed going to tell you right
now I am still speechless from this
event lra over there on
YouTube I'm going to put potatoes in
this healing broth right now
okay over there in IG Thrive says I
watched the live stream from Salvador
thank you so much that makes me happy to
know that you're an El Salvador and
you're actually watching from there how
incredible is that seriously get some
potatoes in here over there in IG merca
says merca spiritual says Hey aw I felt
like I was there heart and soul thank
you to you and your team for allowing us
to be there from afar truly incredible
experience I didn't know today I'm going
to read some notes in a little bit that
you guys left me okay I'll just show you
what I have right here I'm just going to
carefully bring this over this is it I
have some notes I don't want to drop
that Jane essential says the event way
exceeded my expectations thank you for
caring so much about
us chopping up some
potatoes you say potato I say potato
let's Call the Whole Thing Off
over here Eva says hi from Norway it was
amazing to watch the live stream loved
every minute that's over there in
IG let's get some more potatoes in
here I was watching and felt a deep
peace and had
goosebumps whoa over there W wish
heal wise healing wise healing on IG
excuse me my eyes are filled with tears
from my onion cutting and also I'm
getting choked up Kindred Solutions over
there the live stream was just as
powerful the light blast had the had me
in tears of joy feeling light and clear
and you singing made me feel so happy
like I was your grandmother listening
proudly and full of
love are you really trying to make me
cry cuz now I might have to take a break
because
that is like
sweet whoa Centura healing says over
there and IG so many people shared that
watching the live stream was the be
being there in person was like being
there in person all right I got lots of
potato in there that was good let me get
some carrots in here you know what I'm
going to peel these carrots you don't
have to peel them I'm going to peel them
though like I said it doesn't matter
with me really but it's you know if
company
has some of the Skilling
broth someone might say did you peel the
carrots I don't like carrot
skins I don't mind though at
all L over there on YouTube says the
light blast is now part of my life
healing and survival amazes me it can
come through the internet
it does come through you watch that live
leandra's Journey says watch the live
stream it was outstanding I felt so
included and like a big part of me was
there now after the light blast it is
like my soul got into my body again and
a weight is lifted off of me so I want
to say that I want to talk about that
for a
second okay I want to talk about that
for a second the thing is with the light
blast is a lot of people are out of body
they're having such hard times in their
life their soul is is is in them a
little bit then out of them then in them
a little bit then out of them it's like
a a protection method to protect our
soul so it doesn't get truly damaged and
injured down here on this planet Earth
of of so much like evil and you know
trust breaking
and I mean think about it I mean we know
planet earth has a lot of evil crap
going on going down I mean we know that
you know that if anybody is in complete
denial of that like they don't think
evil crap is going on around this planet
and stuff like that they're in there
they're in their own little bubble God
bless them that means it obviously maybe
it's not affecting them or hasn't
affected them yet or they just don't
know what is affecting them or not
but man what happens is we get we get
out of body a lot because of so much uh
adversity and so much struggle
and simple little things that could be
simpler little to somebody somebody else
could be a serious thing for you people
can get triggered so easily and they can
their soul can just be popping out of
them left and right because of PTSD P
PTSD for sure um could be happening for
so many so I got some carrots in there
let me get a spoon
okay
okay I will use this
one going to add a little bit more water
to this
too I got some potato in there I got
some carrot in there let's pop in some
shiitake over there Susan blonda says
over there in IG can we still view the
live stream footage you surely can you
can view it right on Rumble YouTube too
right on Rumble though you
can I'm going to pop some shitake
mushrooms in here
definitely got some shrooms
man where's Bryce oh
man I think what we're going to have to
do is have Bryce come out someday and
visit I hope you guys are okay with that
where's Dr yes when you need them Emily
Kinsley over there on IG says so touched
by everything you did for us I felt
movement pushing through my brain during
the light blast and hours after
that's incredible that's
incredible over there your team was
amazing so
um Brin says your team was amazing so
kind and thoughtful all the little
things like cold packs and umbrellas
water towels towelettes and all all for
the mmers
I'm going to put some more shitaki in
here do a little shitake cut Cuts up
here chopped up here what am I saying
what am I saying the mm standard live
stream was absolutely incredible aw
thank you so much for everything light
blasts were out of this world magical
experiences whoa another shaki
here
okay the wild blueberry babe says I love
that you asked us where we wanted the
light to go ask for light to heal my
Soul and Spirit as well as physical
organs grateful and that's a thing so
Spirit of compassion tells me to ask you
guys where do you want the light to go
to where do you want it headed do you
want it going to an organ do you want it
going to um your soul do you want it
going to your
brain your neurons
you want it going to a tumor do you want
it go where do you want the light going
to and very
important that that you know I asked
that question it's very helpful if you
don't answer it or you don't know where
it's going that's okay too it'll find
its way one way or another Janette says
the next day I re reconnect
it with an old friend that we had a
falling out I believe the light blast
freed up our resentment towards each
other over there on Facebook whoa I'm
going to pop some ginger in here you
don't have to peel the Skins I'm just
peeling them
back cuz you don't have to you can throw
it straight in with the skin on and get
that Tan in off the skin that's okay
popping some off the
ryone popping some ginger in
there Lisa over there on YouTube after
first online light blast I managed
finally break up with my boyfriend
wow managed to finally break up with my
boyfriend I was in a very bad
relationship and I could not get out of
it until the light
blast who that's that's powerful
powerful I got some turmeric right
here another funny little ryome right
here I'm just going to peel this back a
little
bit you don't have to peel the Skins
back on the r on the um on these Ry
zomes
right okay there we go now I'm going to
kind
of cut some nice pieces off of here it's
going in here tumer it
is right in there all right I'm going to
throw some tomatoes in here too I'm also
going to add some
water I'm going to get a bowl of water
Alexandra says the food at the
Afterparty was so delicious thank you so
much aw it was
incredible I was in the back like for
getting on the stage and I was just like
doing this you know like I had a plate
um and I was just like oh my God like
this is so good I was hungry that that
was kind of like what I was saying
earlier too where I was saying
how you guys on IG don't worry I'll be
back tick Tok I'll be back I'm just
grabbing a little bit more water right
now if you guys don't mind
for my healing
broth it's been actually boiling for so
long that it kind of It kind of like
evaporated pretty much there we
go it was getting
concentrated Angels 444 bless says on IG
I had a headache for a few days prior to
the light blast and it was
gone the light blast knocks headaches
out I've seen it knock out headaches
I've used it to knock out headaches for
people I used it oneon-one for people
when I was in office many many years ago
and I used it to knock out
headaches oh let's get a tomato in there
you say tomato I say tomato I am cutting
this tomato right now okay I'm even
going to put the Tomato tops in there of
course there we go
Roger says um rajie says over there on
YouTube the event was literally the best
day of my life I was so happy and felt
surrounded by so much light I truly felt
like a part of your family and could
feel the love and compassion you had for
us I need a good
cry and pretty much I'm like on the edge
right here over there in
IG
amberlin amberlin
Stone Amber says it's hard to adjust
back to the world after so much light
and a piece of heaven at the event it
was like how it's supposed to be there
you know I I I'm touched by that by the
way and I have to tell you that um you
know after after leaving the event and
kind of going back into the world a
little bit the normal everyday stuff it
was like my car turned into a pumpkin
you know is that what it is the carriage
turns back into the pumpkin correct me
if I'm wrong on that I I don't don't
quote me on how that
works you know
like then it's like work back to work
work
work Good Vibes good energy many people
want to know if you Anthony will meet
people again and do this kind of event
again for all of us that could not come
this time I will I will do yes something
again for sure okay I will I will I
don't know exactly when and what day but
I will do
something Marissa spiritual says I
started tearing up watching the live
stream when I saw the umbrellas being
put up so thoughtful and considerate you
know what's what's funny is when we were
asking for those umbrellas when we were
like find somebody now to get these
umbrellas here like find somebody
someone we have to get this stuff you
know what we heard well at events every
place was like well at events um they
don't offer umbrellas for people at
events doesn't matter how hot or rainy
it is or whatever it is they just let
people stand out there including like
you know like rock concerts and
musicians and all that stuff that do
like you know any kind of event stuff in
the world and people come and crowds
come it's like there's no no such thing
and I said doesn't matter I don't care
what other people do I don't care what
other people do
we need to get umbrellas here I don't
care and that's what happened my team
was like fighting for it man they're
fighting for it they're like umbrellas
now get umbrellas and it didn't matter
what every time we stumbled across a
place that might have had umbrellas
they're like that's nonsense you don't
put umbrellas out for people that are
waiting for this or waiting for that
we're like we don't
care like what we went through Fox L
Meadow says over there on YouTube we
watch watch live stream we were amazed
how you thought of everything for
everyone what an amazing caring loving
and thoughtful Hostess you
are I'll do a curtsy too um truly thank
you seriously you are a blessing you are
a blessing Reverend Dr Lee over there on
YouTube it is possible a w that I felt
the power of light blast while watching
your stream question mark yes you did
it's very possible participated in three
of them and I felt the difference in my
symptoms incredible thank you thank you
rev rev doctor Dr Lee thank you for
being
here pop it in some more tomato and then
we're good I'm going to put some parsley
in there too as well okay here we are
all right
nice I can't wait for this healing broth
right here I love doing the healing
broth after a light blast you know even
though it's been a little while it
doesn't matter it's still in us we still
feel it it's there ooh a shiitake
mushroom all by itself let me just give
you a couple little chops and throw you
in the
pot Wonder Woman over there on YouTube
says the medical medium Community is
growing and becoming stronger thanks DW
or thanks aw you know what's you know
what's crazy is I know it's getting
stronger and stronger I know the medical
medium Community is getting stronger I
know people are healing every day using
the medical meme information but I know
there's something else like over the
years the medical meme Community has
been here and it's been
strong but right and people healing and
using the information and having
life-changing results people getting out
of wheelchairs people healing their
Parkinson's disease people healing right
all ALS people healing all kinds of
Strokes people healing and moving
forward and the medical medium
information helping them and giving
their life back from neurological
fatigue neurological it's a medical
medium um term right and getting their
lives back but now something has even
shifted just in the last few years now
where the medical medum community is
getting like stronger and stronger
spiritually and
emotionally it's just getting stronger
in all these other ways like a family
like a big family like the mm Community
is just growing and getting stronger
it's just blows me
away I'm going to chop up some parsley
in which I'm doing here now sorry about
the noise for anybody doesn't like a
little bit of the the noise there I just
want to chop it up pretty good educating
myself good to see you you're there on
YouTube seems all the haters are getting
named and shamed Winds of Change seem
optimistic you know the song baby you
ain't Ain't Seen Nothing
Yet here's something that you're never
going to
forget baby ain't seen nothing
yet you ain't been
around you know that
song set the record
straight sat around
for what is it four years five years
thinking that look
just you
know you know things will work out and
then I was like no got to set the record
straight Tamara it had a deep effect on
me to see the wonderful food being
served to everyone Tamara I seriously it
was so beautiful to see that food and to
see everybody getting what they needed
and after just like you know a long day
and the Afterparty was phenomenal I mean
mean I just was like well this is more
than I can ever ask for to try you know
because we were like short notice we're
trying to make this thing happen we're
like you know kind of like obstacles
were being thrown at us left and right
like haa you think you can do this you
think you can pull off this meet and
greet okay let's throw in you know let's
throw in this obstacle you think you can
pull this off aw let's get a flat tire
okay like you think you can get there
and do this aw let we can't get
umbrellas we've checked every spot in La
cuz nobody does umbrellas for people for
like lines so we just like I mean they
do Umbrellas of course but we checked
everywhere and did everything it was
just yeah it was it was
just intense all right look I'm going to
pop a lid on this broth that was the
longest
broth if you're taking that long to make
your healing broth ice packs were not
coming in on time right we ordered
thousands of ice packs get this we
ordered thousands of ice packs like it
was like like $7,000 in ice packs and
they never got delivered we lost the
$7,000 the ice packs just went who knows
where they were like hijacked somewhere
and we were like no we have to get them
so then we the Heatwave was
record-breaking someone we we think
somebody hijacked our ice packs as they
were being like sent to us we lost the
hunk of money whatever we just have to
get ice packs we then we went another
route and was like emergency find ice
packs and a whole another round of ice
packs and
then because of record
Heatwave right it's like the Afterparty
facility had air conditioning but to
have you know a ton of people in there
in a record-breaking heat wve that every
building in La was struggling with
cooling down like every building in La
was struggling to keep cool we're like
it's not good enough so what we did was
we like we worked hard and my team they
were killing themselves getting an air
conditioning trucking company to come in
the middle of the night and set up these
large pumping tubes into the place and
pump AC into that building at the
Afterparty and I remember like it was a
phone call at 3: in the morning like you
know it was like truck's not here yet
you know what do we do what like it was
unbelievable what happened and then the
truck got there and then was pumping the
AC in it was just incredible everything
that came about what happened was
remarkable you guys I'm going to read
some notes in a minute I'm going to put
a lid on this and bring this down a
little bit
voila a
lid nose is running a little bit um
tears coming on my eyes from those
onions they get me every time
but Angela over there on YouTube says I
I loved you and Joel singing on the live
stream I still have those songs in my
head it was really fun it was
fun it was special and um they're still
in my head every
hour they're still in my
head so I got this healing broth
simmering and boy does it smell good I
am hungry too you can actually do a
couple things I I like to strain it and
make it into that broth but you can have
it as a stew too if you really want to
to like a soup Margaret over there
Johnson over there on YouTube says I am
actually going to the grocery store
right now to get more wild blueberries
and the ingredients for your soup thank
you Anthony have a great weekend
everyone so glad you're going and
getting the stuff you need that warms my
heart makes me
happy so on the on the whole light
blast um I did extra light blasts that
last Saturday that day and it was um a
heartwarming experience on my end
because I want to give whatever I can
give at all times and I think that
um just for you guys being there I can't
believe you were there when I when I
even think about it you were there and
now we're we're talking we're
communicating right now you're leaving
comments and just oh man I don't know
it's just there's something really
surreal about it
just truly beautiful I'm going to read
some notes are you guys okay with that
so you guys left me some notes
I'm going to put my hand in this note uh
note container and get some
out hopefully I can
read the notes I know my handwriting oh
did you get a book did you win a book
with the raffle you guys any of you guys
here now during this live stream that
we're doing right now any of you guys
win a book in the
raffle at all cuz I wrote wrote a note
right here in the first page of every
book that we were raffling I think it
was like 78 or 80 books we raffled out
so
um did you get
one Gord over there on YouTube says
thank you so much for everything you
gave us at the Calabasas everything was
too much coming from your big heart it
was amazing I still live there every
single day my God okay so I wrote a
unique note for all of those 78 books I
think it was 78 in total that we
auctioned I wrote a unique note inside
for everybody did you guys anybody here
did you get one each one was
different Erin over there on YouTube
says I love the songs you chose to play
and the meaning behind
them all the all the songs had great
meaning like Heart of Gold had great
meaning because that's how I feel about
you guys you guys have a heart of gold I
always felt that way about you guys had
great meaning still does every time I
even hear that song and then won't back
down by Tom Petty that has great meaning
because I feel like as I was saying it
there that the medical mean Community
just won't back down you guys are
fighters in every way for your health
all of it and you know I'm I can go into
more detail on this and maybe I will at
another event too about everything that
the songs were special to me because
they remind me of you guys and and
that's really what it's about too
somewhere over
there the whole event blew my mind the
light blasts were powerful the food was
the best I've ever had and I felt so
good after I ate it being at an event
that I didn't have to worry about food
touched my heart more than you know okay
that really touches my heart right now
because when I think about that here you
are you're at an event and you're not
worried about what you're eating you're
not worried about like what is going to
be in this food what is there canola oil
in this food and that's the thing there
was no canola oil in that food and
that's the thing there was no natural
flavors in that food there was no
nutritional yeast in that
food there wasn't there was no vinegar
in that food so there was no vinegar in
that food that was there at the event
how mind-blowing is that no nutritional
yeast no vinegar
right nothing crazy fermented in that
food like not like nothing Frankenstein
food Franken food stuff in that food it
was incredible organic food and it
didn't have like you know sneaky crap in
there things that you have to worry
about there's no citric acid in that
food there was no dairy in that food
super Trish 1999 over there on YouTube
watching from home was so emotional and
incredible it was heartwarming to hear
the stories and to see all the events
through the day what an amazing treat
having you play your music for us thank
you I'm honored
truly rise with melum sa Sue says there
aw the food was the dream not having to
cook and to have delicious re Rees from
life-changing Foods was mindblowing I
loved everything so much riseth Melton
the whole experience exceeded my
expectations it was just so mind-blowing
what you have offered us from early
morning 7 a.m. until the end of the
afternoon party light blast food Etc
incredible rise with mum thank you for
being there thank you for everything
Christine over there busman over there
on YouTube the food was so delicious and
all free it was free and that's that's I
just wanted to do that for you guys the
feeling to just eat outside without
needing to prepare read labels and be
cautious with ingredients is so
unbelievable so freeing thank you
Anthony I made sure hands down you guys
right like right from the beginning that
the food would be free of anything that
we would have to worry about made sure
and my team double made sure triple made
sure and the PE the people who are
making the food were amazing amazing and
just star chefs and incredible chefs
actually and the caring and the
preparation and the washing and
everything was just top level top level
Mar over there in YouTube I Believe The
Canyon Club was the brightest spot on
the earth when all this happened there
all those light blasts and golden hearts
I believe the
same we're just going to check on this
here in
broth smell is so good so good all right
so I'm going to read a couple of notes
you guys okay with that so I'm just
going to put this right
here moving some of my stuff
over okay so
um let's open this door let's see what
we have here I have a note in my
hand okay A W today's meet and greet
plus surprise
Afterparty Trump the last
one times 1 million
okay wait a minute for
Real come
on today's me wait did I just read this
correctly or am I just read or is like
did I read this correctly okay A W
today's meet and greet Plus surprise
after after party Trump the last one by
a
million I love how you give all your
heart and gifts to us all not tangible
gifts you are an UND undeniable
blessing Michelle Kendall that is really
cool thank you it put a smile on my face
you just put a major big smile on my
face because like I've been okay I've
been kind of like I've been kind of like
smacking myself in the head a little bit
about y me in a nice way about was
better than the last one was the June
15th one better than this one you know
the June 15th one was in the park I mean
that was amazing everybody was hanging
out we're having a good time we were in
the park beautiful Park beautiful day
just beautiful trees right that was June
15th and so this one here at the canyon
was also beautiful it's amazing we had
this incredible Afterparty we had the
raffle you know we had the light blasts
right and we had all of that and I'm
like which one was which one was better
and you said this one trumped the June
15th one by a
million this blows me away all
right so I have a note right
here to my darus Anthony I was sick for
33 years 33 years
my God I mean sick for 33 years I mean
people don't understand that out there
and I'm just I I'm not I'm I'm holding
off for a second reading the rest of the
note because I just want to say that
um
that unless you've been
there forget it you know you just you're
not going to know unless you've been
sick for 33 years that journey of being
sick you're sick for a year it's it's
it's a journey that no one
understands five years don't be
understand and you go you know doctor to
doctor to doctor and you're looking for
help and you're everywhere and you're
trying to get help and you're sick for a
long time it's brutal it's a brutal
existence for a lot of people and you
guys know I mean people are sick for a
long time in the medical medum community
before they get here you know it's hard
to they get to the medical medum
community they get to the books they get
to the information right they get the
information and they got people like
saying to them well you're still sick uh
was sick for 10 years it's going to take
more than one day to heal
and but when you get the information and
you start moving past your symptoms a
little bit at a time and moving forward
it's just an incredible incredible
experience so to my dearest Anthony I
was sick for 33
years um had um vertigo oh my God that's
really then pre diabetic uh then
multiple sclerosis and on not only did
you give me the answers to heal finally
but you also gave me something even more
important
as if that is even possible Anthony you
gave me
God okay I'm going to start crying all
right now you
know okay okay all right I can uh keep
it
together here's a note right
here
um thank you for your
generosity your compassion and
understanding Eternal blessings Chris
amazing
um it's another note I know that you
guys put these notes in here and um you
know to to leave me a
message I thought this would be a good
idea and I'm like thought it be a good
idea and now I'm getting so choked up I
can't even almost talk so maybe I don't
know maybe I should do this on another
day uh but here's one right here thank
you for saving my life
aw in more ways than one so grateful to
you you are the best
Amy you know I I think that if
if you
know one thing Spirit of compassion did
for me was to um to to teach me to do
everything I could to understand right
um I always ask Spirit of compassion
like why me why me you know I did that
when I was younger I don't do it anymore
really it's it's rare now um but I will
sometimes squeak that out but it's
nothing like it was when I was younger
you know when I was in my teens and I
tell tell Spirit of compassion like why
me why are you talking to me why why am
I supposed to be helping people why am I
supposed to someday put all this
information out there and be that
messenger and you know can't you find
somebody else can't you find somebody
else that's what I would say I I
remember that was my Mantra you know how
people have mantras and they have they
do affirmations it's like and they're
doing these affirmations my Mantra was
can't you find somebody else you know
when I was a kid and I was like 12 years
old 13 years old and um and I think that
what what happens is that like Spirit of
compassion you know gave me some
valuable lessons and teachings you know
when I was younger about how it was so
critical so the way you care about that
frog with the in with the injury or the
way you care about that Bunny with the
with the broken leg or the way you care
about that grasshopper or that baby bird
you have to that same compassion and
caring you have to you know find it in
your heart and care about people and
care about you know indivual uals and I
remember being taught these lessons in
very powerful times in my life too when
I was questioning something or
questioning this as a younger person in
questioning that and spirit of
compassion would show me and give me
these these profound pieces of
information these messages that I would
use to help me understand you know why
it's critical to have compassion for
people it's critical to have compassion
and to know what 33 years of being sick
or 10 years of being sick and five years
of being sick
is it doesn't matter if I haven't been
sick for 10 years um I have to know what
that either feels like to some degree or
understand it to some degree and feel
that person's feeling and know that it
matters um it matters and it makes a
difference if we can move that person
forward and get them through that out of
the woods and healing to the other side
you know of the into that field the
beautiful sun coming down on them and to
be out of that struggle and that
suffering and to be in touch with that
Spirit of compassion taught me early on
you know even when I was a kid that just
wanted to ride my bicycle and spirit of
compassion be like you have to care I be
like wait a minute why do I have to care
and spir Compass says you have to care
now and and it something happened I just
just one day it it it clicked when I was
a kid and I cared so much so much about
everybody and
everything it was hard it was real hard
and I never lost track of that and U you
know and here's a not right here as soon
as I opened your book I lit up
everything became
clear I am forever grateful I found my
path and you inspire me to
heal this
Earth all of us together I love you
Samantha that's just mind blowing
thank you for leading the way Michelle
said thank you for leading the way I try
my best I try my best to get the
information out there and fight for it I
have for years it's gotten a lot harder
though hasn't it you guys so I mean the
way things are going and the health
scene became like political and became
like um Feeding Frenzy and everybody's
trying to do shock and awe every 10
seconds flat and everybody's just
stealing this and doing that is crazy so
Sophie over there norstrom over there on
YouTube aw we danced like
crazy it was so much fun the DJs were
excellent I was so sweaty and everyone
was
shaking everyone was everyone was
shaking
it okay now that's funny all
right and it suddenly dawned on me that
everyone there was
[Laughter]
sober all right
all right that was funny Sophie that's
actually
hilarious so everybody was moving and
grooving is what everybody was moving
and grooving it and suddenly it dawned
on you that everybody was sober okay
that's that's hilarious that's
hilarious summer
5411 people that aren't sick don't
understand the stress sick people have
around finding food that's okay having
food that we knew wouldn't make us sick
was the most touching part for me you
really thought of everything and at no
cost to attendees was
mindblowing I I think it's interesting
you know it was a new a new experience
for me when you feed when you feed a a
large crowd of people like that and then
you feed them and no no cost mattered it
didn't matter it just had to be the best
it had to be the best of everything and
we had to make it happen and um it was a
it was an experience
because who does that right but but
being that I had to be I mean I have to
experience it myself because word doing
it it's an experience on its own it was
really interesting there's so much I was
learning from that experience of making
sure we had what we had for everybody
and how it was going it was really
awesome I think that and you know
sitting down and enjoying the food like
I did was um was just really exciting on
its own for me it just was
um Sophie over there on YouTube says
thank you for the light infused cards I
saw that and the the message are going
up but I think that like I want to talk
about that too and we read some more
notes but the light infused cards um
it's what what I love about the light
infused card infused cards is that
Spirit of compassion doesn't just send
the light down once on the cards it's
like s so is sending light down a
multiple times on the card so as I'm
signing all those cards and they're
being stacked up it's like every 10
minutes I mean it took a long time to
sign all the cards but every 10 minutes
Spirit of compassion would send light
down on the cards and that's just it it
just it feels so good to see that okay
so I got a note right here today I am
filled with tears of joy to meet you and
be with community and eat amazing food
is so healing I am filled with so much
gratitude thank you Rosal
Le
um here's a note right here
guys just kind came on here I'm reading
notes that were put into this beautiful
glass container over here from the event
a after party and um and I got a healing
broth cooking that I made too if you
just got here Anthony from the bottom of
my heart and my liver thank you you
saved my
life I love you
aen when I hear um when I hear somebody
say that I saved their life it's just
gets
me there Anthony thank you so much for
all you do for people your generosity
your kindness your care and your
genuiness really
Divine and are so inspiring thank you to
you and the team I think the team
too for the events worldwide events you
put together
everything during the two events was
seamless Toby 777 the Wyman shot in the
event oh my God a bartender another
one yep Wyman's wild blueberry juice was
there on top it was how incredible was
Wyman's donated all the wild blueberry
juice for the community it was on tap
over 1,000 bottles were donated for the
occasion so Wyman's donated over
1,000 bottles of Wyman's wild blueberry
juice that's
insane I had to talk to them and say are
you guys
okay that was like that was incredible
like I was like
what all right here's a note right here
I was honored to ask you what s so says
about me he said let go of the
guilt it made me cry because he knew I
carry a
weight I will work on
it I am so grateful for your total life
sacrifice for all of us you are so loved
Karen there's another note right here
thank you for helping my family
heal especially my
daughter love and light
I think the name
is
um I think it's Sig or Siggy I just bear
with me on that I can't quite see
that that warms my heart here's a note
right
here can't imagine I heard
you can't imagine I heard you on Glenn
Beck six years ago I remember
that
um I knew instantly that was it and I
remember Glenn talking about the medical
medium first book right I remember that
and um he was talking about doing celery
juice and stuff and reached out to me
and said aw can you come on here and um
it was really cool I knew instantly that
was it I've given out maybe 50 books so
far to share that's my
loing co took me down for a year and I
still have strep in my lungs but you
give me hope dear Anthony thank you for
everything especially your
compassion love always Joyce
amazing amazing so glad you were there
like physically able to travel and get
there that blows me away so many people
everybody there was like so many people
said I wouldn't be able to travel Gordon
over there and YouTube says I am crying
right now I asked Angels Give Me A Sign
if Anthony read my note that I will
mean that will mean that my Bell's paly
will
heal because I am losing my faith he
just read my message right now that I
wrote that is that's incredible hold on
to that Faith hold on to that hope then
because yes this wasn't by accident
right here far from it so me reading
your note wasn't by accident or wasn't
just happen stance it was much more than
that
Janette over here no one can believe
that this event was
free it blows my
mind that you guys like like just like
appreciate so much what what has
happened like I just blows my mind I
know you guys would appreciate of course
because you're such just good good
individuals good Souls good-hearted
people like you guys all have a heart of
gold like I was like singing about but
but yeah like you guys
just they are
unbelievable thank you for the brain
[Music]
saver
um it has changed my life I love the
community these notes are
amazing here's a note right here Anthony
and
so thank you I have the tools to support
myself I feel better and heal it's
gradual but steady forever grateful and
always open for miracle may you and we
continue blessings
Briana amazing
notes very special to my heart this
event is above and
beyond a buffet of medical medium food
is a dream it was really it was really a
killer buffet of food I mean I'm going
to just say it was so great it blew me
away too thank you so much for for
everything love you
Danny wow there's some notes Here you
guys I'm going to check on my healing my
healing broth is
done let me see I'm going to actually
get a ladle and just ladle it out into a
bowl is that
okay where is a good Bowl I am looking I
would like a glass bowl
and I have
one I can also strain it as well and
just make it straight brao but I'm going
to look here just bear with
me I have a ladle right
here I'm going to get some broth out I'm
going to turn this off Victoria rising
from the ashes over there in
YouTube yes he gives many of us
validation
we never got anywhere
else before finding
him boots McGee your level of
understanding of what we go through is a
powerful healing tool of its own so many
of us have waited our whole lives to be
seen this
way this for The Chronic o to be seen
the way you see The Chronic
eel thank you boots McGee for for just
being there and sharing that truly thank
you I'm going to move this
here so you can do a couple things you
can strain this I'm just going to
actually grab some of the broth like
this as you can
see this is coming out hot so hopefully
this glass bowl is is fine with it which
I think it will be
you guys know how I am in the kitchen
right stuff goes flying and sometimes aw
kind of flubs it a little bit the
recipes
and aw tries to do in third person
purposely aw tries the
multitask
Barbara Soul lightness Academy over
there on YouTube we had a medical medium
meeting at my house that Saturday and
afterwards watching the beautiful event
and getting all the light blast that was
a magical mm Saturday it was such an
incredible Saturday I tried to transport
myself there you know what I mean like I
try to transport myself there right and
I'm going to talk someday more about the
present moment and the future and the
past and telegram I talk about it
periodically but I am going to to
whenever I can I'm going to sit down I'm
going to transport my B self my mind my
body everything right back to that
Saturday because it was it was that
incredible Jackie says on YouTube
Anthony we were chosen because your
heart is like no other you give
endlessly with no
BS like The Fakes out there you love and
care for us like no other could
except this mm
family
wow look I try not to like talk about
like The Fakes out there or talk about
the BS out there but I do every now and
then I can't help it there's a lot of BS
out
there I think a lot of influencers that
are in the health realm whether they're
authors in the health realm or they just
want to take advantage and they're
running 20 billion ads at a time trying
to sell their their courses or whatever
they're doing I think that
they they're they're like they see The
Chronic eel as a cash cow you know like
just one big fat massive Cash Cow you
know and it's like and it's it's obvious
like what do they really know about
chronically ill and what do they know
about people in they're suffering and
struggling but they know this ch- ching
ch- ching ch- ching they definitely know
that you can see it everywhere out
there I get it you have to make a living
people have to make money yeah darn
right and you should work and and try to
do that if you can but there's a
difference when it comes down to the
health scene it's turned into a Feeding
Frenzy of just
sharks and
Insanity did I say too much is Tik Tok
going to punish me
now um anyway I have some healing broth
right
here and are you guys okay if I grab a
glass um let me see what I can do here
I'm going to do
this okay don't want to knock things
over
but okay here we are I have a glass
here and I'm going to put healing broth
in
here on a note I know you guys know this
but don't burn your mouth
because if I took a sip out of that
right now I know that that's going to
happen Hannah over there on YouTube says
Anthony so you're literally changing the
world not only with your health
information but your kindness and love
you show through so many ways that you
show through so many ways I'm always in
awe of
you I have my healing
broth I'm an a you
too that's
hot a that's so good oh that is so
good right after all those light blasts
after the event a nice healing broth
like this wow and there's a nice pot of
soup
behind right
there and I'm going to have it Jennifer
Roman my 74 year-old friend watched some
of your videos he said you're a funny
guy Anthony dot dot dot I try to be
funny when I can uh almost to a
fault I will say you make him laugh
that's amazing in a good way okay okay
he has been doing celery juice for
almost a year every day since reading a
couple of your book celery juices helped
him so much with his asthma after 74
years of having it and being being in an
oxygen tank as a child he loves the
taste of it too laugh out loud never
underestimate the power of celery juice
it's one of the most powerful tools out
there and if that's not doing it enough
for you just know it's doing something
for you and then when you add on another
medical medium tool boom and you add on
another medical medium tool if you need
to boom and then you do some shock
therapy boom you know like a golden
steal shock therapy or or a B12 shock
therapy and you boom and you whatever
you read the books and you'll learn and
then you at the protocols and you say
you know what I'm going to start with
these three things in this protocol then
am going to watch the bees yes and I'm
going to watch the waves roll in on the
beach and I'm going to add those tools
at the same time I'm going to do a 28
day cleanse I'm going to move to a 369
I'm going to try a mono cleanse I'm
going to do the morning cleanse I'm
going to do a heavy metal detox then I'm
going to do a heavy metal detox cleanse
and then you just you take one day at a
time and you chip away and you next
thing you know it everything starts to
heal and you start moving forward you
start overriding it overriding the
struggle and you're healing and you're
moving forward
boom Spirit of compassion just said
don't forget to mention the spinach soup
do not let Spirit compassion isn't using
these words right here though do not let
the
morons of the health movement and the
idiots of the health
movement Spirit didn't use an
idiot I added those I'm
sorry but Spirit of compassion is saying
do not underestimate the power of the
spinach soup what that can do when
you're using that on a daily basis to
heal how powerful that tool is is
just profound and what it can do for you
is that spinach soup that's a medical
medium tool right there and don't let
and I added the words idiots and morons
tell you don't do spinach
don't do spinach it's bad for you I mean
the crap you see out there lean sherald
says over there on Facebook could you
post the ingredients for the healing
broth thanks totally enjoy all the info
that you post I'll get it out there one
way whether it's on a post or or you can
go to medical medium.com and find it or
I'll you know or I'll put a link out
there for it make sure you are on the
medical medum newsletter there is
something very exciting coming out this
week uh oh
okay can I hold myself
back holding myself back on this do not
open your big mouth aw do not open your
big
mouth you
guys keep an eye on the medical mum
newsletter tell everybody else to keep
keep an eye on the medical medium
newsletter you might be sorry if you
didn't keep your eye on the medical
medium newsletter because you might miss
out on
something that I'm going to be doing
so can you tell everybody can you guys
tell other people can you mention it
maybe post about it keep an eye on the
medical me newsletter because I'm about
to put something out literally in the
next couple of days the next couple of
days something else is
happening maybe you're not interested
when you hear what it is you might be
interested so you don't want to miss out
but something else is
happening I'm doing something else
you want to probably listen out in your
newsletter Christina busman says your
speech on on the Afterparty was so
amazing he touched my heart and reminded
me of how important it is to strengthen
the
soul that's incredible and that you know
and I the uh spirit of
compassion it gave me a lot of words um
in that moment and I don't use tele
proops and I'm not using a teleop now
and I never used tele
propter
ever and
um and I don't practice for a speech and
I never practice and I never have notes
and I never go over anything so what
happens is I just the event's coming
like it did right uh last week weekend
and Saturday right and I just do other
things like to help move it forward and
to help my team wherever I can and
and uh and all that but I never think
about the speech I never think about
what I'm going to say I never use a
telepromter or whatever you call it
prompt or whatever and I don't and I
just go on there in that moment and I
listen to S SOC so I do I do cheat a
little bit
so I do I listen to Spirit of compassion
right there when I'm on the stage and I
add a little bit from me
and uh a hunk of it from s so and I get
it
down you perform basically death
question mark question yeah on the
guitar and the singing I was didn't hear
a single thing props to you that's some
incredible Talent like the guitar solo I
didn't hear that
either didn't hear any of it it was just
basically I was just hitting notes as if
it was in the air and I was singing
words that were in the air because I had
no monitors and no way to know what was
happening but hey it didn't matter I
just love being there and I loved
playing for you
guys this is so
amazing so good Soul lightness Academy
over there on YouTube when you were
singing I couldn't stop listening your
music was going directly to my heart
that's more than I can ask for it's more
than I can ask for now Alison the way we
were all treated at Aran and the other
venue is the true definition to comp of
compassion we were so nurtured and cared
for that is the best thing I can hear
because that's what I was hoping and I
was praying before it all happened and I
wanted the the best feeling to occur and
I wanted I wanted you guys to know how
much I cared
and this is hot just don't burn your
tongue when you drink yours fly high
said over there on YouTube guys there is
an mm playlist on Spotify with all the
songs from the
event highly requested we did put out a
playlist because it was highly highly
requested I like making noise when I sip
really hot soup so just bear with me
rise of melum says YouTube the security
at the event was very polite and
respectful although there was a lot
going on I really loved it so there so
here's how it works with the security at
the event security of the vent is to
protect the medical meme
Community you know it's to make sure
that they're
safe that's really what it is it's their
I had my two guys you know like I had my
guys right but the rest of the security
is for the community because you just
don't know who can just walk right in
there it was a it was a private party it
was a Afterparty it was a medical medum
community Afterparty you just don't know
who's can walk in you don't know so the
security was to protect the
community so they care about what I'm
saying is they care about the community
they're there for the community they're
there for the event it just was a great
thing it was just a music playlist is
what it was by the way but it was requ
request it so we we put it out there you
guys incredible I am going
to sit down enjoy my broth I might have
a soup later as well which I'm excited
about a little later on but I want to
get the healing broth in on its own like
this I haven't eaten anything today and
this is like so good I can't get enough
of
it hope everybody's taking care of
themselves pat yourself on the back keep
a light heart one day at a time one hour
at a time many of you it's one every 10
minutes at a time but just take you know
one day at a time one hour at a time
every minute at a time but know that I
care I'm proud of everybody truly and if
you are in
California near in Aran you might still
be able to get I mean you'll be able to
get the bottled up heavy metal detox
medical meme heavy metal detox there at
aan but the customized bottle the
collectible you know there might be a
few left in the stores it's fre possible
it probably is and cuzz they they they
made a bunch of them a whole bunch of
them but that's the heavy metal detox
bottle right there it says medical
medium on it that's the Aran heavy metal
detox bottle right there
so I
mean they're pretty darn awesome to do
that they are pretty darn awesome
they're amazing at air one marger says
on YouTube was so nice to hang out with
everyone thank you aw coming on live
soon after the event so that's what
happened is after the meet and greet I
ran over as fast as I could to the event
at the canyon
right yep aw coming on live so soon
after the event I'm looking I'm double
checking oh coming on live
here coming on live here well just so
you know at the meet and greet I was
also rushing to get over to the
Afterparty as fast as I could to go on
live there as fast as I could so I was
like running on marbles man I was just
like
in
marbles all right you guys love
you God bless