Tonight's Live is about Anxiety and
Depression.
two things so many people are going
through these days i'm going to be
covering the true
causes of anxiety and depression because
it's a mystery
a mystery for so many people millions
upon millions of people
have mysterious anxiety and depression
it's really hard on people so
to talk about what people experience
when they're
living with anxiety when they're living
with depression and how debilitating
these symptoms can be how it affects
your life
you guys probably know somebody with
anxiety you probably know somebody with
depression
so let's get down to it that's what we
have to do nobody's depression
nobody's anxiety is the same there's
they're all unique your anxiety is
unique
to you and what's happening inside your
body
they're not the same you just can't
classify it you can't tag it like that
you got anxiety okay
well you got anxiety too well you're
seeing all your symptoms are identical
that's
really really impossible it's always
going to vary
on all kinds of different levels so i
wanted to talk about that too so
that's one thing i'm glad you guys are
coming on and really excited about this
to heal
anxiety and to heal depression you guys
you
have to have the true cause
i'm sorry but you have to have the true
cause
that's how it works with healing that's
what's so critical
it's like yeah if you don't have the
true cause of what your anxiety is
stemming deep down inside if you don't
have
the true cause of your depression
stemming deep down inside what the root
causes the root right
if you don't have that how are you gonna
get better
how are you gonna move forward if you're
new here i'm anthony william the medical
medium number one new york times
bestselling author you might say who is
this guy
why should i listen to him you know
where's his credentials is he a doctor
who is this guy no i'm not a doctor i've
said it over and over again
i'm the originator of the global celery
juice movement i'm a number one new york
times best-selling author of over six
books this is one of them right here
cleanse the heal which is on sale right
now
amazon.com i have over 35 years of
experience working with over 250
000 individuals one-on-one over the
years
also working with doctors and
troubleshooting their most difficult
cases
i was known as the guy people brought
their bizarre symptoms to from all
over the world that's who i was before
social media turned into social media
before you know there were influencers
before there were social media
for all of it that's what i was known i
had a little shack
has an office people flew from all
around the world
to come into my office and say i got
this weird tingling and numbness
i got this weird burning skin my jaw
hurts and i've been to 30 doctors
and that's what happened my whole life
so there you go
um so i wanted to tell you guys a little
bit about that and
the book's doing really good right now
people are actually really loving the
book if you heard about cleanse the heel
check it out
get it get it get it at the library for
free i mean i always tell people go to
the library
get it for free i mean it's changing
lives
changing lives people are getting weight
loss from 369 advanced cleanse
people are getting their lives back
people are healing so it's really an
amazing thing so it really is
most people in the medical medium
community have seen lots of specialists
lots of internists lots of doctors
alternative
conventional doctors they've been on a
journey seeing lots of healthcare
healthcare practitioners
and getting help in many ways and some
people have seen up to 50 doctors how
many doctors have you seen
have you seen 10 doctors have you seen
three are you a lucky person where
you're not so
sick and you just got your first symptom
or two and you saw an alternative doctor
or
you saw a naturopath or maybe you saw
you know your regular doctor and they
did a little blood work and you got a
little symptom here and there and you're
just
starting to embark on your journey of
cleaning up your foods and
looking on the internet for answers and
stuff if you're in that great position
that's great
but there's a lot of people that are
really sick really struggling the
medical medium information
was for those people and has been and
got people
off of mattress island if you guys want
to know what mattress island is many of
you guys know
mattress island is when you're when
you're in bed and you're in bed too long
you're in bed a lot you spend a lot of
time on the mattress you spend a lot of
time
on the couch couch island mattress
island
it's not a fun place and so many people
have been there and had to find the
medical medium information
so you know here's a point right here
before we go on with anxiety we're going
to cover we're going to cover all the
details about anxiety
what kind of different versions of
anxiety what kind of different versions
of depression and what the true causes
are
before we go into that listen i want to
tell you guys whether you're plant-based
whether you're vegan whether you're
paleo whether you're vegetarian whether
you're animal protein whether you're
keto animal protein right whether you're
keto plant-based
whether you're keto vegan whether you're
carnivore
whether you're balanced diet whether
you're intuitive eating
whether you're food combining or any
other diet belief system there is and
there's a lot of them out there
everyone has something in common
remember this
they all get sick remember this they all
get sick
that's how it's been and that's what
happened so
sure you might have things under control
you cleaned up your diet
maybe you're on a plant-based diet but
plant-based people
they quit eating plant-based they run to
eating animal protein they go
start bringing in salmon they start
bringing in eggs oh should i be eating
eggs
should i be eating salmon should i be
eating turkey maybe i need my protein
maybe that's why i'm getting symptoms
same thing with the vegans it's like
well wait a minute maybe
maybe beans aren't cutting it maybe
beans got too much of something
bad in them and maybe i need to start
eating animal protein and
that's how it works same thing with
paleo people same thing with animal
protein people they're like should i go
plant-based
what am i doing wrong why am i getting
sick and the whole thing is this is that
what we have to understand something is
that
with the food wars and with the
different diet belief systems
everybody eventually gets sick either
they've been sick in the past they get
sick again in the present
or they get sick in the future that's
what everybody has in common whether
anybody likes it or not
and if you're young and you feel
indestructible and you haven't got there
yet you're going to get sick later on
down the road you know because
everybody does i talk to doctors all the
time and
when i talk to doctors they're like
they'll they'll say it too you're like
you're right
everybody's gonna have a thyroid problem
later on ever
you're right aw because you nailed it
you're right everybody you told me that
20 years ago and yes
everybody's getting thyroid problems
they get them before they turn 30 now
instead they used to get them before
they turned 50
and that's how it is so if they get sick
it's
that's what it is everybody has
something in common regardless of the
diet belief system
and that's why there's one thing that's
really important about the medical
medium information there's no
diet belief system here so that's one
thing to know so if you're new here
there's no diet belief system because
diet belief systems
get you trapped and then you don't heal
because there has to be something more
to that
because plant-based people get sick
vegans get sick
vegetarians get sick animal protein
people get sick keto people get sick
everybody gets sick whatever diet
beliefs and belief system that they're
subscribed to
or they're attached to so really
important to know
that there's not that here that's the
last
thing we have going on instead what we
have is tools
that you can apply and plug into your
diet belief system and that's the whole
thing
actual tools and answers for instance
like the heavy metal detox smoothie
right there so
that's the medical medium heavy metal
detox movie i made it for dinner tonight
you guys which i'm really excited about
and talking about the heavy metal detox
smoothie because why
hmm anxiety why uh depression
well nobody knew what causes those until
the medical media books were published
until all that stuff happened what
causes anxiety
what causes mystery depression yeah you
got it toxic
heavy metals mercury aluminum
copper in the brain toxic heavy metals
are responsible
for anxiety that's one of the main
causes of anxiety and depression
so then and that leads to a lot of
different conditions you guys bipolar
asperger's focus in concentration adhd
ocd
all of that it leads to lots of that
even schizophrenia
all of it so i mean you know and you
know what's funny about science and
research you just want to say this
before we go into this
science and research science and
research believes you know your bipolar
is just
a mystery and they believe that it's
just you being up or down
you know you're just you're just that
kind of person where
there's no reason why you're doing this
you're just all over the place you're
either north or south how about that for
a diagnosis
incredible all the money in science and
research
all the incredible you know like doctors
and technology that we have today and
the best they have for bipolar
is we don't know why you're all over the
place
um sir uh we
ma'am we don't know why you're up manic
boom down crashed and depressed um
we're just scratching our heads with all
the science and technology we
have that's what science research has
we're either going to say
maybe it's genetic or maybe we'll just
say um
let's see maybe you need a psychiatrist
try that
and then um maybe we're just going to
label this
this illness and label it bipolar what a
brilliant label
right meaning north and south isn't that
brilliant
oh my god it's unbelievable it's an
insult it's really disgusting it's
negligence at its best with science and
research that's just one
example of what's happening and
you know the whole thing is it's
critical to know why
you have a problem and it's in your way
and it's impeding your quality of life
and it's like in the way of things you
want to do
and and we're going to cover that about
anxiety we're going to talk about that
in the whole bit and
the whole thing with the diet belief
systems is the reason why you won't find
that here is because this is about
answers and tools
and that's what's critical it's about
how to use things therapeutically
that's what it's about medical medium is
not a plant-based diet medical medium is
not an animal-based diet medical
medium is not any of those in any way
which way possible
it's all these answers that can be
plugged into someone's belief system
to help them recover and heal because
what i've noticed and many other people
have over the decades
is whatever you try you're still going
to end up with a problem and get sick in
the whole
the whole thing there's people out there
i thought they were on the best
plant-based
diet possible and they got sick and then
they're flip-flopping and the same thing
with people with the animal protein
diets the best animal product protein
diets possible
and they're flip-flopping they're going
to the other side so it's
it's been like that all along but here's
the difference now
it's getting worse and worse and worse
30 years ago the amount of anxiety cases
that i used to see
30 years ago were a fraction of what
they are today and that's with organic
food here
that's what people are switching up
their diets getting rid of fast food
that's what people do in their peanut
butter
their peanut butter smoothie bowls
that's what people do in their protein
shakes and anxiety is skyrocketing
even with all the good things we're
talking about we're bringing in
that's what's happening here it's
unbelievable so
um you guys you know these things are so
important feel free
to bring what information that you learn
here to your doctor
and to your health care provider to your
health care practitioner to whoever that
takes care of your health feel feel free
i'm going to breed how to cleanse the
heal a little bit right here okay
and we're going to talk about anxiety
the true cost and then we're going to
cover through all the different levels
of anxiety
and you might know somebody that's
dealing with some type of anxiety so
we're going to cover
the first type of anxiety in a minute
we're going to go into emotional anxiety
like what is that
emotional anxiety so we're going to
cover in that too
um support the pause says this is
amazing um this is amazing you're here
thank you for being here
um yeah the mono diets have you guys
checked out the monodites the silly
siberians did the mono diets
incredible right in here the medical
medium mono eating cleanses
these are really great these are really
great and it's not only bananas though
it's not just bananas by themselves but
check that out if you get a chance um
cheryl lane yes no canola or vegetable
oils you know what
people looked at me like a flying saucer
just landed behind me
and i had 10 heads back 30 years ago
when i was lecturing a health food store
and saying
no canola oil you guys have no idea
that you shouldn't be doing canola oil
all the vegans any vegans that existed
back then 30 years ago
were drinking the canola oil and i was
like no canola oil no canola
canola oil right the whole bit and then
all of a sudden what happens now after
that
plus publishing it someone will hear
canola oil is bad and then they'll be
like oh anthony
he just he didn't know a bit he just
what everybody knew that no
no one knew that back then it's
incredible it's one of them that's one
of the advanced pieces of information
that i brought to town
35 years ago 30 years ago which it was
no canola oil
and that you know when the first book
came out medical medium first book came
out six years ago and i said no canola
oil everybody was like what
where huh what it's just funny it's
really funny
i know they love it um let's go to page
490 real quick we're going to cover this
and then we're going to go in depth
into anxiety and depression and we're in
cleanse the heal right now you guys i
mean look it's
amazon.com 16.99 it's 51
off i mean unbelievable price um get a
book for somebody if you know if they
if if you know if they can't afford one
or something or tell them to go to the
library and get it for free
in australia the books in the library i
just i
on facebook last time i was live
somebody said that they said no you can
get the books free at the library and
you know right in australia i couldn't
believe it i was so psyched
so let's go into this a little bit here
true cause of anxiety when anxiety
interferes with your life is anxiety
interfering with your life but do you
have
like any of the anxiety symptoms because
i'm going into it in depth in a minute
is it interfering in your life in any
way
it's caused by toxic heavy metals
such as mercury aluminum and copper hey
maybe you're somebody you're like okay
now i know the answer
let me go and hop on the internet um
toxic heavy metals
causing anxiety first of all if it even
is on the internet and says that it came
from here but
most importantly when you go you might
see a whole bunch of things like um
corella can get my metals out let me go
and do that um
activated charcoal can get my metals out
no
no bad no corella can't get
metals out you know worth the life of it
it can't get metals out of somebody
activated charcoal terrible to take
terrible to take
internally a terrible thing to do and
activate the charcoal internally with
anybody who has bloating gut problems
gut
issues sensitivities in the gut inflamed
intestinal linings
gallbladder trouble liver issues
stagnant sluggish liver
lymphatic issues taking activated
charcoal epic disaster
just so you know and it won't remove
toxic heavy metals because it doesn't
there's no proof it never had there's no
study that can
show it actually grabbing metals it's
one of those those
bad ideas that's number one corella so
your other oh anthony says toxic heavy
metals
is behind my anxiety let me go on here
online oh wait
corella yeah nice try corella this is
terrible bacteria in almost every one of
those different
batches that are out there i've seen
corella barrel people like
get them so sick where they're in the
hospital
vomiting and diarrhea for days at a time
and the doctor's like i don't know maybe
you got food poisoning i don't know
no corella bad bad and you'll still see
influencers today with all the work i've
done try to let people know that it
doesn't get
it doesn't get metals out and all the
work i've done all these years
still see a new influencer that's
remember because no one knows what's
going on
another five years later there's all
these influencers that are being told
corella
and they're just out there saying i'm
taking my corella got it mixed up here
in my drink in my smoothie
it's like first of all no metals are
going to come out second of all
terrible for you and i know listen i
know it's got nutrients in it don't get
me wrong but i'm just saying
that's where it goes wrong these other
avenues
and activated charcoal awful so that's a
couple things too so
toxic heavy metals such as mercury
aluminum and copper
okay and viral issues
when it comes down to anxiety depression
a lot of times there's a viral issue
involved
so we have to know that the the
epstein-barr is one of the most
infamous viruses i talk about i mean
that's the one
that actually is behind a lot of
depression a lot of anxiety now
you don't even have to have any any ebv
you don't even have to have
ebv symptoms which nobody knew existed
as far as the symptoms go until the
publications of medical media book one
but and how that works but the point is
it's it's a combination
of both epstein-barr for a lot of people
and toxic heavy metals because here's
how it works
if you're viral and you have it in your
liver and it's low grade it's been there
for decades
it ends up feeding on foods and what its
favorite
food is is mercury mercury
aluminum copper so when the viruses
feed off of mercury they go to bathroom
yes viruses eat that's advanced medical
information
ahead of science and research and when
viruses eat they release
a toxic heavy metal byproduct
so it's called the neurotoxin that
neurotoxin
floats around and goes to the brain it's
short circuits
neurotransmitter chemicals it lands on
neurons it saturates neurons
causing varieties of anxiety and
depression
you can have that going but you don't
even have to have the viral issue
you can be without the viral issue and
be straight toxic heavy metals
straight mercury in your system straight
aluminum in your system oh i don't have
mercury in my system there's no way i
don't have
oh i gotta had a mercury test i don't
have mercury in my system yeah you do
everybody does it gets passed on from
generation to generation
and it settles in our organs deep
in our organs so it's really important
to know like our brain
settles in our brain and i'm going to
talk about what it does there tonight
like why do we get the anxiety
and you know the whole thing no one knew
viruses and toxic heavy metals
are behind anxiety depression that never
existed
anywhere except for medical medium
information so if you know it
never existed anywhere else but you're
going to hear about it more because of
millions and millions of books
from the medical medium series have been
circulating around the world
and so people get a little tidbit here
and they're like oh yeah medals
somebody might say metals might behind
that metals might be behind adhd metals
might behind brain brain fog
comes from the medical medium literature
medical medium information
um and it's behind mystery depression
toxic heavy metals are behind anxiety
you have to have the
metals there so i'm going to talk about
also the best stuff to use like i got
that medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie right here so if you want to
get metals out
this is what you got to do and i'm going
to talk about talk about how and
and everything and what we what you know
i put in here with spirit compassion and
i put in here
the whole bit how it works and in the
book the heavy metal detox cleanse so
then you can learn how to get metals out
that way
i saw comments recently on some of the
lives
i saw comments in some other places
people leave on the youtube if you you
know check out my youtube right
and people say their anxiety
has dissipated has just disappeared when
they did the heavy metal detox cleanse
when they did the heavy metal detox
smoothies when they do the medical
medium
information that they got rid of
horrific
horrendous anxiety that was crippling
but
there's thousands of people that have
gotten themselves recovered and got
their lives back with anxiety
and depression over the years really
over the years i hope i'm not running
this by you guys too fast i'm talking a
little quicker because you wouldn't
believe how much i have to
be covered tonight so so um we have
we have in almost an hour so let's do it
and
you know the whole thing is it's not
just removing the toxic heavy metals
it's repairing
the damage here's something to
digest right here here's something to
take in you guys when a toxic heavy
metal
sits on a neuron in your brain or sits
on organ tissue it saturates that organ
tissue
okay it ends up burning a hole
and that's what it does a microscopic
hole
because it by it has byproduct
metal oxidizes inside our brain and body
it's advanced medical information from
um from the medical medium information
so and what it does is
when toxic heavy metals oxidize in our
organs
whether it's in our liver whether it's
in our brain whether it's inner spleen
anywhere in our bodies when it oxidizes
it leaves residue that's toxic behind it
and it starts to rust
out holes in tissue it damages cells
tissue is what it does when toxic heavy
metals sit on a neurotransmitter
meaning it destroys it weakens it
dehydrates it
when a toxic heavy metal sits on a
neuron
it weakens it it short-circuits it so
when you have when you have electrical
impulses firing all around through the
brain
that are supposed to keep us focused on
spot on with our
everything you know able to articulate
able able to communicate
able to talk able to have fun able to
kind of feel excitement
able to actually all these things and
multitask and to be on our game and to
be down on
like totally going everything going
great and how we feel
focus concentration like boom all of it
with all of that when our neurons are
saturated with toxic heavy metals
and those electrical impulses that are
firing in our brain hit those
neurons that are that are saturated with
the metals and it hits the metal
it short circuits it weakens the
electrical impulse and then we're like
i got i don't know i got some brain fog
i'm a little more tired i really
and i'm just i got some anxiety i can't
sit still i
i feel like i don't know i'm kind of
clammy palms i don't want to really talk
to this person
i feel like i can't get my words out
right um
i'm just i feel like my skin's crawling
i want to jump out of my skin
um i can't focus i just need to do
something i like to do i can't do this
stuff i don't like to do because what i
do i just get totally out of it
like all these different things you know
and when someone asks anything of me i
just
i'm not responsive i can't come up with
an answer in time
i can't really you know focus on what
i'm saying when i stand there and
somebody's talking to me i'm trying to
think about the next thing i'm going to
say but i don't know what i'm going to
say
and all of these things happen these are
just i'm just going over a couple little
things so we're going to cut into it
let's go in just a little bit more so in
this book cleanse the heel
i talk about supplements and dosages
right here for helping to repair
injuries caused by these toxic heavy
metals causing depression and anxiety
so um kale says what if you have anxiety
depression
acne fatigue all of the above okay what
you do is you take
the symptom that's bugging you the most
this is what i would do this is just
what i would do i would go to cleanse to
heal
or you can bring it to your practitioner
doctor and i would
go and i would take the symptoms that's
bothering you the most
is fatigue bothering you the most and
then i would go in there
and i would do the fatigue thing like i
would look at the protocol i would take
a look and look at everything in the
back of the book okay
and that's what i would do and i would
learn what the true cause of your
fatigue is
and that's what i would do i'd be like
what's the true cause of my fatigue
because i want to know i want to know
the true cause of my fatigue
and once you do that and you start
applying what's in cleanse to heal for
your fatigue
or having your practitioner or your
doctor friend or anybody that you have
helping you apply it you notice other
things
start to go away like the acne will
start going away
anxiety starts getting a little better
depression starts getting a little
better
that's one way to go at it and you could
also go at it individually you can go
with anxiety you can go with the
depression
so let's talk about emotional anxiety
so let's go in there next you guys i'm
gonna read comments too
um does high dosage of vitamin c really
good
high dosages of vitamin c kill viruses
that's really a great a great question
here
you'll see in the supplements in the
protocols and the dosages you'll see the
vitamin c
and you'll see there's vit the medical
medium vitamin c shock
therapy that's there for a reason
so it's really important to know so um
and and the micro c is the one that i
like the best
just looking at your comments i don't
want to try i don't want to miss too
many i want to catch what i can
the micro microc is actually the one i
use right here so there's different
vitamin c
so yeah we can use the term vitamin c
but if it's not a really good one
how much is it doing is it knocking down
viruses vitamin c does a couple of
things okay
high dosages does help kill off viruses
and that's why i've been recommending it
for years and years and years and years
the medical medium vitamin c shock
therapy is there for a reason
but what vitamin c is somebody using
what kind of vitamin c is somebody using
that's a whole other game so the micro c
is the one i use
that's my favorite i'm not sponsored by
this company okay there's a lot of
companies like
you know wyman blueberries is the one i
use for my heavy metal detox movies it's
the wyman
wild blueberries i'm not sponsored by
the company i don't own wyman's
people asset all the time they think i
own wyman's i get questioned on that
there's even articles out there about
does he own wyman's
you know what i mean i don't own vimergy
um but yeah best vitamin c
right there it's amazing how many
stories go around but people just buy
the bs they just meaning they
they believe in any story going around
it's unbelievable anything
you put out on me it's just anybody will
just bite it and be like oh it must be
true when it's not
it's unbelievable and i stand behind
that so
lemon balm is a big deal so lemon balm
the vimergy lemon balm is important too
i'm going over some of these i'm looking
here
so just bear with me a second you guys
one of the one of the most like
incredible things that
i've like recommended over the years and
so forth and i talk about in cleansing
heal is the lemon balm all right
the lemon balm for anxiety is really
helpful but you know and
and i love like if you go into the
anxiety section in the back of cleanse
of heel you'll see
the dosages of lemon balm this is the
vimergy lemon balm it's the cleanest
it's the greatest
and you know people say to me they're
like oh why do you like vimergy
right okay well how about this they're
the only company or the only company
i've known
or no out of all the companies i know
out there because i'm always wanting the
best for people out there
the only company that independently
gets every single product tested for
toxic heavy metals
it costs a fortune that's why companies
won't do it
that's why companies won't do it and
every single product they get
independently tested that's the
difference right there
you might hear some company like that
there's a lot of people you guys
that troll medical medium channels
listening to me because they're
competitors
in weird ways like authors that do
medical
stuff and all that they just get upset
and jealous about all the advanced
information from the
from medical media books and so forth
but there's people out there
that are like um well and then they'll
they'll hear me say this company's
independently tested by metal so then
they'll tell people
they'll get they won't do it
independently but oh we test for heavy
metals in one of our products we test
for heavy metals it's just a scam out
there 24 7.
but this company independently checks
tech gets
sends it out and gets it tested for
toxic heavy metals
costs a fortune that's just one example
you know and i'm saying that because
a lot of people say supplements have
metals in them you know i mean
you know that whole thing yeah bad
supplements do anyway
that's incredible for anxiety that i've
you know that that's what i would do so
panic attacks
that's what i'm talking about and i like
the lemon bomb for panic attacks
i don't have panic attacks but if i had
a panic attack
that's what i would do i would be doing
the lemon bum and i would be doing the
dosages personally that's what i would
do
in cleanse the heel on that that's a
takeaway right here that's important
because it's one thing to talk about the
causes of anxiety which i'm going to go
into
it's another to actually have a takeaway
of what can i do what kind of what
tool can i use and so that's important
so in the supplements
in a protocol section in the back of
cleanse the heel
you look up anxiety you'll see there's
lemon balm like as one of the listed
supplements
so that's what i would do and um
nerves get inflamed with anxiety so
here's the other thing
the most critical nerve that gets
inflamed with your anxiety is your vagus
nerve
that is the big one the other nerves
that get inflamed with you that are
inflamed and are behind
anxiety are your phrenic nerves your
phrenic nerves run
down in through down through your neck
and down here like this they run like
that
your phrenic nerves what they do is they
light up
they get they just light up they get
inflamed from both neurotoxins from
viruses
and toxic heavy metals that are feeding
the viruses
so these nerves these phrenic nerves get
inflamed and when they get inflamed
you're you light up you're
hypersensitive you can be triggered easy
you can be like you can you can get
emotional easy
you can all these things it can throw
you in a panic attack
your vagus nerve can tighten up your
throat and make you feel like you're
you're choking
your your vagus nerve can tighten up
your chest
make it hard for you to breathe and you
feel like you got anxiety and you feel
like you're hyperventilating
or even not even just that you feel like
you have tightness of the chest
and it's it's hard and if you even focus
on your breath it's why
it's why there's two kind of sides to
the story when it comes down to
meditation this is an important point
so you guys hear this okay if you can
all right um
if you got the patience for a second
meditation okay
does help some people with small bouts
of anxiety like
small bouts of of of anxiousness or
anxiety okay
and it does and that's why i love
meditations but for the most
majority of people suffering from
anxiety
they can't meditate they if they sit
there
and they focus on their breathing they
go into panic attack
because their nerves are inflamed and
nobody knows so then somebody be like oh
you're just
you're just too you can't do it you
can't you can't focus
you can't do that you know um there's
miranda kerr right there
flynn says hi tell flynn i said hey
miranda kurds
awesome friend of mine she's the best
she's uh on there great to see you
tonight
incredible um definitely i said hi and i
love him
and um so you know it's amazing how it
works and our phrenic nerve
our vagus nerve all three of those
nerves they
light up so when you're trying to do
your meditations it's difficult
90 of people with anxiety
like real anxiety issues not just
calling it anxiety
and it's not but real anxiety issues
can't meditate
they can't do breath work because it'll
throw them into a panic
it'll increase their anxiety they're
really struggling and i'm going to go
over the different levels of it
that's why band-aids like meditation and
band-aids like breath work
are great and they're great and i and i
always for years
40 years have been saying definitely do
those and i even have meditations i talk
about in the books and and i'm going to
put out more too
in the future but the point is is we got
to get down to the
bottom of why somebody's crippling
anxiety their throat tightens their
chest tightens they can't breathe
they go into you know spasms they go
into panic
they can't sleep their mind is racing
their thoughts are racing
they're you know really struggling all
of that so
you know it just it it matters to know
this information
this is about taking control over your
life samantha says thank you for all
your information i'm very grateful i'm
grateful you're here thank you for being
here
and i'm proud of you for anything you're
doing and applying anything i'm so proud
of you
and um okay look so
so lending the height the light says
definitely can't meditate and i can't
breathe
so you totally get it right well 90 plus
percent of people suffering with any
kind of anxiety and depression but
here's the thing
that you know meditation gurus don't
know this they don't know this they
think you're just not
maybe thinking positive enough or
there's some other emotional
thing happening in you that makes it so
you can't meditate what
people don't realize in the spiritual
movement is why i got so popular back
you got to remember you guys
meditation has been around forever okay
and
and it's a helpful band-aid but it's
been around for a long time when my
office
was filled in with thousands upon
thousands of people traveling around the
world to my offices
years and years ago they tried all that
they tried retreats and meditations and
and all the different levels and unless
you know what's wrong
and how to fix it and get the right
foods in you the right tools
get the metals out get the viruses down
rebuild the neurotransmitters
rebuild the neurons unless you know how
to do that
it you know and then you don't have to
manage and manage
and you know and i'm not talking about
light anxiousness because of emotional
stress i'm not talking about that like
when somebody goes through an emotional
hard time
and they got that anxiousness and they
got that mild anxiety because they've
been through a lot and they have anxiety
you can meditate
pretty easy for the most part with that
i'm talking about
viral anxiety i'm talking about swollen
vagus nerve anxiety i'm talking about
phrenic nerve anxiety i'm talking about
neurotransmitter burnout anxiety
i'm talking about neuron burnout anxiety
it's these things and and that's why i
was so known
too was like oh my god i tried
everything but what can i do
and there's real answers that's what we
need to talk about
um
yeah okay so uh 777 trickster the
nervous system
feels unsafe which is what causes
anxiety nope that's not what causes
anxiety and
i don't think that's going to get
anybody anywhere
i mean i'm not making fun of you at all
i mean it's totally cool to feel that
way
and be like well maybe the nervous
system feels unsafe but
that doesn't make any sense you know um
but listen stay on trickster stay on and
watch the rest of this live because
we're going to cut into everything okay
and it's important to know um so you
guys
all right so let's go
somebody said this makes so much sense i
just saw that everything lemon balm is a
journey x
x oh lemon balm is a lifesaver it really
is
so let's go into this let's head into
here you guys
um so i'm ready when you guys are so
there's
emotional anxiety emotional anxiety is
is kind of like is what i call emotional
anxiety so check this out right
it's like you can't put your finger on
why you really feel this way
right you're not sure if you're happy
you're not sure if you're upset
you're not sure if you're sad you're
kind of like not sure if you get mad
you're not sure if you're really
frustrated and you get
lonely really easy like you're like
on the street walking and you feel like
lonely already and you see other people
vibing out there and you're like you
know feeling like you're missing out on
something
maybe you feel like you're missing out
on something on life maybe
you want to go do something and maybe
you want to go somewhere and you feel
like you wish you could but maybe you
can't in that moment
maybe you need to maybe you feel like
you need to be someplace else like
you're not in the right place in your
life and you need to be someplace else
right
maybe you feel all that at the same time
but yet
you also feel like you want to stay home
and you want to curl up in bed
and you want to just curl up in bed and
be in your comfy sweats and just
kind of hide away and watch your
favorite movie eat your favorite comfort
food
but yet that doesn't make you happy
either and then you feel kind of anxiety
over it you just ate your comfort food
you watched your favorite movie you got
some peace but yet you can't really find
peace
you feel like you're missing out you
want to connect with some friends you
used to know
and you're kind of all over the place
and when you do talk to a friend about
it
and they ask you what's wrong with you
you tell them that you have anxiety
you know and or they or they tell you
you have anxiety where they talk to you
and you're like talking to your friend
and your friends like i think you have
anxiety or
and you know and this is really mild and
the funny thing about this it's not
funny but
you end up it ends up leading into like
going
full force into something this type of
anxiety ends up pushing you into full
force to take care of yourself like
i'm gonna take care of myself i'm gonna
it's like i'm gonna exercise exercise
exercise exercise i'm gonna make my
smoothie bowls make my smoothie bowls
and you feel like full force into it and
you're like going full throttle and then
all of a sudden it could flip to that to
no self-care at all
where you're just all self-care because
you're feeling these feelings and you
don't know why you're feeling them and
you're
trying to get into some meditations
because you don't know why you're
feeling them
and you're trying to like explore
spiritual stuff because you don't know
why you're feeling them and then you're
pushing it full throttle and you're
exercising you're eating better
and then it flip-flops and it goes boom
into no no self-care
and you're doing nothing at all like
you're back in your sweats you're in
you're in your bed
you're depressed a little bit you're sad
you're not sure you're frustrated you
feel like you're missing
out on something and that's one very
mild version of anxiety but people have
it i totally you know
here's another mild version you can't
sit still you feel like there's just
something creeping
you know like in your body you feel like
you're you know there's something
creeping up your spine and you you can't
sit still
and you know you're just you have to
keep moving you have to keep moving and
there's that kind of anxiety where you
feel like if you slow down
and you slow down it's just you know and
it's it's all of a sudden it picks up a
little bit more
here's another version right here of
anxiety a mild one thoughts are
racing did you ever have that do you
know somebody that has the racing
thoughts anxiety
where it's like you can't control the
thoughts
they're racing it happens either when
you wake up first thing in the morning
really early
it happens right before you go to bed it
happens during the day when you're even
trying to focus you're trying to
concentrate on something
and you're just your your thoughts are
just racing
you know that's a whole other thing too
and it makes you feel upset
and uneasy inside and you can't focus on
anything else
here's another mild version of anxiety i
talk about all the time you feel like
screaming
you just you feel like screaming i know
it sounds like not a mild one
but it could be a serious version too um
but it's a mild one too when it's not
really serious where you don't scream
but you just feel like screaming you
feel like going outside and doing that
that's a mild one too
um here's a mild one too here you feel
trapped where
when someone is talking to you so you
feel
trapped when you're like someone
confronts you
someone talks to you and you start
getting a headache and you start to
sweat
and you you feel like your mouth gets
too dry and you feel like your legs are
a little bit weak
and you can't you feel like you almost
turn into like a jellyfish
or a ball of jelly why somebody's
talking to you and you're standing there
and they're talking to you and they're
draining your energy
and you feel trapped that's another form
of anxiety that happens to you out there
too you guys
let's talk about another one here's one
that you feel like jumping out of your
skin
you feel like a strange tickle inside
your body and you just want to shake it
out you know what i mean like i was just
doing this now
and you feel like you want to jump out
of your skin and at the same time
you're frustrated and you're getting
angry and you want to cry all at once i
don't know if you guys ever experienced
that so many people where
they want to cry they feel angry they
want to jump out of their skin
here's another one right here and i'm
going pretty quick you guys because
there's so much to cover so you might
want to watch this from the beginning
again
you can't sleep at night so how about
that version
you can't sleep at night where it's hard
to fall asleep because
you don't feel safe you know like when
you go to bed at night you don't feel
safe you're not
excited about tomorrow you're not
inspired about life you're not inspired
about the next day you're stressed out
about
tomorrow and you're dreaming a lot when
you're sleeping and your dreams aren't
happy ones and your dreams aren't really
that peaceful
so you're frustrated as you're dreaming
at night and you wake up but you're not
looking forward to the morning and when
you get up in the morning you kind of
wake up scared or a little spooked and
you feel
insecure about your day and you feel
insecure about what you're
what you're going through in your life
so that happens too
and just so you know a lot of people
have mixed versions of this that's what
i mean
there's no definitive one
version only anxiety and that's what it
is and everybody has the same thing
no way it is so many different varieties
you can have it mixed
all these different things so let's go
to another one the one where you can't
communicate in your numb
where your hands get sweaty your armpits
get drenched and you get kind of numb
your arms and hands get slightly numb
your temperature fluctuates where you
feel kind of a little bit of chills but
you're not too hot you're too cold
and it's that where you get cold easy
and you kind of shake
here's a moderate form of anxiety here
that i've always seen all these years
and and uh check this one out too hard
to drive in the car
you can't sit in the passenger seat you
feel like jumping kind of out of the car
you feel trapped in the car you want to
get out and the person who's driving you
is somebody that you care about or you
love
or maybe it's somebody that's annoying
you and you carpooled with somebody
but and you just feel trapped and
suffocated in a car
and every time you're like in the car
you're it becomes this phobia
where you feel claustrophobic in the car
you feel like it
gets you get confused you can't handle
over stimulation
if someone turns the radio on in the car
and they're blasting music if it's not a
song you like
it makes it worse and you get over
stimulated and you get just like oh my
god i can't handle this
somebody said yep all the above
so hammer monique says all the above
yeah totally i
i i believe you 100 and um here's
another moderate version tightness of
the chest
do you get that one too is that the one
you get to the tightness in the chest
right you get tightness in the throat
tightness in the chest um
locked up in the stomach you can get
locked up in the stomach so that's a
whole other one too
and that kind of chest tightness um that
kind of like
throat tightness tightness in the back
tightness in the shoulders a back of the
head where you get tightness in the back
of the head
that one right there you know you guys
so there's that
and so the reason why there's so many
different versions it's because you get
the viral issues the shingles the
epstein bars that nobody knows about i
talk about and cleanse the heel
and then you get the toxic heavy metals
by the way i have the heavy metal detox
smoothie right here
and you know miranda kerr who is who's
who's on watching tonight she does the
medical medium heavy metal detox movie
that's what she does and um you know i
like putting more orange juice in mine
right there is fresh squeezed orange
juice and
it's so funny because miranda puts his
fresh squeezed orange juice in there too
so anyway um this is on sale by the way
here's another version is you feel
scared
you're feeling scared but you don't know
why and your mind is trying to find out
like why am i so scared about everything
like why am i scared about life
why am i scared about anything like i i
can't handle news i can't handle someone
delivering
bad news to me which isn't even that bad
i can't handle somebody delivering
good news to me either i can't handle
someone delivering
like any kind of news and there's that
whole thing too and
um that's a hard one for a lot of people
where you just get
spooked easy your heart race is easy
every time
you think of thought and your heart
starts picking up you know and
every time someone's about to deliver
news even if it's good news
you got some like ptsd with your anxiety
all combined
and your your heart races when someone
even gives you good news and you get
scared and you get spooked easy and the
whole bit it's critical to know
what's going on it's why people who have
lyme disease have all these anxiety
symptoms because it's viruses and metals
that's what lyme disease is i've said
this all along and it's why um
that's why it's that that's a reason all
on its own so
plantar fasciitis you guys that's that's
viral and i talk you know i talk about
that in cleanse of heal too
and that's a viral issue that's that's
plantar fasciitis is mostly
epstein-barr i've seen shingles pop in a
little bit too with that one too
so tightness in the stomach that's a
different kind of anxiety i talk about
where it
locks up in your stomach it's
gut-wrenching it feels like your
stomach's flipping
where you feel like your stomach's
flipping there's that kind right there
and that's the whole
tummy problem where i can't eat i can't
eat
there's no way i can get food in here
there's no way i could put food in there
and it's all of that too look that's a
really good question right there
i love questions like this um sherry
lane
cherylin sorry how how can i
tell heavy metals are coming out with
heavy metal detox
the heavy metal detox um smoothie
right here that there's like this one
right here and the heavy metal detox
cleanse
is you improve and you improve and you
improve over time
a lot of times it's three steps up two
steps back three steps up two steps back
three steps and then you're stronger and
then you're stronger now you're doing a
whole bunch of things you didn't expect
you're even doing
and now you're pushing it hard did you
like what happens with a lot of people
you guys i'm going to lift this right
here for some reason
um
sorry some reason i'm adjusting the
whole thing there and
there so what happens is that it's three
steps up two steps back
three steps up two steps back and you
you improve
and you improve but it all depends are
you doing the heavy metal detox cleanse
where you're getting the fats low in the
morning are you doing other tools with
it
and and are you doing supplements for
your condition so do you have anxiety
what condition do you have
um um sierra lane with that's the whole
thing so it all depends are you working
with some of the supplement protocols
there's
hundreds and hundreds of different
protocols in the medical medium cleanse
the heel book
and in medical medium information so
what avenue are you customizing for
yourself
to get better and so that your heavy
metal detox smoothie works for you more
and more
and more and each person has metals in
different parts of their body they'll
have metals in different parts
of their brain and in their liver and
there's thousands of different
combinations to think about so really
important to know and
you can customize your own protocol to
get better but how you know
well you know what the same way so many
other people thousands of people know
is they get better and they're doing
their heavy metal detox movie and
they're getting their lives back
so let's talk about another moderate
version right here tightness of the
stomach i talked about before
which makes it hard to breathe shortness
of breath you feel like you can't get a
breath
in you feel like you can't breathe
there's that version
um another moderate version is short
circuit of the brain
brain fog can't think clearly you go
blank
just boom blank and you can't think
clearly
and you got the brain fog you can't
remember what you're you're talking
about
or you're trying to remember and you're
trying to bring it back and you
then you get frustrated and you just
start breaking down
there's that variety where the neurons
are short-circuiting and that that's why
i like the celery juice i don't have a
celery juice with me right now
i think someone said he doesn't even
drink celery juice even though he
what are you kidding how many times have
i showed you guys a glass of celery
juice
and or sipping celery juice um
so and then you know tongue turning
black by the way
that's metals coming out that and you
can have the tongue turning black
when metals are coming out and you can
have the tongue turning black
when you're overloaded with metals
oxidizing
without them coming out it can be both
ways
you can have met you can have the black
tongue which means you're high in heavy
metals
which means your metals are oxidizing
that's the black tongue is
okay and you can also get the black
tongue when you're pulling that stuff
out um i think somebody just asked for
how much the book is 16.99
it's a medical textbook really packed
with information
amazon.com um get it you know overseas
and stuff get it free at the library
whatever
as well too so um all right let's let's
keep on going you guys we've got more to
cover
uh let's roll
um a moderate version you wake up scared
your heart rate your heart is racing
so i don't know if you guys have that
where you wake up in the middle of the
night your heart's racing
so you wake up the middle of night your
heart's racing and you're frustrated and
you get up and now you're pacing
um that's a version right there i talk
about and you feel like you're wired
then you can't fall back to sleep
because you're spooked
and then you're spooked about everything
in the middle of the night so there's
that version right there
and there's a version you feel like you
can't be in your own skin i talked about
but a serious version of that where you
feel like you can't be in your own skin
you don't feel safe you don't want to be
alone but yet when somebody's around you
don't want to be with them either and
you're all over the place
that's a version that's really hard to
you guys are so many different
of these so i'm trying to get as much as
i can um
the panic attack the severe versions
where you get the panic attack
your chest gets so tight you feel like
you're dying
you can't walk you can't move sometimes
it puts you right on the floor
where you're laying on the floor and
you're just doubled over and you're
really struggling and suffering
and you're having that massive panic
attack right there that's a
tricky one where you feel like your
lungs don't work you feel like you can't
get a breath in or get a breath out you
feel like your chest is expanding
you feel numb in your extremities where
you're completely numb
everywhere in your body you feel like
your legs are weak
you feel like if you wanted to get up
you couldn't even get up and run
um that's inflamed nerves that's
pathogens and inflamed nerves that's
viruses and inflamed nerves right there
so that's a whole version all on its own
so i'm covering all the things i know i
didn't cover depression some
so the silly siberian said yes yes
it's not in your head by the way and
that's something to know
anxiety is not in your head even if your
thoughts are triggering it
it just means your nerves are so
hypersensitive and inflamed
from the metals and the viral issues
that yes your own thoughts can trigger
it so that's why i love positive
thoughts i love all that
of course god we need that but the point
is
is i've seen anxiety so bad positive
thoughts trigger it
that's how inflamed your nerves can get
this is all medical medium information
can't get this information anywhere else
it's why the medical medium community
grew so big over the last 35
plus years um for the chronically ill
for the chronically ill it's the largest
community and safe space for the
chronically ill if you're new here
so there's all kinds of different things
where that was the one i was talking
about where stressful thoughts can
actually make it worse
anything stressful because your nerves
are already inflamed
they're already lit up your phrenic
nerves your
your vagus nerve is already a hot spot
because it's inflamed from toxic heavy
metals
it's inflamed from pathogens and viruses
like the
like how i described earlier so when
those nerves are inflamed like that all
you gotta do is get jarred
all you need is some bad news all you
need is to think bad thoughts all you
need is to think good thoughts and
you're just now you're just feeling
anxiety you can't
and then you're trying to tell yourself
i'm okay i'm okay um or
i don't know if i'm dying and and now
you're at like different doctor's
offices looking for different
medications it's really difficult for so
many people
another version of of anxiety is you're
nauseous and you can't eat you just
can't get food down you're so nauseous
you can't get food down your family
members don't understand
nobody gets it where you know they you
got an eating disorder you got an eating
disorder
you know what's wrong with you you can't
eat meanwhile anxiety is what it is
um trisha marie 75 oh my god
you are explaining this perfectly that
is what happened to me
with the numbness afterwards um i'm
sorry you're going through that
i'm sorry you went through that it's it
breaks my heart to know that
like i care about people you know and
that's the whole thing and the more and
more i care about people and the more
and more
i want you guys better the more flack i
get out there you guys wouldn't believe
how it goes the more and more people
want to stomp me out and silence me it's
crazy
because you're really not allowed to get
people better you're just supposed to
play this game maybe some food science
game or write some
books that don't get anybody anywhere in
health and regurgitated
information you pass around over and
over again you're not allowed to get
people better and medical medium
information actually
gets people better and let me tell you
something
there's some bad people in the world
that don't want people healing
you know in the industries and medical
media information has saved
countless lives already and it pains me
to know that you actually went through
that that you're go you you went through
those symptoms and you suffered like
that
and the more and more i care and the
more and more i fight for you guys and
fight for the underdog and
in all that the more and more bs gets
put out there
stories aren't real this and that
happens paid trolls go on
oh my god the pay trolls the industries
but you know amp up those paid trolls 24
7. it's incredible
and they got every trick in the book
like oh i tried medical medium and it
didn't work oh sure
you tried it you tried the hundreds of
protocols you locked down your
customized protocol
sure you read the book but by the way
you guys over 200 symptoms and
conditions in here
and um you guys i love fighting for you
guys and i'll tell you why
okay because when i'm when i
wake up in the morning and i know so
many of you guys are suffering out there
and you've been through hell and back
and i know you can rise out of those
ashes
i know you can rise out of the ashes and
heal and move forward
and you know and i'm never gonna stop
fighting for you guys
because i know that you've been
struggling and suffering and people with
anxiety
man they're not treated good they're not
treated good
and i've seen that over and over and
over again
and you guys i'm going to cover more in
depression
one thing about depression i'll cover a
couple of minutes of depression though
with depression is the toxic heavy
metals play a really large role in
depression
and you got to get the metals out
because when the neurons are saturated
with toxic heavy metals
it weighs down the electrical impulse to
the point where your neurotransmitters
start to dehydrate they start to not get
used properly they don't ignite the
neurons
don't work right because electrical
impulses are hitting metal
and we get that deep depression and
everything and and all that and i'm
going to cover you know i'm going to go
to facebook live and i'm going to cover
depression there
so that's what we're going to do uh
miss cabral says you got me better bless
your heart for
you know what you probably worked hard
for it too with all the information
cabaret yeah um
yeah so cabrera
um
trying to look for your comment i
thought i saw it
i got two monitors here you guys it's
funny i got one with the comments on one
side one of the comments here
i'm just
i'm going over the facebook right now
i'm going to answer lots more questions
is what i'm going to do
um i'm proud of you guys seriously proud
of you all of it
um thank you anthony we live and
appreciate you in spirit of compassion
bless your heart
i'm blown away by you guys
over four years mm for life darcy lee
you're awesome
thank you anthony you helped me so much
i'm blessed to have been able to be
graced with your spiritual knowledge
i'm so beyond nick ivana nikki vianna
hey
awesome spiritual knowledge and beyond
grateful god bless you thank you viana
incredible um okay i'm going over to
facebook now you guys we got a lot more
to cover
bless your heart take care