we're live right now we're talking about
poop
there's all kinds of stuff going on with
poop you know
i posted
a few reels guys
about
poops
sinking
poops floating
and the hit the fan
like it hit the fan
people were going berserk right comments
everywhere he's wrong he doesn't know
what he's talking about don't take his
advice i always liked anthony williams
don't like him anymore because of what
he said about poop yeah he always talked
about good stuff and i believed in all
of it until he talked about poop now i
don't believe him at all i'm gonna
unfollow him
poop mania
everybody gets jazzed up about poop they
get jazzed up
they get really upset
and everything else around it and that's
what happens but we're talking about
poop and this is really important
because
we're going to talk about the digestive
tract we're going to talk about how
celery juice
fixes your digestive tract
yes
helping you have healthier poops and
we're going to talk about poops floating
we're going to talk about poop sinking
we're going to talk about what's bad
about poop what's good about poop and
what's crazy is you know you put some
information out there right everybody's
all throwing at you they're
throwing poop at you they're so mad
that's what's happening right
and they all think their don't
stink that's what's incredible every
single person health professional i'm
i've been a health professional for many
years and that's opposite of what we
have learned in medical school uh
am i missing something because
i thought
it was well known by now
that all the medical doctors that
graduate from medical school never
taught anything about like poop and food
and things like that or anything about
nutrition or anything isn't that what
everybody knew all these years because i
talked to a lot of doctors and everybody
knows that so why is all of a sudden
medical school the expert about poop
it just doesn't make any sense so we're
just going to cover a lot of little
pieces about this this is going to be a
good talk and probably really
educational
maybe fun hopefully
but you know
yeah everybody's an expert they just
google
yeah anthony's got to be wrong because i
just google it and it says no he's wrong
about poop look on google right
and
that's a funny one all on its own okay
so let's go into this let's start
talking about it we're talking about
poop right now you guys good to see you
guys if oh here's a funny one too where
is anthony ben
where's aw ben where's the medical
medium been i've been trying to finish
up my book i think i'm only one day away
from finishing it and getting the
manuscript to the publisher
thank god i'm like one day away
but i had to talk about poop i couldn't
help it i got pulled away from finishing
that last day on the book because man
those poop posts they went out of
control there's what over a thousand i
don't know a couple thousand comments of
everybody freaking out so we're gonna
have to i just dropped everything i said
you know what you know what the book's
gonna have to wait one more day
one more day because of poop
so that's just what we're gonna have to
do i got some poop in front of me
but we're also gonna and i also have
some different things in front of me too
i have some cashews
right
haha i got some chocolate here too
why do i have that here
i have some almonds here too this is
very interesting wonder why
i got some tahini here that's
interesting too all in its own hmm
almond butter
wow and some peanut butter
very interesting it's gonna be part of
our poop talk
good to see you guys coming on we're
live right now on tick tock we're live
on facebook we're live on rumble we're
live on telegram we're live on youtube
and it's awesome to see you guys i
missed you guys i haven't been live in a
long time
we're gonna have some fun so it's going
i have right here
whole bunch of comments that were on
those posts which is really fun
and we're going to cover them and talk
about them dr fong good to see you poop
pep talk is what it is indeed i'm
excited about this
i was told by my doctor
because doctors know everything right
that's why people are dying people are
sick
people are bedridden
right people have chronic illness a
whole lifetime because doctors know
everything right
oh google knows everything just google
it you could be fixed that's a good
thing you could do if you're bedridden
with a disease and you're suffering and
no one can help you why don't you just
google you'll be fixed tomorrow google
will fix everything
okay
i was told by my doctor
the absolute opposite statement with
matter what medical medium said
floating stool is a sign of not properly
digesting fats
think about the drops of oil in the
water well
here's how it works okay
you want a little bit of almond butter
which is a lot of fat in there right a
lot of fat in that almond butter okay
so let's get a little bit of almond
butter here
that almond butter should just float
shouldn't it so let's get some water up
here
well that almond butter just should
float to the top of the water shouldn't
it
right probably should float right to oh
it sunk
it's sunk
huh
seems like everybody knows what they're
talking about including every single
doctor i guess
because they're saying it's supposed to
float fat is supposed to float i'm
scratching my head right now that's
interesting why did that almond butter
sink like lead huh
all right let me put that away here
let's take some peanut butter how about
that
peanut butter really high in fat that's
right
you eat a tub of peanut butter every day
you're going to get fat you're going to
get fat real fast right
so i'm going to get some peanut butter
here right
let's get a little peanut butter here i
got some water in this cup okay
so let's put some peanut butter in here
now that peanut butter should float
right
why that peanut butter sink
i am so
darn confused everybody's telling me
that
wait a minute everybody's telling me
a poop
that floats
or mid-floats
means it's all fat and that's why it's
floating
scratching my head right here let me do
some tahini how about that
uh-huh let's do that
and this is why you shouldn't talk to aw
or you shouldn't listen to aw just
because millions of people have healed
with his books that never had a chance
to heal oh don't listen to him listen to
some dietitian right listen to a
dietitian about poop right dietitian
knows everything about poop here's some
tahini here right
tahini
with a lot of oil on it
whoa
that tahini had so much oil it was
soaking in oil
that's what that tahini was doing but
why did it sink i'm really confused here
this is really interesting so let me put
this tahini back right
let me put this
almonds are high in fat too
i think i'm going to do something else
here let me get some water here
get a little bit of this
and
i'm going to put some water right here
so you guys don't mind
okay
and
oh chocolate
cacao
cacao butter cacao fat
it's a lot of fat in there
what the hell
how did chocolate sink
how's that possible how's chocolate
sinking i thought everybody was telling
me that it's going to float to the top
so that means if your poop is filled
with
with anything
like any kind of fat it's going to float
to the top well that's funny because
guess what i talked to a lot of doctors
that actually test fat levels in poop
and they're all sinking poops
yes because everybody's beat up
digestion track screwed up digestive
system weak livers wheat pancreases and
everything else they can't break down
all their fats
so their fats end up in their stools
every day everybody out there on keto
diets or anywhere else and when they do
an actual fat exam on that stool they
find a lot of fat in that stool that's
undigested that's actually in the stool
and guess where that stool is it's sunk
at the bottom of the damn toilet and
there it is the cacao sinks just like
that
cacao did right there hey let's do
another one
let's do another one right here okay
because everybody's so smart out there
everybody's so smart oh
why are these almonds why are they
sinking to the bottom of that bowl well
almonds are sinking down to the bottom
of that bowl right there
right there they are sinking down to the
bottom of that bowl
right there all sitting at the bottom
right now there you go
right
all those almonds are sitting down at
the bottom of that bowl so let's put
that there now wait a minute let me get
some cashews in here you like cashews
huh
cashews
oh cashews are cranking high in fat
there's no question i'm going to keep
the cashews coming
see what happens is our broken digestive
tracts don't break down the fats and
proteins and so our sinks to the
bottom you see
that's what happens i love how a
thousand comments telling me that i
don't know what i'm talking about
because google says different well
that's interesting because we're going
to go to our next point which is really
important too as i keep on putting some
cashews in here we'll put some more
cashews in here too
this is fun
so let's go into these questions you
guys by the way the mm-900 right here
is on sale again
almost 72 dollars off
and this machine is one badass machine
that's all i can say i use it every
single day i juice the celery it's
saving me money food costs are going up
inflation's going up right and that
machine has been saving me money and i'm
juicing some killer celery juice that's
it omega juicers.com so that's where the
sale is omegajuicers.com
if you haven't got a juicer yet you want
a juicer that's kicking and you want to
get that celery juice in you to restore
your digestive system and start healing
right there boom you got it right
so and i'm going to do some celery juice
talk about it a little bit too missed
you guys too lolita missed you terra
appleman missed you see you guys all
coming on so let's keep on going let's
talk about poop for a little bit longer
if you guys are up for it because i'm
excited about this really
so
there are people
sick
and dying
hospital beds
are filled
all around the world with dying people
they're dying of all kinds of diseases
across the gamma
and their
sinks
are you telling me they have a healthy
even though they're dying
their shit's healthy but they're dying
i'm confused
there are nurses
helping patients go to bathroom every
single day in every hospital around this
country and globe and their is
sinking to the bottom of that toilet
so
their stool is healthy
so that dying person stools perfectly
healthy because it's sunk to the bottom
but they're going to be dead in 10 days
from some kind of disease in the
hospital
that person's stool is so healthy at the
bottom of their toilet let me just get
their stool out of the bottom of that
sick person's toilet that's dying in the
hospital it's the healthiest stool there
is
and the person's got three four diseases
and they're dying in the hospital right
now across the world
do you see how disturbingly
ironically
deranged
people are in the health movement
because they'll tell you
i'm wrong
because i'm saying a really healthy poop
should mid float and i'm going to tell
you why it should mid-float
or even float
yes you can have an unhealthy poop still
float
in rare occasions and we're going to
talk about that too
but people have to understand
that there are millions and millions and
millions of people
out there all their sinking but
they got problems galore
right
they got problems galore so that's
important to know right there so
we're covering some more of this stuff
right
um
so
here's the problem
you can have a functional medicine
doctor you can have a functional
medicine doctor right
you can have a doctor
that's telling your microbiome is
completely out of whack
you have the worst microbiome you have
all these bad different microorganisms
in here you get all these problems with
your intestinal tract
but they're sinking
how is anybody on any level any
dietitian any nutritionist any
functional medicine doctor any health
advocate any health influencer anybody
that could leave a comment
on the medical medium post and tell me
that i'm wrong
about
sinking and not being good
and not being a good thing
right
how can that be possible
okay
so that's really that's really important
right there it's all it's we're talking
about all this different stuff so let's
go i'm going to move some of these
things out of the way out of the way
here
[Applause]
and we're going to go into it a little
bit more
so
back to poop talk you guys i'm glad you
guys are coming on we're live right now
this is a really important understanding
today i think it is it's very important
for a lot of different reasons you got
functional medicine doctors all around
the world now convincing everybody that
their guts are a mess completely they
got sibo they got celiac they got all
kinds of intestinal tract disorders and
they're telling them right their
microbiomes off every bit about their
gut is off every part of their
intestinal tract is off every part of
their intestinal tract's messed up right
with all kinds of different microbiome
problems but they're sinking
and that's that's just perfect that's
just great
see
that's that that right so it's important
to know how it works so let me tell you
a little bathroom story right
i had to use a public bathroom
a while back
it was right before the whole thing of
the what we're dealing with now out
there and i use the public bathroom okay
so i was traveling
so it was a bathroom that didn't have
more than one toilet so the bathroom the
public bathroom only had one toilet
it was a small bathroom
okay it was in a restaurant
and it had one toilet and a sink
there were a few people in line i was
waiting in line okay the guy in front of
me all right was obese
and very sick
i was standing with him
and we were talking about how sick he
was he wasn't a well man he had acid
reflux he had intestinal tract disorders
he was very overweight he had ulcers he
had all kinds of different problems he
was sick so he was waiting with me as we
were standing there and finally when it
was time for him to go to bathroom and
get in there because the next person
left they flushed the toilet and left he
went into the bathroom
he sat on that toilet for quite a while
how do i know because i waited there
like this because i had to pee really
really bad and i was about to pee my
pants standing there so i was like okay
this guy has to hurry up i know he's
sitting on the toilet right now he's got
to hurry up so i'm sitting there kind of
moving around like this okay as if i was
like 10 years old or something like that
and i'm like oh my god i gotta pee
and
the guy
i hear him wash his hands in the sink
but i don't hear the toilet bowl flush
and then the guy comes out
and the smell that came out with it was
oh
my god the smell was just whoa you
know what i mean there's somebody in
back of me we were just like oh my god
but i had to go in
i had to go into the bathroom so i went
into the bathroom to urinate
and there was a really big turd sitting
in that toilet
okay
and that turd was sunk to the bottom
and he forgot to flush the toilet
and that thing sunk to the bottom
and spirit of compassion said to me that
guy has more wrong with him
his guts are a mess
all kinds of bacteria his microbes
totally all twisted backwards fungus
yeast mold in his gut
he had gallbladder problems he had
pancreatic problems he had liver
problems he had gastrointestinal
problems from his mouth to his butt hole
and
his
looked fine by any standard it was just
sitting there and it was sunk to the
bottom of the toilet
you know
it's unbelievable when people just pick
things up from google so if i say
something it's always against the grain
i always say something against the grain
and i'm always proven like right later
in a couple of years you're gonna hear
you're gonna see it somewhere else
you're gonna see somebody come out like
i'm doctor so doctor is blue
and i'm just gonna tell you we have
found out that stools are healthier when
they're mid-floating you'll see that in
two years just like i told you that
multiple sclerosis was caused by
epstein-barr 35 years of teaching people
that
and publishing it right and then science
says oh wait we think we know the
finally we think we know the cause it's
epstein-barr okay nice try he came way
too late
to the party
just like
the shingles virus is not the chickenpox
virus but you guys are all told as you
google every single day and you google
and everybody says it doctors say the
chickenpox viruses the shingles are no
they're not they're two separate viruses
and now i've been saying that for over
35 years and now
doctors are starting to say that
just like the blood draw problem right
remember the blood draw problem
aw you're wrong you're wrong don't trust
him don't take advice don't take advice
from aw whatever you do take advice from
a licensed health professional
remember when i told you they're drawing
the blood and they're killing everybody
by over drawing the blood they're
throwing the blood out or doing
something worse with the blood when you
can ask for half files or quarter vials
and guess what now
it's getting out there
i'm always proven right
always so when i talk about poop oh i
can't trust jw anymore i'm not gonna i'm
not gonna follow him let me unfollow him
because it says here on google
it says right here on google that aw is
wrong because google has all the answers
so let's go over some of the questions
we're talking about poop we're going to
do celery too if anybody just came on
here
i can't say enough about the machine you
guys know the machine the mm-900 it's at
omegajuicers.com right
and
it's a killer machine
right it's a medical device it's an
herbal extractor
and the price of food like i said six
months ago and i said a year ago you're
the price of food's gonna go up and
right got the inflation got the price of
food going up and every time i run a
celery stick through my mm-900 i'm
saving money
because it's squeezing more juice out of
the celery and i'm saving i'm buying
less celery and i told you guys about
this with the mm-900 how much i love it
it doesn't have the metal gears you know
the metal gears that are grinding
against each other so you get bits of
metal and you know what
when juicer companies with the metal
gears
try to do their like cleanup you know
like fire control like fire damage
control because it gets out about it and
they say no our metal gears never touch
each other that's insanity not only do
they touch each other they're grinding
against each other
as they're as they're grinding the food
they're also rubbing and grinding
against each other
i love how people like to do like you
know they like to do clean up like dying
out fires like that the truth is you
don't have metal gears grinding against
each other it's an incredible machine
and it's 72 dollars basically for 72 off
off omegajuicers.com
i was told by my doctor right the apple
absolute uh opposite statement floating
stool is a sign of not properly
digesting fats think about the drops of
oil in the water right
yes if you put straight oil on water it
will surface to the top
but our stools when our digestive system
isn't working has fat that's gone rancid
mixed in with protein and it sits like
lead
it sits like lead
that's what happens okay now what you'll
see is
cashews have air in them you have to
know that so there's a pocket inside a
cashew and i want to show you something
about a cashew right you see cashews
have an air pocket
air
floats the cashew you actually have to
open the cashew to let the air out
and that's that's important to know
right there
now what happens here okay
all right when you have a nut butter and
it's down here at the bottom you got all
that protein and you got all that fat
and that protein and fat is intertwined
with itself and it doesn't digest and
break down thoroughly and it sinks the
stool down to the bottom same thing with
chicken fat chicken fat
is mixed in with the protein so it's
protein and fat both combined protein
and fat goes rancid it's both combined
inside your gut and wonder each cl is
low and their digestive strength is weak
and your bile reserves are low
your food ferments
and it doesn't totally break down and
everything sinks to the bottom
that's what happens your stools sink
very important to know protein and fat
sinks to the bottom of the toilet bowl
now there's a question here that's
pretty funny right here and i just want
to make sure
i clear this up okay
all right and this is this is
interesting right here okay
so
someone says right here
floating and feeling fabulous
they feel incredible and they got a
floating stool
keep that in mind right that's something
that's very interesting all right
here's a question right here what if it
piles up so what if our poop piles up
out of the water
i'm just asking for a friend
first of all i think it's kind of funny
because
sure you're asking for a friend
no you probably are asking for a friend
uh-huh
yeah no sure you're asking for a friend
i believe that no no you probably are
asking for a friend right
sure
no yeah
no i don't know i don't know if you're
asking for a friend you probably are
what if it piles up out of the water
what happens is a lot of times people
have so much poop in them
that it's it's piling on top of each
other so
the poop will go down into the into the
toilet bowl right it'll be lodged up
maybe it'll be a hard poop and it'll be
lodged up right so the poople large will
lodge up right you'll get some poops to
lodge up or whatever and start building
up they're going to bypass the water to
the point where you're going to have
you might even have something where
you've got the tail end of the poop
which is softer
so the softer poop is higher up
okay and your intestinal tract and your
colon
so your descending colon
has softer poop in it so if you do a
really big poop or a long poop
you're gonna have softer so you might
even get a swirl on top so you might get
the harder poop is at the bottom so
that's at the bottom of your colon right
ready to come out so that actually comes
out right so you can pile that up in
your toilet to the point where your
water might only be this high
or your water might be only this high so
what's happening is your shit's just
piling up until you're out of the water
that's not floating that's just a lot of
in a toilet bowl not enough water
and it's all kind of it's basically
showing itself above the water because
it's piled up above the water right
so that's that answers that question
which is really important
okay
so someone said floating poop is not a
good poop please don't listen to this
guy
all right
well that's a funny one really okay
because
what happens is that
there are people
who get their colons cut out every day
they get six inches of colon cut out and
then they get 20 inches of colon cut out
now they get more inches of colon in in
small intestinal then they get their
elio sql removed right
now they've got the colostomy back now
they're in really big trouble now
they're getting connected now they're
they're take some people are getting
their small intestinal tract and it's
being pulled on down and they remove
their colon altogether and their
intestinal tract is being pulled already
down right to the rectum right and now
now it's just their small intestinal
tract attached to the rectum
you have to understand something this is
important
all the while all that's been happening
all those years their poop was sinking
and don't listen to me
when science of research all they got
is snip and cut snip and cut
so when you got intestinal problems
right
when you have intestinal problems
because everything just falls right out
of here let me take a look here right
all they can do is give you steroids
anti-inflammatory
dangerous pharmaceutical
anti-inflammatory steroids
antibiotics
so they can give you and then they have
to cut you then they have to remove your
intestinal tract and colon
that's all medical science and research
has for intestinal tract problems now
functional medicine doctors they they'll
they'll just say you got some microbiome
that's off
right they'll study your poop but
they'll never measure how much fats in
your poop they don't look at that
they're just looking for different
things like they're looking for mold or
something they're testing for mold right
they're testing for yeast or mold
they're looking for those things
they're trying to actually look right
so sharon says former colostomy rn here
so many people getting colostomies
saddest job i've ever had and sharon
all those people
their
was sinking to the bottom of the
toilet now let's get something straight
so nobody's having poop fear i don't
want poop fear happening here it's okay
if your poop sits at the bottom of the
toilet i never said it was a terrible
thing
you can be eating the healthiest diet
and it'll sit at the bottom for a while
until someday it'll take a mid-flight
because everybody has compacted rancid
fat and protein still lining their
intestinal tracts so even when you're
eating healthy for a long time
you're going to be now breaking off
little pieces that start to wrap around
the stool little pieces of rancid fat
and protein that are intertwined all on
the inside of the intestinal tract and
it's going to wrap around it and
actually get caught up
and it's going to sink
it's not a bad thing if your poop is
sinking so that's not the big thing here
i'm not trying to say that i'm saying
but for the healthiest poops there are
keeping fats out of the diet
right
like eating all raw right
raw fruits and vegetables raw oranges
raw berries raw spinach and as you're
cleaning up your intestinal tract long
term and bananas and you're cleaning out
your intestinal tract
the stools will start to mid-float
because you've cleaned out that
intestinal tract to such a degree
and you're not bombarding your liver
with so much fat you're not overdoing it
with the avocado you're not over doing
it with the nut butters you're not over
doing it
with all the nut butters and everything
else in the tahini right and what's
happening is you're giving your liver a
break so when you go raw
and you could do it cook too it's
steamed vegetables but if you go raw and
you keep the fats out
you get cleaned out over time where now
your poops are the healthiest poops ever
because they'll start to mid-float
the mid-float and they won't smell your
poops won't smell
people's poops smell because it's
ammonia
and it's rotting putrefying protein and
rotting rancid putrefied fat and that
rotting rancid putrified fat and protein
sits and it makes a streak in the toilet
you guys know about the streak
does anybody know about the toilet
streak
you know that toilet streak
that gets in there where the turd goes
down in there and then it just streaks
and you're like whoa that's a streak at
the bottom of my toilet that's fat
and that's protein
protein sticky
and fat becomes sticky with it and
they're both sticky
so what you're seeing when you eat a
whole bunch of nut butter and it hasn't
been digested
you've eaten a whole you've eaten a
whole bunch of nut butter
and it hasn't been digested
it creates a streak at the bottom of the
toilet
not only does your poop
sink
but you left a streak
as well
same thing with avocado
have a avocado
the fat
gets trapped inside the rest of the
debris in the stool
yes you you do absorb some of the
avocado yes you absorb some of the nut
butters and yes you absorb some of the
tahini and yes you absorb some of the
peanut butter and yes you do
but a lot of it you don't
because everybody has weak digestion
weak livers
all kinds of different food allergies
all kinds of different problems all
kinds of different issues
and their hdl is really low and what
happens is the streaks in the toilet
from their is from fat that's a fat
streak
if you took that streak in the toilet
and actually cleaned it out and ran a
test on it
it would be mostly fat and protein
and it's undigested it's not digested
it's not broken down properly it's all
rancid and that's the streak in your
toilet bowl
if you read the comments you'll see that
people had a field day on that one and
they were trying to rip me apart
and i thought it was you know
i thought it was fine i thought it was
great i want people to actually be i
want them to be challenged
right
in the sense where they so they could
learn right
and but you don't see really people say
you know what he could be right because
you're right because all they do is cut
people's guts right out all they do is
just remove everybody's colons and
everything i never thought about it you
know you know aw you might be right that
people with colitis crohn's ibs people
with sibo all their sinks to the
bottom so why am i saying it's a healthy
when literally these people are
suffering i know people that literally
all these years they're walking around
like this they're hurting they're
bloating and distention and their poop
sink down to the bottom of the toilet
but google's right
so let's talk about you know let's talk
about how it works a little bit more
we're going into this you guys
this is a fun show for me because i
haven't seen you guys in a while and
it's really great to see you guys i'm
glad i'm here
right
listen from natasha says this
information is golden helping so many
people thank you so much for you in
spirit of compassion i'm honored you're
here
truly
you know and i was looking at some of
these other
other questions which is interesting
someone said i thought it could also
mean you have a lot of gas in your bm
for it to float like all the gas in your
digestion is causing it to float right
so here's how it works
when you truly
absorb all the fat out of your food and
you truly absorb
all of it out of your food and your
protein you absorb and utilize when you
absorb and utilize your protein and fat
your stool
is light
it's light
it's just fiber
and fiber
will float
so when you have such a sharp digestive
tract it is so strong it's lightening
fast strong too the fats get totally
used immediately
the proteins get utilized and broken
down immediately
the rest of that stool is going to be
fiber and that fiber is going to come
out in a stool form and it's going to be
light and it's not going to have smell
so it'll float because it's light
it's light
it's a really important thing to know
somebody could have really bad gas and
they could have so much problem they
could sit like rotting like everything's
rotting inside of them to such a degree
that they can have an ammonia gas filled
stool that does float
right but most everybody most everybody
the ship sinks
the ship sinks in that toilet
billions of people on this planet every
morning go to bathroom and they look in
their toilet and their sinks
and they're dropping like flies they're
dying like flies right now we have
people dying like flies in the united
states everywhere and their was
thinking we have people dying everywhere
around the planet in hospitals dying at
home and their is sinking
it's really sad
right
so someone said i came to the comments
just to see if anyone else had the same
thoughts
totally backwards from what i was taught
in college
so i'm scratching my head on that one
because
what you're taught in college is all
right
all that's like
all that's correct
because that's that's a funny one there
so everything you learn in college
is ironclad
correct
everything you if you learn in college
that shingles is the is the chickenpox
virus like they'll teach in medical
college
but yet it's not they're two different
viruses and nephrologists actually are
starting to they're starting to talk
about that now two different viruses
i've been talking about 35 years how'd
that one escape it's like they're wrong
in college all the time they're wrong in
universities all the time university
studies are all hypotheses and they
change by the month and by the year
yes you were taught wrong in college
absolutely
everything
and here's what's funny
everything i teach
has been the opposite of what anybody's
known in health
and if you hear something out there that
is the same it came from medical medium
information i know you guys don't like
to hear that i know some people just
hate hearing that
but it's true
but what am i going to do
not
say what it is i've been teaching this
stuff for 35 years
and have paved the way
like on the frontier of health all these
years with so many things it's it's
actually couldn't count them there's so
many now and i was going to do a podcast
someday and show you all the things that
were published by medical medium or are
you know released by medical medium and
how they get figured out later and
proven right we're gonna do one of those
that'll be fun
but
i can't cover everything today because
we're gonna do a series on the poop
because there's so much we're gonna be
covering and talking about we're going
to cover all these questions we're going
to go into details about these questions
too
so and
very important so someone was worried
and they say great there goes my life
i'm a sinker so someone was worried
because their was sinking right so
they were like great there goes my life
no not at all it's okay if your poops
are sinking and it's okay if you're
eating healthy and your poops are
sinking
everybody on a keto diet their poops are
because it's filled with all that fat
and protein poops are sinking right so
it's okay if your poops are sinking it's
not something to fear it's not something
to be worried about it's not something
to be scared about or scared over so all
that's important to know too so let's
use some celery and that's then that's
where we're heading now it just means
you're in a work in progress your
intestinal tract is still trying to heal
your liver is still trying to heal it's
all in the process of healing and we
need to understand that that's a big
part of it all if it's in the process of
healing
then
you got to be open to that right look
someone with colitis
their poop is thinking
someone with
ibs their poop is sinking this is the
way it is right caroline barrett says
i've been but have been having problems
explosive poos cramps bloating feel
nauseous went to the doctor and he said
my bowels are blocked and wants to give
me laxatives
gabe's stool samples no results results
back you're a blessing thank you
what i what i love about celery right
it's helped so many people
gastrointestinal problems
it's it's
it's
crazy at this point how many people are
getting better from it
it's really amazing
are you making celery juice motivation
right here oh that's incredible this
strengthens the hydrochloric acid so we
have to understand what that is
so your stomach
right
your stomach
that's where your hcl is produced right
there everybody has a stomach you guys
you have a stomach
just so you know
that stomach has stomach glands
so there's tiny stomach lands inside
here that's what proves produces your
hcl is those stomach glands that's
really important to know right
because
your stomach lands
they weaken over the years and they get
shot
everybody walks around and their stomach
glands are just obliterated they're like
they're damaged
people have annihilated stomach glands
where they're not even working anymore
their hydrochloric acid is non-existent
they're not digesting their proteins
they're not digesting their fats and
their poops are sinking to the bottom of
the toilet it's fine but you can start
getting your hcl stronger and you can
start getting your liver stronger you
can start getting your stomach land
stronger and your poops can still sink
because you're not all the way there yet
but you're gonna get all the way there
yet
right
celery juice
kills the bad bacteria
that's another thing too
right the reason why people have all
this bad bacteria thriving in their
intestinal tract it's feeding off of
rotting protein and rotting rancid fat
that's what it's feeding off of
keep that in mind it's really important
too right
the juicer link is in the bio you got
bio you guys in the bile the juicer link
is in the bile
it's it's in the bio right there you
guys the mm-900 hds
what i love about the hds you guys know
right you guys have it is you squeeze
more celery juice
out
you squeeze more celery juice you have a
smaller food bill right
you have a smaller food bill and that's
what's really cool about it juicing is
not a joke
it literally is a life-saving tool a
life-saving tool
i can't tell you how many times a
cucumber juice which you can juice in
here a cucumber juice has brought a
fever down for children all through the
years
i can't tell you how many times a celery
juice has neutralized acids and has
stopped somebody from aging and is made
so their cramping and their gas problems
went away right i work with omega you
guys know that
i endorse a mega i endorse this
it's an incredible juicer
right people are always asking me what
do you use for a juicer
how do you use celery i still see it
every day so i have to do these once in
a while right the sales on it's almost
72 off right now so it was 72 off on
this juicer so you go to megajuicers.com
it's almost 72 off
incredible really is it's the mm-900 hds
just so you know that it's their celery
juicer model so make sure you know that
it's your celery juicer model
it's almost um 72 off incredible
so yeah
it'll juice anything
when you're juicing all kinds of
different things take your celery juice
cap off
i keep my celery juice cap on there when
i put greens through here you can take
your celery juice cap off when you're
juicing other things
tatar says
best juicer saves me so much money was
worth every cent
it has saved me so much money it really
has
santara yeah thank you for for letting
everybody know incredible
yeah
mary allison says i have an omega juicer
it doesn't look like that it's probably
not the mm-900
hds
[Music]
thank you for sharing your hearing
healing story santara really appreciate
it
really good
on ig your healing story on on instagram
i really appreciate that i saw that
and i really appreciate that i really do
i want to give shout outs to like
everybody
uma kali
hey uma
umakali your videos
they crack me up
[Laughter]
they really do they crack me up
and i appreciate the videos that you put
out like educating people about medical
medium information
i really appreciate it
thank you uma
so i got some celery juice right here so
i like to strain it
right
you got to think about it right
now remember i mean when we eat food we
just forget we have the stomach even
though we know it's there but we don't
know what's there you can't see it you
just eat and you're like okay let's just
move on but inside that stomach the
minute something falls in that stomach
so let's get some nuts or something so
let's do that
let's get some almonds
the minute you eat something and those
almonds
end up in the stomach right so they go
down and they end up in the stomach so
i'm putting some almonds in the stomach
right here see so the minute that
happens
okay
these little stomach lands inside the
stomach
these little stomach glands
release gastric juice
hcl hydrochloric acid medical medium
information
says that hcl is not one acid it's seven
different assets so it's a blend science
research doesn't know that yet but just
like it always happens science of
research ends up either poaching medical
media information or discovering
something later on this medical medium
and they're going to say how hcl isn't
one acid and how it's very complex so
gastric acid that comes out of the the
glands here stomach lens is really
complex
and when that gastric acid comes out
it's supposed to break down the protein
inside that nut
so when you eat the job there for those
glands is to break down the protein but
it doesn't break it down so now these
nuts
right
start to
leave your intestinal tract
that nut just sunk down to the bottom of
the water there
look at that
interesting right
those nuts are high in fat i wonder why
they're sinking
just sinking down to the bottom you know
like
it's nuts just sink down to the bottom
unbelievable
so
we're back here
when you drink that celery juice you're
restoring those stomach glands
it strengthens that hcl and here's the
thing people don't know no one knows
this
you kill off those viruses and bacteria
each pylori gets killed off
right you kill off h pylori
so what you're doing is your hcl is your
weapon that is your anti-bug weapon
that's your critter weapon
that's your anti-critter weapon
i hear because i was using critter as
bugs i hear a bunch of people now out
there using the word critter right but
they don't say they got it from aw they
just start using it whatever
bottom line is
here it is the critters and that hcl is
your critter destroyer right there it
kills the critters
your hydrochloric acid has to rebuild
and celery juice rebuilds your
hydrochloric acid hydrochloric acid so
you can destroy the bad guys those evil
ugly critters that in your gut each
pylori e coli c diff staff streptococcus
right
food poisoning bugs salmonella
so what happens is that your hdl
destroys that so when you eat some
undercooked chicken in some restaurant
that you don't die that night instead
you just throw up and vomit and diarrhea
right you can do all three at once i
don't know throw up and vomit i guess
you can do just
one sometimes you throw up sometimes
your vomiting whatever you're hugging
the toilet
but the whole point is is that when your
hcl is strong it might be that brinker
it might stop you from getting that food
poisoning really bad that day it might
stop your h pylori from creating an
ulcer it might stop the e coli from
creating an ulcer it does even more than
that it even helps you in so many ways
when your heat shield breaks down
everything and that's important
so what i love about the
mm-900
the containers much drier
than any of the other juicers out there
that i've ever used
so that means the juice was squeezed out
the pulp is drier
and that's the whole point right so
you're just getting more out of what
you're juicing and that's what i love
about the 900
carly says juicer is the best one i ever
used it's worth the money
you use less celery and get more juice
aw is a godsend
incredible i love that
all right so let's strain it gotta
strain it
because it's herbal medicine
you don't
eat
the tea bag right
you don't eat the tea you don't open up
the tea is what you don't do right
so keep that in mind
so when you have your lemon balm tea or
you have some kind of tea or your
chamomile tea so you have your chamomile
tea right so you're at a restaurant are
you out there with your friends
in the restaurant after your herbs were
extracted so here you go right
you just extracted herbal medicine out
of your tea i feel like some chamomile
tea excuse me can i have some chamomile
tea here thank you yeah me and my
girlfriend to have some chemical tea
okay there it is after it's extracted
inside the tea right i'm inside the
water you drink your tea you don't sit
there and you open up the tea bag excuse
me i'm gloria i'm just gonna i'm sorry
wait i can't go yet did you pay yeah i
know i gotta hurry up and eat all this
old
tea out of this tea bag yeah don't worry
don't worry gloria i don't want to waste
this
you don't
my husband was on the liver transplant
list i have fibromyalgia and chronic
fatigue we have followed your
recommendations
we are presently on our second 369
cleanse yeah
that's so good for you my husband is now
off the transplant list
what
oh my god that's incredible
my husband is now off the transplant
list and all medications
incredible i'm feeling better than i
have in over 20 years thank you for
continuing your quest to inform all of
us despite those who are negative
we have been blinded by our institutions
those who refuse to open their minds are
the ones that will lose out tracy
vanderpool smith
i just want to say thank you for being
on here
bless your heart god bless you and your
husband truly for everything you know
you've gone through everything you're
you're you're doing on facebook over
there right you're on facebook
incredible i'm so proud of you too right
i know that's the thing but when you
look at all those comments and you read
about all those comments on the post we
did right on ig
on the the poop posts right don't listen
to that guy my dietitian says that he's
wrong this and that google this and
they'll tell you differently right and
then people are like oh i'm gonna
unfollow medical medium he was always
right before but now it takes the cakes
he's wrong
all right let's strain this celery juice
i'm not trying to crack myself up here
for some reason i do a little
hello anthony i don't have a gallbladder
how celery juice affect digestion well
there's no fat in the celery juice it's
not an overt fat
it's a herbal medicine
i i've always used that for people
without gallbladders it's very helpful
because every time i drink celery juice
i get cramps and diarrhea but i feel
better next day you feel better next day
what that is
is you're killing off these
you're killing off these guys
because there's a good chance you lost
your gallbladder because something got
in there
and created a problem like some of these
guys got in there and now you're killing
these guys you're knocking them out and
killing them off you might cramp up for
a minute because when one of these guys
dies right here one of these critters
dies inside of you because everybody's
got them in them right when one of these
critters dies
it releases a toxic poison
when one of these critters die
just so you know
and that toxic poison can cramp you up
for a second oh man i'm cramped for a
little bit but the next day i'm feeling
even better because i got rid of these
right here
these guys let's strain the juice
here we are
you want to strain it because it's just
like the tea
you don't eat the leftover tea right you
want the medicine right here okay
you want the medicine
that's what you need
very important there it is
really nice you know 28 to 32 ounces of
celery juice a boom
right there so you guys are interested
in the mm-900
it's on sale almost 72 off right now at
omegajuicers.com it's the celery juice
model it's the mm-900 hds
i work with the company i endorse this
machine okay i live by it i love it i'm
just letting you guys know i have to
stand behind this machine because if it
saves people money and it's extracting
medicine i got to get the word out i
want people better and i stand behind
all of that it's critical everybody's
asking the thing is i try not to do a
lot of celery juice
um
you know celery juice days like this
it's just that it builds up you guys
because you know we get thousands of
thousand thousand thousand cm's and
everybody's like sorry you started you
started just
like okay when are you gonna do the next
live i wanna i wanna see the machine it
doesn't work does it not work whatever
so it's just it's endless what do you do
what do you use so
you know if you guys have a machine i'm
sorry i have to actually put you through
that but it's for the people that are
like trying to figure it out bless your
hearts for hanging in there
and
so yeah
i bought three of these juicers for
ourselves and our parents amazing get
the parents on the celery juice that is
the best thing you can do
get the folks on celery juice
i mean i have like
like world famous doctors calling me up
and being like can you get on the phone
with one of my my family members i want
to get them on celery juice and you'll
convince them so i got like i'm gonna
get on the phone be like
yes
yes nana
nana you gotta be on the celery juice
it's very very good for you and she'll
be like well i can only drink four
ounces in the morning that's okay
drink four ounces we gotta do it it's
gonna be good
the celery juice from the store
effective good question sarah
if it's juiced fresh
did someone juice it in the store did
they actually run it through a juicer at
one point and put it on the shelf saying
only good for like one day because it's
freshly juiced or
is it in a bottle saying it's fresh and
they're lying to you
they're lying
it's in a bottle and it's called high
pressure pasteurization high pressure
pasteurization and what that is hpp is
that is screwing people over so when you
buy hpp and you go up there like i want
to buy that celery juice oh that looks
like fresh raw celery juice let me buy
that off the shelf and it's hpp
you just got ripped off it's not going
to work as good not even a fraction is
good with celery juice it can't be
pasteurized and it'll say raw and it
will say unpasteurized but that's not
true hpp's high pressure pasteurization
that's important to know everybody ask
about that all the time
you guys i have like one day
i think one day left to try to finish
the book
from spirit of compassion a manuscript
that i'm handing into the publisher i'm
hoping i'm handing in to the publisher
the next day or two
i'm i'm praying praying to god okay i
can hand it in
and
but
cleans a heel
that right there
is
is a book that's saving lives around the
world so if you're interested in
guidance
about everything out of the sun cleanses
all of it make sure you have cleanse to
heal i'm going to be doing a cleanse
coming up pretty soon i think i'm going
to try to do it next week i don't know
i'm not sure you can get the book free
at the library too it's also amazon.com
16.99 it's 51 off
amazon.amazon.com us right
i'm going to try to do a cleanse and i
think i'm going to try to do it for this
weekend and we're going to do
one of the cleanses from the medical
medium but we might do the heavy metal
detox cleanse
or we might do the the morning cleanse
maybe we'll do the morning cleanse so
i'm not sure it might be the morning
cleanse so just get ready for that it's
a free cleanse free free free
love it
gotta be free
get the book of the library if you can't
buy the book
16. amazon.com if you can't buy the book
you don't have the 16
book i think it's like retail 35 dollars
it's on sale for 16 if you can't buy it
go to the library get it free at the
library
it's important i know people have been
asking questions about the dogs and back
of me it's starting to build up again
and build up again and they're like why
why why is the dogs
i can't watch that guy he's got dogs
why's he got stuffed dogs everywhere
like why is he doing that
why does he have the dogs everywhere
like what's up with that
why is the other dogs
cause everybody's asking it's just it's
crazy how they're saying it's like why
is he doing that tell you why because
is there a new study is there a new
study hey is there a new study hey you
guys there's a new study there's a new
study hey guys we're all dogs world dogs
dying here we're waiting for a bone
we're waiting for our science and
research to cure us his science and
research is going to cure us they know
everything science of research knew
everything here's the study there's a
new study there's a new study coming
here's the new study here it is ready
ready
green tea
is really good for me
and it can fix me
but i'm dying i'm dying green tea is not
fixing me i've got all kinds of problems
i'm bedridden i don't feel good my bones
hurt my body hurts my doctor says i only
have a year to live we're not we're all
waiting for a bone science research
savings saving say hey a universal study
a university study oh my god they're so
smart in the universities which
university is it hey it's the university
star university quick the student should
release they found a new antioxidant in
chocolate
we should eat more chocolate
they're saying is chocolate good for us
are bad for us they're saying it's good
for us
we're dying here my puppies are dying
all kinds of diseases where dogs waiting
for a bone
well couldn't help myself
told everybody i wouldn't do that
we're going to
i love you guys
tik tok we're turning tick tock back on
telegram we're turning telegram back on
we're turning tick tock back on return
telegram program back on we're gonna
have fun
on ig i'm just letting you know so we're
gonna have a blast
come to ig we're gonna talk about poop
again but we're gonna have some fun
don't miss it i love you guys