everybody gets sick hospitals are filled
with sick people do you think you're
going to go through an entire life not
getting
sick no one's done it no one's done it
before out there do you think you're
going to go through an entire life and
not get sick I love this even people who
have survived right they've survived
through surgeries and different
sicknesses and all that and they get to
their 80s and they've survived with
gallbladders being removed and all kind
you know pieces of their lungs removed
right and all of that and they actually
get through to the point where they're
in their 80s and they made it that far
and they're in the late ' 80s and all of
a sudden they die and that happens it's
horrible they die and then they say well
they died of natural causes because
they're older so they say it's natural
causes meanwhile it's pathogens they
just got to them later somehow it's
viruses it's bacteria that got to them
later somehow it's toxic heavy metals
it's all the junk that's in everybody's
systems it got to them later right
pathogens if you ever walk by any place
like if you're walking down a street and
if there's a medical center or or a do
or a doctor's office or if you ever
drive by a doctor's office if you ever
drive by a
hospital what is going on is broken
immune system broken immune system
broken immune system every time I drive
by a hospital I'm like broken immune
system every single person in there
they're in there because they have a
broken immune system they got a busted
up immune system it's not function
properly you drive by a doctor's office
broken immune system you drive by a skin
doctor's office right broken immune
system you got a whole bunch of people
waiting in in the waiting room at a
dermatologist office or a skin skin
surgeon's office broken immune system
broken immune system whole bunch of
people getting different tests in a
facility a medical facility broken
immune system that's how it works and
yeah another thing too back to what I
was saying in older people they die of
pneumonia they die they get sick easy
they still get sick easy too everybody
young people old people they get sick
they get sick at some point in their
life and why it's because their immune
system isn't working good it's because
the pathogens that we're up against
that's what it is it's a big part now I
know that many of you be like well it's
stress you're not getting enough rest
you're not getting enough sleep you're
too stressed out sure all triggers
definitely you don't sleep that's a
trigger you don't get enough rest that's
a trigger you don't get enough you know
stressfree moments that's right a
trigger all those things are triggers
but triggers for the pathogens to rise
up and rise up and grow and expand and
and explode and everything I'm going to
show you guys a little bit about what it
looks like to have a broken immune
system and I'm going to talk to you guys
about a healthy immune system as well
what that looks like is is well we're
going to cover a lot of cool stuff
that's what we're here for today and so
anytime you see anybody struggling
whatever it is on the internet right on
social you know I got skin problems I
got this I got that it's because their
immune system is challenged it's all
immune system completely underestimated
completely underrated out there the
media doesn't talk about the immune
system it's really rare nowhere do you
really see the immune system talked
about enough meanwhile the reason why
you are sick is because your immune
system is not handling what it's up
against the reason why everybody is sick
is because your immune system is
struggling it's weakened it's not
functioning the way it needs to function
that is just a fact Jack that's the
bottom line right there people don't
realize out there that everything UTI
headaches this that you name it right
conjunctivitis body pain ACH a achy body
fatigue okay all these different things
people are dealing with every single day
bladder
infections everything from PID
everything from cysts and tumors and all
that immune system you name it warts
immune system there's people out there
they got warts on their hands they got
warts on their elbows they got warts on
their feet on the bottom of their feet
they got warts in all kinds of different
places immune system you catch colds you
catch flu you catch all that all that
just immune system you can talk about it
all day everything people are suffering
with one way or another it's because
their immune system is broken down you
know somebody with cancer immune system
you know somebody is struggling with any
kind of cancer diagnosis any kind of
cancer problem and they're struggling
with that immune system it's just it's
everything Lyme disease ra fibro thyroid
problems on any level immune system
something's wrong something is
struggling within your immune system
it's weakened anything like that does a
matter what it is skin problems all of
it immune system so we're talking about
the immune system I'm going to do a
little art today I am an
artist I went to Art School no I didn't
but I have a board here and I'm going to
do a little bit of drawing too I want to
show you guys some immune system stuff
and everything like that but what's
really supposed to happen you're
supposed to have a strong immune
system immune cell immun
self eat it all
up and there you go you got a nice
healthy immune cell ready for another
one no no immune cell immune
cell gobbling it all up and then you got
a healthy immune cell right there and
that's what it's supposed to do but it
doesn't always work like that instead
this is what it's like for a lot of
people right here here's what it is you
ready here it
is I've SE bar flu
RSV whatever
STP
here immune cell dead gone and then the
virus is still there the pathogen's
still there right and then all of a
sudden
again another one immune cell immune
cell coming to rescue immune cell dies
pathogen is still there what the heck is
going on that's how it work works over
and over again the pathogens stay your
immune cells die that's why people are
sick they're filling in the hospitals
fill in the doctor's office is because
their immune cells have died sure they
got some new immune cells being produced
they're coming out but they're weaken
they're
broken and they die fast and they die
easy that's how it works you got a cold
sore you got a fever blister and it's
sitting there a little too long your
immune cells are dying trying to fight
that so you got the fever
blister right it's sitting there you got
that fever blister your immune cell
comes out to get die you just lost
another one and now there it is still
you got the Simplex it's still sitting
there and then you got another immune
cell coming here coming in there to get
it boom your immune cell dies what the
heck is going on your immune cell can't
kill it it can't kill it still there for
another couple days another immune cell
coming out boom dies that's how it works
but people don't talk about that they
don't know they don't talk about it I
don't see anybody talking about it in
the health realm at all about how many
immune cells die and drop dead so fast
and get annihilated by the pathogens by
the viruses and by the
bacteria that's doing it to them and
people don't talk about it they don't
know you're in the doctor's office you
got fatigue you got fibromyalgia you got
depression whatever it is you're sick
you don't feel good immune cells are
constantly dying they're trying to fight
the bad boys your immune cells are
trying to fight the bad boys and they're
getting eaten alive and then the
pathogen stays there and the immune cell
is gone and then here it goes again you
got more pathogens now now they're
doubling now they're tripling then you
got more pathogens now you're just sick
for months you got all kinds of things
going on you're catching a cold a flu on
top of the fact that you got up SE bar
and then your immune cells come in here
and they get eaten alive again and guess
what stays there you lose lose your
immune cell and then that's what stays
there all of this and then we're up
against immune system Busters we're up
against the fragrances the toxic heavy
metals the toxic waste that we're
dealing with every day the pesticides
the herbicides everything we deal with
all day long the air fresheners and all
the other stuff and the detergents the
fabric softeners and all that stuff and
it's just weakening their immune system
even more every single day cologne
weakens the immune system it does so
your immune cells they can't can't
battle all of this so okay someone hey
look you know I've been sick on and off
for 5 years do you know how many immune
cells died in five years I've been sick
for like three years now I got fatigue I
got this i got this neurological symptom
I don't feel good I got all kinds of
issues I've been diagnosed with Ms or
diagnosed with fibro and diagnosed with
chronic fatigue syndrome diagnosed with
Lyme disease whatever it is all kinds of
things that I have do you know how many
immune cells died trying to fight those
pathogens
how many of them disappeared and got
annihilated boom gone pathogens just
took over still sick you got a liver
full of pathogens you got a spleen full
of pathogens you got like a thyroid full
of pathogens that's what people have
they got thyroid problems forever
they're taking thyroid medications they
got the hypothyroidism they got the
hyperthyroidism they're strugg like the
graves you name it they got the Epstein
bar sitting inside their thyroid and
guess what you got your immune cells
going there all the time and they're
trying to fight it and they're dying
they're going bye-bye but guess what the
bugs still stay there in the thyroid the
bugs still stay there in the liver the
bugs still stay there wherever and
that's how it
works
sobering really really really
sobering is what it is I mean very
important does the immune system get
smarter if we're eating better well our
immune system doesn't get smarter if
we're eating this kind of stuff right
here I'm just going to have a piece of
cheese that'll fix my immune system let
me go and have lots of cheese there's a
here's a a whole a slice of Bree nice
aged Brie right there and we got the
pecarina Romano we got parmesan Rano and
we got all the nice cheeses so great to
put on our dishes our immune system
doesn't get smarter when we're dealing
with things like this this feeds the
bugs even more I've been talking about
that for years when we give our immune
cells though phytochemicals that they
need they get stronger when we feed our
immune cells what they need they get
stronger this does not get your immune
system stronger this right here doesn't
I no people love their eggs the amount
of crap I get because of eggs the amount
of crap there's that's one of the
reasons why there's so many haters
there's so many haters there's so many
of them for medical medium haters
because they've been so upset about
things like eggs when I talk bad about
them or say hey they feed bugs and they
feed pathogens people get upset and then
you then you just birth another hater
born another hater another hater born
another hater born but people don't
realize though this is information to
help them if your immune system is
weakened and you're on eggs it'll stay
weakened because the pathogens will keep
on feeding off the eggs I talked about
this this is not an egg show but I'm
just giving you guys a little quick
rundown on a couple of different
things guys I want to tell you something
about a product before I forget okay I
don't know if you've seen this
revolutionary have you seen this you
probably can't see it right here it's
called total immune it's by
VY okay
revolutionary I'm Downing it right now
during this flu season right here I got
my family on this right here I got my
friends on this right here right now
this is the Mullen and the time of the
highest quality potency unbelievable
this is the Mullen in time and what's
I'm noticing is the media is not talking
about how bad it is out there the media
is not talking about the white lung
anymore the media is not talking about
everybody coughing their guts out
everybody's sick right now and they're
sick with the flu they're sick with the
whatever RSV they're sick with the c and
then you got this new virus that's
blowing through right now they're
getting sick and that's what's happening
and I just called that shot back a month
ago and I call that shot two months ago
and I told you guys people are going to
be CAU coughing their guts out and sick
and totally into that long that long flu
that everybody has right now they're
getting that long flu they're getting
whacked down beaten down and it's hard
to come out of it and that's happening
to everybody right now I wanted to show
you this product right here I'll show it
to you in a little bit okay this is the
Mullen it has a little touch of zinc in
there just a little touch so what I'm
doing is I'm still taking my zinc and
taking this at the same time but it's
the Mullen and the th this is a
combination that's incredible
respiratory you name it immune system
you name it this is it right here I just
wanted to show you guys and I'm going to
show you a little bit more later but we
got a lot of work to
do and you guys know I work with them I
support those guys because the stuff is
incredible talked about that over and
over again so let's go into it a little
bit
okay all right just lost my cap so an
immune
cell okay there's an immune cell right
here okay it's supposed to be strong
it's supposed to be vibrant it's
supposed to have what I call Sun
qualities it doesn't mean getting
Sun keeps it strong getting sun is
healthy setting getting some sun is good
for you yes it's it's supportive for the
immune system definitely but what I like
to say is immune cells I like to call
having Sun quality
Sun qualities to them what I mean is a
brightness the immune cell is alive the
immune cell is vital it's strong that's
how we need to envision our CS that's
the cells we want that's the cells we
want to feed and keep strong and keep
stronger and stronger we want our immune
cells like this right here and imagine
your immune cells having blue around
them imagine your immune cells having
White white light around them and blue
light around them okay so what immune
cell is supposed to admit is energy your
immune cell is supposed to Emmit
strength and energy okay that energy is
what weakens the virus or the pathogen
on point keep this in mind all right so
here you go you
got all right I'm going to move this
over a little
bit there we
go your immune cell is supposed to be
emitting strength and energy okay that's
what it's supposed to why not just
because of its vibrancy not just because
of its
Vitality that's not just it because the
energy it adits weakens a pathogen when
the pathogen is in a certain radius of
the immune cell a certain
radius keep that in mind you got a a
pathogen coming closer to you got a
pathogen coming
closer missing all my little
markers so if you got a pathogen
okay and that
pathogen that pathogen is coming near
the immune cell what's radiating off of
your immune cell is supposed to be so
strong so vital the energy coming off
stuns the pathogen that's what it's
supposed to do actually stun it to
weaken it it's kind of like a spell it
puts on the pathogen that's the key we
want our immune cells
strong so that they weaken the pathogen
when the pathogen gets close so as the
pathogen gets closer to the immune
system cell or the immune cell gets
closer to the pathogen the virus the
bacteria and so forth okay this
radiating energy you see coming off of a
strong healthy immune
cell puts the pathogen in a weak in
state like a trance so you see what I'm
doing right here when your immune cell
gets closer and closer to that pathogen
it sends out more energy frequency more
vibration
more Vitality emits from your immune
cell as that happens it starts to hit
the pathogen as you see right here on
the board see the
pathogen whether the pathogen is flu
whether the path EBV whether the
pathogen is something else is
strep
okay regardless of what it
is that energy emitting from a healthy
vital immune cell an immune cell that
was fed an immune cell that was
supported you guys this is a big deal
not an immune system not an immune cell
that was starved not an immune cell that
was broken down when you got a strong
one here's how it's supposed to work
it's supposed to disable the pathogen
and prepare it to get eaten it's a
supposed to actually weaken it so if
there's more pathogens as well say
there's another pathogen here okay
because they explode and they piperade
and they they grow and there's another
pathogen here right here
okay you can have two pathogens three
people get the flu then they get what
happens is you get the flu your immune
system weakens and your immune system
weakens from the flu and then all of a
sudden an Epstein bar shows up Epstein
bar are growing as well okay a strong
immune cell radiates a frequency and an
energy has strong vitality and what this
is right here what this barrier is
you're seeing okay this barrier is
it's a
tranquilizer for the pathogen makes it
docile makes it
sleepy makes it
weakened puts it in a trance puts it in
a spell that's your strong immune cell
right there okay as the pathogens weaken
and then they get placed in that
energetic spell you see right here the
immune cell can determine what pathogen
it's going to tackle first which one
it's going to hit right away okay and it
makes a decision because your immune
cells are smart they make a decision
there's your IM cell right there on
which one they're going to attack and
Tackle first to gobble up so this energy
that's admitting that science doesn't
know about that science is unaware of
they don't have their finger on this but
that energy that's admitting putting
those pathogens in a trance
okay allows the immune cell to determine
which pathogen which virus what
bacterium it's going to attack first and
Gobble up first because the goal is your
immune cell is trying to stay alive your
immune cell is trying to be strong and
Outlast the
bugs your immune cell does not want to
die our immune cells do not get
created in our bones in our body and
they do not get created because they
want to die fast they want to live long
they want to prosper they want to have
strength and they want to do their job
and eat up all the bad
stuff so you got your immune cell right
here that's vital it's got vitality and
strength it's admitting that frequency
it's weakening the Invaders the
pathogens it's making them docile it's
making them sleepy it's making them weak
and then the immune cell makes its break
it determines from admitting that energy
which Invader it's going to attack first
most of the time our immune cells attack
the strongest one the one that's acting
out the virus that's acting like a
problem it's not as docile it's not
getting put into a trans easy it's
radical it's a radical one
okay and that radical one is the one
that your immune cell goes after that's
what it does right here it goes after
the radical
one and it leaves the other ones in the
trance sleepy and Spellbound IND doile
and as your immune cell goes It goes to
the radical one and goes into war a
battle that's what it does and in that
battle your immune cell wants to win it
doesn't want to die and a strong immune
system stays strong and it wins and it
kills that pathogen right there and it
destroys it and once it destroys it it's
gone right and then it moves on for
another
okay see piley says where does the
immune cell get its incredible
energy we'll talk about that in a little
bit that's a great question and I want
to answer it so what happens now is you
got these other viruses and pathogens
and they're in that sleepy State the
doile state and that's where the immune
cell gains a little bit of strength
again lightens up brightens up gets
strong and then it starts attacking each
one that it knows it actually made spell
back bound it attacks each one one at a
time that it knows it made Spell bound
that's how it
works
okay but it's not always like this okay
here's what it's like out there you
drive by the hospitals you drive by the
doctor's offices I don't care if you're
10 years old 20 years old 30 years old
the the doctor's offices are filled with
them a lot lots of people young people
older people filled with lots and lots
of people they're all struggling with
their immune system because everybody
has immune system problems now here is
an immune cell right here that's your
immune
cell okay this immune cell is a little
weaker
fragmented it's got pits in it pits and
divots in it
okay that's that's what people's immune
cells look like these days right there
they look like
this a worn out tattered immune cell
that didn't even go through a lot yet
even if it's fresh off the press inside
your body that's the immune cell that
most people are walking around with
every single day it's the weakened
tattered beaten
down immune cell it's got divots and
marks in it and pits and
indentations and
inconsistencies and the cell membrane is
weak okay now when it admits strength
and admits Vitality it doesn't admit
what I was showing you before instead
it's kind of feeble it's kind of
broken parts of the cell don't even
admit anything only certain parts of the
cell will admit a little bit of strength
and a little bit of frequency okay
and so what happens is though there's
other parts of that cell this is what
people are walking around with every
single day every single day out there
they're struggling with all kinds of
immune system and health issues that's
what they're dealing with their immune
cells are tattered broken down don't
look good beaten down they got
indentations inconsistencies all of it
and so even parts of the cell Shadow so
it people don't realize as parts of that
immune system immune cell Will Shadow it
won't have have the pop it won't have
that strength coming off of it it's
fragmented it's weakened and then what
happens is you got the pathogens next
pathogens come around you're getting the
flu you're getting the RSV whatever it
is you got the EBV and you got the
pathogens going on here
right put a little fur on the
pathogens some bacterium some viruses
don't judge me on my
artistic
talents okay the radiate sorry the
energy that's admitting the
vibrations that energy field that your
immune cell is supposed to have is
weakened it doesn't put these into a
sleep mode there's not enough strength
coming off the cell and so what happens
instead is these invad ERS pick up and
they know you have a weaked immune cell
they know it they can smell it a mile
away all the different bugs
hhv6 cyega virus hsv1 hsv2
hhv7 EBV right wrong there
EBV okay
HPV and these invad haers know that the
cells are
broken so much so they don't even have
to be stealth anymore and when those
Invaders don't have to be stealth
anymore they rule the roost and you get
the Lyme disease diagnosis and then the
fibro diagnoses and then the ra and then
the sertic arthritis and then the
autoimmune diagnosis and then you get
the neurological symptoms and then you
get all the other different stuff with
it and then we live with a host of
different symptoms neurological all
kinds of of other symptoms too because
What's Happening Here is our immune
cells look like that right there
fragmented broken and weakened we can do
something about it this is about
empowering you and doing things for your
immune cells and that's what medical
meum information is all about it's all
about restoring that immune system and
restoring that immune cell and making it
strong and making it vital and
vibrant a weakened immune cell has a
problem once it admits its energy it's
already weakening itself it's not
staying strong and then it decides what
pathogen it wants to go after and a
weakened immune cell goes after the
weaker pathogen it goes after the one
that seems like the less aggressive and
the one that's the least amount of
trouble when it goes after that
pathogen like this to eat it up and to
take it out something happens as it's
doing it a stronger pathogen will come
and rage war with the weakened
cell so then we have a problem on our
hands the stronger pathogen will rage
War by going to save the other pathogen
yes viruses save
viruses but bugs save bugs bugs join
together and gang up on the immune
system bugs join together and gang up on
your organs your glands your thyroid
your liver your pancreas your spleen
your intestinal tract your brain your
heart they gang
up they smell
weakness and pathogens can even fight
each other too for the
prize sometimes you'll get a pathogen
that will not just gang up and join
another pathogen but that pathogen will
go and fight another pathogen for the
prize because it wants to take out the
immune cell why because when it eats up
the immune cell it learns information
about your immune system it digests and
gobbles up critical secret
information that your immune system
holds and harbors
intelligence and the pathogen gains from
it every time a pathogen wins a war wins
a battle against an immune cell it
gleans information and
Intel and when it does that it
strengthens it for another war and
another battle we walk around with
broken immune systems every single day
you see it out there anyone with the
problem you talk to anybody well I got
an acne problem broken immune system
well I got you know an ovarian cyst
broken immune system well I got PCOS I
get endometriosis broken immune system
well I got this and this and this and
this and it's endless it's endless and
it's not supposed to be like this it's
not supposed to be like this we're not
supposed to be this sick we're not
supposed to be a country and a world
filled with
sickness Global sickness we're not
supposed to be like
that as that immune cell gets destroyed
and eaten up and annihilated by Invaders
the
Invaders learn information in
Intel that makes it so when the next
immune cell is
born okay the next immune cell is
born there's intelligence inside the
pathogens that they're passing down two
other pathogens about what the
weaknesses were inside that immune cell
so that they don't lose the fight with
the new immune cell that's how it works
that's why people stay
sick one of the reasons why they just
stay and stay sick and 20 years of
sickness and 30 years of
sickness Chris me perspective haven't
seen you in a while that's why
everything you teach is focused on
building the immune system makes so much
sense that's why I'm screaming from the
rooftops about the immune system medical
Med information helps people's adrenals
it restores people that are dealing with
Crohn's and Colitis and gut problems it
helps people with acid reflux it helps
people with all kinds of different
conditions and symptoms but I talk about
the immune system for a reason a
reason okay and it's also why when a
immune system tools come
out I am freaking out because I'm so
excited okay and maybe you don't maybe
you don't care and you don't care about
your immune system and you don't care
about you know a product that has come
out for the immune system and it's not
your thing and that's you don't care but
somebody else might care somebody else
might care and I'm showing you right
here that product right there total
immune is critical I can't even tell you
can't even tell you enough Uma says how
come these bugs have such
intelligence because they were raised by
humans in labs they were all raised by
humans and labs in eggs they cut the top
of the egg off they inseminate the
actual pathogen inside the egg the
pathogen is raised inside the egg and
then they're able to manipulate and use
these pathogens once they come out in
experimental ways on animals and even
humans and these pathogens are smart
they gain Intel
intelligence so we got more to talk
about with
this okay and pathogens
outli people unless you break them out
break them down and beat them down and
kill them they outli people people live
a whole life of sickness because their
immune system is broken and the
pathogens are sitting there winning
until finally the person has too many
things going around too many things
going on they got this and they got this
and they got this and they got this this
and they got this and finally they get
older and or younger happens all the
time and they just go and they leave
here pathogens survive over time taking
out more and more people's immune
systems and they learn and adapt and
then we pass that pathogen along to
somebody
else cu the pathogen mutated and then we
pass that mutated pathogen on to
somebody else and that's why medical M
talks about so much other stuff
medical medium information talks about
like the toilet seats and you guys know
that intricate information in the
medical medium books right talk about
like relationships and all kinds of
different things how we pass bugs around
and that's okay if we pass bugs around
that's okay but we have to be proactive
we have to know what we're doing we have
to build up our immune system we have to
starve the pathogens of foods that the
pathogens eat we have to
starve those pathogens and I want to I
want to show you some War stuff okay a
new cell is
born every
minute a new cell is born that new cell
along with many other cells born every
single
minute is there but now it's up against
the army of bugs that have a higher
intelligence level and it kind of does
the same thing it admits some strength
out but not a lot because it's a weak
and broken cell it's got It's an immune
cell that's contaminated with toxic
heavy metals air fresheners all kinds of
different fragrances fragrance soaps
this and this all these different
chemicals you name it right it's a cell
that's already hindered already beaten
down and so it's emitting only so much
energy sometimes it'll just be like this
but not here and here so you'll have
energy coming down energy going up but
you don't have energy going here or
here all the different pathogens are
wise ER they're a day wiser they're an
immune cell smarter and so it comes down
to this again the immune cell goes
seeking out the pathogens or runs into
the pathogens it emits a tranquil lizer
a Spellbound
energy okay it emits the
energy that's what it does admits it it
even spins around the cell turns around
and turns around and turns around
like and then as it's turning
around and doing that it goes up against
the pathogens if the cell is strong
enough the cell will go for a strong
enough pathogen it'll go for a stronger
one if the cell is too weak it'll go to
a weaker one and the same thing happens
again it goes into
war and it fights for its life to save
you it might might win it might eat up
the doile the docile pathogen but then
the one that's not so docile will come
in get into it break it down and explode
it and then what you'll have is an
immune cell that just exploded and
died that's how it
works and the game goes on and goes on
and goes on every day every hour as
we're sick
that's why medical medium has been
sitting
there talking and talking and talking
about Epstein bar talking about the flu
talking about all of it all this time
that's why medical meme
information was the first to put out the
Long Haul flu the flu breaking down your
immune system then being sick for months
because of the flu and then science took
it years and years and years later and
we have that documented by the way
and so and nowadays pathogens are
getting so strong we can do all the
right things and still we struggle to
fend them off because pathogens have
gotten stronger out there and so we have
to build up the immune systems is what
we have to do we have to build our
immune systems up so let's do a little
bit more
here
you'll see a big difference when you're
using the right tools have to have the
right tools it's critical big part of it
because we can make immune cells strong
they need to be fed so let's go into
that part
next you got a brand new immune cell
okay it's
weakened it's born weak it's not
emitting a lot of power
okay but it's hungry it's
hungry our immune cells are starving for
the right
things and we put Foods in there that
are not the right
things we put eggs in there we put dairy
in there we put gluten in there we put a
whole bunch of things that I've talked
about in there we put corn in there we
put all kinds of stuff in our body and
then we do high fat high fat high fat we
fat ourselves to death and when we just
pump in the fat the all all the overt
fat we pump in because everybody that's
what their meals are it's all fat and
when they pump in all that fat we lower
the immune system more and we starve the
immune cells so what people have are
starving immune cells our immune cells
want to thrive they want
Fuel and so when you look in the medical
medium books you'll see in there all
kinds of
stuff stuff that feeds the immune
cells that's critical for it how many
times have I talked about time tea
time right the herb
time how many times have I been here
live with you guys and talked about time
I don't know so many I can't count them
where I had a whole thing of time water
and I'm putting fresh time right in
there in the water and I'm like time you
guys
time how many times have I told you
about
time
okay tools that we need and so what I
love about time is time doesn't just
feed the immune
cell it doesn't just feed the immune
cell okay it
also
inhibits the
bugs when we have immune system problems
we need things that inhibit the bad guys
not just pour and feed our immune system
Julie Tuesday 144 by the way I read your
comments all the time you're you're like
you're always just putting out some
great stuff by the way um and then Sandy
says what brand is the immune blend in
viy right
there vimergy V is in Victor i m is in
Mary E
rgy vimergy.com total immune blend
that's it right there it's time and
Mullen with a little bit of zinc the
link is in the description you have to
check this
out I am taking that every day right now
if the link is in the bio check it out
if you can
okay that's it right
there putting a little bit in here here
you go I just put two droppers right in
the shot
glass B to give me another one so what's
happening out there is women's immune
systems are lowering rapidly
that's what's happening in our
world the women on this planet are
getting sick sicker than they ever were
50 years ago sicker than they ever were
40 years
ago for the last two decades I've been
saying and even before
then that life expectancy is dropping
but they're not reporting it life
expectancy is dropping but they're not
reporting
it I have I've said this I've written it
in the books I've put it information
from s so in the books how life
expectancy is dropping but no no no
science is like we're only getting
better and better life expectancy is
getting better people are living longer
than ever before that's what they're
saying we have the technology we have
the medical technology and Kno how the
how to do we have it all people are
living longer and we should be Su we
should be proud of our
successes but it was a lot Li it was a
lie Spirit of compassion always told me
it was a lie and it was and now they're
faced with it they have no choice life
expectancy is actually dropping life
expectancy is dropping fast they know
this they have it on record and they're
still not reporting it correctly it's
dropping faster and more grave than what
they actually document it's even
dropping faster than now what they're
saying it's dropping medical me
information was right once again again
and proven right once again and that's
the thing people who they make fun of mm
info or me and they tell somebody keep
in mind that it's proven right all the
time constantly Pro way ahead of science
and research over and over again and the
life life expectancy is one of those
things right there it's a medical medium
win in the sense we're having Advanced
information so you can protect yourself
and you can look out for yourself and
not be like well you know we're living
forever I don't have to take care of
myself they're saying life expectancy is
just boo we're we're doing greater than
ever the medical world has everything
for me I could just live forever and
ever I don't need to take care of myself
that's why I call it a medical medium
win it's because when you have the
knowledge you get empowered and you can
protect yourself what an incredible
thing women's immune systems are
lowering they already have immune system
challenges during their cycle because
menstration lowers the immune system
menstration lowers the immune system by
80% 20% of the immune
system is looking after the rest of the
body why 80% of of women's immune system
is looking after the reproductive system
and when this happens you catch the flu
you catch the ebvs you catch the
simplexes you catch the hhv6 you catch
the shingles I forgot that one too you
catch them all that's how it works
people pass them around we get them we
pick them up we get the strep all of it
now we're sick with weird sinusitis and
we're sick with weird UTI we never had
and then then your acne kicks up that's
the strep all on its own during you
never noticed that women in their Cycles
they have their cycle pre-cycle post um
during cycle present cycle and post
cycle all a sudden the acne kicks
up it's like why is my acne kicking up
during my cycle because the immune
system is lowering that's why the immune
system is
lowering it's not hormones it's the
immune system lowering that's how it
goes and then shrep and pathogens kick
up and they drive up right so women are
already dealing with immune system
challenges all on their own and then
when we have pathogens plenty of them we
end up in trouble again so we have the
EBV we got that one right we got the
strep got the HH you know we got the
Herby Simplex right and the list goes on
hhv7 you'll hear a lot about that pretty
soon I've been talking about hhv7 for
years and years and years you guys are
going to hear a lot about that and then
once again you're going be like medical
M was right his information was right
never ends
okay all right so let's keep on going
because we still have more to talk about
the immune system and everything about
it it's important Sayes says yep I
always get colds around my period and
that happens to so many women they get
colds it gets flu they get pneumonia
they get bronchitis during their period
and around their period okay so we got a
brand new immune cell that brand new IM
immune cell is actually emitting lots of
energy right on different parts of it
still a little weaker on the sides but
it needs to be fed because it's starving
it's
starving I don't know if that helps you
guys I'm running starving upside down
right there the immune cells are
starving they need fuel in order to
fight they need a little bit of zinc
they need Molen they need th right they
need the
propolis the incredible
propolis that I talk about and show you
guys they need the licorice they need
the golden
seal they need things they're
hungry okay so let's go into this
now all right immune cells have to be
fed they can't exist on their own cells
need to be fed every single cell in your
body needs fuel
it needs the right trace minerals it
needs phytochemical
compounds it needs all these different
things that are in our food which is
critical I wish we only needed
food I wish we only needed food and food
only in this world that would be
incredible and we do need food and
listen a lot of people get better just
on celery juice just on one thing just
on some tools just on the healing broth
just on the spinach soup I know people
that say look I'm going to do spinach
soup for like two weeks aw I'm like
that's incredible they do spinach soup
for two weeks they don't do anything
else and they just start healing and
they start recovering right the medical
mem spinach
soup the point is is that we can do a
lot with food and we need to keep that
food going in we got to keep the bad
stuff out when we can we got to keep the
bad stuff out right we got to keep the
gluten out and all the vinegar is out
and everything else we got to keep the
bad stuff out because it it boggles down
our immune
cells but we need things that feed the
immune system friend of mine eat
something similar to this right now what
you're seeing see I don't shun my
friends just because they do
things I don't shun you know what I I
hear this all the time out there I hear
like there's all kinds of spiritual
gurus there's all kinds of like Health
gurus out there I hear about and they
they get rid of their friends that don't
do what they what they what they preach
they get rid of them they like shame
them and shun them I got friends going
back
decades and I you know and they don't do
they might do something like Vape they
might do something like eat a big old
hogy with all kinds of vinegar and
cheese on it but I don't shun them I
don't punish them and I don't judge them
it's a hard world out there hard world
but what I do do is when I run across a
friend who's eating something like this
I'll be like well that's feeding the
immune system right there they're like
what is that I'm like that's lettuce
that's lettuce that's feeding the immune
cells right there and they're like okay
what else is feeding the immune cells in
here aw I'll be like oh there's a tomato
you see that tomato right there that
tomato in your sand which is feeding the
immune cells you see that right there
and they're like all excited they're
like oh my God I can't believe it a w
this is amazing I got some stuff that's
feeding the immune cells and then I
go see that pami right there that's not
health helping the immune cells it's
just not helping you see that cheese
that prolon cheese on your hogy right
there that's feeding the bad guys
they're like what do you mean it's
feeding the bad guys that's feeding the
bad guys you see that bread right here
like Bread's good for you right bread
whole grain bread that is the gluten
it's feeding the bad guys it's not
feeding yourselves and they be like see
this right here but yeah onions I love
onions that's an onion that's feeding
your immune
cells that's feeding feting them and
strengthening them so what you have
right here is good and evil Darkness and
Light you can just all box it up and
package it up into like Darkness and
Light a spiritual war right here in a
sandwich you got some foods in here that
are trying to save you and feed your
immune cells you got some foods in here
are trying to take down your immune
cells by feeding all the pathogens it's
dark and light it's good and evil
all packed up right here in a
sandwich and our immune cells they
need support and they need things okay
so why have I always been like time time
tea time
tea because time is critical for our
immune systems and what we go through it
is one of the big ones right there and
I've been waiting waiting
for vimergy to come and outdo themselves
once again and put together something
that's so mind-blowing to me so
mindblowing and I don't care what
anybody thinks I don't care what anybody
thinks like oh there's a w with
something let me tell you something I
got my family on this I got my friends
on this and we're going we're in January
in the new year now and all I hear is
people out there like sick sick again
I'm sick I got the Mullen in here going
in me I got some time in here going in
me when I take this Mullen for the lungs
I got the time for the immune system I
got both like that is something that I'm
excited about like I'm passionate about
this I'm excited about this because more
tools that I know can feed an immune
cell and help restore it and fight the
evil the darkness the pathogens that are
out there so that we have a better
quality of life is key having a better
quality of life existing here on planet
Earth in a better frame of mind in a
better healing mode in a better
place that's what matters right there
right there so that's the total immune
blend it's got the Mullen it's got the
thyme I never doubt the Vim stuff
because they take it to the next level
and they always surprise me and they
take it to the best that you can find
out there what you won't find in here
right here okay you won't find alcohol
you won't find natural flavors but it's
not just that you won't find citric acid
it's not just that you won't find dried
herbs dried powdered herbs that have no
power in them and I see that in all the
tinctures now I see that in all the
capsule herbal powders now what you'll
find in here is a powerful potency and
extract of th and Mullen that is
mind-blowing it's right there okay I'm
just
saying and if it's something you can do
for yourself amazing if you're not in a
position to to get a bottle then maybe
someday you will but it's that
incredible I'm going to take a
shot and it tastes delicious for some
reason because you can taste the
healing um vimergy has a big sale right
now right if you get up to $200 worth of
stuff you get a free
ashwaganda you get which I take every
day I take the ashonda every single day
and you get a free D3 right there and an
ashwaganda there you
go trying to get it to
focus we're going to talk a little bit
more about this incredible
information
okay strong cells we want strong cells
let's get into that a little
bit you have it in you to have the
strongest immune cells I'm going to tell
you right now you guys you have it in
you to have the strongest immune cells
okay you do I don't care if you've been
sick for 20 years you have it in you to
have the strongest immune
cells try not to strip on that
okay when you do stuff that's critical
for your immune system when you get the
junk out like in the medical meme
information you're doing your hmds
you're doing the things you need to do
right yep verus spiritual tasting the
healing exactly Kim says what is the
name of the Bimmer product is called
total immune blend is what it
is total immune blend I'll put that
right up to
you
okay a new immune cell is
born another immune cell is
born another one is born
name them what you will they're all just
names
lymphocytes nutrifil basophils killer
cells white blood cells name them what
you want they're all just names but you
got a host of immune cells inside your
body they're all just names that some
guy came up
with right the medical industry is like
well we think we found an immune cell we
might name it let's name it okay we're
going to name that one a lymphocyte oh I
think we found it me cell again we're
going to name that one something else
they're just naming them
right I I tend to not like try to use
the names
because is that the real
name is that the real name of an immune
cell I think about that all the time
because every time I talk to S so s so
is like yeah that's some guy in a lab
that's like we're going to name that a
killer
cell so what what you have is your
immune cells right they're born
constantly and when you feed
them they strengthen and they start to
have the ability to gather more
intelligence not only are pathogens
highly
intelligent not only are bad pathogens
highly intelligent here's one right here
an EBV here's a a shingles here's a um
herpy simplex one right
here's a strep antibiotic resistant
strep not only are they
intelligent and can get more intelligent
as time goes on your immune cells can
too but the only way for your immune
cells to get smart is you have to feed
them they need
things they need
garlic they need
spirina they need things they need
tomatoes they need Apple
they need celery celery
juice and then they need potent herbs
Molin the total immune thyme the total
immune they need
zinc they need to be fed they need trace
minerals phytochemical compounds within
the
herbs and as they get
stronger and they win a battle
okay and then they win a battle against
an evil
bug and that immune cell radiate
strength and vibrancy and it weakens
that pathogen and then it wins the
battle quickly it it ascends upon that
pathogen and then eats it
up and cancels it out it now gains
intelligence back it strengthens
and it gains the intelligence
back and then it's
stronger it's smarter it goes for
another one does the same thing weakens
it crushes it and gains intelligence and
then that immune cell might lose a
battle because it's eating so many bad
boys up so many of them up that if
someone has a little too many of the
ebvs and they got four different
varieties of Epstein bar they got four
two varieties of shingles and they got
an HPV they got a ceglar virus they got
a simplex one and that immune
cell can't handle them all and
eventually burns out like a
star in the
universe and when it burns
out it
dies but in that
process it did something that you guys
don't
know you know what it did it passed down
information to other immune cells look
at
that and then those immune cells pass
down information to other immune
cells and then the war goes on and
you're winning the
war your fibro is getting better your
Lyme disease is getting better your ra
is getting better your life is getting
better whatever it is you have your
autoimmune is getting better things are
getting better your immune cells can
strengthen when they're fed the right
things they can grow and strengthen and
they can beat out the bad
guys and
that's what it's all
about right
there medical medium tools are about
destroying the bad guys cleaning out the
junk that feeds the bad guys getting rid
of the foods that feed the bad guys and
supporting your immune system and your
organs with the good stuff that's what
it's about because people walk around
with broken busted immune systems and
they're sick and they stay sick and
they're constantly flared up and they
get flared up again and then somebody
out there says go try this don't do that
and they go try it they're flared up
more and someone else is like no you
should do this and only do this only do
carnivore nothing else else and they
just be like try that and they get
sicker in six months and they like no
just eat what you want just only eat
what you want that makes you happy and
then when you're happy you heal and they
do that one and they're just like boom
then now they're sick all over again or
they'll be like do this one and do that
that one and do this one it's never
ending and mm info is about restoring
those immune cells recovering them
restoring them making them stronger
getting the intelligence Factor up on
all those immune cells so the intellect
on each immune cell is strong powerful
so admits what this is going to happen
here as I clean this board one more time
for you
guys
hello all
right how's
that
a cell is born you've been working on
your healing process for quite a while
you've been doing your celery juice your
hmds you've been using
tools you've been working on your Foods
you've been keeping out the foods that
don't serve you I'm starting to use that
term I don't like that term it's like
whatever serves you that doesn't serve
me people hear that all the time do what
serves you it's like
all of it keeping Foods out that do not
help you
okay and then a cell is born you guys
that's right Envision that cell because
that cell's inside of
you envision it and see
it a cell is born inside of you that has
Intelligence and strength in and it
wields a sword and that sword is going
to go right through those pathogens and
Destroy them the darkness and the
evil a cell is
born it's got a strength to it it's got
no indentations it's not tattered it's
got no divots in it it's got no pivots
in it
either the membrane is Juicy the me
mebrane is
strong and it admits that
frequency but it admits it everywhere
see this cuz you've been doing the work
and you've been working on yourself and
getting what you need and that strength
is admitting
everywhere and that's your immune cell
right there you have it in you it's
there and many of you have ignited those
already and you have won battles after
battles and you've gotten rid of 50
symptoms I see it on YouTube I see it in
your comment section I see it in so many
like in the comment section you guys are
leaving I read them all I read them
all and you guys are winning those
battles and your immune cell is crushing
it and destroying those Invaders and
those pathogens because you guys have
been giving your immune cells what they
need and that's your immune cell right
there that you guys are building it is
strong it is powerful it is nothing to
be messed with and when an Invader comes
around it crushes it when those Invaders
come around the evbs and the simplexes
and the shingles and the strep and maybe
you don't know any you have any of this
you're just sick then just do this then
you're sick something's in you because
you don't know maybe you didn't learn
yet and you don't know the bugs that are
in you you have no idea fine then
something is just keeping you sick
whatever it is
in your head in the sense where you're
really sick but in your head you're
thinking I don't know why I'm sick
something's doing it whatever it is that
you
believe your immune cell is strong and
it's vital and it starts to spin around
and spit around and spit around and what
happens is that it's turning and science
doesn't have that Peg they don't know
about this they don't study a cell
through its
fruition
they
don't they don't study
it from its birth because they don't
follow a cell science doesn't know how
to follow a cell they can't they don't
have the technology to follow a
cell they can't they can only they can't
follow it in the body when it's coming
out of a bone and then it's just growing
through your and it's moving through
your body they're not following it being
like there's that cell we got our eye on
it it's not like a bird that they're
watching and they put a little tag at
it's not a penguin they put a little tag
in its ear because it's
endangered and they're trying to keep an
eye on it so they send some people up
there to the Arctic and they're and
they're looking for that penguin that
actually has a little red tag in its ear
it's
fin It's
Finn I don't know penguins have ears but
keep in mind that that cell starts to
spin and it starts to rotate and it has
strength like no other and when you feed
these cells they can turn into this and
in your body you will have the strength
and it will do this and then when it
comes across these pathogens what it
does and this is incredible I'm going to
tell you right now and this is what some
of you are doing right now when you do
medical
medium I can't speak for other
modalities and other things out there
and other whatever Lifestyles or
whatever they call it out there I can't
I can't speak for all those but I can
speak for medical medium information and
when your cell gets strong and stronger
and stronger and it starts to Road
rotate it runs across all the bad bugs
right there and what it does it radiates
this powerful powerful light out of that
cell that blue light and as it radiates
out it puts everything docile everything
goes to sleep around it all your streps
all your five different strips that are
antibiotic resistant all your different
ebvs that you have all your different
shingles that you have everything it
completely puts it into a trance like
this you see this into a spell it spell
bounds it and then it goes and it
gobbles every single one of them up
that's what it does all like this that's
the cell we have it goes like this and
it gobbles every last one of them up and
it wipes it clean and then it heads down
into your liver and it does it all over
again and then you start healing on
medical medium and you start recovering
and that's what happens right
there we are up against the strongest
pathogens we've ever faced in history
they're out there now they continue to
strengthen but we don't have
to live by that Madness can take care of
ourselves do what we need for
ourselves anyway check out total immune
blend I hope you enjoyed the show it's
information from Spirit of
compassion I've been teaching on and off
for
years that I've been
messaging all these all these
years messaging to others they could
become their own experts and they can
teach
others I wish I can call myself a
teacher I want to so bad but I can't
teacher is somebody who's a researcher
and they learn through
researching and then they go and teach
it I don't learn through
researching I want to call myself a
teacher teacher bad but I can't cuz
Spirit of compassion says you're not a
teacher you're a
messenger because I'm not out there
researching I'm not out there you
know doing all that and then teaching
what I learned from the Internet or
whatever and that's a
teacher but I'm just a little old
messenger and I have to accept that and
be that CU I know people have a lot of
respect for teachers and I don't know if
they have a lot of respect for mess
so but got to be what I got to
be anyway check it out total immune
blend right
there link is in the bio I'm going to
pop a little water in here and I'm going
to send it
down bartender give me another I'll take
that have compassion for your body's
immune systems have respect for your
body's immune systems are working hard
for you they're not attacking you
they're not and that takes me to this
next place of how evil things are out
there because the industry both
alternative medicine unfortunately and
conventional medicine believe your
body's attacking itself your body's
immune system is going attacking itself
that's why everybody's getting diagnosed
with autoimmune because their immune
cells are going after their thyroids and
after their livers and after their
hearts and everything else and it's not
true it's not true it's a
theory that isn't real your immune
system loves you unconditionally it's
looking at for you build it up make it
strong tell it you love it yep Steph
over there on IG says mm please describe
what the total immune blend tastes just
tastes amazing I'm not just saying it
actually tastes really good I don't know
why but it's really potent but it
actually tastes good I just love
it love it love it love it and you guys
know you guys know I endorse this
company and I'm proud of it proud of it
and then some because you know I could
go to bed at night knowing I'm endorsing
company that puts out the best stuff
that's ever been out
there and you know what you know what's
crazy it's like companies now what
they're doing is they're trying to like
they're trying to catch up the
vimergy and but nobody knows their dirty
past citric acid natural
flavors all the different you kagene in
all the different
stuff right
um Alto Jack Tren like all this
different stuff in there alcohol all
this crap in there and all those you
guys have no idea maybe you do oh I
stand and
corrected I'm really sorry maybe you
guys do know this that all the
supplements with all the junk and
garbage in
it like all these years the stuff that's
been in there well the companies they
have to kind of morph they chameleon and
they they look at what vimer is doing
and then they start kicking out kicking
away the citric acid and they make it
look like that they've always been like
that and nobody knows the person who
goes and buys their product doesn't know
that they had this in there last year
and this in here 5 years ago and this in
here they got a dirty nasty gnarly past
and they have it in their
supplementations in their supplement
companies and what happens is nobody
realizes this and so they try to make
themselves look squeaky clean now but
they're still using glow grade stuff and
they're like oh we don't use citric acid
anymore where'd you get that from
because that's medical medum information
and citric acid is bad for you that's
been put in supplements we don't use
alcohol oh really because guess what all
the herbalist all the all through these
years say that you need alcohol in your
supplements in your in your herbal
tinctures that's medical meme info that
there's no alcohol in them anymore oh we
don't use um this that we don't use this
it's like really where'd you get that we
don't use natural flavors well how' you
learn that because it's mm info huh and
they what they try to do is they try to
emanate they try to actually copycat
like a company like Viki and then nobody
knows about the dirty past and they
think they're like so squeaky clean
clean but if they're not
link is in the bio link is in the
description go to Medical medium.com get
on to my newsletter because I got an
announcement coming up that's coming up
pretty soon remember when I told you
guys there's a chance you might be able
to to see me and maybe you don't want to
see me that's fine that's fine believe
me okay all right and but I'm going to
try to arrange a book signing in person
I've never done a book signing ever
millions of copies sold around the world
almost in every single country in the
world the medical medium
books the number one best-selling book
series in the world for for health right
almost a decade later I've never done a
book signing never did a book signing in
person I never did an official book
signing for for my publisher for hey
house um I never did a big book signing
for Hay House my publisher I don't even
talk about my publisher sure I even talk
I act I mean I just like just whatever
I'm just
like I don't even talk about that stuff
right when do I rarely say I'm a number
one New York Times a seller I rarely
ever say that kind of thing because it's
not important what's important is
getting people better who are sick
that's critical that's important the
point is I'm trying to arrange a
situation where you bring me your book
and I will with my own hand sign
it I'm trying try to arrange that
situation where yeah where I'm some
place it's probably going to be only one
place because I just I can't do I can't
go around the world gallivanting around
the world you know eating croissants
here and having a baguette here and then
doing a book signing and having an
Exquisite piece of fish here having a
beautifully made pizza in Italy here and
then doing this and then whatever and
I'm not up my ass like that the point is
is and I don't eat those things the
point is is is that sign up to my
newsletter because I'm going to make an
announcement at some point where you
bring me a medical medium
book and I'm going to sign it right
there boom and some other cool things
too with
that go to Medical medium.com
also um subscribe to my telegram please
if you can I leave personalized messages
there that hit me in the middle of the
night 1:00 in the morning and I get on
there medicalmedium.com get on my
newsletter so you guys know what's going
on
okay and
um
yeah but it's it's I don't know I call
like a bucket list thing for myself like
I never did a book
signing where I'm like I'm right here
and you're just like aw you're like a
W like I never did this like a w I got
your killer Li rescue book that saved my
life I'm like
dude dude that book looks tattered you
definitely used it and I'm like a w can
you sign it I'm like just give me that
book
man I'm going to sign it with light
because I've been talking to so and
there's got to be a way I can do this
book signing first time
ever but have S
so emanate some light like sending light
down as I'm doing
it different than the light blast and
that's what I'm trying to do it's all
about if I can withstand it because it's
intense and it's all about s so doing it
and
then that's what I'm I'm trying to do as
well anyway I have dreams I have dreams
dreams please don't break my
dreams all right you guys all
right love you check out total immune
please check it out vimergy.com link is
in the
bio um that's vimergy vi v is in Victor
i m is a Mary E RG y that is an
unbelievable
product so worth it I wanted to give you
guys an immune system informational
today because that's how pumped up I am
about this because that's what I'm
seeing I'm seeing that immune cell and
I'm seeing this feeding that immune cell
right there the time and the Mullen and
the quality of it feeding that immune
cell right there I love you guys
dearly and um please be easy on yourself