Beatrice says that he throws his scrubs
he just throws it on the floor with
blood all on the scrubs from the
patients like nesby you're not crying
are you this is day eight of the medical
medium brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge relationship breakups
stabilizer it's incredible try this shot
if you're going through any kind of
relationship turmoil you use this while
things are not going that bad either I
wish I would have known this one 15
years ago
cheers truth
it's good I love you know
Soul protection your soul which normally
resides in your brain gets projected
boom out of your body to protect you
from a certain amount of Soul injury and
that's the whole thing where someone's
like I was out of body that was an
out-of-body experience I was looking
down at myself the soul is not inside
the heart it's why in the medieval times
they focused on beheading everybody
right and there was a reason for that
everybody knew that this was the most
important area you may have heard of the
supernatural occurrence of Mike the
Headless Chicken Mike was a chicken Mike
the Headless Chicken was a chicken Mike
survived long after his head was cut off
they don't understand how a chicken can
get his head completely cut off and
still go around and eat through its neck
and live what's wrong Beatrice you look
sad here's what no one knows about how
Mike stayed alive a chicken has a soul
no that's not me saying it's Spirit of
compassion is saying a chicken has a
soul which resides in the chicken's
brain instead of floating away in The
Ether the chicken's Soul entered into
the chicken's body the soul of the
chicken gathered intelligence from the
chicken's brain and took it along with
the soul and then the Soul re-entered
into the chicken's physical body with
the intelligence of what was in the
brain
each Soul has its own free will
that's why Mike the heckless chicken
Mike's Soul had its own free will
that Free Will can determine if you're
going to be a ghost down here that Free
Will determines a huge part
of when we leave our physical body
someone asked what book this is this is
brain saver right here amazon.com us on
sale big time right now and protocols I
think I'm going to make a relationship
breakups stabilizer I'm going to get my
juicer going
all right half cup fresh or thawed
frozen strawberries half cup of tomatoes
or quarter cup of cherry tomatoes
quarter lemon peel half cup of parsley
half cup roughly chopped lettuce all
right and then we got half stock of
celery going in here
[Music]
it's incredible it hits me by like the
fourth set see what you guys think
[Music]
let me try
hmm
very strong Taste of parsley
and lemon
bitter and sour like any breakup
they have to save some
for Dr Nesbitt and his wife Beatrice is
over here Dr Nesbitt is over here too
they're having a problem so here's
What's Happening Now relationship issues
problems with relationships when
emotional injuries are repeated from any
kind of relationship that we're in an
area of the brain can basically get
electrocuted so as things get really
chaotic and really problematic the soul
projects out of the brain out of the
body
and awaits
for things to cool down and calm down
they're making up oh it's the best thing
ever Beatrice said she doesn't
appreciate Mike the Headless Chicken
story she feels that that part should
have been cut out of the medical medium
brain saver book