We're back right now talking about
angels, demons, and spiritual tools.
We're back. Tech problem behind us.
Anyway, what is a demon? We're going to
talk a little bit about that. It's
interesting. What's your favorite part
of the angels demons and spiritual
tools audio? What is your favorite part?
That's a question I wanted to ask
people.
How is it working in your life to have
this
information? Is it groundbreaking in
your life? Information, life-changing
information. I see a lot of people are
having like major profound shifts and
realizations which I had to also have
receiving this information from
SOC during the whole process. So, I had
to have a lot of realizations myself.
And just so you know, it leads to like a
hundred more
questions and I intend on trying to
answer a lot of them as we go along and
and we're doing
these. But yeah, Uma says, "The whole
book is my favorite part." Wow, that's
that's amazing. Uma, thank you for being
here. Ria says, "I have listened to the
book three times already." You know what
happens when you do that? Just
another wow hits you. It's like, "I
didn't remember that." or whoa that's
right the information so thick and dense
in there Melanie says the privilege of
knowing whoa that's really cool that
that's a really cool
part like uh healing with Ana lifech
changing Angela hi hey the I'll tell you
right now checkmate I saw a checkmate
right there wow so I'm on here I'm going
to talk a little bit about it if you
guys are okay with that angels demons
and spiritual tools art for the soul
over there on YouTube says It's lifech
changing.
Whoa.
Whoa. So, so special. So special.
Whistling. I saw that. Conrad whistling.
Sick boy says, "My favorite part is that
we can vanquish a demon that influenced
us in the past."
Haha. Yes, you can. And that's how
powerful this is. If you guys don't know
what I'm talking about and you're coming
on here, angels, demons, and spiritual
tools, you can go to Amazon, type in
medical medium, medical medium right
into Amazon right there in the books,
audiobooks, all that area. Medical
medium, angels, demons, and spiritual
tools. It's on Audible on Amazon. It's
also on
Spotify and Apple. I got a little clip
right here that's interesting. Let me
see if I could play
this. I could actually show you instead.
Me and tech do not blend well. I'm just
showing you right
here. Laura right there. I liked how you
made reference to real people and
situations occurring now. Indeed. Yeah.
Because because it's it's powerful real
information. It applies in our lives.
I'll read a little bit to just a couple
little pieces. talk about how it applies
to our life, our
lives. It's amazing how it works. You
know, you got the fallen angels. Fallen
angels are not
outnumbering God's angels, but yet
there's so many demons involved working
for the fallen angels. And not every
demon works for a fallen angel. And
there's so many demons involved that
work for the fallen
angels doing their
bidding, really tangling things up down
here. Do you know anybody that you think
might have some demons behind them? Have
you ever met anybody in your life that
you think might have some demons around
them? Have you ever met anybody in your
life that might be influenced by demons?
Like you can tell it's there it's
there's influence there. Lynn Fouch,
good to see you.
Enlightenment part is profound and now
knowing the game checkmate. Life is
shifting for me. The entire book is
golden. Listened three times and going
on the fourth. Gratitude. I'm honored.
Lyn Fouch, good to see you, by the way.
It's always great to see you. Molly over
there on IG.
Wowee. Your demons angels audio is just
blowing me away. really has helped me
grab very personal issues, grasp very
personal issues. Whoa. And you know, I
think this is how demons work. Demons
don't want you to know any of this.
That's how it goes with personal issues,
including relationships. That's a big
deal. That's a really big
deal. So, it works like this. Demons
don't want you to really know anything
because that's how the game is played.
So, we just walk around all kind of
stupid down here on planet Earth. That's
how it's supposed to go. So we end up,
you know, running into all kinds of
problems like addiction and so forth and
everything else. I mean everything from
suicide to addiction to just hardships
on on even a basic minute level.
Bullying bullying is demonic all on its
own. So we're not supposed to know
though that demons play a role in it on
any level because that would be against
what demons want because demons want
this to be secretive. They want this
information to be, you know, unheard,
unknown, so that we just go about our
business. Go about our business. Did you
read the ghost information in it? Or
read, did you hear the ghost information
in
there? That's just mind-blowing when I
think about it.
Everybody thinks anything paranormal
happening in their house or paranormal
happening in some institution or an old
school or an old hospital or something a
basement in an old hospital and they see
all this stuff happening. They think
it's just all ghosts. It's always about
ghosts. Ghosts.
Ghosts. Just a 411. Ghosts don't throw
crap. Usually don't throw crap across a
room, bang all kinds of locker cabinets,
and do all kinds of things like that.
Ghosts don't do that. Those are demons.
Demons do that. Did you get into the
whole pushpull demon thing? Did you see
that? How many people like they're
standing on the edge of the cliff? Like
a real cliff. They're standing on the
edge of a real cliff and it's deemed a
freak accident. I mean, they weren't
even too far off like the edge. They
were just like four feet away. And you
know what's crazy is I remember I
remember I saw something years ago, a
story
of this husband, this wife, they went to
this
um went to this beautiful place to
overlook some trees and some mountains,
some hills and so forth. And they were
in an area that people usually sit and
they picnic and they have they put out a
blanket and they put out a towel and
they bring a little picnic basket. They
crack open a bottle of wine and bring
out a piece of cheese or something, some
bree or something and and they're
enjoying the sight, the sightseeing and
all that and they're like 15 feet from
the edge of the cliff and all of a
sudden the woman gets up and she's
standing there and she's stretching and
she loses her footing 15 feet and all of
a sudden boom boom boom boom goes off
the cliff, goes all the way down, drops
a 100 feet, hits all kinds of branches,
gets dismembered, just everything
horrible that you could ever think of,
lands on the ground somewhere.
It's just it's like the husband didn't
push her off, you know, and you know,
it's it's crazy how that works is like
how did that happen? Freak accident.
What? A freak accident? Is that what it
is? I love when things are passed off as
freak accidents, too. It's really
empowering when you know information so
you can see more. And angels, demons,
and spiritual tools is an eye openener,
but it's like a real eye openener. So,
you're not blind, so you can actually
see what's going on.
I noticed this when you study this
information when you hear it and you
hear it more than one time. You just
keep on listening to it and you listen
to it whenever you can, right? It's like
it's like everything just starts really
opening up. You see things entirely
different. You see the world entirely
different when you're on the road and
you're driving. When you're on the road
and you're driving and there's somebody
really pissed off and angry and they
just they're like a road rager, you
know, and they're beeping behind you or
something like that or driving around
you and cutting you off or something,
you know, now like why they have they're
demonically possessed in some way or
influenced. They have they're a road
road rage, right? That's the kind of
situation where people get out of their
cars and they go and they kill somebody
else. they get out and they have a tire
iron in their hand or a gun or something
like that and they go and they shoot and
they kill somebody else on the road or
something. You know, when you see like
there's stuff like that happens every
day out there. Like it's something that
happens every single day, this road rage
thing. And then there's a lot of
innocent people that are involved with
the road rage thing. But you wonder how
it even gets to that degree. You wonder
how it gets to that
point. How did it even get to that
point? Just cuz somebody woke up on the
wrong side of the bed.
Boom. They woke up one morning, they're
cranky, they woke up on the wrong side
of the bed and something's just wrong
and now now this happens. But what you
notice when you learn this information
about how demons work. you it starts to
open up and you start seeing so many
things like how did how did that woman
fall off that cliff down 100
ft and land down there and just get
chewed up and boom just fell and got
ripped apart going down. You had hitting
branches and all kinds of things like
why would that happen? They were just
picnicking. Everything was fine. It
wasn't somebody that was feeble. they
actually were
strong and they just go off the cliff
and I just I just you know there's
another story too this one happened
recently I mean you could probably find
this one somewhere in the media friend
was telling me about this one said he
saw the story out there as like a guy
who just dove off a cliff in Hawaii
because people it's a famous spot you'll
probably know know more information
about this than me cuz I don't have the
details about the famous spot and
everything like that in Hawaii a a guy
that actually knows how to swim and
knows how to dive. Guy dives down in
there, boom, never never surfaces, just
gets washed away.
And you know, you wonder how a lot of
these things, first of all, like what
made him go and want to dive like that
anyway? Like what pushes people to do
dangerous things like bungee jumping?
What pushes somebody to bungee jump? Is
just because they want to prove
themselves and prove themselves that
they don't fear anything? And that's a
whole another thing. It's like the
challenge of fear. I don't fear this.
I'm going to jump out of that plane. I'm
going to get my license to fly a plane
and then, you know, and send all my
friends jumping out of it with
parachutes. I don't fear anything. I'm
going to go parachuting and have a
trainer treat teach me how to parachute
so I could jump out of planes. I'm going
to face my fears. Face my fears. Why
isn't this parachute opening? How come
it's not opening? Oh
[ __ ] Splat.
But basically the bottom line is this
all these things are hap but this stuff
happens every day. This isn't this one
thing. This isn't just one thing, you
know, it's one thing. It's like cave
divers. Okay. The whole thing with cave
divers. Now how many people go into
caves and they're diving and they're
going down, but they know they know
they're supposed to go back after a
third of their tank has been depleted. A
third of their tank has to be depleted.
Like it's depleted for them to go back.
But what happens is there's some kind of
adrenaline surge that happens like an
adrenaline high. But who's propelling
that adrenaline
high? The guy knows he's conscious. He
knows that he has to turn back after a
third of the tank has been depleted. 33%
of the tank is down. But he's down there
in a cave that's, you know, as narrow as
like 2 feet wide, 2 and 1/2 ft wide. And
he's down in this cave. Then he keeps on
going further and further because he's
trying to explore a new part of the cave
that hasn't been documented yet. And he
wants a big plaque, you know, with his
name on it. And then he ends up
obviously dying down there and he has a
plaque with his name on it somewhere
else. But the point is is like it's
amazing how it works. Like who what's
driving the guy? The guy looks at his
tank tank meter and he sees he's down a
third of a tank. Am I boring you guys
with this information? I'm talking about
angels, demons, and spiritual tools. You
got to listen to this original audio
audio. You can go to Spotify. You can go
to Amazon, Amazon Audible. Type in
medical medium, angels, demons, and
spiritual
tools. So, you got a guy, he's he's cave
diving. He's been down there for two
hours. He's got a third of his tank is
down. He's in some He's in some narrow
cave. He's 300 feet down. He knows if he
keeps on going, he's going to get in
trouble, but he can't help it. So, he
keeps on going. Why can't he help it?
What's telling him to keep on going?
What in his consciousness is telling him
to keep on swimming? Do you
know? Basically, he doesn't want to die.
The guy doesn't want to die, but he
keeps on
swimming. And then he's down in that
cave and he realizes, "Oh, oh [ __ ] I
went too far. Now I'm so far in, I can't
make it on the way back. So, what I need
to do is go find an air pocket. So, I'm
going to keep on swimming until I can
get to this certain part of the cave
that I heard of folklore in this cave
back 20 years ago. There was a guy in
here and he said he found an air pocket.
So, now the guy's trying to find an air
pocket. The air pocket never shows up.
He runs out of his his
oxygen. But what drove him to do that?
You know, it's another thing, too. And
it's the same thing like what drives
people to jump off of a bridge with a a
cord attached to their leg, their ankle
going for like a fun ride. Is it fun or
is it demons
like trying to get the best of
someone? I mean, I'm in a different area
now that what I'm talking about with
this angels, demons, and spiritual
tools. I'm kind of in a different area.
There's there's all kinds of stuff to
talk about, but um I'm in an area though
that's really interesting. But then it
but then it kind of goes along the freak
accident area too, like with it, the
freak accident thing, you know, and
that's a whole another thing all in its
own. So, back to what I was saying is
you got all these angels, all right? You
got God's angels, they haven't
fallen. God's angels that haven't
fallen. And then you got these angels
that have fallen. And then you got
angels that are falling. They're
falling. They're playing both sides.
They seem to think they're doing the
best for themselves. They think they're
doing the best. The mission is right.
Isn't it interesting? You know anybody
out there like in the world like humans
that do stuff like that? They're sitting
on the fence or playing both sides. You
ever find that out? Do you ever see that
out there? Are there humans that you've
met in in your day or met in your time
here on planet Earth? Do you ever met
any humans? They're they play both
sides, right? They're like loyal here a
little bit for this, but not really that
loyal. Then they're loyal here for a
little of this. They play both sides and
they think they got the game down,
right? Meanwhile, who are they fooling?
Like something like that. But what
happens is these falling
angels, they think they're doing what's
right. They think they got God's back a
little bit enough. They think they're
smarter than God. A little bit smarter
than God. The falling angels, I'm not
saying fallen falling. the falling
angels, they're a little smarter than
God. They feel like they also feel like
they're kind of like smarter than the
fallen angels that have already
fallen and they're they're in between.
They think they're smart. They think
they got it down. So that's the falling
angel. They're in the process of
falling. So that's interesting
information that came from
SOC. If you guys just got on here, I'm
talking about angels, demons, and
spiritual tools. Just go to Amazon, type
in Medical Medium Angels, Demons, and
Spiritual Tools,
Spotify,
Apple. You won't be disappointed, you
guys. Right. I
mean, I'm just going to tell you right
now, it works like this with me. When
I'm talking to SOC and getting this
information, I'm getting mind blown. I'm
not just like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah." I'm
just like,
"What? What? Oh my god." Like,
"What? I didn't know. What do you mean
there's no grim reaper? But it's a there
is kind of like a grim reaper, but
there's no grim reaper. Did you get to
that part? It's angel of soul life. Did
you get to that
part when I heard that I was just like
blown away. Blown away. I I don't even
know what to
say. Is that Rachel over there? I mean,
no. Real Chelsea Field. Hey, real
Chelsea Field. Chelsea, what are you
doing? Dear, dear, dear uh friend of
mine, beloved friend of mine, the best
audio book ever. Explanation points.
Thank you for all that amazing info. I
haven't talked to you in a little bit. I
I I'm so excited that you're listening
to it.
Wow. Thanks,
Charles. So, yeah.
Um I mean, the thing is with this
information, too, is it's really dense.
I'm just going to say it again. I have
to because you think you may may have
digested all of it or or taken it all
in, but it takes time. I mean, I know
because I can listen to it again and be
like, "What? That's right." And I
recorded it like I did the
recording. Did the
recording for Hay House my P Kate over
there. gave me the most compassion and
forgiveness I've ever been able to reach
for myself because I was doing a lot of
self-lame. I've been rebirthed. This
explains the insane injurous events. And
what happens here is here's how here's
what demons want right here. Demons want
[ __ ] to
happen. Just excuse my French. So sorry.
Demons want things to
happen and then we blame ourselves.
That's just how it works. Blame
ourselves. Oh, I wish I did this. I wish
I did that. Why didn't I do this? Why
didn't I do that? What was wrong with
me? I'm such a crappy person. I'm a bad
person. I'm a terrible person. Wait a
minute. This happened to me. Why? I must
deserve the punishment. I must be
deserving of it. I must be deserving of
all these things that happen. And we're
not taught how to protect ourselves from
demons. We're not taught about how to
protect ourselves. And interesting, you
know, you hear, okay, you got the film
industry, they talk about demons, but
it's all just [ __ ] right? Because
it's the film industry and it's just
scary movies and obviously it's not
real. So, it's all
[ __ ] And then you got demons in the
um in our civilization
language on this planet, human
civilization. You have demons in the and
they're just intertwined into the
wording like, "Oh, man, you're demonic.
Yeah, you're being demonic. You know,
wow, that person's demons are like out
of control, right? You hear things like
stuff like that. But people in the end,
I mean, what do they really know or
feel? But when you actually hear this
information and know how it works and
what it's about, like what is a demon?
And then you learn all that information,
it's just like it's like it's a whole
another whole another
level. Really
is. Aiona says, "Will us killing demons
make a difference in the spiritual war?"
I believe
so. I believe so. I
do. I
do. I think what's happening is so out
of control now. And you can see it out
there. It's so out of
control. I I mean, not a lot of people
care about people these days. It doesn't
work like the world has changed. People
really don't give a crap about people.
People can watch somebody dying in the
street and they'll just walk by. And
there's a reason for that in a lot of
ways. I mean, you know, also people are
scared like I'm not going to get
involved or something. You hear that?
But there's that's just a like what I'm
saying is that's just like one example
extreme example. People don't really
care about people much in the world
anymore. I think a lot of people are
there just people are very selfish these
days out in the world too. It's a lot of
self it's it's a big deal. Awareness
alone and not giving into demons is
going to make a difference. Awareness
about this information alone and not
giving into demons makes a huge
difference. Huge difference. That alone
can change this world. That alone can
change this world. And that's what this
information is. It's life-changing
information. It's not just for fun. It's
not for fun. This is life-changing
information. World changing
information. like
worldchanging
information, you
know.
Yeah. Kid Jordan over there on
YouTube. Bully is demonic because I've
been bullied all of my
life. I'm just kind. You know what's
interesting, Kit? Is like uh I've been
bullied. I have. I've been bullied. And
um you know
bullying it's demonic for
sure.
Bullyers either influenced by demons.
They can also be a bad person. That's a
whole another thing too. A person can be
just a shitty person, a bad person. A
person can be just that and still have
demons too.
Both. A person could be a really bad
person. No compassion. just terrible
person, only gives a crap about
themselves, you name it, everything
around it. And then have demons too on
top of it. You can have a
coldhearted, demented,
despicable, devious
person. And that's that's who they are.
That's who they are. I know in the new
age out there, it's just like, you know,
you'll hear like, "No, everybody's good.
Everybody's got good in them." How many
times have I heard that? You still hear
that out there. Everybody's got good in
them. Everybody's a good person. Really?
Not everybody's a good
person. Where do you think the demons
came
from? Where do you think they came from?
And that's the information you find in
angels, demons, and spiritual tools in
here. What is a demon? A demon was a
human. A demon is a human soul. That's
what a demon is. How did you become a
demon as a human soul? You became a
demon as a human soul because you were
one bad bad human. You don't believe
there's bad humans here and you don't
believe there's bad human souls
here and you see it every day. Death,
destruction, war, hate,
crime. I mean, you see it. You see, you
don't think there's bad people. Sure,
there's people that there's people that
try to change their ways. They make big
mistakes. Of course, they fight for it
and they try to change their ways. They
try to restore who their soul is. They
do everything they can. And they can
they can crawl out of it. But there's
people that don't they don't want to
crawl out of it. They're not they're not
looking to crawl out of it. They're not
looking to better themselves and and
heal their soul and repair their soul.
They're not looking to that. They're
looking just to wreak havoc. Wreak
havoc. Wreak havoc. Still wreak havoc.
There's people out there that do
that and it's dark and yeah, they become
a demon. If you listen to the audio,
you'll you'll see how they become a
demon. Wondering wishing over there on
YouTube says, "The audio book is a lot
of new true info. A lot for me to take
in. I take a few days off just to let it
sink in. And now on my second time
listening, it's incredible. Thank you,
SOC." and
AW. You know, I I play very little role
in this unfortunately because, you know,
I have the the privilege and the honor
to listen to SOC and I bite my lip
saying that because, you know, SOC's has
been a pain in my butt since I was four
years old. But but I do have the ability
I do have the ability to be mature about
it and be like I do, you know,
appreciate SOC to such an extent and it
is a privilege and an honor to have this
information from SOC and and so yeah,
it's life-changing and it's it's
incredible information.
Okay, so um Betsy over there on IG says,
"Literally amazed at this original
material, making everything make more
sense. Clarity on so many levels." And
that's okay, that's an interesting
comment. Thank you, Betsy. Clarity
matters. And what this does is it
creates this clarity. It provides us
clarity.
Honestly, like just I see things even
differently by having to do because
usually I'm I'm I'm deep I'm steeping
deep in the medical deep in the medical
save lives. Deep in the medical
information true true reasons why
someone's chronically sick. True
reasons. Not all the biohack crap and
the eat better books that have happened
all these decades. Not that stuff like
true reasons getting people out of
sickness and poor health and chronic
illness and getting them to heal and
bring them back rising out of the ashes.
That's what I've been buried buried
buried deep in right up to my neck right
in that for so long. And you know always
talking to spirit of compassion about
different things spiritually happening
in the world about Mars, planet Mars and
so forth and all kinds of stuff. And but
when when I really really worked on this
original audio with SOC, I I I was just
like eyes are open wider now. Now
they're open wider now. Spirit of
compassion, you always told me about
demons. You already told me about that.
Yes. You told me they're real. You told
me why. All these things. But man, when
you crack into it and you get this
information, then you're just like bing.
My eyes are like open. They're
open, you know? And they were open to a
degree before, but now
like Yeah.
Yeah. Seriously. Over there in IG
Marisol over there 144. Great number.
144. That is a number. You know how
people are like 11-11? What time is it?
11-11. You know, they they got these
numbers and stuff. That number doesn't
even touch 144. You look for that
number. 144. I lived with a narcissist
and really wished I had this knowledge
then. Wow. I understand. I understand.
However,
repeating I'm on to you would have been
part of my everyday
vocabulary. Message received. Message
received. And thank you for leaving that
comment. It matters to me. You know,
your lives matter to me. your health,
your mental state, all of it matters.
This information
um is
to offer you something. It's to offer
you something that really really makes a
difference, really matters. And I know
there's going to be a few people that
are like, "Demons, I don't want to hear
about that. It's just it's scary." Or,
you know, it's but someday someday you
might want to listen to this.
someday. It's not scary to be empowered
empowered and have the information to
help help you in your life. You don't
want to be blind. You don't want to be
blind and not be able to see in front of
you. You don't want that. You don't
because you might meet somebody and and
this information is powerful because you
can weed out demons. You can help. You
meet somebody and they got demons and
you don't know it, but you're not sure.
And then they're being they're playing
with you, but yet you think it's all
good. They're playing with you. You
think it's all good. They're playing
with you. You think it's all good. And
then finally you're just you got bit.
You got bit too much. You got bit on the
hand too many times. You're like what
the hell just happened? I got that was a
freaking roller coaster ride. What the
hell is
that? I talked about in the um in
Angels, Demons, and Spiritual Tools. I
talked about the roller coaster,
right? And I talked about the the
so-called ghost that was in the uh on
the ride. Right. The ghost that was
spotted and on the ride. Spirit of
compassion told me, "No, that was a
demon." And so I saw somebody posted
that out there. Uh a friend of mine
said, "You got to take a look at this."
I was like, "What?" And they that they
showed the roller coaster and everything
going by and they showed the demon on
the back of the cart. I was just
like, "Oh my my god." You know, I
think Cable over said, Cable said, "So
grateful you're sharing this
information, a lifeline in the
darkness." I know that people want to
live in a bubble. They want their
blinders on and they want to live in a
bubble. And I get that. And if they got
enough resources, they got enough
beautiful things in their life, enough
support, they can skate by and skate by
like that. But then something's just
gonna like something always
just an alligator always snaps its jaws
and gets somebody's foot and it just
just happens, you know? It's just it's
the world we live in. Demons love people
being naive, too. They just love that.
They love you not knowing there's
demons. They love not knowing about you.
They they love people not thinking
demons are behind anything, behind
people, behind what people are thinking,
influencing them and so forth. And
that's another thing, the free will
thing, how it it can alter somebody's
free will. How screwed up is that? When
I found that out from um spirit of
compassion, that one hit me really hard
because free will is that's ours. That's
you. That's yours. No one can touch
that. But yet, a demon can influence a
person. Kind of like making the like
creating a situation where the person
changes a choice they're making. They're
using their free will to change a choice
they're making that's not that great for
them because the demon's influencing
them. So now their free will is being
altered and shifted. Like how crazy is
that? That information is mind-blowing.
I don't care what anybody says. Hands
down, that just blew my mind open. Soul
Light over there on IG says, "I am a
therapist and this book brings therapy
to a whole new level." Wow. Wow. Wow.
That's a compliment. That's a
compliment. Truly is. over there on
IG. Okay, let's see. Mm. Family
gratitude. Because of the
audio, it takes away the fear and just
empowers our lives. You know, I got to
tell you something about that. That's
incredible because, you know,
um fear develops when you're just
getting the crap beat out of you along
the way in life, too. You know, it's
like that's how it develops, right? You
got a hot stove, the stove's on. You're
a little child, you touch the stove,
you're burned, and now you're you're
afraid of that stove, right? But we we
go through life and we get burned in all
these different areas. And that also
creates fear because like bad
relationship, boom, got burned
there. Um, you know, a bad friend, I
listened to this friend, this friend
told me to do this, we all got hurt, bad
there, right? Like you get burned,
burned there. You get burned along the
way. You know it happens in this world,
right? It just does. You know, you're
walking on a side sidewalk and there's
black ice and you can't see it and it's
20° out and you slip, you crack the back
of your head. It's like we get burned,
you know, and we go through life and we
get we get burned all the time and that
creates the fear and sometimes that fear
is good because you don't want to touch
a hot stove. You don't want to slip on
black ice. You don't.
But at the same time, we get a lot of
wounds that also get incorporated into
the fear when it's other people derived.
It's one thing to be walking down the
sidewalk alone and you just don't see it
and you slip on some black ice and you
crack the back of your head and you're
like, "Son of a gun, that was really
bad." And now you're fearing that and
you go outside and you're like, "Whoa,
I'm just black ice and me don't we don't
get along and you got to be careful."
It's one thing, right? It's another
you're walking along with a friend and
you know
and something happens, the friend shoves
you and you slip on the black ice and
now you got you get into an argument
with a friend and you slip on the black
ice and you feel like the argument with
the friend most likely involved that
that's how that freak accident happened
and you're like wait a minute and then
you start
fearing fearing different things. You
start learning and it's it's a whole
whole another thing. People have demons.
They just do. They have a they have
demons around them. And then there's
family tree derms, right? You guys, what
do you guys One thing I want to talk to
you about
is demon is not even the real word.
That's not even the real word. How crazy
is that? If you don't know what I'm
talking about, angels, demons, and
spiritual tools. Type in medical medium,
angels, demons, and spiritual tools. Go
to
Amazon. Go to Spotify. Listen to it for
free. Right? If you got Spotify in the
whole bit, listen to it for free. I
mean, everybody is pretty much listening
to it for free if they they're signed
into all those different places you can,
you know, that you stream all your
stuff.
But what's crazy about it is demon isn't
even
the real word. That's the second word
that developed through human
language where it became demon later.
Spirit of compassion told me there was
something earlier called
derms. So
derm derms and so not demons but derms.
And that's really powerful because you
don't think it's powerful but it is
because once you use that term demons
are demons like what how did you know
that? How did you know that? And and it
it gives you power. It's like true
empowerment when you know their real
name. It's It's incredible. So, right
there, you guys see this? I don't know
if you can see it right
there. Angels, Demons, and Spiritual
Tools. That's what it looks
like. So, if you get a chance, go to
Amazon, Amazon, Audible,
right,
Spotify,
Apple. Think about
it. Demons were humans.
Demons think they're smarter than
anyone. Demons think they're smarter
than the people all living their life
here on
Earth. Demons know that you don't know
that nobody knows their real name, which
is
Derms. And then when you get empowered
with that information and you have their
real name
already, boom, you just pulled out an
ace. You just pulled out an
ace. Chris over there on YouTube says,
"I was scared at first, but after I
finished reading, I feel liberated."
Incredible.
Incredible. Wendy says, "This audio was
such an eyeopener." And that's the whole
point. I
mean, you'll see things different, see
people differently. Learning this
information is beyond empowering. And
then you have tools to disempower
destrengthen demons. Is dstrengthen a
word? Drengthen
demons. You actually have the power to
do
that. And that's powerful. Elizabeth
over there says, "I've listened to the
audiobook once and I'm on my second time
listening.
Great information."
Yes, people are careless out there in
the world. Accidents happen every day
where people get hurt and injured. Are
all accidents purely human error? Or are
demonic forces involved in so much of
what we think of as bad luck, happen
stance, and freak accidents?
Demons love when something terrible
happens and someone keeps saying to
themselves, "If I only did this, if I
only did that, why wasn't I this? Why
wasn't I that?" Demons want you to take
that hit. Demons want you to go into
despair. They want you to feel hopeless,
to go to a dark place, to think that
dark place is where you belong. Demons
don't want people to know they could be
involved. They want you to feel like a
failure, to think that what happens is
your fault because you are an inadequate
person, a bad
person. And that's what demons want.
They want you thinking you're a bad
person, you're inadequate, that it's
your fault, the whole bit. Demons want
you to take the hit. It's right here.
Demons want you to go into despair. They
want you to feel hopeless, to go to a
dark place, to think that dark place is
where you belong. Yeah. And a lot of
people feel that way. They do. It's no
joke. A lot of people go into that dark
place, that rabbit hole, and they just
feel like, whoa, this is where I need to
belong. This is this is who I
am. It's terrifying. Demons don't want
people to know they could be involved.
Meaning, demons don't want people to
know that demons could be involved.
They want you to feel like a failure, to
think that what happens is your fault
because you are an inadequate person, a
bad
person. Yeah. I mean, look, accidents
happen and people make mistakes. Doesn't
mean you're a bad
person. But demons would love you to
believe that every single thing that
happens, you're just a crappy bad
person. Just that's how it works. And
and you might be saying, "That's not me.
It doesn't." And then two years from
now, you're like, "God, why did that
happen? and I'm such a terrible person.
Now I'm sick with chronic illness and
now or this and this. I must have just
did this to myself. Demons love that.
They love
that. And somebody may feel like they're
on top of the world right now. You see
it every day. I mean, it just happens.
People feel like they they're young.
They're indestructible. They think
they're on top of the world. They think
they're so smart because everything's on
the internet. You can just look up
anything. You know what I mean? There's
every app on the planet. And they just
think they're so smart. They think
they're, you know, whatever. And then
boom, eight years, you know, from now,
they're like they're they're on some
kind of addiction. They're like on some
kind of drug. They're, you know, using
shrooms every day and they're blowing
their mind out, like whatever. I mean,
I'm just this one example of a billion.
But if demons are there, they're they're
they're ready to really kind of like
steer people in a bad direction and send
them in a bad direction and everything
else.
It just happens. A lot of demonic
stuff's happening during spring break,
like this whole spring break thing that
just happened. So many different things
that have happened where people send
their kids out spring break. They just
it's like, "Okay, honey, you'll be fine.
Don't worry. Come back." And something
terrifying happens. It's every day. It's
like there's demons everywhere. You
don't think there's demons happening in
all the parties during spring break?
There's no demons there in those
parties. You know what's crazy is and
people aren't bringing their demons and
demons aren't being involved, but
alcohol and everything else, the amount
amount the amount of demons involved
just in alcohol consumption is a whole
another game all in its own. But that's
the having eyes and being able to see
and not having blinders on and having
this information is like a the next
level. It's the next level. I mean,
that's what I'm learning from Spirit of
Compassion just by getting all this
information down. And whoa, it's it's
something else. It really is. So, if you
get a chance, Angels, Demons, and
Spiritual Tools, if you get a chance,
check it out on Amazon, Audible,
Spotify, Apple, right? And you can find
it. Type in medical medium. There you
go.
Ray over there says, "My
ex-husband,
look." Oh, okay. Okay. Sorry. It's
moving quick. I'm trying to get it back
down. My ex-husband took his life 43
years ago. I was there when he did it.
Oh my god. He was going to shoot me as
well, but all of a sudden, he decided
not to.
He
said he was the bad one, not
me. Just know first of all, just first
of all, just reading
that, you need to know. Um,
Roxy, just reading that, I I I like have
tremendous respect when just you going
through that and and staying here. I
mean, that's 43 years ago and you're
still here. You're still here. Something
inside of you. There's something inside
of you that says, "No, I'm going to
fight for it. I'm gonna I'm going to be
a fighter. I'm going to stay here and
I'm going to be a fighter." And that's a
big deal. Um I'm not just reading your
comment and blah blah blah blah. That
right there, that that hits me hard
because having a psychic mind and also
being able to hear a voice um spirit of
compassion and having that
ability and um and having that ability
to see when I'm reading that
I'm seeing things that I'm not saying.
I'm seeing things. I'm going back to 43
years ago. I'm going back
there. SOC is talking to me. Just know
that my heart pours out to
you. So you
guys, angels, angels, uh, demons and
spiritual tools, the tech problems we
have is another. I don't have Tik Tok on
right now, just so you know. I won't
even put Tik Tok on because they'll ban
me for talking about this. Just talking
about demons, they'll ban me. So anyway,
let me uh head over to uh page 68 if you
don't mind. If you don't mind me doing
that. I think it's over here somewhere.
No, no, no. Come on. Come on. Where am I
going? Where am I going? Oh, right here.
Here we
go. No one understands how many factors
are involved, including free will. And
that's why people then blame God and the
angels for doing
nothing. They think God has a magic wand
and should be able to fix everything
with one wave of God's wand. Yet God at
the beginning created a set of laws.
These laws surround the existence of
free will. Change one of these laws and
the fabric of free will becomes altered.
All right. So, that's a really powerful
piece of information all on its own
right there.
Okay.
Um, and so I want to talk about like
what leads that to, you know, what leads
us there anyway.
Okay.
So, to begin with, there's only so many
of God's
angels. That's just to begin with
automatically. Then you have a portion
of the angelic realm that fell.
that portion of the angelic realm that
fell. Okay? It's a smaller percentage,
it's still a lot of angels, okay? And
then you have the angels that are
falling really, they really don't want
to jump. They don't want to jump to God.
They don't want to jump to somebody in
strife. They don't want to they want to
make the decision really kind of like if
they want to even help. They're in the
process of falling, you know. So there's
a lot of things and a lot of people do
think that God has this magic wand and
this is information that's just just
blew my mind. It just just
does. And so I'm reading here, no one
understands how many factors are
involved, including free will. And
that's interesting. Including free will.
And that's why people then blame God and
the angels for doing nothing. So when
something
happens and why didn't God stop it? Why
didn't God fix this? Why didn't God stop
this? It's the thing I think that also
really breaks Christianity in so many
ways because there's so many people
they're Christians and then something
happens in their life and then they have
to choose their faith. It's like do I
stay a Christian? Do I believe in God?
Because why would this happen to my son,
my daughter? Why would this happen to my
uncle, my aunt? And what happens is that
like if there's a God, why would this
happen? If there's a God, why would God
let that happen to me? Okay, I could see
God letting it happen to somebody else
but not me. So what happens is you know
you you people they go through this
process this this brain screw about God
and about Jesus and about their faith
the religion and it doesn't even have to
be Christianity it could be something
else and they go through this whole
thing it could be another religion could
be another faith okay so just using that
as an example and they go through this
process and they're just like why didn't
God
wave his magic
wand and so they get really upset
And free will has something to do with a
lot of this too. Free will that the
angels have, they have free will and
that's a whole another thing all on its
own. So no one understands how many
factors are involved, including free
will. And that's why people then blame
God and the angels for doing nothing.
They think God has a magic wand and
should be able to fix everything with
one wave of God's
wand. Yet God at the beginning created a
set of laws. These laws surround the
existence of free will and that's a
problem too because God created all
these laws based around free will and
spirit of compassion was telling me all
about that and it just blew my mind.
Change one of these laws. Do you guys
hear that? Change one of these laws and
the fabric of free will becomes altered.
And that's another thing all on its own.
So you change these laws, free will is
just out the window.
Anyway, you guys, if you get a
chance, would love for you guys to hear
this. I'm sitting Okay, so Stephie over
there on IG, I'm sitting here two months
postpartum, struggling so much, been
avoiding IG because these
expectations and standards are hard to
match.
I'm so glad I'm on today and caught this
live. Just know my heart pours out to
you. Any kind of struggle you're going
through, any kind of difficulties,
anything like that, you know, just know
that that that I care. Spirit of
compassion
cares. Sue is over there on I IG. My
daughter was murdered by her husband 11
years
ago. I don't even know how to take that
in. I I'm like right there. That just so
my daughter was murdered by her husband
11 years ago in front of the
kids. I got her four kids. There has
been major bad energy in the second
son. He killed his sister's dog. He is
now
evil. Wow. Wow.
And that's the thing when it comes down
to uh demons is there's different
degrees of demons. And that's the thing
too, you guys. When you when you listen
to this audio, it's an original audio.
Type in angels, demons, and spiritual
tools. It's an original audio. And I
talk about the different levels of
demons. It's just they're not all the
same. They're not all equal. Just like
humans are not all the same and their
souls are not all equal as well. And
then depending on how evil a soul really
is. And then and then so meaning a human
soul right human alive and in their
physical form right here on planet earth
and then depending on how evil that
human is like truly evil that human is
and that human then passes on dies and
then their soul I don't if you heard
this right their
soul basically goes up for grabs I'm
just giving you like the quick quick
rendition real quick rendition not you
know you have to listen to the audio but
their soul basically goes is up for
grabs. And you got you can get more
dangerous demons, ones that are more
evil, ones
that embark in uh fallen angels, and
they're bidding ones that will work for
fallen angels because they're so dark.
And
then they just Yeah, they just allow bad
They create bad things to happen. It's
just heartbreaking. I have my heart's
broken.
Kirstson over there on YouTube. It
really helped me forgive my dad that
passed from a drug
OD. That's a big deal. There's there's I
have I've talked about that too in here.
The drug addiction involved with the
demons. Elena says the book is
absolutely mind-blowing. Answer to
answers to many questions. Thank you
much so much an Anthony June over there
on Facebook. Wow, amazing information.
Mind-blowing you guys.
I'm going to do another one of these
soon, too. I've seen a lot of great
comments come up. Wonderful. Julie
Tuesday 144, you're always being so
supportive. You're on YouTube. You're
always answering people and being so
great to them. Just know I see it and I
really appreciate it. Learning that
demons were once humans made a huge
difference in how I perceive them. And
it makes a huge difference how I
perceive them. It's a reminder. Spirit
always told me this that part that
humans become the demons. And I I just
never talked about it, but because I
wanted all the information to to get in
here to be able to really put the
information out for people so they get
all the pieces. But yeah, Allison over
there on YouTube, I had a demon take
over my husband at the time and tell me
I wanted to
chop he wanted to chop me up into little
pieces. Oh my god. Dear
Lord. And tell me it wanted to chop me
up in little pieces. Oh my god.
Yeah. And and but we're supposed to all
sweep that under the carpet, right?
We're supposed to just think that's just
crazy people or something like that. And
yeah, somebody could be an evil person
in dark, like I said, and be a very
cold-hearted person, but demons just
they can really do some serious damage
with all of
this. A met says, "I have never
understood why demons in the family
attack those who seek peace and harmony.
Now it makes sense and I have doubts
whether my family is too harmful to my
daughters. I think what happens when you
know your consciousness gets like like
really opened up, you know, you know
when you hear like the whole thing like
get your third eye open and you know and
you meditate and get your consciousness
you know like you know geared up and you
know all the things and and do all the
self-help and all that stuff and that's
all great but I mean it's all great and
all but without the information like
without the
information we're still left stranded
you You know, I I think
that this is a world
changer. This is a world changer. And
that's the thing. If you don't have the
knowledge, how are you going to like
know? How are you going to know? Same
thing about if you don't know why you're
really truly
sick. If you tried every biohack, you're
still sick or whatever it is, you're
just not past it. It's a mystery. Like,
until you know why you're sick, you're
not going to heal. You have to know why
and how you can address it. And in this
situation on a spiritual level, this
information, it's like you learn how
this is happening or how something's
happening out there. You have to have
the knowledge in order to address it and
take it head on and and heal and and
bypass this information
and jump ahead. Be free from it, free
from demons,
germs. That's an empower thing all on
its own. An empowering thing knowing
their true name.
Derms. Jess Lane. I'm amazed at how
specific, detailed, and deep it all is.
You think I let you down,
Jess? Spirit of compassion. Not going to
let you down. Beth Paige, it is helping
with my nailbiting addiction. To think
that they could be taking advantage of
that is helping me stop that habit. And
they can be taking advantage of that.
There are demons that are of lesser
damage or lesser depths of evil, but
they're still evil and dark. And they
they would love you to bite your nails
off your fingers. They would love you to
bite your nails right off your
fingers. Anyway, until next time you
guys, and there will be a next time I
will be talking about angels, demons,
and spiritual
tools. Lena W, the book is amazing. Feel
so empowered now to work for God and the
light. Feels like time is slowing down
too. Can concentrate better and feel
more
present. See what happens when you push
away demons and you disempower them and
you start moving forward. See what
happens. It's powerful.
Powerful. You guys check out the medical
podcast at Apple podcast when you get a
chance. Listen to those episodes. Those
are profound. The information from SOC,
it's all incredible. So, make sure you
check that out. Check out my Telegram,
you know. Um, I'm on Rumble, the whole
bit. Look, that's it right there. There
it is. Go check it out. Angels, Demons,
and Spiritual Tools right there. Go
Amazon, Audible. Type it in if you want.
Go to Spotify. Go to Apple. It's the
most profound powerful information there
is on demons and and just move demons
aside on spiritual information in
general on the
soul just the soul alone and other
information too there's so much here
it's not just about demons it's
empowering on all kinds of levels and
those spiritual tools in here help on
all levels too so just know that this is
a world
changer and um God bless God bless