it out there people catch a bug they get
sick they're coughing their lungs out
they're really sick they got fevers
going up and down they start to recover
they go to a doctor they get on an
antibiotic whatever it is they start to
recover and then they stay sick they
think they're going to recover and
bounce back completely but they're
dragging or two weeks later they're
doing a little better and then it hits
them and they're dragging and they're
going down
and what's happening out there people
are getting sick and then they're
falling into this chronically ill
trigger and now they're getting all
these different things like brain fog
and weird tingles and numbness on their
body and aches and pains and fatigue and
brain fog again and they just don't feel
themselves and now they're triggered
into something entirely different
because of the bugs going around right
now right now in New England in the
United States there's a stomach flu
neuro virus and and it's pounding the
crap out of people right now up there
and it's heading through through the
United States and around the world and
it's giving people like insane diarrhea
and gut disturbances and we're going to
cover that a little bit cuz I want to
talk about that like what does it do in
the gut like what happens there's people
all about you know microbiome what
happens if you get the neuro virus and
you got the stomach flu and it's ripping
through your guts and you're sitting
there and you're just diarrhea diarrhea
vomiting too and diarrhea diarrhea and
then what like what happened how's your
microbiome then is it all fixed is it
all great what's it like nobody really
talks about that they don't talk about
what happens when boom you get that
neuro virus and you got the stomach flu
and then is your microbiome is is that
going to get back to normal wasn't even
normal to begin with and is it going to
get back to normal eventually or is it
going to be out of balance now for next
another two years until you get another
stomach flu
so I'm talking about a bunch of
different things okay there a lot of
bugs out there quick announcement too
did you hear the episode the medical
medum podcast at Apple podcast black
tongue did you hear the episode the
black tongue syndrome so many people get
it there's a whole thing about it with
metals and everything else I talk about
in the episodes the medical medum
podcast at Apple podcast black tongue
I've seen people get the black tongue
and they're sitting there with the
toothbrush and they're like scrubbing
scrubbing and they injure their tongue
they're trying to do everything they can
they're rinsing with salt water they're
rinsing with mouth
rinses they're rinsing with everything
under the sun and they can't get rid of
that black tongue have you ever seen
that out there people get that and it's
just like it's coming it's going it's
coming and then sometimes it's just jet
black for a very long time right in the
center of the tongue going swiping all
the way down so check out medical mean
podcast at Apple podcast please listen
to it when you get a chance it's an
amazing informative show about Black
tongue discolorations and so forth and
everything I'm sure so many of you guys
have had discolorations with the tongue
so it's good information very important
but I'm here to talk about our immune
system and how it's getting pretty beat
up these days with what people are going
through do you know anybody that's
coughing do you know anybody that's got
a sore throat and a fever do you know
anybody who's been hit with anything
that's going on because people have been
getting hit it's like a surgence of it
insurgence of it happening right now
this is like one of those hot spots
we're in where it's just really starting
to pick up pace I hear it all the time
people are sick for a month with it
coughing out their lungs the whole bit
but then to add insult to injury there
is a neov virus stomach flu hyper catchy
hyper catchy that's actually steaming
streaming right out of New England right
now and it's going to be cutting across
the country and and you know overseas
and everywhere else and that one really
sucks really really sucks so what I'm
doing right now is the reason why I'm
even here is because I'm saying are you
taking care of your immune system are
you taking care of your immune system
right so I have my family on this right
here just a safeguard I need a safeguard
my family and my closest friends you
know safeguarding them too and all that
so that's the total immune blend do you
have it what's crazy out there is what
I'm seeing right now is all these
different supplements are coming out
it's like crazy right and they're
claiming all this stuff and claiming all
this stuff but they don't work they
don't work and you look what's in them
it's like yeah all poor quality crap all
garbage whatever you name it and they
just don't work it's so sad that's what
I'm seeing out there you guys know I
endorse these guys this is vmer g v is
in Victor i m is in Mary E RG y I'll get
a close-up too on this right here this
is the total immune I'm living off of it
to protect myself cuz I can't get sick
right now with any kind of cold or
anything like
flu anything like that I use the term
cold but you know how there's no colds
anyway but is this back in stock it's
back in stock so I give you a little
closeup on this before I move on because
we're going to talk about some stuff in
the immune system which is really
important so that's total immune blend
right there there it is that's the
vimergy I don't know if you guys see it
there it is very important critical
critical
um resource right there it's got the
time it's got the Mullen it's back in
stock it's sold out like this when it
came out so a lot of people armed
themselves and armed their immune
systems for what was coming but I want
to talk about even more than that I want
to go into like what people are dealing
with post getting sick and what they're
dealing with pre getting sick because
everybody has immune system problems and
that's that's a big thing right there on
its own if you got a
symptom if you got any kind of symptom
if you got any kind of
condition if you've been diagnosed with
a condition if you're struggling with
any kind of symptom immune system right
there anything people who are dealing
with cancer immune systems broke down
people are dealing with all kinds of
different things like fibro and ra and
lime and anything immune system people
that're dealing with all kinds of aches
and pain pain and Tinkles and numbness
and vertigo and ringing in the ears and
dizziness and balance issues immune
system we have injured depleted
diminished immune systems and that's
what people live with every single day
if you know somebody and they're getting
things and they're getting symptoms and
they're
struggling yeah it's their immune system
it's struggling that's the whole point
it can't handle exposures it can't
handle the toxic heavy metal exposures
and then the herbicide and the fungicide
exposures and the
fragrances and the caffeine addiction it
can't handle the immune system can't
handle that so many people are drowning
themselves with coffee and espresso
drinks and they're just beating the crap
out of their immune system so immune
system is just under attack all the time
and So eventually what that leads us to
is a sickness no matter
what everyone is going to get a sick
symptom no matter what you see somebody
out there right now they're on social
like yeah I'm doing this I'm doing that
I'm Into Fitness I'm into this you're
going to have a symptom you're going to
have a symptom it's going to come later
maybe but you're going to be pushed over
the edge too many exposures your immune
system is going to finally kick down and
you're going to be in the immune system
pit just like everybody else so keeping
our immune system strong is critical
having immune system power is
critical having it strong and you'll
hear things out there like you don't
want your imun system too strong oh you
don't really like okay whose immune
system is too strong somebody tell me
whose immune system is so strong you
know I mean even like the best
influencers out there talking about
health and everything they're dealing
with immune system problems that's how
they got into it anyway they got into
the health industry in general because
they got problems and they're seeing
their naturopath and their herbalist and
their acupuncturist and their MD and
their do and they're seeing everybody
because they got all these problems
because everybody's immune system is
challenged that's the day and age we're
in we're in the age of the quickening
right here this is the quickening where
[ __ ] just speeds up and speeds up and
speeds up stuff is happening real fast
out there and sickness and disease is
climbing at an all-time high and it's
staying climbing and climbing and
climbing
2030 so many people are going to be sick
2035 it's going to be unbelievable on
how many people are going to be sick
everybody's going to be sick and
everybody's going to be on social
talking about their
sicknesses that's what's going to happen
it's going to dominate social
entirely to a point where all articles
out there all the media is going to be
talking about sickness everybody's going
to be talking about sickness stories
this is just what it's going to be by
2030 nothing but sickness sickness
sickness
everywhere and that's the world we live
in that's the world we're going to be
living in and that's how crazy it really
is when you really think about it right
I mean did you ever expect that did you
ever expect
that yeah you're not alone so let's talk
about the immune system a little bit and
why it's so important to support it not
just support it rebuild it rebuild it
critical really is writing for truth on
IG says do you take the total immune
blend every day even when not sick I do
I take it every single day even when not
sick I take it every day okay but you
can take it every day right do what your
doctor wants to do but I tell my family
you can take it every day but you can
take a smaller dosage if you're not sick
every single day then when you get sick
or you're struggling with something you
can increase the the dosage to what your
whatever doctor believes or however
what's in it a
blend of thyme and Mullen and a little
touch of zinc it's this perfect
combination right here and what people
don't realize it's the quality of the
time on top of it it's the quality of
the Mullen that you don't get in other
places it doesn't happen it just doesn't
I know I know the quality I know what
they do I know how they do it and it's
unbelievable it's about making sure that
alcohol wasn't used that alcohol is not
involved at any level making sure all
these different things matter that this
is really clean but the real thing not
everybody saying good quality this is
good quality everybody's allowed to say
that did you know that you're allowed to
say everything's good quality did you
know that anybody who just opens up a
door hangs a shingle and sells something
they're allowed to say our quality is
great nothing beats our quality there is
a difference huge difference that's
important to know it really is an IG
Roxy says where can I buy it that's
vimergy V is in Victor i m is in Mary E
RG y vimergy.com
link check out the link in the uh
description so yeah Details
Matter Details Matter I agree I see that
right there okay so let's go into it a
little
bit all right couple of things to know
one is
why are immune systems so chopped up why
are they so beat up and that's something
that nobody really talks about they're
just like this is immune supportive
immune supportive everybody's immune
system is just beaten to a pul basically
and that's why everybody's so sick it's
struggling immune system you got to
remember that if there's anything
someone's dealing with instantly the
immune system is under siege Under Siege
if someone's got panic attacks and they
got the Titan chest and they got that
Vagas nerve I talk about that Vagas
nerves the
inflammation and they're dealing with
all kinds of anxiety and panic and all
these other things immune system
everything is like that thyroid
condition at all thyroid anybody
hypothyroid hyperthyroid any kind of
thyroid problems at all anything
Graves whatever it is nodul in the
thyroid whatever it is immune system was
challenged the thyroids immune system
was challenged the liver's immune system
was challenged and then weakened and
then kicked down a notch so people walk
around with weak immune systems that's
what they do all day long and then the
thyroid disorders creep up and then the
panic and the aches and pains creep up
and then the vertigo and the tentis and
the tingles and numbness and the body
aches and pains and the trigal neur Alia
all creep up because their immune system
is suffering their immune system is
struggling so very important to know so
let's talk about like stomach flu I want
to go into that a little bit stomach
flu okay so the reason why I would take
like something every single day or I
tell family to take something every
single day like I tell my family take a
little bit of this take little bit of
the propolis every single day right
little bit of the golden seal every
single day this is what I tell my family
to do all the time and a little bit of
B12 and I want to talk about why B12 is
critical cuz when we catch something
like the neuro virus or white lung yeah
which is really hurting a lot of people
I mean they get scar tissue in the lung
that lasts
forever I mean that's just unfair like
why do they put bugs out there like this
so that we get injuries in our lungs and
then for a lifetime we actually have
scar tissue in our lungs like does that
make any sense
so I tell my friends and family it's
critical to get B12 in you after
especially after you've been hit with
something because you need that extra
B12 to power up the nerves so important
that alone okay and so what I'm telling
my family right now with all these these
hard times of people getting sick cuz
it's it's really sad when you see
somebody really struggling they get what
feels like a cold to start with then it
then it lingers then it runs into a
fever and up and down and then after
that when they're better they're not
better because now their immune system
was dropped and they were triggered into
something else an Epstein bar rising up
out of nowhere herbus simplex one rising
up from nowhere because that's what's
happening to people people are getting
shingles a month after they get white
lung a month later they have the
shingles because their immune system was
so kicked down to the bottom that the
jingles virus said this is my time to
shine and then it comes up and it just
boom it's up there let's talk about the
Norovirus that's coming around and it's
circulating right now and it's it's
kicking up so right now there's a
stomach bug out there and what people
don't realize is that a stomach bug can
knock your gut balance off for a really
long time really long time but what you
what you'll never see out there is what
happens in inside the intestinal track
when that bug is around so let's go into
that let's let's try to like makeshift a
little bit of an intestinal track
okay so let's do that we'll make shift a
little bit of a a colon here
right all right and then we'll just do a
little intestinal track in the center
here if you guys can see this
okay so you pick up the stomach flu pick
up the neuro virus you get it in your
mouth just goes in you you breathe it in
it's on your tongue now it's heading
down to your gut okay and it's on its
way so that virus is getting there okay
virus goes down the dadum it's it starts
in your stomach right it goes down your
stomach in your dadum it's heading in
there and what that virus is doing is
it's multiplying really fast and it's
it's feeding off of foods that you eat
so it's multiplying it's exploding so
what a stomach virus does is it
proliferates at a speed no other bug Pro
proliferates no other bug fires up to
that degree to multiplies to that degree
spawns to that degree but the neuro
virus
explodes and it feeds off of undigested
proteins it feeds off of gluten that's
in the system from you ate a week ago
yeah a week ago it feeds off of any egg
residue egg material any kind of egg
material in your gut it feeds off of
that and then it feeds off of any dairy
products and then it feeds off of other
things it'll feed off of soy
potentially it'll feed off of virtually
anything right so what it does is it
feeds and it explodes it produces itself
rapidly like rapidly and it's highly
toxic so what the neuro virus is is it's
a bug that when it produces the bug then
goes to the intestinal lining walls and
it starts to make divots it starts to
basically try to poke holes in your
intestinal tract and your colon but
nobody talks about this they're just
like you got a stomach bug you know
that's it wait till it's over and then
take a
probiotic so that's what they'll say
some of the best functional medicine
doctors to be like well you got a
stomach flu um go to the hospital you
got a stomach flu and then make sure you
get on our probiotics at our clinic or
or our doctor's office make sure you get
on our probiotics so that's all they do
but what people don't realize is that
virus is mean really mean so stomach
bugs stomach flues explode they multiply
fast real fast thousands upon thousands
of replicas then all those bugs end up
attaching themselves to everything the
stomach lining the dadum lining the
small and top of the small intestinal
tract all through and as it's happening
if you have a weakened immune system
it's not slowing it down it's not
stopping it instead that person is now
diarrhea they got stomach pains they're
really nauseous they got a fever
cranking
up because their immune system isn't
stopping it it's not breaking it down so
their immune cells are not there's not
enough immune cells number one to stop
the neuro virus to that degree and if
someone has a weakened immune system
then they really have very small amounts
of immune cells going into this area
trying to stop the neuro virus
so the neuro virus the stomach flu the
stomach bugs what they do is they attack
the Linings of the small intestinal
tract and this is why people get Pockets
later this is why people get divots
diverticulitis diverticulos losis this
is why people end up with crohn's later
on meaning a trigger to get into Crohn's
where other bugs can actually contribute
it's all about knocking the immune
system down allowing other problems to
happen there's people who get stomach
flu that never have a normal stomach
intestinal tract ever again in their
life they don't know how to recover it
they know don't know how to rebuild it
they don't know about Mono eating from
the medical medium book series they
don't know about all these different
things they can do they're just stuck
their intestinal tra is rocked for a
very long time and then if they're older
and they're not younger and they're
older it affects them even more because
they already have intestinal tract
issues on so many levels so the neuro
virus explodes and then it attaches
itself to the Linings of the intestinal
tract and if you're somebody that has
pockets of undigested protein from a
weak liver that I talked about in the
last episode or if you're somebody
that's dealing with anything like
putrified rancid fats that are caked
along your intestinal tract old fecal
matter that's just stuck there and
plastered against the intestinal Linings
and bad bacteria like strep it all Rises
up so the neuro virus and the stomach
flu and the stomach bugs go ripping
through you and then it awakens all the
STP all the staff all the tiny bits of
sea that you were keeping under control
you know just managing your immune
system was managing all this time and
then what happens is we get triggered
now we have all kinds of intestinal
tract disturbances years later down the
road a month later so as the virus is
ripping through the gut it's clinging to
the wall of the intestinal tract and it
starts to try to burrow holes inside the
intestinal tract just like white lung is
doing to people when they're getting the
sea and they're getting the flu and the
C and the RSV and the white lung right
now and it's going in it's injuring lung
sacks well the stomach flu is
created
manufactured to injure the lining of
your intestinal
tract stomach dadum and so forth it's
there to scar tissue and burrow and
weaken the
lining and wake up other predators that
lie inside of our intestinal tract
like the strep and the seiff and
different varieties of staff and the
hpylori
so as that neuro virus and that stomach
flu is ripping through and exploding and
people are having like explosions of
diarrhea and they're sick and they're
nauseous and they're throwing up or
they're fevered and they're getting the
runs and they're really struggling for a
day or two sometimes a week right now
there's one that's ripping through
that's really messing people up and when
that's happening it wakes up strep it
wakes up SEI it wakes up staff it wakes
up other bugs like viruses that could be
in the intestinal
tract and then it tries to burrow holes
in the Linings because that's what it
does the bugs go in and they try to
destroy tissue so they're cell
destroyers the reason why we're having
diarrhea and fever and everything else
around it is cuz our body is
reacting and mucus is is being produced
off the lining of her intestinal tract
because it's burrowing little holes tiny
little divots in her intestinal tract
and so our intestinal tract is releasing
gobs and gobs of mucus and water and
mucus and it's just straming out it's
streaming out to try to defend against
the Invader but the Invader causes a lot
of Havoc reaches a lot reaks a lot of
havoc and a probiotic is not going to
fix it
after a really bad stomach flu a fever
and also intestinal tract being invaded
like that it takes time to heal it takes
time to eat the right Foods it takes
time to understand what you're doing and
it's critical to keep the immune system
strong
so I just wanted to show you that right
there and there's other stuff to talk
about because we are here talking about
the fun stuff for sure all right then
move this over a little bit
okay it takes a tremendous amount of
adrenaline to fend off any bug that's
out there right now any kind of flu any
kind of C any kind of white lung RSV any
kind of neuro virus or stomach virus it
takes
adrenaline heart rate goes
up as you're getting sick your heart
rate goes up that's how it works because
epinephrine is being released adrenaline
is being released to try to protect you
but adrenaline itself doesn't help the
immune system so what these bugs do and
these viruses do that get into us when
they get into us our adrenals end up
fire alarming it and releasing all this
adrenaline to try to because that's
actually this response this automics
response that's happening immediately
when an Invader enters into our system
but as it's happening our immune cells
are struggling even more because we have
so much adrenaline pouring into our
bloodstream and immune cells hate
adrenaline hate adrenaline it holds them
back it keeps them from functioning as
good as they can function so our immune
cells need
fuel need
fuel and that's why I talk about like I
have my family and my closest friends on
protocols I have them on supplements
it's critical because when you get sick
if you're somewhere and look no one has
no one has it perfect where well man you
know what I could be wrong about that
there's people on Instagram that they
never have to work a day in their life
right they're young they come for money
or something or they're just extremely
wealthy or whatever it is everything's
taken care of and all they have to do is
sleep 12 hours every night they could
sleep as many hours as they want they
don't have to stress out about work they
don't have to they just worry about
their appointments their stress is their
appointments like I'm getting my
lymphatic drainage here I'm getting this
here I'm doing this here I'm going on a
vacation here with my friends here I'm
going to Europe whatever it is that's
their stress right and there are people
like that and they can at least protect
themselves because they're not living
with a lot of real life scenarios
situations they're not trying to work
three jobs to survive they don't have
you know like all these problems in
their life meaning from other family
members or something happening and they
don't you know there's a lot going on in
a lot of people's lives and we can't
help it because there's so many people
that don't have that perfect life life
where they can just relax all day long
and never have to worry about working a
day in their life you know there's a lot
of people that are struggling and they
have to fight to survive and when you do
that right we're always up against a lot
and it's important to keep our immune
system strong and in the eventually
someone who has it really good in their
life and they're young and strong now
still will get symptoms later they'll
still wind up in trouble they'll still
wind up sick I see see it all the time
but it usually comes later instead of
early let's see sole purpose on IG says
my fiance was just sick three times in
six weeks flu bug stomach flu bug and
then flu bug again now lots of crazy
symptoms so he's joined me in medical
medium protocols this week now that's
exactly the example I'm so sorry you're
going through that first of all I want
to say that that's awful that's awful
but that's how they set it up you have
to understand that's how they set it up
so that's what they do okay so let's do
a a different little thing on the
Whiteboard okay I don't know why my
whiteboard doesn't really work that
right I really don't
know okay so all
right excuse me for my art Artistry
work okay
right kind I put a little chimy up
here all
right
okay that is the bug manufacturing plant
that's what that is that's right that's
the bug manufacturing
plant yes
indeed
okay and here are some houses over here
some
roofs okay okay there's some different
houses
everywhere um there's a little village
here lots of different roads like this
quick art this is really great right
it's a building up here with some
chimneys here whatever that's the
village The Village the innocent
people okay there it
is and the manufacturing plant they just
let out all kinds of stuff out there
front
door is what they do they let out lots
of
bugs lots of bugs and they do it
purposely and they time it just right
okay and these bugs end up going to the
village and everybody gets
sick apologize for my my writing
my Artistry
skills I did not go to Art School
and uh I wish I did I really do anyway
listen so check this out you guys bugs
are layered on top of bugs purposely so
they release them with a
schedule okay so there's a
schedule there it is
here got all the different days of the
month right here's the first here's the
second here's the Third third the fourth
the 5ifth each month they release one
flu bug on the first of whatever day of
the month they want to release it
on when they know it's gotten out there
good enough and it's running its course
they time it and they have schedules and
they release another one on another
month maybe they'll release it on the
third okay they layer the manufactured
bugs purposely so it kicks the crap out
of people they want you to be triggered
and injured so you're kept down and you
feed the system that's how it's done see
so you catch the one flu six weeks ago
you catch another flu three weeks ago
you catch the stomach flu last week it's
layered they put them out like that and
they want everybody in the village to
get sick everybody and they want older
people elderly people to
die correct they want them to die and
get knocked off that's how it's done
they want them sick and they want them
gone that's how the system is set up
it's a kind of a fun little system isn't
[Music]
it they manufacture the bugs and they
then they stick the bugs in a
containment unit with a bunch of white
mice and they see if the mice all die
and they see if the mice live they see
if the mice chalk you know cough and
choke on fleem they see if the mice have
diarrhea all around the mouse
tank and then they kind of say well
we're ready and they eventually let it
out that's the system it's the way it's
built lady Kath over there in IG just
said I really appreciate how how you
pointed out that most of us have so many
stresses bringing down our immune
systems indeed everybody does I am
included in that I am not immune to that
I have stress just like anybody else
plenty of it in fact a lot of it and
that's what happens when you have the
most healing stories on the planet of
people healing you have the most people
with multiple sceris that got out of
wheelchairs in
history the the information that's so
Advanced every single you know somebody
who's somebody in the influencer world
is stealing and poaching it and using it
because they can't get their own
information and all these people are
healing around the world and it creates
tremendous amount of stress that's how
it works you're not allowed to get
people better in large quantities you're
allowed to get one or two people better
and be like hey I got somebody better
you're not allowed to get millions of
people better hundreds of thousands of
people better that weren't supposed to
get better you're not allowed to do that
not on planet
Earth so my stress is
great chamia says Anthony the flu bug
got around our household but we were
able to stop it in its tracks with
vitamin C shock and zinc shock therapy
plus time water thank you so much for
these tools I'm all pumped up from that
that's actually exciting and I love
hearing that because it's that powerful
and that helpful so um um let me make
some vitamin C shock therapy let me do
that I'm going to have some now if you
guys don't
mind looking for some utensils here so
I'm going to pop some vitamin C in there
just like that I got some honey over
here too I'm going to pop a little bit
of honey in here and then I'm going to
get some water going some warm water got
that going right let's see I got some
orange juice right here this is what
I've been doing fresh squeezed orange
juice by the way you guys right that's a
luxury that is a luxury seriously like
going out and getting oranges this
really good oranges if you could find
them right squeezing them making a glass
of fresh squeezed orange juice is an
incredible luxury here okay see not
everything is all bad down here okay
anyway I I got some water warming up as
we
speak there we
go give it a second warming it up right
now so micro C is what I'm using for
this right here do you guys know about
this can I show you this is also a
collagen
Builder and the one thing about medical
medium information is I was the first to
blow the horn on the BS [ __ ]
collagen Market
where the collagen Market was selling
all this collagen but you can't build
collagen eating collagen just like you
can't fix your eye eating an eyeball you
can't eat a pig's eyeball to fix your
eyeball you can't eat a liver to fix
your liver it doesn't work that's not
how it works you can't rebuild collagen
in your body you can't rebuild collagen
in your body eating collagen it's not
going to happen so Medical medium
information was the first to call that
out that you can't get better on
collagen you can only build your
collagen with collagen Builders that's
how you do
it all right so I got some water heated
up right
here I'm going to add a little bit of
orange juice to this as well this is the
vitamin C shock
therapy this water got a little toasty a
little bit toastier than I probably
wanted it so let me get some nice
cold orange juice in there fresh
squeezed orange juice look at
that nice can I have a double espresso
please can I have an espresso coffee an
espresso drink can I have a coffee with
two espressos put into the coffee um you
know I'm kidding though you guys know
I'm kidding so this is the micro SE
immune power okay this sa is incredible
for the skin and credible for the skin
credible for the immune system that's an
immune Builder difference huge
difference okay so I'm doing what um you
were doing right for your family you're
doing the vitamin C shock
therapy
incredible I'm going to mix it really
good this has a little bit of the honey
in there it's got the fresh quar juice
it's got the warm water see Anna over
there and IG says I love that micro C I
have been doing the Skin Potion and it
helps so much my eczema on my face
incredible I have a lot of people doing
this for the skin right now a lot of
people by the way friends and family and
so
forth see Trace over there in IG I'm
doing the micro orange juice and MSM and
I've noticed my bruises from Posts
surgery treat in my my um physical
therapy treatments disappear incredible
so much quicker game Cher hope I read
that right incredible so that's the
micro C that's the total immune okay
things at work is what I care about
things that work it matters it's
critical I'm seeing a lot of stuff being
put every day out there being put out
there everybody wants to pop a
supplement out there I don't blame I
don't blame everybody everybody wants to
put a supplement out there I don't blame
them and you guys know I don't own
vimergy this is not my company I don't
have shares in the company I don't have
stock in the company I don't have a
percentage in the company you guys know
that right cuz I know BS goes around and
stories get go around I do not own any
part of vimergy on any level people need
to know that it's not my brand it's not
my company very important but it's the
only company I trust at this point to
like to to the degree that I trust I
know the people I've known them for a
long time now I trust them I trust that
they won't won't let me down and my
people down they won't and they stay
literally like straight as you can be
I'm making sure this stuff is that
incredible that's why I support them
that's why I endorse them the Skin
Potion helps with my spots and they
disappearing whoa on on IG that's
incredible okay um so anyway you guys
know about the MSM too that's another
thing for the skin which is incredible
skin and joints and everything so the
MSM that's an amazing one with silica
and that's a whole game changer all on
its own I mean this this is actually
exciting this cheers me up because I've
been wanting to talk about some of the
things that I'm using my family is using
the medical medium Skin Potion have you
tried it which is the MSM it's the
vitamin C right the micro C and let me
just be clear about this so you guys
know okay if you're interested this
isn't ascorbic acid this isn't the thing
that burns holes in people's stomachs
that that's what I'm talking about
that's a different difference with
fmer that is the difference right there
because people don't realize that they
go and take the ascorbic acid and next
thing you know they got the runs they
got diarrhea they got stomach upset it's
burning their Linings it's burning their
gut if they're sensitive they had ulcers
in the past and they're taking all that
ascorbic acid it's sitting there like
sizzling up the ulcers like I I can't I
can't even go even go there like I will
never take an escor acid straight
ascorbic acid vitamin C ever again in my
life I've taken it when there was
nothing else available out there in the
world I've taken it when there was
nothing available I will never ever ever
take an escorp Bic a TR scor Bic acid
vitamin C ever again ever and so I'm
just I'm just like I know that I'm
blessed to know that this is out there
for me to take personally for my health
and for people to take personally for
their health and I'm blessed to know
that this is actually here it's just
it's incredible this isn't about like
supplementation and supplements and
selling something this is about stuff
that literally is critical for life like
because of what it is and what they do
it's it's a real Mission that's the
difference with vimergy and then people
just trying to Hawk supplements grifters
H you know selling and Hawking
supplements because they're just trying
to make a book big difference I don't
own this company I don't have a
percentage a Share St stock nothing in
this company but I'll tell you right now
I know what they're doing and it's
unbelievable and that's why I endorse
them like flying colors kind of thing
anyway here's the micro shock therapy
can I actually have a little bit of it
if you guys don't mind Julie Tuesday I
read all your comments on YouTube and
you're always helping people too Julie
you're always helping people as well
you're always like letting them know
stuff and everything and I always I
always read them Julie Tuesday 144
vimergy products have really helped me
get through some tough times I can feel
the difference there is a difference
thank you for saying that Sage star over
there on YouTube thanks for the honesty
and your Protocols are helping me stop
multiple sclerosis in its tracks dang
right you fight for it you fight for it
okay and that it's critical to fight for
it so many people recovered from Ms so
many people with mm information so
important so important anyway okay I'm
just going to sip this right now I just
want to I can't help it want to have a
little real quick here we're talking
about neuro virus we're talking about
flu we're talking about um C RSV white
lung but then we're talking about like
what happens when the scale is tips so
much you guys you know how I've been
talking about the scale tipping all this
time and and death by a Thousand Cuts
for like years right and now I just saw
like someone just said that someone was
on a podcast like some influencer guy
was on some podcast doctor or something
was on a podcast and talking about scale
tipping
Death By A Thousand Cuts like dude get
your own stuff get your own
stuff but that's what's happening the
scale is tipping and that's what these
bugs do it knocks them down and their
immune system then struggles their
immune system is already struggling and
now they're sick and it's unfair it's
not right that this happens to people we
shouldn't have to live our lives sick
life is short and as it is life is short
as it is okay we're not living to 500
years old we're not living to 400 years
old right it's another story I want to
talk about on a spiritual talk one day
maybe I'll do that on like the the um IG
broadcast right are you guys actually
signed up to my Ig broadcast are you
guys signed up to that where I send you
the direct message maybe I'll talk about
it there and on my telegram as well so I
want to talk about why this is
interesting why in the
Bible people were living to a thousand
years old really early on living to 900
years old living to 1100 years old I'm
going to talk about that about how that
happened and what was going on if you
guys actually are interested in that
kind of information I'm not sure but I
want to drop some stuff on that maybe on
medical Med podcast as well at Apple
podcast check out the black tongue
episode on medical meem podcast if you
haven't checked that out all right
okay all right just going to sip this
real
quick micro medical medium shock therapy
love
it
powerful and delicious you put a little
bit of honey in there and you have a
little bit of that fresh squeezed orange
juice in
there right
incredible all right I'm going to get
the total immune out I want to do a
little total immune
shot mebe 787 on YouTube good to see you
all right you're out and about what's
the IG handle please the IG handle
please medical medium it's medical
medium Marissa spiritual good to see you
too on YouTube I read your comments too
yes aw they are stealing your verbage oh
are they ever information constantly
about Metals too right stuff that isn't
anywhere science or nowhere they just
where do they get it they just came out
of thin air where'd it come from I know
it's yeah it's so dark and it's coming
out of them yeah I know I know it's
actually sick and then they're running
ads to the medical medium Community with
the medical medium information how sick
is that pretending they came up with it
or something it's actually despicable
like how can people live with themselves
it's because they're they're slimy
Kimberly says I have been listening to
your new podcast they are awesome thank
you thank you for listening thing and
I'm going to put out a stream of them a
steady stream of medical M podcast at
Apple podcast don't miss them make sure
your notifications are on make sure
you're always checking in case you don't
get notified yeah I know okay okay so
the total immune is really revolutionary
all on its own okay it's like with me I
I know that people need their immune
system
strengthened but they need them rebuilt
rebuilt not just fortified not just
strengthened not just supported but
rebuilt because that's the kind of
immune system trouble so many people are
in thyroid problems hypo hyper you know
nodules cysts on the thyroid whether
they're tiny or large people that deal
with all kinds of issues under the sun
everything from neurological problems
from skin problems our immune systems
are under attack
from everything from fragrances and
anything people who drink alcohol it's
another thing did you know that it was
taboo you guys on another note can't
help it you know that it was taboo to
either to utter the word you can't do
alcohol like it's bad for you it's not
good for you it's not going to help you
even all the vegan
doctors podcast doctors all drink all
drink wine champagne everything right
vodka all drink okay and then suddenly
now years after I've been talking about
how bad alcohol is and I was getting
crap for it that was taboo you weren't
allowed to talk about it on a podcast
anywhere you weren't allowed to talk
about it on social you mentioned that
alcohol was bad everybody The Gauntlet
came down on you man to chop off your
head I'm not kidding but yet I stayed
with it stayed with it stayed with it
talked about the books stayed with it
was heavy on it said no you can't do
this if you want to heal you got to get
off alcohol it's bad for you whatever
and then now guess what they're all
paring it now like yeah alcohol is bad
for your brain really cuz science
doesn't say that where did you get that
idea all right look what I like about
total
immune okay
is
um the fact that it works that's just
one right off the the bat me me over
there on on YouTube I noticed that Mayo
Clinic Now talks about non- rashing
shingles no mention of the source um
there is a hijacking of the medical
medium non- rashing shingles information
both there at Mayo PubMed wherever all
of all of it like they've just hijacked
medical medium information with no
science and no studies behind it no
studies behind it and when you look when
you look at whatever they show check
this out how sick is this when they look
when you look they show they're talking
about post herpetic pain when the rash
goes
away but they're trying to chalk that up
as it it's non- rashing shingles no they
had the rash it went away and then they
had pain for a year so science of
research did do a couple of papers where
you have pain for a year or more after
shingles but that's not non- rashing
shingles non- rashing shingles is
medical medium information it's having
shingles never a rash ever and having
symptoms right well now they're claiming
they knew that when they didn't no signs
to back it up but mayo and everybody
else is using medical meme information
on that just CRA it's crazy you know
what there's you know there's good news
though because they're so evil that when
you leave here that evil and you don't
make good with that you don't resolve it
you don't you don't work on that you
don't clean about like how many people
you screwed over with chronic illness
that couldn't get back to the source to
heal and it's your fault that so many
people aren't going to heal because you
were evil and you didn't care and you
stole that information to just
manipulate people and then you're on
your deathbed many years down the road
you think you're just in the clear with
that you think you're in the
clear I see my medicinal home on YouTube
propolis shock therapy is in the brain
saver protocol book it helped heal my
canker sorce and that's the propolis
right there I'll give you a close-up on
the propolis you
guys I mean honestly look if you look if
if you can get one thing one thing okay
you can't you can't lose with total
immune you can't lose the propolis pure
if you can get two things it's like
total immune propolis pure
right if you can get two things that's
how critical that is for our immune
systems right there that's how critical
that is all right you guys we're talking
about all kinds of good stuff flu and
everything else in post flu and post RSV
RSV and white lung and neuro viruses
which are going around and we talked
about like manufacturing they got the
manufacturing plant right there they're
growing the viruses spawning them right
out of eggs themselves and then they get
released Magic Al into our environment
and it hits the village right here and
then they calculate it on the calendar
of when they're going to release the
next one and next one because they want
to clobber the crap out of everybody's
immune system and they want elderly
people to die early so that's the
plan and if you don't believe it then
fine it's all make
believe sure we can think that maybe
it's just all make believe and it never
happens no and that's fine whatever want
to think but yeah it's interesting isn't
it all right so what I'm doing right
here is I am I got my total immune right
there I take shots of it I put it in the
shot glass just like this
okay and I'm going to pop a little bit
of orange ju so I want to talk about
this there's a lot of people that even
know these don't taste bad these taste
good some of some of the vimergy
products taste amazing that people don't
like to use water they can use juice
then so here I got some fresh squeezed
orange juice and pouring in in there it
is and
mhm all
right top 20 things to keep a strong
immune system get plenty of sleep but
what if I can't get plenty of sleep what
if I can't what if I'm working too hard
what if I'm too too stressed out get a
minimum of 8 to 10 hours a night sleep
if you're actually somebody that's
having any kind of problems okay yeah
easy for you to say let me just
magically sleep 10 straight hours
because I have such an easy life maybe
I'll sleep 12 hours because I have such
an easy life like okay look maybe some
of you guys do sleep 12 hours because
you know you do but I'm just saying that
a lot of people can't get that 12h hour
sleep in I've had two hour nights I've
had four hour nights because I had
deadlines on stuff when I did the brain
books I was sleeping like 3 hours on the
average every single night to get those
brain books to everybody
that's was like 3 hours of sleep every
night what if you can't go and just have
this magical nice life where you're
sleeping 12 hours a night what if you
can't I know I sure as hell can't I mean
crap three hours a night of sleep when I
was doing the brain books so yeah so
guess what I cranked up my Subs right I
cranked them up total immune wasn't out
at that time right but other stuff was
right cranked up the golden seal I
cranked up the propolis pure I cranked
up my B12 and that's what I used to push
through and to do
that Angelo over there okay on X see do
the mm Skin Potion it will help your
hair too Christino Lee says on YouTube
what are your suggestions for night
shift workers I'm a nighttime post
production coordinator for a TV show and
work 6 pm to 4 a.m. hey you're on my
schedule that's amazing but am often up
until 5 to 6: a.m. how do I need to
supplement my body first and foremost
right always remember that even if
you're not sleeping if you're just
laying there and you're resting your
nerves and your eyes are shut your
immune system is recovering just from
that alone and I want to say this this
is very important for people who can't
sleep or can't get enough sleep they're
working hard everything's off right is
that when you're even laying there
you're laying there and you're calm and
you're shutting your eyes your immune
system is responding and it's
reproducing and it's building back up
even if you're just laying there you
guys keep that in mind even if you're
somebody who's struggling with insomnia
or you have some kind of sleep issue
your immune system is sitting there
building and rebuilding up when when
you're actually just laying there with
your eyes shut relaxing relxing keep
that in mind right there okay what I
would do if I was on your schedule which
I am on your schedule pretty much I'll
work 20 hour days whatever and I'm on
your schedule where I'm working all
through the night too I've done that so
many times I crank up my micro c i Crank
It Up that is something I do I crank up
the the micro I crank up the
B12 these are some of the things that I
do and then I I focus on hydration I
focus on a little bit of coconut water I
focus on right my celery juice I if I
can if I can get it done I I focus on
that um there's there's other things too
but and I don't eat really heavy meals
that's one thing right there I don't eat
real heavy dense meals that are fatty I
don't eat big fatty meals when I'm
underslept because that's a recipe right
there for a heart attack right there
you're eating heavily ladened fat yeah
overt fat meals now all the vegans are
doing overt fats that's what they're
doing they're all doing overt fats all
the animal protein people they're all
doing overt fats if you're not if you're
working really hard and you're not
sleeping much cranking up over fats it's
like asking for a heart attack I mean so
then so I make sure that that's not
happening that's important on its
own
yep great information you guys talk
about rebuilding the immune system a
little bit couple things you can do
right okay I was going to the top of the
list what you'll see out there it's
happening now it's like great ways 10
great ways to rebuild your immune system
sleep a crap ton of hours um stay away
from fried greasy food um and you know
the list goes on right there's a whole a
whole bunch of things out there like
that okay and so my list is making sure
I got enough zinc making sure I got the
micro SE making sure I'm taking my
propolis pure every single day making
sure I am hydrated but not hydrated with
like garbage stuff not hydrated with
with um you know alkaline water um you
know uh products and stuff like that on
the Shelf where they're like this is
alkaline water and you guys seen what's
happening out there right there's some
bad stuff that's happen it's terrible
it's terrible and I've been telling
people stay away from alkaline water
crap that's out there I've been how many
how many years have I told people to
stay away from that and look what just
happened I mean it was just terrifying
what just happened to people out there
right it's like you know like there's a
lot of things that I do to keep the
immune system strong and you know what I
do is I eat every couple of hours so
that my adrenals aren't flooding so if
you want to keep your immune system
strong you want to build your immune
system back
up you make sure you're not trashing
your adrenals get caffeine out of
there get caffeine out that's critical
by the way there's no science behind
caffeine hurting the immune system but
recently I saw something out there of
somebody like yeah stay away from
caffeine really because there's no
science that says it they science says
caffeine is good for you it's
crazy
so how it is the point is is staying
away from caffeine eating every couple
of hours don't intermittent
fast when you want to rebuild your and
recover your immune system don't do the
intermittent fasting where you're on
coffee all day then you eat a big greasy
fried meal at the end of the night or a
big overt fat meal at the end of the
night I'm intermittent fasting my
stomach's staying down I'm not as
bloated at night I could eat what I want
yeah you just trashed your adrenals
people who intermittent fast they seem
to improve improve but do you hear about
like things like 5 years later ask him
then oh yeah um well uh I don't know my
health has been really gone to [ __ ] um
all these different things yeah but you
were on social media talking about how
your urit and fasting four years ago and
how great you were doing yeah but then I
went to carnivore and then I got really
sick on Carnivore and then I tried this
and then I tried that and I was trying
this new program that I just purchased
for $5,000 from this guy that says he's
a chiropractor or something like and
then I just did this and did that and
people are just like they're everywhere
and it's like Yeah because it didn't
work intermittent fasting burns out the
adrenals so what I like to do is I like
to eat every couple of hours I'll have a
banana I'll have some oranges
right I'll eat some
cucumbers right I'll drink my celery
juice I'll have a little coconut water
okay I'll have some fresh squeezed you
know fresh squeezed orange juice okay
and then but I'll be I'll be eating I'll
be eating I'll have some dates but I'll
be eating every couple of hours I'll
have some greens I some colored greens
and some dates and I'll just eat them
together I'll have some kale on some dat
I'm just saying that this is what I do
and it's to keep the
adrenals strong then I'll have some
steamed potatoes later but it'll keep
the adrenals strong and it'll also stop
the adrenals from releasing and that
lowers the immune system there's so many
things you can do I mean that's what I
do right there keeping myself like
stable so that a I'm not burning the
gasoline in my body which is your
adrenaline I'm not burning it all out
and then I do medical medium recipes
like medical medium soup recipe with
there's so many soup recipes and light
options in the medical medium um books
that are incredible to help protect you
if you're not sleeping as much if your
immune system is low if you got to
support and rebuild your immune system
live Li rescue smoothie rebuilds your
liver's immune system heavy metal detox
the medical me and heavy metal detox
incredible for the immune
system so
yeah all these things you guys know the
tools you guys read the
books definitely organic red apples yeah
they're wonderful did you do you
remember the whole green apple thing
remember the fruit fear was so bad
before medical medum information C back
down on it and broke its back do you
remember
that and when literally every single
acupuncturist naturopath herbalist do
functional medicine doctor MD said stay
away from red apples only eat a green
apple low
glycemic just a granny smith apple is
all you're allowed the rest is just
Atkin where you're just eating meat meat
meat and you can have a green apple how
stupid was that the point is is we broke
we broke down the walls of of fruit fear
and yes red apples you're allowed to
have you guys anyway check these out so
let me run through them a little bit too
right that's the propolis pure that is a
gift from God that's what that is the
propolis pure is a gift from God it
truly is I'm going to pour a little bit
out here it's like
this it's the way I like my
propolis
I just pour a little bit right out I'm
going to do a little cocktail right here
I'm going to do some total
immune I'm going to pop a little golden
seal in here too as
well let me pop some golden seal in here
nice I'm going to pop a little bit of
B12 in here too there we
go right
there looking good I'm going to pop a
little fresh squeezed orange juice right
in there as
well
okay and there it is you can mix it if
you would like too you can mix it in
your little shot glass I've never mixed
it in a shot glass before I'm actually
trying
it and of course I make myself a
mess there we are that's my
little immune sister immune system
rebuilding
shot huh
what bartender give me
another too
good can I have some of that orange
juice that
spiked and I chase it down with a little
bit of orange
juice so good bartender give me another
Mr Ferguson get Mr Ferguson
downstairs you guys this is been
incredible we covered a lot of stuff we
talked about the intestinal tract we
talked about the the different bugs that
are going around how they're going
around how they release them out there
why they do it we talked about uh
supporting the immune system in so many
different ways I love you guys listen
make sure you sign up to my newsletter
because I'm going going to be doing a
book signing in person and it's going to
be in La I don't have the dates yet but
I'm working on it it's going to be in La
I've never done a book signing an
official book signing ever in all the 10
years and all these books and everything
I've never done one and I'm going to do
one in La I hope you guys if you're in
the area or if you're heading out there
I hope you come and bring your books
just bring your old books books I'll
sign up your old books right there right
there in front of you voila that's what
I'm going to do and um so I'm just
letting everybody know to keep a lookout
at Lookout for that so and make sure
you're signed up to the IG broadcast
where you get a DM message from me
because I'm going to leave like really
great stuff information from Spirit of
compassion and I'm going to leave a
telegram message tonight be sure to
subscribe to
t.me slmed medium that's my
telegram rosangela aw could we have a
little soul talk please or just some
enduring words of wisdom it's a crazy
time at the moment I'll do that tonight
I will actually leave a telegram and
I'll do some soul talking on the
telegram
tonight I'm
gonna I don't know what time but I'm
going to do it tonight yes wondering
wishing good to see you on YouTube yes
telegram message
yes telegram message you guys
incredible um so yeah check things out
oh medical mean podcast and apple
podcast black
tongue yep it may not be interesting to
someone until you get one and you got a
black tongue and then you're going to be
interested crispy perspective hey
crispy you leave some serious comments
there's one that you left
recently that it read I was blown away
about o I'm at the vet emergency right
now due to my dog having been
attacked stomach in knots I'm praying
for you crispy okay I'm praying for you
and your dog and I'm so sorry stomach is
at knots mine is too um I do have a weak
spot a real serious weak spot and that's
that's animals going through anything
that's just that that's that's my
kryptonite
mebe 787 wine was recommended as a
health drink for pregnant women 13 years
ago when my wife was pregnant 13 years
ago that's it just 13 years ago check
this out too okay wine was recommended
by podcast doctors up until a few years
ago until they were kind of like getting
scared that we talked about it so much
being that bad and they're like oh crap
the medical meme community and the
medical meme information is taking a
turn and pissing everybody off Terry
Johnson over there on YouTube I knocked
down shingles with zinc shock and
propess shock therapy added to Total
immune and move forward
rapidly yeah
amazing Elaine I would love the
spiritual book please I was I was
delayed on the spiritual book because of
all the
lies and crap and false stories and all
that like stuff that they try to do
framing me and everything else for
something I I didn't do and so yeah
pretty sick right pretty demented just
slowed everything down and no I don't
have a spiritual book right now but yeah
I would love to do one and finish one
Maria man forini so thankful for this
info and you so thankful for you too
thank you for being here and I mean that
though I actually mean that yeah you
guys incredible all right love you guys
I will see you next time let people know
where the info is at so they can
heal yep and give me a thumbs up or a
like or whatever it is on YouTube or
whatever whatever you know platform
you're on that would be
amazing zero VR aw please tell me it is
possible to heal allergies to dogs had a
lot of people heal their dog allergies
I'm going to do a podcast episode um
medical mean podcast at Apple Apple
podcast and it's going to be I'm going
to be talking about animals and stuff at
some point so just listen
out
yep all
right
okay all right you guys oh wait wait
wait so you want to actually heal
allergies to your dog dog allergies yeah
a lot of people a lot of people have
healed their dog allergies their animal
allergies and cat allergies a lot of
people have using medical meme
information so many throughout the years
so me keep a light heart always ask your
doctor what's right for you but keep a
light heart but
yeah okay right there EO fruit and
veggies I almost thought it was fruit
and sandwiches no fruit and veggies I've
healed pet allergies right there on
YouTube thank you for actually telling
everybody so you give them the
inspiration cuz that gave me inspiration
it's giving them inspiration Maria
Isabel over there on Facebook thank you
for all your valuable information thank
you for being here
Maria I do appreciate it you guys are
amazing Veronica thank you Anthony thank
you Veronica for being here over there
you
guys truly many
blessings yep and um love you guys I do
guys on Tik Tok I'll see you next time
you guys on YouTube you guys on
Rumble I'll see you guys next time as
well and you guys on IG I will see you
next