science protects itself is what it does
in chronic illness not in some other
things because I love science research
but it protects itself in chronic
illness it doesn't protect the person
that's what it does by saying it's your
fault by saying you're the cause of your
illness by saying it's your body your
immune system
it protects signs of research because
they don't know the answers yet and it
puts the blame on you and what's the
best way to do it for science and
research and the conventional way and
even the alternative way now put the
blame on the woman put the blame on her
on her body being faulty on her being a
bad person on her being you know an
emotional problem with her illness
calling or you know maybe like it's all
in her head by saying you're crazy or
you're just bored or lazy or tired but
you're not really sick that's happened
for decades still it happens today