today we're talking about why eggs are
bad for you we're also making Millet
sushi too so I'm excited about that
we're making a millet Sushi I hope
everybody has their ingredients and
they're ready because that's going to be
totally fun here it is right out of
brains saer protocols now you might be
thinking this is going to be a terrible
show a horrible show because we're
talking about why eggs are bad for you
but when you hear what I have to say you
might take some consideration you might
think about it and it might play a role
in your health one way or another
whether you think the information is not
true or eggs can't be bad or I raise my
own eggs in the backyard and I have a
chicken shed or I've been getting fresh
eggs from my neighbor for 20 years and
nothing ever happened to me so how can
this be whatever it is that you think or
you have stored away in the memory bank
I still would like you to hear what I
have to say today of why eggs are bad
for you and we're going to make a recipe
and have some fun a little later on
first I got to get the Millet cooking
before we go into the egg
show all right what I'm doing here is
I'm going to do two cups of millet I got
a pot the pot's hot we're going to get
some water in here I'm going to go with
four cups of water into this hot pot
right here good to see you guys I hope
you watch the beginning of this show so
you get caught up on what's happening
this show is going to be shocking
actually kind of scary
shocking I hope we all can handle
it all right two cups of millet is what
I'm going to do for four cups
of water there's one cup of
millet let's go into two cups of millet
so what I'm going to do is try to scoop
this nice big one right there there and
I'm going to add a little bit more just
to make sure we're up to par two cups of
millet right there incredible what's the
Millet for the Millet is for the sushi
it takes place of rice in the sushi as
you can see right here in the Brain saer
book if you guys just got on here I just
want to forewarn you this is a show
about why eggs are bad for you and I
don't want you getting upset I don't
want you getting mad and some people are
just going to be like talking all kinds
of crazy like how dare you my
grandmother's 103 years old and she ate
eggs her whole life so there's no reason
why we should be able to eat them I get
it I know what you guys are thinking but
we're going to cover it and cover how
things
work I'm even nervous how about that I'm
even nervous who would have thought
right out of all the things I'm just
going to mix this Mill it in here a
little bit then I'm going to get a lid
on it I want it to simmer and I want to
keep a very small mild simmering going
on once it hits a
boil so I've been making Millet for
years more than three decades I like
Millet for a lot of just a lot of
different recipes it's grain I realize
that a lot of people they don't want a
grain in their diet I completely
understand but like medical medium
information goes you can go as far as
you
want far as you want you can be
grainfree
you can be on meat you can be on
something else but you you can use
whatever cauliflower rice the point is
medical meme information is about going
as far as you need to go when you want
to and when you're ready but also
certain ingredients like Millet when we
can use it if we would like to and so
forth I feel it's one of the best grains
from the information I've received from
my source if you're going to ever have a
grain or you can just do cauliflour Rice
as well that's an option too and I've
done that many times you guys are coming
on here we're getting ready for why eggs
are bad for you so you got to get ready
but I just want to get this Millet to a
simmer I want it cooking and we're going
to make the Millet Sushi a little later
on bring the temp down a little cuz it's
about to take a boil I got my Wasabi
right here I got my Nori sheets right
here do you have yours I want to make
sure everybody has their ingredients
with you all right swimming in the green
says I don't eat eggs should I still
wash
indeed you should indeed you shall for
sure Rebecca Leaf says I couldn't walk
two years ago I found your info on eggs
and immediately stopped eating them and
was able to walk again I was 49 years
old I'm going to read that one more time
I couldn't walk for 2 years two years
ago I couldn't walk found your info on
eggs immediately stopped eating them and
now I can walk I was able to walk again
Rebecca Leaf Becca Le that is incredible
thank you for leaving that comment
that's inspirational and
Powerful my God my God all
right wait do you have the rest of your
stuff do you have your carrots do you
have your cucumbers I am asking if you
have your cucumbers do you have your
carrots do you have your Ginger do you
have your carrots do you have your
oranges I want to make sure you guys are
paying attention here all right let's go
into it the eggs let's talk about
it why are they a problem before we go
into it I want to read you a little
something really quick
okay something that's very
interesting living hungry viruses did
you know viruses eat did you know all
viruses eat did you know viruses have to
eat in order to stay alive do you know
that when viruses eat they get strong
did you know they can
multiply you don't believe in viruses no
h you know when someone has Simplex
herpes one it's on their lip it's the
fever blister it's the cold
sore right you go and you kiss somebody
else or share a glass with somebody and
you have that fresh fever blister some
people's fever blisters gets pretty
gnarly that fever blister can spread to
the other person and then a couple of
months later or 3 days later depending
on the variety of the simplex one or 2
years later depending on the variety of
simplex one in the person's immune
system they will break out with a fever
blister and they will have their first
cold sore because there are viruses they
do exist I want people to heed that
understanding and actually realize that
when you hear out there viruses don't
exist it's all just parasites viruses
and bacteria don't exist it's all all
just parasites want people to understand
it's actually the opposite in the sense
where viruses exist hardcore baby it's
hardcore they're out there yes you guys
probably know that by now before the
whole sea thing that happened 3 years
ago before before that whole thing that
occurred right you know the crazy flu
stuff before it all occurred there were
a lot of people in health that didn't
even believe viruses even existed
anywhere and then that whole thing
happened in 2020
and then boom now even people in the
health realm and Alternative Health
believe that viruses do exist now
there's still a lot of people that don't
but they do just like you can catch
herpes simplex one just from a glass
just from bodily fluids just from
kissing someone and they have it too
just like you can catch that yes they do
exist and they're catchy for the record
viruses are
living in the publicly known Arena of
Science Now I want to just say this this
real quick publicly known Arena of
science what does that mean it means
what public publicly known like a doctor
down the road in a practice what he is
allowed to
know publicly known scientists what
they're allowed to know publicly known
medical research and science it's just
whoever is in the arena of Health what
they're allowed to know just so you know
there's a battle about whether viruses
are dead or alive viruses are alive and
viruses are hungry hungry hungry hippos
they
are no one can agree and neither side
has proven facts here's a pillar of
Truth viruses are alive viruses are
cells viruses eat now if you're
wondering where I'm going this is going
to be really interesting
here I'm going to a place of viruses eat
now what does that matter what does that
mean and why is he talking about eggs
being bad for us give you a quick window
really quick into it right now you got
an egg right here and you got a virus
right
here you eat the egg the virus eats the
egg you eat the egg the virus inside
your body starts to thrive and eat the
egg you might be somebody that
hey eats eggs for a lot of years I got
nothing wrong with me meanwhile you got
like ra rheumatoid arthritis meanwhile
you have other things too and you get a
fever blister once every six months
whatever it is what people don't realize
is the virus is helping to
feed off of the eggs the egg is helping
to feed the virus they work together
that's what it is they become one the
egg helps to feed the virus the virus
gets help from the egg and they work
together and they work with each other
that's how it works so you got to
remember that so when we eat eggs it's
good to know viruses are involved sure
viruses are not on the egg viruses may
not be inside the egg but as we eat the
egg viruses inside of us we'll start
feeding and eating the egg egg that's a
simple explanation in the moment but
we're going deeper we're going to talk
more about it so let's roll a little bit
for a virus to live long enough inside
the human body to create a chronic
symptom or condition it has to be able
to find food and sustain itself viruses
sustain themselves by fi finding
food by consuming things that it likes
to
eat and eggs are on the top of the
list now
now eggs are fun to eat they taste good
some people swear by them some people
say hey they don't hurt my stomach they
feel good inside of me we're going to
cover that too in a little while of why
eggs feel good in people's stomachs and
intestinal
tracts and how it doesn't seem like a
problem when someone eats an egg and
we're going to cover the whole chickens
behind the house on the farm the Chicken
Shack chicken right the p raised eggs
the farm raised eggs the backyard raised
eggs we'll cover that a little bit too a
virus does not have a
mouth it's not an
animal it's not like a human eating so
even though this little virus right here
has a mouth for fun viruses do not have
mouths they absorb the food through
their membrane that's what they do so
when Foods available it's inside your
liver it's inside your bloodstream it's
inside your organs
any viruses inside your body inside your
liver bloodstream your organs will find
that
food so we eat the food we eat the egg
the egg goes down inside of us it's in
our
stomach it's there starts to break apart
our hydrochloric acid starts to break
apart the protein and eggs
protein and with that the egg starts to
break apart and go through the
body just want to let everybody know if
you just got here we're making Millet
Sushi hang out it's going to be fun
we're talking about why eggs are bad for
you and truly I hope you don't get too
upset and too bummed out if you want to
eat eggs you can eat all the eggs you
want that's perfectly fine with me I'm
just saying hey I want to talk about why
maybe it's not a great
idea and show you in a presentation why
they're not good for you this is going
to be fun I know that this is a heated
topic people get charged they get jacked
up people get the pitchforks out the
Torches the shovels they want to beat my
head in man they want to just take me
out they do not like going like they
don't even like hearing
egg if it's going to be something bad
you eat the egg you chew the egg you
swallow the egg the egg gets down into
the
stomach what's left of your hydrochloric
acid because most people have low
HCL what's left of the HCL starts to
work on it and breaks down the proteins
of the
egg the fat from the egg by passes the
stomach and ends up in the dadna
your liver has to produce
bile and the bile has to come up and
into the intestinal tract to break down
the fats from the egg a normal
digestive
process but as this is happening signals
are
occurring and if you have bugs in you
which most likely you do do you have
chronic fatigue syndrome did you have
fatigue do you have brain fog do you
have tingles and numbness aches and
pains do you have ra
fibromyalgia did you have Lyme disease
were you somebody that was diagnosed
with Lyme disease years
ago what kind of symptom condition do
you have do you have
UTI do you get lung infections kidney
infections badder
infections
conjunctivitis
sty what do you have that's going on
what kind of symptom condition do you
have eczema do you have
psoriasis do you have
Vitiligo what else is happening inside
the body because people have symptoms
and
conditions much of which is caused by
pathogens which are
bugs and those bugs start seeking and
searching for particles of eggs
for instance strep a bacteria everybody
has many people have multiple varieties
of strep inside their intestinal
tract many people have multiple
varieties of strep inside their
lymphatic
vessels they have them in their ears and
around the inside of their ears they
have strep varieties on their
anus many people have strep sitting
on their
anus and when they go to the bathroom
strep pops off their anus and ends up in
the
toilet and sits there why more strep is
produced inside their
colon people are loaded with strep they
get the diverticulosis
diverticulitis they get different
problems in their intestinal tract they
get
IBS whatever kind of bugs you have those
bugs enjoy an
egg they enjoy
eggs something important to
know now we have these comforting
feelings around eggs I understand
completely we find them the ultimate
comfort food indeed we do we find them
the ultimate comfort
food so it's really hard to let go of
our eggs
because hey maybe your grandpa when you
were a kid made you eggs it was really
healing and really soothing maybe your
mom packed you up an egg salad sandwich
when you went to school elementary
school maybe Sunday brunches with family
there were different kinds of eggs
scrambled poach
omelets maybe have a loved one that made
you eggs every day of your life
maybe you remember as a kid just walk
into the chicken shed the coupe the
chicken Coupe and you harvested fresh
eggs yourself and it was just it's
ingrained in you and it's a beautiful
experience and you harvested your own
eggs for years and your family had them
I don't doubt any of that isn't good and
I don't doubt that any of that isn't
special or
beautiful that's not the problem the
world has changed
which leads to this next thing I want to
talk
about eggs would be fine and dandy they
would be fine and
dandy if what happened by the medical
industry didn't
happen don't blame me for being the
messenger and bringing you the
information about eggs about why they
are bad for you blame the industries the
medical industry yes that's why eggs are
bad for you
and I know that you're thinking hey look
okay I'm listening I'm
listening but it's not enough I want to
know how it works why people get sick
how come they can eat an egg and we'll
go into that as well so but let's hit
the medical industry first of all
classified medical industry let's start
with that for a little
bit back over 100 years ago they were
playing with their food they were trying
to feed virus uses and pathogens and
keep them alive in the
labs and what they found classified
medical research in science was that if
they cut open the top of the
egg and they
Place
pathogens
bacteria
viruses inside the egg they would would
duplicate they would Mass
produce inside the
egg now when they took those viruses and
those pathogens and that
bacteria and they put it
beside some bacon
pork it didn't Mass produce like
that so over a hundred years ago they
took bacteria and viruses in the lab and
they put it beside pork they put it
beside meat beef they put it beside
different vegetables and they
noticed that none of the pathogens would
Thrive they wouldn't explode they
wouldn't duplicate
multiply but what they did notice is
when they took took the
egg and just the outside of the egg and
they put pathogens on the outside of the
eggshell they noticed the pathogens
would stay
alive
interesting and then when they cut the
egg open and they cut the top of the egg
open and they had it in their little
dish
thing they notice when they cut the tops
of the eggs and they put pathogens
within it back bacteria they already
identified they noticed that an
explosion
occurred for some
reason pathogens viruses
bacteria
mold
yeast
fungus grew
rapidly and exploded inside those
eggs and they knew they can use the eggs
as a tool now this is over 100 years
ago keep that in mind this is over a 100
years
ago but classified medical research and
science learned that they can manipulate
bugs sound
familiar sound familiar doesn't
it because bugs have been raised in labs
for well over a 100 years and that very
bug on your lip when you get the simp
Lex one was raised in a lab
originally and it was fed
eggs so that cold sore that you
developed a long time ago in your life
or just developed yesterday because you
picked up the cold sore the fever
blister from somebody else the simplex
one that bug is an old bug been around a
long time was raised in Labs off of
eggs very important to know let's take
it a little
further every single bug was raised on
eggs at one point early varieties of
Epstein bar virus were raised on eggs in
Labs Epstein bar anybody fibromyalgia
thyroid thyroiditis
Hashimoto
hypothyroidism ra psoriatic
arthritis lime disease yeah lime
disease ring a bell anybody the Epstein
bar virus long C long
Co the epin bar virus was raised early
on by medical research and Science in
Labs knowing knowing that the eggs was
an amazing fuel source for those
pathogens and those pathogens fed and
fed and fed on that egg material why now
let's go to that point real quick how
come viruses and bacteria and pathogens
thrive on egg how is it possible because
it's an underdeveloped
protein the egg has an
underdeveloped
protein a protein that's not fully
developed it's easy to conquer easy to
feed off
of pathogens and viruses devoured the
underdeveloped velop protein inside of
raw
eggs the baby chick never had a chance
never had a
chance for
survival not that it would have survived
the eggs were already cracked open and
used in the lab
anyway the chicken would have never made
it no matter
what but the underdeveloped proteins
that that baby chick had was a fuel
source for viruses to easily conquer and
invade
it was a quick fuel source whether
anybody likes it or
not what whether anybody likes it or not
I don't believe him that can't be true
he's evil what does he know he's not a
doctor I eat eggs every day and feed
them to my kids eggs are good staple for
me I got strong fingernails and I got
good skin my grandmother ate eggs for
150 years she never had a single problem
I get it everybody's going to be
freaking the Freak Out totally and they
do and they do I'm an athlete and I eat
eight eggs a day this is
BS go listen to blah blah blah this link
right here this guy will tell you how
good eggs are heard it all seen it all
it doesn't change one powerful fact the
industry used eggs to create more
viruses and
pathogens those were released in our
environment through certain
means and
exposures and those viruses have thrived
and that's why nursing homes have 30
year olds in them and that's why nursing
homes are loaded with 30y
olds uh-huh who can't use their arms and
legs any anymore who are literally
trapped in bed neurologically sick being
spoonfed IVs food being drawn up through
their stomach through a j
tube because of pathogens from
classified medical research and science
going all the way back over a hundred
years ago but eggs make me feel good but
eggs go really easy in my stomach he's
full of it eggs are great for you eggs
are high in
protein
but the viruses and the pathogens the
bacteria that are here and the super
fungus the super
fungus and the crazy bugs Mera and
crap they love eggs they love
eggs you're sitting in the hospital
you're battling a Mera infection from
hell and yeah can I have two eggs over
easy
please um can I ring the buzzer nurse
yeah nurse can can I have two eggs can I
have two scrambled eggs please can I
have two fried eggs is that okay coming
right up merca patient well make
sure it's not the people in the
hospital's fault it's nothing like that
it's just a hardcore truth whether
anybody likes it or not
and guess what my feelings don't get
hurt when people talk crap about the
medical medium egg information that's
out
there I just always have this gleam of
hope that somebody who's really sick and
suffering and struggling who's eating
eggs in that moment might be able to
switch gears not eat eggs and get a
fighting chance so at least the
pathogens are keep that are keeping them
bedridden are not feeding on something
that in the end will keep them bogged
down
lot to talk about we're still going man
wild blueberry dreams on IG says a w my
functional medicine doctor had me
reintroduce eggs back into my diet and
soon after ended up in the hospital
diagnosed with multiple sorosis multiple
sclerosis I wrote in the medical medium
books from above Ms caused by Epstein
bar virus and lo and
behold Harvard took that information
from the books because guess what it was
published here first that Epstein bar is
the cause of multiple
sclerosis Queenie says over there in IG
funny how Fitness influencers I follow
that are in a strict diet with eggs Etc
are ending up in the hospital with
stomach problems funnier than that which
is not so funny can't tell you how many
Fitness instruct structors die of heart
attacks on their treadmills I can't tell
you how many train ERS die of heart
attacks at age 42 43 39 45 47 and I'm
not saying the eggs are doing it I'm
just saying whatever bugs and pathogens
and stuff inside of them it's having a
smorgasborg is having a Feeding Frenzy
man that's what's happening right there
Jenny Mack over there What on YouTube
great I was if BB Pro figure Fitness
bodybuilder eggs almost killed me
totally
understand wondering wishing says on
YouTube a doctor didn't get rid of my
migraines but medical medium information
did so happy to hear that by the way so
let's go into the body a little bit you
guys we're making Millet Sushi if you
just got on here before I go any further
of why eggs are
bad I'm letting you know I got some
Millet cooking right here do you have
Millet cooking did you cook yours
already maybe you don't do Millet and
that's fine are you doing cauliflower
rice cuz we're making sushi rolls do you
have that that's totally cool if you're
somebody that's into rice is it rice but
whatever it is we're making sushi I got
my ingredients here I'm pumped it's
minus the Mercury minus the Mercury man
which is the tuna fish right Erica over
there on YouTube says oh my God I have
cold Source all the
time cold sores all the
time Jolene says no such thing a
viruses it's terrain Theory clean up the
environment okay so if I'm laying in bed
and I'm
bedridden and I'm stuck in bed sick as a
goat I can't even use my arms and I got
tingles and numbness I got all kinds of
problems I got body pain that's killing
me my jaw is on fire my tongue
Burns I've been to 30 doctors I've tried
every drug
practically okay I'm going to take that
advice viruses don't exist that person's
right terrain Theory screw that Anthony
what does he
know instead it's like I'm sick I need
to get better what was that about the
eggs I need to know all right let's go a
little
deeper
here we
are got this little hardboiled egg right
here okay I don't care if it's over easy
fried poached I don't care if it's an
omelette I don't care if it's eggs
benedict I don't care if it's just in
your Mayo which is kind of funny because
how come we're told not to leave the
mayonnaise out in the sun because you
can
die how about
that how
about why would we
die if you leave that tuna salad
sandwich that tuna fish sandwich that
has mayo
outside too long you got to keep it
refrigerated
or you can
die are we allowed to leave egg salad in
the Sun how come we can't leave egg
salad in the sun all day because chances
are someone's going to say dear lord
lord throw that egg salad out you're
going to
die yeah interesting because I'm still
trying I'm like scratching my head and
I'm thinking how come how come if you
leave some cucumber salad in the outside
on the table and in the sun you're not
going to
die how about if you leave something
else out there too whatever some fruit
you're not going to die how
come you can even you can even leave a
steak sandwich out there you can leave a
freaking steak sandwich out there on the
table at a picnic for hours come to it
and be like whoo this is a good steak
sandwich I'm just going to eat this now
but the minute you leave an egg salad
out there on the table and you went out
there playing frisbee for a couple of
hours and that egg salad sitting on the
table someone's going to say oh my God
don't eat that smack it out of your hand
slam you in the face while you spit out
that egg salad and they're going to say
what do you want to
die how
come because
eggs can explode with bacteria and
pathogens that's why because too many
people have gotten sick from eggs
sitting out too long or at a picnic or a
mayonnaise they've gotten sick food
poisoning W how is that possible is it
okay what about an orange sitting out on
the table half the day are you going to
die if your orange is sitting on the
picnic table for half the day are you
going to die then you can go up there
and eat that orange right but how is it
possible you leave that egg salad out
there too long or how about this potato
salad with the mayonnaise you leave that
out there too
long you're playing Russian roulette
man crazy next thing you know you're
barfing your brains out you're [__]
your brains out you're in the hospital
you're on IVs you're totally your system
is crashed your your immune systems
crashed your adrenals are crashed
because that Mayo that egg can PL riate
man it can explode in bugs because bugs
feed off of eggs I'm sorry to tell you
but it's more than that bugs inside of
our body feed on the eggs we
eat important to
know I'm going to check my
Millet want to give him a little Quick
Check
nice want to make sure it's good I think
it
is let's
go excuse me I hope you're okay with
this hold
on don't want to burn my mouth it's done
it's cooked I just would like to taste
it m so good
perfect
wow all right c a little bit
more yep guys we're going to make Millet
sushi in a couple minutes just want to
give you a little bit more insight on
eggs you eat the egg the egg ends up in
the stomach if you're somebody with acid
reflux and you got bacteria creating
that acid reflux if you're somebody with
ulcers and you got bacteria creating
those ulcers guess what the bacteria is
going to feed off of it's going to feed
off of egg particles underdeveloped
proteins the minute that egg drops drops
down into your intestinal tra and you're
dealing with crohn's colitis
IBS any kind of inflammation in your
intestinal tract corners of your colon
corners of your small intestinal tract
ilium anything you got in there bacteria
strep staff
SEI it's going to have a bonanza it's
going to be eating off the
underdeveloped egg proteins it's going
to feed off of it I hate to bring this
news
once that egg gets down and it's now
down there to the alium it comes back up
it's it's asending then it's going
across then it's descending and we got a
whole bunch of different kinds of strep
and other things in this bacteria yeast
bad yeast fungus that's not the good
fungus all of it mold whatever we got in
US guess what it's going to thrive and
it's going to be happy and it's going to
feed off those particles but more than
that when that that egg is sitting
inside the intestinal
tract it's going to start going through
the intestinal tract lining as it's
being broken down and digested and
particles of that egg is going to ride
up into the liver up the hepatic portal
Highway when it gets to the
liver people have a lot of sick livers
they're loaded with things that create
things like hepatitis C which is Epstein
bar
they have all kinds of pathogens and
bugs inside their
liver it's going to feed off of the egg
inside the liver people walking around
with sick livers I couldn't believe it I
saw an ad the other day an ad out there
on
social of some [__]
drinking and I say this with
respect some [__] doctor or somebody
out of respect was drinking a whole big
thing of olive oil telling people this
is really good for
you a ni nice way to kill your liver
just kill your liver drink let's just
drink a whole thing of olive oil why am
I saying this
because those same practitioners and
doctors believe in eggs they believe in
them like nobody's business they believe
eggs are good they're filled with
nutrients I get it there's nutrients in
eggs there's some minerals and eggs of
course because the baby chick needed
those
minerals there's protein and eggs under
under develop proteins but they're there
there's amino acids and eggs of course
the baby chicken needed those amino
acids there's a lot of different
nutrients inside the eggs too to provide
that baby chick steam to actually
develop and
grow and I think a lot of people are
hanging their hat on that my eggs have
you know a mega 3es in them our eggs at
our farm have lots of Omega-3s in them
our farm fresh eggs are loaded with
Omega-3s and many
nutrients that doesn't determine what's
going to happen with bugs inside of us
that are keeping us sick it's not going
to
determine what bugs in us do just
because there is a little bit of Omega-3
in somebody's farm fresh eggs doesn't
mean that's going to protect you for
when the pathogens viruses yeast and
mold have a Feeding Frenzy on particles
of egg that it wants there ain't no
omega-3 that's going to stop that and
there ain't no mineral and there ain't
no Trace mineral and there ain't no
nutrient or amino acid throwing nothing
like that inside that egg that's going
to stop that pathogen from eating and
eating and here's the other thing you
can be healthy seemingly healthy and you
can have eggs every single day you can
be eating them and lo and behold you
finally get sick because guess what one
egg too much pushed you over the edge
your immune system was low Death By A
Thousand Cuts you already had other
exposures and problems maybe you picked
up a new bug in a relationship or
something and finally that omelette
you're eating or that poached egg or
that fried egg or over easy or sunny
side up got to you finally because it
fed the pathogens and maybe that
UTI that you got that you had to take
antibiotics for wouldn't have happened
if eggs weren't in your system all these
years and you weren't eating eggs on a
regular basis you would have been
protected from that UTI because those
eggs just push things over the edge just
enough for pathogens and bacteria to
feed on those eggs and then double in in
amounts per ounce of
blood when we eat the egg goes into our
liver it goes up the hepatic portal vein
it goes into our bloodstream and if
you're you're dealing with infections
all through your body like trigeminal
neuralgia because you got simplex one or
the shingles you dealing with the
shingles and the shingles is giving you
all this jaw pain all this ear pain and
facial pain and your nerves are inflamed
your vagus nerves are inflamed all
through your body and you're
struggling and you're panicking and you
got problems with your nervous system
eggs will help and feed the problem they
won't help fix the problem they help
worsen the problem now I don't tell
people never eat an egg if you don't
want an egg I tell them if you're sick
and you're struggling it would be a good
idea if you refrain from eggs and keep
them back and not have them in your life
because they're
trouble because they feed the bugs all
right you guys I'm going to make some
Millet
Sushi let's roll let's have some
fun and on a note okay I know the
emotional attachment to eggs I know the
Comfort the comfort food I know that
some people say it's the one thing that
doesn't bother my stomach because if I
eat a raw vegetable my intestinal track
if I eat a lettuce my intestinal tra
hurts and doesn't feel good I know
there's a whole bunch of people and they
say when they eat an egg it feels good
let me tell you why real quick before we
get
rolling when you have eggs they don't
rub against your intestinal lining when
you eat an
egg they don't massage your intestinal
lining this is so important to know
probably one of the most important
things to know because I know so many
people are going to be like no eggs make
my stomach feel
good but what you have to
know is that the eggs turn into a
liquefied glue that doesn't massage or
create peristaltic action it doesn't rub
your Linings when you eat a piece of
lettuce it must massages the Linings as
it's going through you when you eat a
little piece of red cabbage when you eat
some
Millet when you eat a piece of fruit an
orange it's going to massage it's going
to go through your intestinal tract and
you might be one of those people where
you've got hot spots inside your
intestinal tract pockets of inflammation
because of pathogens bacteria likee
strep and different viruses and those
Pockets that have the strep and the
different viruses and yeast and mold and
fungus that's not the good fungus when
you have pockets of this you get
inflammation in the pockets expansions
and narrowings your small intestinal
tract will expand in areas and it'll
also narrow and tighten up and lose its
elasticity in areas and
then you eat something like a vegetable
you eat a steamed vegetable you eat a
raw vegetable you eat a piece of lettuce
you eat it orange you eat a piece of
fruit you eat a cucumber and you're like
I'm not digesting this food good I can't
eat salads I can't digest good but what
you don't know is it's digesting it's
just that you're feeling it rub and
you're feeling it roll and when it rubs
and rolls you got hot spots you're going
to be like I better go back to eating
eggs because those eggs felt good and
the reason why they may feel good is
because they become a glue they become a
liquefied goop and that liquefied goop
doesn't rub it doesn't touch the
intestinal lining too much it goes
through and it sits there like a goo and
it's not creating peristaltic action
it's not going into corners and cleaning
them out instead it's feeding what's
ever there to begin with that's giving
you the sensations of I got problems
with my intestinal tract and guts to
begin with and that's why people find
eggs soothing they find them easy on the
system they find that they're not
creating a problem in the moment they
could eat the eggs they feel soft
they're cuddly they feel like a warm
comfortable blanket and that's how it
feels inside of
us and we get tricked and we think we're
good and we're
fine all
right now I'm hoping to actually
replicate this right here but if you've
ever been to Medical medum lives and
recipes and stuff like that occasionally
it just goes a little different but I'm
going to try to make it look like this
I'm going to marinate the
ginger in some squeezed orange juice let
me get rid of
these you
know let me get rid of
these just hold
on hold hold
on just hold out a bit this don't worry
I'm closet eating the eggs you guys
didn't see that right all right I'm
going to
marinate you know I wake in the morning
and I'm like am I going to create a
situation where someone's not going to
be happy I'm going to slice the ginger
and I'm going to get the orange juice
going first of all let's get some orange
juice
going
nice all right let's get a little juice
from the orange squeezed in
here no disrespect to egg lovers no
disrespect to
chickens you
know no disrespect to animal protein
eaters this isn't propaganda because the
vegans don't know this information they
never did this is not like a vegan
Channel where it's all about vegan vegan
you're evil if you eat meat you're evil
if you eat an animal protein this isn't
what this is this is for all this is for
vegans plant-based people cuz they end
up eating eggs anyway they go back to
eating eggs the minute they get a
symptom because they're eating you know
a vegan diet they get exposed exposure
problems expose to something they're not
eating um their vegan diet right right
for what they
need and so they end up getting sick
they get their first symptom and what
happens lo and behold they're freaking
out and they go back to eggs
anyway how many people do that there's
some people I think just in the medical
medium community that are that are like
telling people you need to eat meat
every day and eggs and
cheese because I'm telling you eating
medical medium is going to hurt you
meanwhile they weren't even eating
medical medium they were eating just fat
vegan overt fats just vegan food they
were eating like cupcakes with canola
oil throughout the years they were just
eating whatever but it was vegan
meanwhile they'll be like don't eat
medical medium you should be on eggs and
cheese and butter I give my kids eggs
and cheese and butter and lots of it
right now you you'll hear that once in a
while and it's like dude i' love to i'
love love to see what you were eaing all
these
years all right
so what I'm doing is I'm just squeezing
some
oranges I'm just going to marinate some
ginger in
here
great okay all
right now I want to kind of slice them
in slices just bear with me here and I'm
going to take off the Skins you can keep
the skins of your Ging Ginger maybe
we'll get some close-ups too today whoo
you can keep the
skins on your Ginger I'm taking them
off simple as that and I'm going to
slice them like this you can slice them
in different ways I'm going to slice
them this way hold on here there we
go nice I'm doing thin slices of Ginger
here not thick
ones
and I'm just being slow and a little bit
more
careful
great as you can see we have some orange
juice I'm going to put these slices in
here and I'm going to marinate them get
them
going look you can eat eggs if that's
what you want to do I'm still going to
love you I'm still going to like you I'm
not going to hate you I'm not going to
think you're a bad
person nothing of the sort just going to
get some more Ginger going
here eat what you
want
right and and that's fine but I'm going
to give you the
four warning the
messages that I can message to you about
how it works with eggs
and we're going to we're not even done I
have to tell you why it even got to this
degree eggs were a great survival food
years ago before 100 years ago they were
an important
staple and everybody needed to eat them
everybody they needed to eat them for
survival okay so I'm marinating let's go
there we go take a look you guys and see
what you think how's yours coming along
cuz I know that we're doing this
together today do you have everything
you need if you don't have everything
just make one without something how
about that like if you don't have the
Cabbage then make it without cabbage if
you don't have the ginger then that's
okay now I just need a little honey in
here and I'm going to mix it
up eggs were a really powerful survival
food people need needed
them they were a
lifesaver famine it stopped families
from starvation in the Dead
Winter chicken coups were
everything everybody had a chicken cpop
everybody had one if they
could I'm just mixing this up this is a
little marinade
here but the the world has
changed they manipulated the eggs and
they ruined eggs on people of course you
can still enjoy them and have them but
if you get sick someday you're feeding
whatever pathogens are creating your
sickness it's not your fault they ruin
the eggs they just they do diabolical
things that's how the industry Works
they do diabolical stuff you must know
this by now who doesn't know this by
now let's make some
nice little fixings
here for our Millet sushi so I'm just
going to cut this down back here little
like
that we
go couple of ways you can slice a
cabbage for
this you can you can cut it in half this
way
okay and then I'm going to make
these nice pieces like this there we go
you don't want them so big if you do
them too
big what's going to happen is it they
could pop through they can break through
your Nori if if you make them too
big so I'm doing these slices these
ribbons right out of
here I don't want them too thick I don't
want them too thin
I just don't want big hunky pieces
that's just not going to work all
right here we
go
nice
nice I'm going to put this aside if
you're okay with
that okay let's
roll and then we're going to stick some
eggs in this gory
roll no we're not yeah we are no we're
not yeah we are okay let's get a
cucumber going I'm gonna peel this
cucumber if you guys don't mind got a
peeler we're peeling our cucumber
here
yes okay
I like getting the skin off the the
Cucumber because this is not a garden
cucumber you do a garden cucumber man I
love leaving the skin on because it's
not a garden cucumber uh I don't want to
keep the skin
on they put waxes on the skin of the
organic cucumbers they put waxes on
everything they put all kinds of MSG
there's nicotine on produce all of that
stuff I'm just not kind of in the mood
for that right
here and I washed that cucumber just so
you know now I am going to cut this
cucumber in
half so what I'm going to do like this
for a moment can you guys see
that boom
right okay and then I'm going to cut
this cucumber this way
right we
go all right then I'm going to make
these nice
rectangle
sections like
this there you go you don't want them
like huge you want them just
right
there we
go being
cautious you guys see that how does that
look does it look
good I hope you guys are making it with
me if you're not still great it's
okay look at that
huh perfect Siz Jennifer says over there
on YouTube my daughter has a bad cold
making her vitamin C shock therapy as I
watch
you wo
boom you see the
powder and this insane deal by the way
vimergy has that powder and they're
giving away a
free lemon balm take a look you guys up
close look at that and it's the best
quality stuff there is I did a lemon
bomm presentation one day with you guys
remember and I had all those different
lemon bombs and I showed you the
differences in why so crazy you get a
free bottle right here of this lemon
bomb which is actually incredible stuff
I know you probably can't see it I just
don't want to spill it but there you
go
nice look at
that it's just it's just incredible
stuff really is look at
that
amazing you guys know I work with these
guys mem is an amazing company that's
the micro SE powder um when you purchase
the micro SE powder they give you the
free lemon balm that's how it works just
want to tell you why we're making the
mil sui since you brought it
up
amazing collagen building skin you guys
like my skin you like my skin it's
glowing my skin is glowing I just just
had a facial never had a facial in my
life I just had a facial I got my facial
appointment I was wrapped up in seaweed
had my whole body wrapped up my face
wrapped in seaweed and they stuck me in
some kind of thing and they heated it up
and then they gave me this facial and
scrubbed my face and exfoliated they
didn't never did one of those in my life
never not saying it's bad or good I'm
just saying I never did anyway for the
skin for the skin and the immune system
with all the colds going around when you
purchase the micro C the link is in the
bio and description when you use the
link in the bio description and purchase
the micro SE they load this up in the
cart
free nervine nervous system the lemon
bomb you guys by any chance do you hear
it out there I just want to ask you do
you hear it out there you hear it lemon
bomb use lemon bomb I'm Dr ston so use
lemon bomb hear it it's everywhere
everywhere I'm an influencer and I
recommend lemon bomb I'm a trainer on IG
and you should be on lemon bomb every
single person in health is squealing
lemon bomb because of medical medium
information and medical medium books
teaching people how powerful lemon bomb
is and what it does and because of that
it literally started an entirely new
trend which is the lemon bomb Trend it's
in everybody's green powder everybody's
whatever it's in everything it's just
used everywhere because of medical meum
information in books and that's why the
lemon bomb thing is crazy right now out
there but that's the best lemon bomb out
there it goes comes free with the
micro all right all right I'm getting
hungry let's just make sure we do this
here cut a few more of
these I like these nice squares
triangles
it should look good all right we got our
cabbage we got our Millet cabbage we got
our Ginger soaking in here take a look
let's keep it going we need carrots
now we need
carrots let's get some carrot action
going real quick can you guys see this
let's do a little peeling of the carrot
of course I I can hear it now I hear
someone yeah I hear someone talking
someone talking in the crowd there I
hear them out there they're saying keep
the skins on they have nutrients why are
you doing that there's dirt in the
carrot skin they got nutrients
man and I agree they do but these
carrots I'm skinning them I want them to
pop inside
yeah so let me just get a couple more of
these real
quick take a look you guys peeling
them I'm I'm getting this these aren't
from the garden I'm getting the skins
off of these carrots they're not from
the garden they're from the
store they had a little bit of a smell
to like you know stuff that's just in
the store they were just a little bit
more of that so I want to take the skin
off they're fine they're good but they
had a little something going on like you
know what I mean like maybe someone
handled them with
cologne you you know you people walk
through the store they're hand you know
they're handling stuff they got fresh
cologne it's like let me put fresh
cologne all over my hands and all over
my face and put it all over my body and
then let me go into the store and then
wipe that cologne on everybody's fruit
and
vegetable all
right okay so let's let's get these
carrots going here all
right going to cut this carrot in
[Music]
half
just ranting a little bit about produce
in the
store all
right going to cut these a little
differently
here
okay and I'm going to cut these a little
differently
here there we go go can you guys see
this I'm making it a certain way I have
company coming over
later and I'm making these just a little
differently I want them to have a look
to them a little presentation to
them you don't want to stick big hunky
carrots in
there you don't want your nor roll to
have that you want it just just right I
mean you could do anything you want but
I'm I'm looking for something here I'm
searching for something searching for
certain
appeal there we
go so you
guys
um got a hankering for eggs right
now just kidding all
right boom
the thing is what people don't
realize is that everything does
count when when you're really sick it
all
counts and so I like
to get as much information as I can out
to people so they can make a decision
themselves conscious Choice how can you
make a choice if you don't know the
truth about something how can you make a
choice if you don't know what's really
happening out there how you might have
been tricked or duped in life
right can't make a choice if you don't
know what's going down if you don't know
what
happened keep that in
mind you can make your own decisions you
can say sure I can have an egg I'll just
grant myself permission I feel pretty
good these
days but I want people to know what's up
all right we got our carrots going I
might take these
CES slice them a little different real
quick add a different uh look to them
and we're almost there this is going to
be really good really
good
boom those are actually there we
go all
right
so okay can you guys see this
still all right just about there and
we're going to make these Millet sushi
rolls which are one of my favorites how
many of you guys have tried these
before it's like crack
it's like literally
kidding did you love when people say
literally I was actually making a joke
about that the other day someone told
they said literally is this I'm like
really literally like
what all
right literally that fish was so fresh
on the table it it was flapping around
literally it's a fresh as fish fish they
use all right let's
go I'm moving this
over let's make some
rolls all right so I don't use a sushi
mat I hope you guys are okay with that
like I don't use one I never did I find
it's harder for some reason so I see a
lot of beginners when when they make
Nori they make a Nori roll I see a lot
of
beginners they have to have the sushi
mat and it comes out disastrous or it
takes them
forever like rolling them up T like
takes
forever I don't do that you can learn
the trick with your hands really easily
and you don't need to use a sushi mat
you just don't have to now if you get
brand new sheets this is to it Nori
right here if you get brand new sheets
fresh out of the package they're going
to be crumbly when you actually roll
they're going to break apart and just
explode on you you're just going to get
gy everywhere they're going to crack
they're going to break so I want you
guys to know that that's going to happen
the minute you take it fresh out of the
package like that when it's fresh
toasted and you open up the vacuum
sealed pack they're going to just
explode on you this package was open for
a while moisture kind of got in here
and so what you see now is they're not
breaking apart look at this it's not
like falling apart on me check that out
I don't even have to use a lot of liquid
on here here's another thing a lot of
people they'll use a lot of water on
their Nory sheet they'll tear it apart
so they'll actually get a lot of water
like this right
here or more water than that and then as
they're rolling it up and putting it
together it's ripping it's tearing apart
so you don't have to do that when it's
in this in this phase right here I
probably put too much water on that one
so let's go there we go all right now
this is the marinade what I like to do
is take a little bit of that marinade
and I like to dab it on here a little
bit like
this gives it
flavor major flavor
okay let's get some
Millet now what I'm going to do is if
you keep the lid on the Millet won't
harden up
yet if you take the lid off it starts to
harden up a little bit in the in there
so it's just about right though where we
got now you want your Millet to the
edges you don't want a ton of
millet just a couple of tablespoons you
don't want too much
you won't be able to kind of put
everything else in but you want just
enough there we
go you want it to look good when you
roll this
up
okay recipes for from the brain saver
book protocols all right let's pop in a
couple of pieces of
carrot two pieces I allow myself two
pieces of carrot I'm going to put a
couple of
pieces there of
that
cucumber I'm going to put a couple of
these in now this one might be bigger
than I wanted but it's going to still be
good and you can choose how you want to
do it doesn't matter if anything sticks
out the side
don't
worry okay all right here you go now you
got your Ginger marinade right here I'm
not going to put it inside the rollup
but it's still like that I still have to
make the Wasabi but let's just do this
first okay by
hand you're going to get some little bit
cracks and sometimes whatever but that
is it right
there
okay now I can slice that now and give
you just a real quick show of it I'll
put it over
here one of the tricks is when you
slice you don't want to push down you
want to like slice you're going like the
saw action see what I'm doing letting
you guys know so so it's not going to
get destroyed on you I don't like the
ends too small because they'll just fall
apart so I like it
big enough now I'm doing a
saw there we go and I cut right down to
the
bone take a look you can make them
smaller if you really want but I'm
making a pretty good bite size look at
this remember you got to do the sawing
action make sure your knife is pretty
sharp make sure it's not too dull now I
got a problem here at the end you can
use this as one big end just like that
or you can cut it and get one more out
of it I'm going to try to cut and get
one more out of it who knows what we get
okay
yep all right I just want to get this
first
one on
here you know I've made them so many
times meaning different Nori rolls for
so many years
right so you got a couple little pieces
of Mill it around but there you go
that's the start let's make some
more kind of clean off your board a
little bit so you don't have Millet on
everything let's get another
sheet now the reason why I'm choosing
Millet and not rice a lot of people
sensitive to Rice
people need an option
Millet has the
potential of being the least
inflammatory it's the safest grain there
is hands down if you're a grain person
and you're eating a ton of rice I would
flip to Millet if you guys are okay with
that so let's get some Millet on
here did I say
millet
okay let's move this best we can
over there we
go
okay it's the least irritating for
people it's the least mucus
forming okay a lot of people have mucus
they have a lot of
mucus because they're dealing with all
kinds of different stuff that I've
talked about the medical medium
information but it's the least mucus
forming in the
body it's an what I call an alkaline
grain that's a big deal all on its
own it's one of the only
grains that isn't that that's an what I
call an alkaline it's high on its pH
it's High baby it's high all right let's
get some of this here carrots get a
couple of them in
here
nice I'm putting three carrots in here
this time let's get some of the cucumber
in
here so if you're somebody that's doing
grains anyway like your big thing like
you're like look I'm I'm macrobiotic I'm
all grains there's some dinosaurs left
maybe that are like macrobiotic people
like I'm pretty sure there there's
there's not too many out there anymore
they've been just beat they've had so
many beatdowns about grains being so bad
right all right so we got all that in
there let's roll this baby roll this
puppy like I said I don't like the sushi
mat I like it by
hand got a little tear on that one on
the back end and that will happen I
might not put any more moisture on these
but there we
go may cut this one
here do some sawing
action now it's inab
you're going to get braks no matter what
in your Nory
Sheets if you're like not used to doing
these on any level roll two and I'll
show you doing two at a
time you can go to Medical medium.com at
the supplement directory in the section
you can that has the kitchen tools and
you can see that section there and you
can find what I'm using today I'm going
to be using a Wasabi which I still have
to make the you know the the
Wasabi go to the food
section now some of these are just like
you can do the best you can but you're
always going to get a Nory sheet that's
not going to
cooperate it's like you you know you do
the best you can with what you have so
far all right I'm liking these now what
I'm going to do with this one is I'm not
going to add any moisture to this one
okay I'm going to leave this one just
like
this the moisture will actually cause a
break let's get some Millet on here I'm
sorry am I boring
you so told me that someone said oh my
God I'm bored because I just want to eat
them but how come you're not making them
then how how are you going to eat them
if you're not making them you got to
make them to eat
them all
right now I put a decent amount of
millet in this
one you can go less you could go more I
decided to put a little bit more Millet
in this one I'm going to make this one a
little bit more fatter let's get these
cucumber slices in
here I'm going to do one carrot in this
one I'm going to do some more
cabbage all right David says this is
like watching PMP it's
soothing all right let's roll it
up now like what I did this time was I
made it a little bigger it's a little
bit more plump was that a bad idea not
sure I'm going to put a little bit of
moisture on the
edge boom that's a nice one right there
that's what I'm talking
about that's what I'm talking about okay
slice this up you know what I'm saying
you ever run into somebody like you know
what I'm saying you see what I'm saying
I'm like yeah I see what you're saying
no you see what I'm saying man I go yeah
I see see what you're
saying I'm just saying I know you're
just saying it's okay I do that a lot I
do that a
lot all
right okay some of these are going to be
a little crazy let's just get this going
let's kind of do a little close-up on
here like
this where'd you go remember when you're
slicing make sure you slice all the way
to the bottom and they're not
connected multitasking man
multitasking you know what I love about
this this isn't going to feed any
pathogens this isn't going to feed any
bugs yeast mold fungus it's not going to
feed any of that over there on IG o aw
you always put a smile on my face even
when I'm struggling with symptoms every
day that means a lot to me that means a
great deal to
me thank you for being here
and bless your heart let's get some more
Millet going
on I'm trying to be careful with these I
don't want to butcher
these
okay if you just got here you're in aw's
kitchen we annihilated eggs I hope
everybody's
okay
all right and then we're going to try to
move this over
here there we
go we're using Millet Millet an alkaline
grain it's the only grain that's
actually
alkaline if that like matters to you
guys or not some people that matters
greatly that's a big deal to some people
out there like is it alkaline like is it
alkaline what's the pH is it up there
this one is this grain is so for grains
that's what this
is let's put a couple of pieces of
cucumber let's not be a nemic about it
and then we'll do couple of carrots we
will get some cabbage in there now too
let's roll this puppy
up all
right thing is with
people you know I told totally
understand it's like you get programmed
on the food you eat and you can't break
it and then even if you've healed you go
back to that food you know you go back
to that food there's a break in that one
it's a little bit more
difficult that Nory sheet let's make
another let's get this one up
here let's go there we
go
a lot of people will use medical medium
information and they'll start
healing they'll spend 2 years 3 years on
it they've gotten rid of 10 out of their
20 symptoms that no doctor could get rid
of they've gotten rid of 15 symptoms out
of their 20 symptoms that no doctor can
get rid of no practitioner can get rid
of no self-help course can get rid
of they started recovering started
getting better and better started
talking about the medical medium
information supporting the medical
medium information talking about how
great it
is they get to a point they're just sick
of doing
it or you know they want to do something
else meanwhile without that medical meme
information they wouldn't be in the
place they
are
all right we got some cucumber in here
I'm doing four pieces of cucumber I'm
going to do
two carrot sticks right there let's get
some more cabbage I really like
these and then we're going to do some
Wasabi we're almost there all right now
keep in mind the Cabbage will tear into
this these norish sheets you know hard
like crunchy vegetables will actually
rip and tear in so you you when you're
rolling it up this is when you can tear
you know but yet you want it tight
enough because you don't want it Loose
there you go that's actually a really
good
one
okay py Ren says I always feel better
after watching aw live just like with
PNP Pride and Prejudice Pride and
Prejudice 1995 version critical to know
more light-hearted and even symptoms
pull back so your nervous system is
relaxing when you're watching medical
medium and so so your nervous system is
calming down your mind
calms y listen to my audio on telegram I
just talked about P&P Pride and
Prejudice the 1995 version can you catch
up on those go to my telegram when you
guys get a chance after this and check
out the the last four I think four three
or four um audio clips that I did about
Pride and Prejudice how how important it
is how how like healing it is why
because Darkness wasn't in the film
production on that you know because the
problem people don't realize that in a
lot of documentaries and a lot of movies
a lot of TV there's Darkness
involved on all kinds of levels and
there there wasn't any in that it just
really incredible process that happened
it's one of those Miracles and when you
watch Pride and
Prejudice you'll you'll feel it you'll
see even if you don't like the story
line if you don't like Jane Austin
originally whatever it is it's really
something
special something to
experience it's easy on the system it's
healing it's a healing tool is really
what it
is all
right see right there it's a little
connected you want to cut really good
right
there sure a little crumbly but but good
so far and then I'm going to make uh I'm
going to try to salvage this one this
one was a little beaten up here there we
go you want to do a sawing action like I
said you guys or you're just going to
just it's going to tear apart look at
that there you go little sawing action
now this one broke at one part of it so
I'm going to just kind of take this
piece out the middle there you go that
will happen happen from time to time
there's nothing you can do about that
there you go let's get these in here
nice nice look at that look at that it's
coming together so good scoot that
over and let's get one more
actually
interesting oh yes
nice going to have some fun here let me
move this
over okay guys I need a couple little
different glass
bowls I'm going to get the ginger in one
of them right
here
okay let's take a look these are the
marinated Ginger
pieces you want to know it tastes good
these tastes good so good it's insane
you got your nice little Ginger pieces
in there look at
that so
[Music]
good oh my God these are so
good okay let's get that on
here let's get a Wasabi going freaking
Gourmet W sa Su
says all right got some Wasabi right
here it's
fresh fresh out of the right out of the
bottle
here nice let's get this
going now I don't know if you guys ever
do the Wasabi but man be careful the
rush you can get is insane you do too
much Wasabi that horseradish that Rush
it's just like it like blows your mind
it blows your sinuses out so if you've
never done it just kind of be
cautious okay need a little bit of water
in
this so I'm going to drop a
touch go a little bit at a time you
don't want it sloppy you don't want it
like sloppy
wet you want to make sure it's it's got
some consistency you don't want it dry
to the Bone either so I'm going to go
one
tablespoon I'm going to go with another
tablespoon right
here of some water a lot of people use
Namo you they use
tamari they use coconut aminos keep in
mind you don't want to put that in your
Wasabi together in the mix you'll ruin
the flavor of the wasabi you'll destroy
it I see people I've seen them out there
this is a perfect consistency of Wasabi
right here and then I'm going to put it
in a smaller little glass
bowl I
think you don't want to destroy your
Wasabi and you don't want to put
something else in there you just want
water in there you have to trust me on
that you have to believe me on
that
we're in the ew kitchen right here I am
going to put this
Wasabi right in this little glass bowl
you see
it this stuff is hot I already can tell
it's already getting to my sinuses right
now it's already got that like blowout
feeling like you're going to be blowing
your nose
man that's what saab's got cooking like
that kind of thing I'm going to do one
more roll up I want to I want to just
kind of fill this in a little bit so I'm
doing one
more okay let's do our last
one thank you very
much all
right little bit more
Millet Rico Diego this is going to be so
good dude this is going to be good this
is way better than Sila iins man I'm not
saying that's what you do or anything
cuz you cuz it's not I'm just saying
this is way better than that this is way
better than smoking weed I'm not saying
anybody here smokes weed I'm just saying
it's going to be way better than
that
and it's going to be way better than
frog
poison you know the Frog poison people
are like killing their brains with the
toad Venom frog Venom toad poison it's
way better than that
crap just want to make sure this is well
rounded this
one you know was that Burning Man and
they had me trapped in there for three
straight days and I was cover I was
naked and covered in mud and I was
crawling around in theud mud it was
freezing cold and everybody's getting
hypothermic and nobody had food and the
government like shut off the access like
roads and people were like freaking
dying like people were damaged from it I
wasn't there but that did
happen I'm kidding I wasn't there all
right all
right can you imagine being like
starving and burning man you're covered
in mud you're freezing your ass off
you're wrapped in a dirty blanket and
you're like stuck under in somebody's
tent some guy's tent who smells really
bad and you're in there right and you're
out there and then someone delivered
these these Millet Sushi it would be
amazing I would be like whoa dude give
me that now like whoa dude give me those
noris now like yeah I'm freezing in here
man dude give me those
noris I got a friend he's tattooed on
his eye
right I'm not kidding I'm not kidding I
got a friend who's got a tattoo on his
eye and you know like he asked me if it
was okay to get it done and I told him
it's I don't think it was smart and a
good idea and he still had his eye
tattoo not the eyeball he had his eye
like something around his eye he had
something written there and I can't read
it I I was trying to read it one day he
says you can only read it when you close
the lid and it said something like
Freedom something or whatever and I said
dude did you really have to do that you
know like it's okay if you did it no
totally okay but but you know I I
wouldn't do that I wouldn't get that
tattoo I
wouldn't you know and he's a friend of
mine I wasn't making fun of him Uma says
uma uma
C nice good to see you Bryce was there
Bryce was
there all
right see Sage love 432 says thank you
aw Victoria rising from the ashes says
that's how Bryce would be yeah I know
I've been Bryce has been rubbing off of
me or I've been I don't know which one's
what I'm trying to think right now H
okay yeah I like Bryce he's a good guy
he's a little crazy though he's a little
crazy Bryce is a little crazy I mean not
totally nuts not totally freaking nuts
but just a little crazy
you
guys I just want you
guys to have some killer
[Music]
food like just some really kickass
food you
know I just want to present here I want
to
present
presentation I'm going to clean this up
later I'm going to kind of push some of
these Millet pieces onto the floor for
now and then I'm going to vacuum it
later like I do someone ask do I clean
the kitchen yeah yeah totally do check
this out you
guys I'm going to show you a close on
IG that's right over there on Tik Tok
check it out boom can I spin it for you
without having it fall can I give you a
little spinning
presentation check that out Tik Tock you
guys on IG check that out Millet Sushi
is that sick or
what and check that over there on
YouTube
Rumble the rest of you guys
getter
X yeah d
bang
now are you guys okay cuz I'm going to
have
one is what I'm going to do all right
now I'm not really great with chopsticks
I'm usually shoving food down my throat
with a spoon or a fork every day I'm in
a rush I got a lot going I'm doing a lot
I'm under stress and I'm just like just
eat and set it down right I know what
you're saying you need to sit down down
you need to chew you need to do a food
meditation I totally agree totally agree
but I'm going to take a little bit of
this right here all right a little bit
of this Ginger if you guys are
okay all
right okay see if I can do this today
there we go are you all right with this
Ginger now I'm going to put this ginger
on one of these right
here
okay all right I'm going to bring one of
these
back okay now I'm going to put a little
bit of this on here because I swear the
stuff will just light you up I'm a
little scared of that Wasabi on
there why am I having a problem with the
Wasabi sticking so much just bear with
me I'm going to put some more Wasabi on
here oh man I'm scared okay now I'm
scared that's a lot of Wasabi let me
just get one more piece of Ginger on
here kind of hide this there you
go now what you see I did take a look up
close is you can see I'm an expert at
Job six right um what I did
was I hid some of that wasabi with that
Ginger cuz that shit's going to light
you up and you got to be careful on that
like you're going to get like that that
Rush all right now I'm going to put this
in my
mouth
now just going to go and do it I don't
know what to
say
[__]
damn I'm not kidding ever happen to
you
woo for real
man
woo I never even did that with hot
pepper there's a difference right Wasabi
can like just directly blow out the
sinuses and you feel it you hear me
right that eyes are watering I don't
even get that with hot pepper like what
the heck right that's crazy I don't even
get that with hot
pepper brain saer protocols you got the
book Let's make
them that was hot Lee says please re
repeat how you can get the lemon bomb
for free by ordering the micro SE
powder the micro seed powder is an
immune powder critical for colds flu is
all that right now right it's an immune
Builder this is Vitamin C but there's
two kinds of buffered vitamin C in here
this isn't like that acidic ascorbic
acid that tears people up and like it
seriously people get the scorz they get
diarrhea they can't take enough of it
they get stomach acid problems they get
reflux that doesn't happen this is the
real real buffered two kinds of vitamin
C and then it's got the organic bamboo
silica for the skin combined collagen
building which is incredible plus immune
and then you get loaded in a cart free
lemon bomb the link is in the
description link is in the profile when
you hit that link and you actually
purchase it that way the lemon bomb gets
loaded automatically in the cart if you
go straight to vimergy.com you just have
to look at the directions on how to do
it but the bottom line is the free lemon
bomb which is a nervine nervousness I
like it for all kinds of nervous system
stuff boom and You Got
That Rock And
Roll anyway I love you guys check out
telegram dude if you haven't like
subscribe to my telegram page please do
I leave private
messages sometimes like 2 3 in the
morning when I'm drinking with Dr Nesbit
and Dr Nesbit and I are both like
totally wased like [__] wasted shitfaced
Dr Nesbit and I on vodka and stuff and
then I go on Telegram and I go on there
and I'm like hey guys hey Dr N Stop man
Dr n been stop hey
guys anyway no I don't drink I do not
drink and I do not recommend drinking
and I do not promote promote that at all
I don't believe people should drink
alcohol I think it's bad for everybody
get on the medical medium newsletter I'm
not shaming anybody I'm just saying it's
not good for you it destroys the
brain destroys the body seriously and I
would never drink get on the medical
medum newsletter so you know what's
coming up what's happening and so you
can actually a also please subscribe to
my Tik Tok page I'm back on Tik Tok yeah
I had almost a million followers was
verified with a million followers and
they made it go poof poof and it took
this long to get the account back I'm
verified
again I think all the media lately
actually helped me get verified was
crazy all the media you know like all
the media about me and stuff it like got
it helped me get verified you guys
anyway I love you guys and I hope all is
good