right why does anybody get sick like why
should anybody get sick
shouldn't we
be born
we grow
we stay strong
and then we die in our sleep
99 years old to 110 years old or
whatever
shouldn't that be what should be right
but wait
it's not like that
it was
almost like that
almost
30 years ago now how's that possible
the
elder homes
right
had people 98 105 109.
technology wasn't great
heart heart
operations heart surgeries were
antiquated
right
you name it medical technology
mri scans were really bad antiquated
everything was antiquated 30 years ago
35 years ago why was it when you go into
a nursing home
or retirement home that person's 105
that person's 108 that person's 106.
that person 35 years ago 106 108 104 99
right
you know what nursing homes have now
if you can't be nursed at home
45 years old 42 years old 55 years old
30 years old 27 years old 22 years old
61 years old yep bedridden 65 years old
bedridden 27 year old bedridden that's
what it is now
35 years old 35 years ago you wouldn't
find a 35 year old 35 years old 35 years
ago you wouldn't find a 25 year old you
didn't find a 20 year old that was
basically wasting away
it was rare they were there but it was
so rare it was sprinkled in different
parts of the country sprinkled around in
different parts of the states
but now that's changed
life expectancy has dropped
dropped tragically dropped
that's how it is now
it's not about
you grow up you
ebb and flow with a couple little
sicknesses boom you're back on top
you're strong you live your life
now you're 65 now you're 75 now you're
85 and it's just your joints freak a
little bit i'm 85 years old and
yeah i'm a little stiff but i'm still
playing a little bit of tennis
and i still enjoy whatever i want to eat
for lunch and drink whatever drink i
want to have i put a little rum in here
i just drink whatever i'm 85 years old
nothing wrong
and you know it it's not like that
anymore we don't have that anymore
it's a whole different story so why are
we sick why are we all getting sick
and
that's the answer that's the question
what's the answer
why are we all sick so
what happens is with medical medium
information it's all about about the
truth of why we're sick that's why when
you go all the way back
years ago with medical medium
information people all walks of life
sick traveling around the world looking
for doctors 10 doctors 20 30 doctors
and they were looking for this
information right here
they were looking for this information
and then when they healed when they got
the information they said write a book
anthony write a book
a w write a book mr medical medium write
a book write a book write a book we
heard it so many times
i remember my receptionist heard it a
billion times year after year after year
as people left the office healing and
more people healed and more people
healed anthony when are you going to
write the book doctors anthony when are
you going to write the books what are
you going to write the books
when are you going to give the answers
out there somehow you lecture you talk
about it you lecture on the scene you go
here you teach doctors when are you
going to write the books and put it in
the books
the answers to why everybody said
science and research didn't know the
answers
right so
the whole point is is it's not like life
used to be
where you can get rid of a little bit of
butter and you can get rid of a little
bit of gluten and boom you're back on
track and you're 75 years old and all's
good your tip top shape those days are
over now people are suffering and
struggling and nobody knows what it's
like to be in somebody's shoes man
especially when you're young when you're
young and you got the anxiety and it's
through the roof you've got the
depression and it's through the roof and
you're really sick and struggling nobody
knows
what it's like when you when you're like
22 25 28 18
whatever
and nobody nobody knows what it's like
any even when you're in your 30s and 40s
and 50s and been through hell and back
and you're struggling
and you got more you got the hashimoto's
but you got more that brain fog is
brutal your brain fog is brutal you got
the anxiety attacks and panic attacks
then you got the depression you can't
breathe good and you're at every
pulmonologist and you're trying to
figure out what's wrong with the lungs
pulmonologists are saying fine your
lungs are fine your lungs are fine
and you can't breathe right
jamie lee says i'm currently 25 so
you're currently 25 and struggling
it's really difficult
god bless you for just keeping strong
through it and probably fighting every
day to get through it right
i'm proud of you i truly am and
and then so many people have so many
different conditions and they have all
the weight gain come on and then they
have other things too it's not just a
heart condition anymore it's not just
you get old you have a prostate or a guy
you got a prostate condition and then
you get a heart condition
or you're a woman and you get you get
some other could do okay you get some
other condition but the point like
depression or some anxiety it's not that
anymore it's far worse
it's vast
everybody's getting a neurological
symptom left and right everybody has
these neurological symptoms their brain
is a big part of it ashley barnes says
this man changed my life a monitor here
totally
we're live right now on facebook youtube
we're lying on live on rubble or live on
tick tock we're live on telegram we got
so many platforms i can't say them fast
enough i'm blurring them all together
okay
so
what i wanted to talk about you guys and
i hope you're here for this and hang
around for a couple of minutes all right
i wanted to talk about
just
we can break it down to some kind of
simplistic level
you either have something toxic in you
or you have
something alive in you that shouldn't be
in you
you either have
something toxic in you right
okay
here's some copper you guys like my new
copper bracelet
okay
got my new copper bracelet
so i ordered it online my new copper
bracelet they said it's really good for
me
they said let it touch your skin it's
like healing and good for me this big
copper jewelry line that they have they
got copper earrings they got copper
bracelets they got copper necklaces
they got copper anklets right all of it
the place is like incredible
right i ordered this nice copper
bracelet here and god i hear copper is
so healthy for you by the way it's not
copper's highly toxic
and they're just they're just playing
with fire when they play with copper
touching it is really bad touching
copper is bad
right there i have to do my heavy metal
detox smoothie tomorrow morning you
better believe it
so
we're either
saturated with some kind of toxin
whether it's metals whether it's
chemicals
right for old pharmaceuticals but we're
saturated with either that
or
we got the bugs we got some things
inside of us alive that's not supposed
to be there alive it's not supposed to
be there
but it's there and then
having both having both toxins
and the bugs combined is even harder on
people
monica says i just lost my beloved hubby
he was 33 he was so sick
it's on facebook
uh monica i'm so sorry i really am
honestly i i just don't even know what
to say because there's no words
just know that that
that with all my heart that i hope
somewhere somehow you can find some
peace through all this
what happens is people have two things
going on they have the poisons and the
toxins or they got the bugs they got the
critters
right and you can have both you name you
name the disease
name it
name the illness
name the illness name the disease
right
name the condition name the symptom
is it ringing in the ears
is it raining in the ears
is it whooshing in the ears fluttering
is it popping in the ears
right what that is
the epstein bar
that's what that is
okay
and it's releasing neurotoxins
and it gets into the inner ear the
labyrinth of the inner ear and that's
what that is it's
bugs that create the tinnitus there's a
comment here
tanya says i stopped drinking coffee in
december and then just tried the lemon
juice cleanse and celery juice for three
days now doing well and the red bumps on
my back of my arms are disappearing
incredible
incredible it's on facebook honored to
hear
medical medium books have this
information in there you guys it's got
this information in there
turns people's lives around so they can
get the answers they need
and
it's here it exists you just have to
know how to look at it and say hey wait
a minute what is this what dosage do i
do what is this how much do i take wait
a minute what do i have to avoid wait a
minute what is this what what's going on
what's causing my problem how much how
many drops do i need like what it's
there the information's there
in the books
it's there
anxiety
okay
depression eczema psoriasis vitiligo
there's answers to those
okay
neurological conditions tingles numbness
ticks spasms aches pains burning skin
burning tongue burning jaw pain in the
jaw pain in the neck pain in the back of
the head pain in the back lower back
right
different rashes hives there's answers
to all of it
they exist
and people can heal
lynette says my oldest daughter is 21
and having different issues has ruptured
ovarian cyst
kidney stone borderline anemia anxiety
so
if that was happening to
a family say a family member came to me
and said look this is what's going on
the anemia
is viral
that's what i would tell my family
member
the anemone the anemia is viral
epstein-barr causes anemia that's
mystery anemia
right
epstein-barr also
causes ovarian cysts
reproductive cysts
so it's another thing epstein-barr
causes
toxic heavy metals
cause anxiety
okay what's happening here is
published in the medical medium books
quite a long time ago now
uh kim d'andrea says you cured my son
from hypothyroidism on facebook
incredible incredible
medical medium information is so
advanced and so ahead of research in
science that research and science ends
up stealing it years later
but the jokes on research and science
we're stealing it because it's already
been published
and
it's already here
way before as proof
that another source up above
a source
had the answers before research in
science
so what they're doing they're taking
medical media information now about
epstein-barr and a lot of other things
is actually insane what they're doing
they used to say
this disease or condition cause unknown
and now they put viral infection now
they put epstein-barr now they put
shingles it's like okay but where's the
research paper and you look there is no
research paper and then you look there
really is no research that was done then
you realize it's just somebody
going like this
whoa
that guy sold millions and millions and
millions of books
talking about epstein-barr doctors are
using it all around the world we can't
let this guy get away with this we
better just take it and steal it doesn't
matter if we don't have research yet
yeah our a is now epstein-barr ms is now
epstein-barr with no real research
behind it interesting
so when it comes down to being sick
there's real reasons i've been saying
this for over 35 years
if you have
vertigo
it's the vagus nerves it's the vagus
nerves being inflamed by a critter you
got tinnitus
it's a critter getting into the
labyrinth of the inner ear
and inflaming that nerve channel causing
your tinnitus you're popping you're
fluttering you're washing
viral infection right
if you've got other conditions like
eczema
and psoriasis that's a combination of
having toxic heavy metals like copper
inside your liver
and then having
a little buggy right here that feeds off
of the copper because that's what
happens to little bugs inside of a speed
feeds off the copper releases a
dermatoxin and now you have your skin
problems your psoriasis and eczema
if this is really hard for someone to
understand because it could be hard for
somebody to understand when you think
about it right if it is you just gotta
break it down you gotta break break it
down it's the most simplest form
you got a critter in you
and you got some poisons and toxins of
some kind in you
you can name them all right
and one is bothering you
on its own
or
both of them are bothering you together
that is as simple as it gets and then
ready after that
our immune systems break down
we become deficient dehydrated
and toxic
and then we just start to fall apart as
the years go on
i can sum it up that easy
that fast
for anyone
and if i heard that and i was sick so if
i had something wrong and i was in bad
shape and i heard that be like what do i
need to do
it sounds to me like i have to get rid
of the critters
find out which ones
and then i got to figure out how to get
rid of the poisons and the toxins like
the metals or anything else
and then i'm home free
but how am i going to do that
answers are here
it's doable
people are doing it all around the world
they are
so let's go into a little bit
now now
if i was sick okay
i'd be drinking licorice tea if i had
symptoms
that were
looking like
they were because of epstein-barr or
shingles
and those symptoms are
fatigue conditions like lupus chronic
fatigue syndrome
brain fog right
autoimmune of any kind and so i'd be
like okay licorice tea
because that's an antiviral right there
even if you're doing little things like
this well i'm going to do my licorice
tea that's one thing right there so i'm
going to go into auto immune right now
and i'm going to look forward here
right
and
so let's go to autoimmune
so autoimmune diseases and disorders
right so if you get diagnosed with an
autoimmune disease and i'm going to read
real quick the autoimmune part right
if your individual autoimmune
issue isn't listed here because there's
so many there's hundreds right
if it's not listed here you still can
use this autoimmune section by the way
the true cause of autoimmune is unknown
to medical research and science health
problems that are labeled autoimmune are
in truth viral infections viruses that
cause autoimmune conditions can be one
or more
of the 60 varieties of epstein-barr
over 30 varieties of shingles
okay
many varieties of hhv-6 hhv-7
undiscovered hhv-10 through hhv-16
multiple varieties of herpes simplex
ones so the fever blister people got the
fever blister in their body their whole
life but then what happens is the fever
blister virus you guys
ends up
causing jaw pain teeth pain
strange headaches back to the neck right
trigeminal neuralgia other problems so
that's what happens with the herpes
simplex viruses herpes simplex one cold
store fever blister i just got a fever
blister
yeah don't worry don't worry yeah what
do you see on my lip don't worry
it's just a fever blister is what it is
and that's what people don't realize
it's like oh no it's no big deal
meanwhile you know it is a big deal
because in the end it can cause some
problems and it's important to kind of
like be like open to that it's like it's
like
yeah i know i have a fever blister don't
worry about it
you want to share my glass i'll share my
glass with you right
it's like yeah no can i borrow that i'll
give you your glass back can i try that
drink don't worry about this fever
blister right now yeah don't worry the
fever blisters are highly contagious
right highly contagious
and
and they cause so many troubles but
people don't know they cause any trouble
so it's like okay no don't worry
we have
doctor says my child's fine my child has
a fever blister
obviously came from me the parent and
the parents
but you know no one talks about it the
doctor says it's perfectly fine it goes
away meanwhile it means early trigeminal
neuralgia unless you do something about
it it means early migraines it means
early symptoms it means all kinds of
issues if you don't do something about
it
so in the autoimmune section right here
okay
i'm reading this the cause of autoimmune
disorders and diseases
right
are not the body's immune system
attacking its own organs and glands
medical research and science you know
what they did recently they took
epstein-barr information from medical
medium books
word for word plagiarizing
and
but they still think the body's
attacking itself too because they can't
let that old theory go they're bringing
in something fresh
something that's solid and works like mm
info about epstein-barr causing all
these symptoms and conditions and then
they mix it
they just can't help themselves they
mismix it with the ah the body attacks
itself with it
it's ridiculous really they can't keep
it straight there's no consistency
there's no check and balance
they constantly contradict itself you
notice how that's the world right now
it's nothing but contradictions 24 7.
there's no check and balance
right medical medium science
is what they're using so they're using
medical medium science
so it's a theory that the body attacks
itself right and that's what the
industry always uses started from the
1950s
the truth is though
people are dealing with viruses
responsible for these illnesses that are
they're living with viral activity in a
combination with toxic metals and other
chemicals
these viruses feed on foods too that i
always talk about
if you want to weigh out if you want out
do you want out yeah you want out no one
wants to be sick you guys don't want to
be sick i don't know anybody that wants
to be sick
i definitely don't know anybody that
wants to be sick
right
but there's a way out
there really is
it's about learning about whoa wait a
minute i can go after the bugs inside of
me i can actually get the toxins out i
could do something about it
powerful that's powerful
so
if you have lupus if you've got ra if
you've got anemia if you've got other
conditions anything any kind of
autoimmune condition
someone's asking on tick-tock do you
drink licorice tea the rest of the day
look i'll go and i'll go in times where
i'm drinking licorice tea to keep my
immune system strong because i'm working
a ton of hours if i get exposed to
anyone or anything like that i like to
keep my immune system nice and strong so
what i'll do is i'll say you know what
i'll do licorice tea for a while and if
i can't find any licorice tea i don't
have any licorice tea then i'll just get
a licorice supplement right
so i'll get a licorice supplement from
vimergy right here
and vimergy is that company i always
talk about right i'm not sponsored by
these guys here's their vitamin c but
they got a licorice fruit
vimergy's v is invector i am ergy dot
com i'm not sponsored by those guys i
don't own the company but the stuff is
incredible at me says i thought you were
doing amazon live i did the link is in
the description so check it out you can
watch the
replay of the amazon latte we made
spaghetti and meatballs
so we made spaghetti and meatballs on
the amazon live
and the reason why it took such a long
time was since i ate a bowl i ate a
plate this big spaghetti and meatballs
and i was like oh my god i can't go live
yet i better just work on other projects
i was stuffed i couldn't help it it was
so good it was so good i had did this
waffle garlic bread i made like i don't
know 10 meatballs i had two pounds of
pasta it was gluten-free pasta you guys
gotta check the amazon live out it was
fat free it was radical fat free
it was it was it was really great
you can drink the licorice
sure ask your doctor of licorice if you
can drink licorice tea but me personally
yeah i'll drink it keep my immune system
strong i'll drink it every day
that's traditional medicinals that's i'm
not sponsored either by these guys but
this is the company i use for my teas
right there traditional medicinals
thought i'd have that on there because i
don't talk about these guys that much
even though i do when i can
so
um rosangela says the amount of times i
heard that my body was attacking myself
had me thinking something was wrong with
me for years
that's the way the system is built up
it's on youtube thank you for being here
rosa
that's the way the system's built it's
built to convince the person their
bodies are faulty attacking themselves
their bodies are no good
and their body wants you dead because
your body is attacking itself so that
means your body wants you gone right if
it's attacking you and making you sick
to the point where you can't live life
anymore then yeah maybe my body turned
against me but that's not what happens
has nothing to do with your body doing
that
it's about these little critters that
everybody has inside of them and when
you have autoimmune which everybody's
getting a diagnosis of autonomy do you
think that's normal
because is that a normal great thing
every single human being on this planet
will get an autoimmune diagnosis
every single one of them in the coming
next 10 15 years
maybe young people not as much but but
most of them will still get an
autoimmune diagnosis
but
everybody will have that label
eventually have it if they get a little
older i'm not talking about a little
older like 90 years old i'm talking 30
years old
35 years old every single person on the
planet will have an autoimmune diagnosis
everyone
is that good is that normal
rachel catherine says my high blood
pressure is gone after two days on lemon
water lemons
amazing
lemon water and celery juice and cutting
out all all the no foods all the bad
foods right i talk about all the bad
foods in here
long road ahead with other health issues
but keeping the faith that will give you
faith
glad to finally commit you finally
committed and now all of a sudden boom
you knocked out that high blood pressure
incredible thanks aw and soc
amazing right on facebook
i'm so proud of you i'm proud of all you
guys if you guys don't have the book get
it free at the library or amazon.com 51
off right now say amazon.com 51 off you
won't be making a mistake getting the
book
you will not you will be blown away
and probably in shock because the
information is so advanced
lynette says my thyroid is finally
healing i have gone from 120
to 88
on levothyroxine
totally understand i do i'm so glad your
thyroid's finally healing you're working
on it that's the best thing i ever heard
i'm very happy about that so what you're
going to find coming up is all these
autoimmune disorders everybody's going
to have autoimmune they're going to have
also blood disorders so you'll be
diagnosed with all these different blood
disorders as well
and then they're going to be diagnosed
with all these autoimmune disorders
because they're going to have
neurological problems so where we're
heading now is everybody's gonna have
something wrong like a twitch a spasm a
tick
tingles in numbness burning skin
headache body pain
brain fog crazy brain fog
you know migraines and strange ways all
kinds of infections and everything else
people are just going to have also all
these neurological symptoms mainly
and
that's what we're heading and then their
diagnoses are all going to be autoimmune
you got autoimmune you got autoimmune
you got autoimmune it's gonna get so out
of control it's already heading there
right
but it's gonna be everybody on the
planet
and i don't think butter in your coffee
or apple cider vinegar
[Music]
or
oil pulling
whatever
charcoal is going to save anybody it's
not
it never did
and never will
but there's so many newbies that are
going to get autoimmune disease that all
these conditions and symptoms and be
suffering and struggling and they're
going to have to go through it oh my god
they're going to have to go through it
what butter my coffee might help okay uh
what green tea might help let me try
green tea now okay what else can i do oh
charcoal okay let me swallow a bunch of
charcoal okay uh bentonite clay okay let
me try that okay go go bend tonight clay
it's gonna be like this and they're just
gonna be like okay that's your first
year of suffering
let's go through another two years
another three years another four years
before they'll ever know
lisa said one year on celery juice and
now cooking only with medical medium
recipes and feeling so much more energy
75 medical medium recipes and cleanse
the heal
if you think i'm trying to push off a
book
sell a book
go to the library and get it for free
don't pay for it please i don't care if
no one pays for it if you could go to
the library
and just take it out of the library
that's all i care about if i know you're
sitting at home and you're looking into
this and you're like what
i i can actually get better
there's answers in here
right
so yeah important to know
so let's talk about just a couple little
the little nitty gritty i've talked
about it before i'm going to talk about
it again
you have to be careful when you're
getting your blood tests that's critical
people don't stand a chance
they don't stand a chance unless they
learn
to ask for half files from your doctor
or quarter vials from your doctor if the
phlebotomist says
no
we can't do it
call your doctor and you tell them
you're only going to give half files
or quarter vials
that's what you do
and then the doctor will tell the
phlebotomist just take the blood
and then that blood will do the same
thing any other blood will do because
they only need
a quarter or half file they need way
less than that i talk about that all
these years right
one of the ways they're getting
everybody right now and if i don't
explain this to you guys once in a while
you're just gonna fall into the traps
there's a lot of new people here too
they'll get you on the blood tests
they'll take the vials from you and
you'll lose your white count while
your white count is trying to stop this
right here
so inside your body there's a war all
the time you're sick you got the brain
you don't feel good you got
symptoms you got conditions
you're not well you got anxiety you got
severe depression you got body pain
you've got fatigue you've got all these
different conditions you've got skin
rashes you've got hives and what's
happening is your white blood cells are
trying to control and gobble down and
eat the bugs
and then you're going to your doctor
because you feel so darn sick and your
butt doctors can be like i need to look
at all your profiles
let's get all the profiles here
i want to look at metabolic i want to
look at everything
and then you get i want a thyroid panel
metabolic panel i want a nutrition panel
i want to whatever and that's what they
do
and then what happens is your white
blood cells are removed
with every blood test with every vial
but before they can restore which can
take weeks and even months for many
people because you already have an
immune system problem because that's why
you're at the doctor's office the bugs
are still in the organs without your
immune system in the blood anymore to
keep it under control and you get sicker
this is why people have lost their lives
with neurological lyme multiple
sclerosis and cancer in almost every
other condition because they take and
the more you get sick and complain the
more blood they take and then the
specialist takes and then the next
specialist takes no one cares and then
you're sick in the hospital and they
take it every day
until you lose your life
or
somehow end up home without a blood test
long enough to regain your life back to
sustain yourself enough before they try
to draw your blood again and kill you
this is not radical thinking
i talk to doctors about this all the
time i have doctors now reaching out to
me saying that's the best thing they've
ever heard their patients are rebounding
quicker their patients are healing
they're ordering quarter miles and half
vials it's changing medicine right now
but if you're not on board you're just
gonna get ripped off
yeah ripped off
the one thing
about the medical medium books
is they teach you about this blood draw
too that's one thing right there there's
so many cool things right
so
there's a section in here there's a
section in here about like where like
that i'm going to show you in a minute
too
when it comes down to lyme disease right
it comes down to lyme disease and i have
a lime section in all my books there's a
lime section in this book right here
you can never heal from lyme disease
unless you learn
what you're after you got to go after
the bugs and the right kind
you have to go after the toxins and then
you have to look out for the blood draws
the blood frogs are a big part you know
you know who heals with lyme disease
when they start feeling a little better
when they do the right things like the
medical medium information and then
they're they're going to the doctors a
lot less
and they're getting less blood drawn and
now they're rocking now they're getting
their lives back it's incredible it's
incredible
right
so i got this little part here in this
medical medium book one all the medical
medium books are so loaded with
information
right
when a larger number of blood vials are
drawn it could be stressful on the
immune system
four full vials six full vials 20 full
vials 34 miles right
okay
because the very immune defenses that
are keeping the viruses behind lyme
symptoms and any other symptom or
autoimmune disease or anything else
you're up against are being drawn out of
the body when the blood is being drawn
so your very defenses like your immune
systems being sucked up and drawn up
if you don't know how to ask for quarter
vials and be cautious and be cautious on
how much blood is being taken
blood draws tend to take away a
substantial portion of a person's immune
system that day and it sometimes takes
weeks to months to rebuild those
portions of the immune system
fancy that
within those weeks
that the full power of your immune
system is not present anymore
in your blood monitoring bugs and
viruses
there's a window of strength all the
bugs get in that moment they rise up and
now you're sicker and you're going to
the doctor one more time and when you go
to the doctor one more time you're
getting blood drawn again darcey lee
womack says i see a lot of people having
ha ha aha moments here thank you for
teaching us aw i haven't talked
thoroughly enough about blood tron quite
a while it's one of the reasons why we
stay sick and today's talk was why are
we sick
i have a podcast you guys you should
check it out medical medium podcast at
apple podcast it's the blood draw
bloodletting vampire
episode
right it's on apple it's on spotify
so check it out when you can
you know what happens to our elders when
they're sicker and they get sicker and
they get sicker they get bled to death
they die early
our parents or grandparents
or great-grandparents whatever they die
early before their time because they're
bled to death
that's a big part of it
that's not just medications which is the
third reason for death medications in
the
in the united states
millie says i suddenly got stricken
with hand eczema in 2020 it spread to my
neck and then my face i went to two to
two different dermatologists
prescribed four prescriptions that only
gave me temporary relief
per medical medium i started juicing
cilantro juicing celery reduced my fat
intake yeah ordered the recommended
supplements and after three days
right like the vimergy stuff that's
recommended
and after three days
okay
i began to heal i am over the moon with
gratitude and joy milly
i'm monitor here
truly i am
so what about donating blood so let's go
into that the podcast lynette talks
about that check out the podcast when
you get a chance about donating blood
and how that works
okay so i'm not against blood donations
but check it out
definitely if you can't
so when i talk about why are we sick i'm
giving you guys the foundational tools
right
you got some kind of critter in you
right we got a critter
right i gave you that one we got toxins
we got poisons right it's another one
and then
we get broken down
too many blood draws
too much caffeine
chocolate coffee green tea matcha tea
too much caffeine foods that feed the
bugs
right
deborah says i'm not getting any
notifications for you how do i get them
again i keep missing you deborah
that's by design
not for me
keeping you from seeing these but it's
by design
and that's been happening since 2018
so
try turning on your note face
notifications again and try to give it a
you know give it a shot try to reset it
so
jen's gen z says
i've been advised to donate more blood
because my blood is poisoned with carbon
monoxide so it's not good blood to keep
look
i want you to listen to your doctor
because that's what you should do you if
you're advised by your your
your
health care provider to do something you
do it if that was me
i wouldn't be doing that
if that was me but that's just this is
just my life i could i could say that
okay
and because i would ask myself like why
would that help someone else then so
am i going to give i would say to that
doctor
i would say to that doctor
if you want me to donate my blood
because it's poison with carbon carbon
monoxide
isn't that what if there's a child that
needs my blood
and they're going to do they're going to
do a blood transfusion in a child and
they're going to poison that child with
carbon monoxide
that's what i would ask my doctor
and
that's really
disturbing
i'm going to ask dr nesbitt if he'll
come out right now because i want to see
what dr nesbitt has to say
because dr nesbitt is a better doctor
than i i believe than probably your
doctor so i'm going to get dr nets with
you you just came out of surgery
dr desmond just came out of surgery
right now
he's here
so this is really interesting so i was
did you hear that before
so
okay this patient this doctor's patient
which is very nice person here
left a comment right saying that
she's told to donate her blood because
her blood's poisoned yeah
and uh what are you doing doctor
announcement
dr nesbit
dr ness likes to play with everything he
thinks these are all toys even though
he's he's a he's on
he's on the medical board and he's a
surgeon
what do you think about that that
doctor hasn't stopped sticking that in
my face
um
he says
he wouldn't donate the blood
what
he said that doctor is definitely
a quack what
he says the doctor's a quack
and there's a lot of bad doctors out
there really what why do you say that
home doctors are good
he says it's the third
reason why people die in this country
alone is from malpractice
because doctors
are like
no that's not right no doctors
are they're not no what they haven't no
they have an what are you trying
to say what
dr nesbitt
doesn't even know what he's saying
he's saying that
doctors are like everybody has
one
that doesn't even make any sense anyway
dr nesbit has to go back into surgery
he's taking this with him he's going to
going to inject this vial of blood that
has carbon monoxide and some other
dangerous things in it
he's going to inject this into his
patient he thinks he thinks that was
wise advice from the other doctor to
just
put blood that's not good in someone
else and put it in someone else is that
release no he's only kidding he would
never do that
okay
dr nesbit has to go can you can you drop
that please i need it for my
demonstration
ah dr nesbitt dr nesbitt's going back in
the surgery
you guys on my newsletter medical medium
newsletter
um i'm gonna be doing some exclusive
videos on there that you're only going
to see on my newsletter not going to see
them on rumble not going to see them on
youtube not going to see them on
facebook not going to see them on ig now
i can see them on tick tock i can see
them on telegram
i'm sorry it's just going to be on my
newsletter
and maybe look
maybe you'll sign up for the newsletter
so you can see those so
medicalmedium.com plus the newsletter
link is right there it's right there in
the description it's right there in the
profile on tick tock
telegram you got you'll find a link to
so sign up to the newsletter because i'm
gonna i'm gonna do like exclusive never
anywhere else videos in these
newsletters coming up just not tomorrow
but like trying to try next week or
something
and i think we're gonna start that so
make sure you sign up so you don't miss
these
okay i'm going to instagram now
tick tock i'm turning you back on
telegram and turning you back on we're
going on instagram and we're going on
pretty fast too right from here to there
i don't have a mess to clean up and
we're going to talk about supplements
dosages illnesses we're going to talk
about some other things too while we're
sick and check out that amazon live i
just did if you can
the link is right there in the
description the amazon live i just did
go there uh
and follow me over there and check out
the medical medium cooking show live
link is in the bio as well
all right you guys
i love you much okay
i'll see you guys later