the greatest mistake you can make is
mixing things in your celery juice it's
critical you don't mix water ice cubes
lemon-lime other fruits and vegetables
collagen apple cider vinegar charcoal
protein powder or anything in your
celery juice this is how it works when
you add those things in you dilute that
chemical compounds so when you drink
your celery juice it doesn't do what
it's supposed to do I was suffering with
like really difficult to digestive
problems like constipation lots of gas
and bloating celery juice is the newest
thing out there medical medium cures
everything I started noticing my body
coming back to life right away when you
drink 16 ounces of solar juice on an
empty stomach that's where the magic is
that's where the miracle powers are it
enters into your gastric glands it
rebuilds them so they can produce
hydrochloric acid to break down proteins
so proteins don't rot in your gut and
then it goes into your small intestinal
tract where it runs into food that you
might have in there from the dinner
before then it has to kill off pathogens
bacteria viruses yeast mold unproductive
fungus then it travels down it has to
eventually get into the liver through
the paddock portal vein once it's in
your liver it builds up your bio
reserves helping to improve your
digestion by breaking down fats then
after that it heads to the gallbladder
and starts to dissolve the gall stones
and that's why it has to be at least 16
ounces to have enough liquid to get
through the entire obstacle course that
you have in your body so you can heal
and move forward one of the first things
that I started doing that I read from
his book was the 16 ounces of celery
juice in the morning on an empty
stomach I remember just feeling like ah
yes this is what I needed and it
instantly clicked for me the reason why
you have to juice celery is because if
you leave the pulp or the fiber in there
it won't work when you leave the fiber
and the pulp you're trapping the
medicine slowing it down stopping your
digestion so you can't get the medicine
to work if you drink tea you don't eat
the teabags you have to extract the
medicine out of it and consume it
without the pulp in the fiber it's the
only way it's going to help you heal
[Music]
you