here we are again talking about brain
saver the brain saver book's gonna read
in the chapter called Static brain it's
about scatter brains you know anybody
who's scatterbrained like you know what
are you scatterbrained you hear that a
lot right A lot of people have said that
over the years that's a term
so there's a network of neurons inside
your brain
that need to be clean and healthy and
pure
they need to be
in good standing so the neurons inside
our brain are not supposed to be
polluted they're not supposed to be
corrupted and polluted and saturated
with all kinds of waste and sludge and
Gunk and toxins and poisons but what
happens is in our lives we have brains
that become like a filter and they're
saturated with all kinds of toxins
poisons all kinds of junk and garbage
and waste and everything else byproduct
everything right
and so our brains have all this stuff in
it that's not supposed to be in there
and when that stuff is in there and it's
saturating the neurons of your brain
then all of a sudden we become scatter
brains and anything can go wrong even
accidental rumors could happen I'm going
to read a little bit about that it's so
cool in here so this is mind-blowing
information you guys
the books are on sale right now
amazon.com us
take advantage of it if you can take
advantage of it the very heavy the books
good to see you guys again very heavy
the books loaded with information and a
forewarning to you too there's so much
to digest there's so much information to
take in it's insane how much line for
line it is absolutely incredible and I'm
just gonna be I'm just gonna be farting
around in your static brain right here
and
I'm not even talking about the amount of
information the anxiety chapter and the
Alzheimer's chapter in the bipolar
chapter in the OCB chapter and the
eating disorder chapter that's just a
few things there's symptoms conditions
and explanations and incredible
information so this is groundbreaking
information that's not known out there I
want to make that clear because
you know I saw somebody earlier make a
comment like oh he must be just reading
all the latest Neuroscience really that
must be a genius or something okay or
you know spiritual compassion is a
genius or whatever you want to say but
this isn't the latest Neuroscience you
know Neuroscience doesn't have this
information this is far more advanced
than our Neuroscience today as far as
what's out there
and which is incredible so this is
Advanced this will become
the latest Neuroscience it will because
already information for medical medium
throughout the last 10 10 years and even
before has become Staples in the
Neuroscience world and I even talk about
some of that in here
so about how you know I published it
first and whatever so I'm just going in
here into static brain the most advanced
comprehensive detailed information about
how our brain works is in these two
books brain saver brain saver protocols
so take a look when you get the chance
these books are so good Sherry said good
to see you these books are so good I'm
honored I'm so glad you have the books
and let's get into it a little bit you
guys
so your static brain so I'm on page 10
of this massive book
and there's two books remember that
some of you like which book do I get
there's two books they become one big
book so I'm in a network of neurons I'm
reading right out of here so each line
is packed and powerful and filled with
information
when it comes to your brain
neurons mean practically everything
healing brain related symptoms and
conditions whether those symptoms and
conditions are traditionally associated
with the brain or not
critically depends on understanding the
neurons that reside inside of it so if
we don't understand our neurons inside
our brain
we can't heal our brain we cannot heal
so if we don't understand our neurons we
can't understand what's wrong with us we
can't understand our brain it's critical
neurons a type of nerve tissue
are the means by which communication
occurs in the nervous system enabling it
to send and receive messages neurons are
about input and output so your neurons
inside your brain are about information
going in information going out
information going in information going
out
neurons are your transcribers
that's your transcription method
so your neurons are your transcribers to
information coming in
that's what they are
imagine okay
imagine
billions of tiny people inside your
brain
can you imagine that
billions of tiny people inside our brain
each sitting at a desk in front of a
computer
translating information that's coming in
through your ears or eyes or other
senses such as smell taste or touch and
trying to decipher it so imagine
billions of tiny little people inside
your brain
the neuron transcriber's job is to make
sense out of what you're experiencing
and then pass that along to the next
tiny neuron person inside your brain
the hope is that a the information
travels uninterrupted and that's the key
uninterrupted that's the key so I'm
getting someplace right now check this
out travels uninterrupted
the hope is that a the information
travels uninterrupted to that next
transcriber neuron
and B that next transcriber neuron
takes the information that was just
deciphered keeps it in purified form and
possibly adds an addendum that's
efficient and accurate and prepares it
for the next tiny person neuron inside
your brain to receive
so you got this transcriber which is a
neuron receiving information through
electricity
and then
transcribing it organizing it and
sending it back out if the neurons
are not interrupted but everybody's
walking around with brain problems
everybody's walking around with a brain
issue and they're sick in all kinds of
different ways so something's getting
interrupted something inside their head
is getting interrupted
aren't these aren't these fun to do you
guys
so let's let's keep on going here
you can imagine
your brain as a tiny spaceship
so imagine your brain is this tiny
spaceship
flying through the universe that's
pretty cool that's really cool
your neurons are billions of tiny aliens
inside that spaceship so your neurons
are tiny aliens billions of them inside
your spaceship right
so your brain
is a spaceship
and you got billions of type poor grogu
grow grogu's being used as an example
tonight you got billions of tiny little
aliens inside your brain
and all of these aliens
are communicating together
at the same time there's a Supreme Being
oh whoa whoa whoa at the same time
there's a Supreme Being
on the ship watching all of it so you
got your brain as a spaceship it's got
billions of tiny aliens inside of it
communicating with each other and
there's a supreme being inside that
spaceship that's strange
what's the Supreme Being inside that
spaceship what is it what can it be
so you have the Supreme supernatural
being that's sitting inside the
spaceship watching over all those
billions of tiny aliens communicating
inside there
that Supreme Being is your soul
that's your soul
your sensory input isn't the only
information your neurons decipher and
pass along they also translate
information about your body processes
neurons apply to every single function
your body has and how healthy your
neurons
are determined on how comfortable you're
going to be in your mind and body
that is neurons are involved you guys
got your books I'm on page 12. you guys
will probably read it better than I can
so
that is neurons are involved in both
mental functioning and your state of
health so neurons involved with your
mental health
mental health not just physical health
mental health and physical health
when you have brain related symptoms
even on the mildest scale such as mild
fatigue and Mild brain fog It's really
because neurons can't transfer
information properly to the next group
of neurons
so if you've got brain fog
or anything like brain fog It's really
because neurons can't transfer
information properly to the next group
of neurons something is hindering the
pathway where the electricity is
traveling so as electricity is traveling
through your brain something is
hindering the passageways the pathway
something's in the way he had all these
people with brain fog and every kind of
problem and all these other issues
what's going on something is actually
impeding the information traveling
across to neuron to neuron
something is blocking or otherwise
impeding the pathway within the synapsis
so the neurons sending out electrical
impulses are not reaching other neurons
that need the information we're not
reaching the neurons as intended so
what's happening is you got all these
people man
she's just walking around
they're seeing their psychiatrists their
doctors their MDS their functional
medicine doctors their therapists their
counselors they're depressed they got
anxiety they got to personalization they
got bipolar diagnoses
they got depression in the worst way
different ranges they got dementia and
Alzheimer's if you want to add those in
they got all kinds of different issues
they're triggered easy they're emotional
emotionally sensitive all these things
but there's real problems it's not their
fault
foreign
you can see this in everyday life when
you're telling someone a story about
apples and they and they find out that
the whole time you find out the whole
time they thought you were talking about
oranges
so you're telling somebody a story and
you're talking you're talking about
apples you're like this apple tree is
incredible and then by the time you're
done they're like what was that orange
tree
right any kind of a p impedement within
a person's neurons can mean that the
information their neurons process gets
altered affecting that person's ability
to focus listen or properly receive
information from a conversation or story
so here's how it works you're
conversating with somebody you're
talking to somebody and you're not
getting along like you know
something's happening in that
relationship something's going wrong no
one's seeing eye to eye it could be a
couple it could be a relationship could
be family members it could be friends
but you're not seeing eye to eye it
could be somebody you just met on the
street but you're not seeing eye to eye
and you don't know why you're not seeing
eye to eye what is wrong what is going
on here
there's a good chance it's because that
person you're not seeing eye to eye with
has got an impedement in the neurons and
that information going through is being
blocked
a lot of people don't actually hear what
I said or what's in my books it happens
all the time you see it out there people
say he didn't say that and I did or
he said this and I didn't
I've seen that for years on social media
people have problems with their neurons
and so when they read the medical medium
books sometimes they don't it's hard to
get the information in I've seen this
it's why it's critical to do the cleanup
so many people don't read things
correctly either or hear things
correctly because their neurons are
having problems
so we have billions of people on this
planet
and they all got brain problems
it's easy to have
it's nobody's fault in the end except
the industries
an evil
because they want everybody just
scrambled eggs in the brain
but what happens is when we get when our
brains get too many toxins and poisons
and junk and metals and everything else
and pathogens and pathogen toxins inside
of our brain it becomes this filter and
then
we get scatterbrained
misread initial question guess I need
brain saver so that come up
Nobody's Perfect
there's a lot of people suffering and
struggling with their brain and I'd love
to see people get better I would love to
see them get better so badly
then that person may tell someone else
in entirely different version of the
original story that was told to them
you ever had that happen like you tell
somebody a story and they change the
story as they tell somebody else's Story
how crazy is that and it's not that it's
crazy it just happens but think about
that you tell somebody a story you're
like hey look I'm telling you this is
what happened I got this this you got
this yeah you got that okay great go
okay and they go tell somebody and
they're telling somebody and they're
like you know the the guy had this and
he fell off the cliff and next thing you
know it he he broke his leg I didn't
break my leg I I sprained an ankle but
everybody's confused the story go gets
passed on down the line and passed down
the line
and it gets completely
right dismantled and
deconstructed and reconstructed and it
goes on Down the Line
Chris it says telephone
I'll have to get the telephone
this is how gossip and rumors can be
twisted and turned into hearsay
the game telephone
so this is how gossip and rumors can be
twisted and turned into hearsay as the
story goes from person to person
it goes through each person's
contaminated impeded blocked or
diminished neurons and the story changes
dude
it goes through everybody's contaminated
neurons
so the stories changing and it turns
into this different story and this
different story and this different story
and it goes down the line and when it
reaches another person
it can get twisted up again
this can happen on the most basic level
and it can happen on even the hierarchy
on this planet as well
people that run this planet
don't have pure neurons
where they're
completely uncorrupted
they don't have any toxins poisons
metals and junk and pharmaceuticals and
everything else in their neurons so when
they hear the story they get it all
right
people that run this world have this
problem too and what comes out of their
mouth is all twisted up but the problem
is everybody pays the price when they
don't get their stories right and the
information right crazy how it works
Matt says definitely need to read
them and re-read them and reread them
and reread them one more time incredible
thank you Matt
look I've been schooled by Spirit of
compassion big time on these books
every single word that went into the
books SOC would be like
gotta add this gotta add this you gotta
add that you got to fix this this is
what it is this exact word
and man I was schooled and I had to
learn
still learning I have to read the books
over and over again
scattered brains
as electricity travels through an
impeded neuron system it can become
diminished meaning that electricity
within the brain is no longer traveling
at its full capacity
so as electricity is running through
your brain it no longer runs at that
capacity
that is a group of neurons can receive a
fully charged electrical impulse and
then in the process of assimilating and
registering that electricity
which is filled with information and
sending it through the synapsis to
another group of neurons electricity can
be diminished so here's how it goes
you've got a full power source boom
electricity you got full electricity
going through your brain and then it
hits the contaminated neuron bam and
then it diminishes
that's how it works
you got some electricity to get super
powered that electricity it's running
good in here but then it's moving over
to here you guys it's moving over and as
it's moving over it hits a contaminated
part of our brain it goes boom and all
of a sudden it diminishes
[Music]
Mateo Mr Taco says I thought they were
just extremely extremely emotional
they're just too emotional that's what
it is
go see a counselor you're too emotional
now there's real problems why we're so
emotional and when we get hurt
emotionally listen here's what's
incredible about the brain saver books
if you've been hurt emotionally mentally
like mentally damaged from abuse
emotional damn emotionally damaged
from abuse and hardship and loss it does
something to our brain physically which
is medical medium information because
you know Neuroscience doesn't know that
this is all originally unique
information in these books
from first page to the last page
and our brains can emotionally
get injured but physically injured from
an emotional occurrence physically
injured and then impediment happens and
then we're sensitive Vivian says oh my
God yes I have that
happen in the grocery store I was
telling a lady something and she
repeated a whole other story I was
confused I didn't say anything back to
her out of respect I never understood
what happened
you were talking about apples
and after you're done and you really
explained that story probably a really
great top-notch
the lady said
what
oranges
foreign
with electricity is something that's
mysterious
and not understood the truth is that
electricity isn't just electricity so
medical research in science doesn't know
that electricity in your brain holds
information did you guys know that
that's medical medium information it's
in the brain saver books they don't know
they don't know how the brain holds
information they have no idea
so research in science the best
Neuroscience out there does not know how
your brain holds information like where
is it they don't know
the electricity in your brain that's
swimming around that's flying around and
rotating is carrying
the information
it's information traveling within the
electricity kind of how we use
technology today a thought is not just
something that resides within the
neurons and glial cells the brain tissue
and stays there a thought can travel
with the electricity that leaves a
neuron electricity can carry tremendous
amounts of thoughts Ronnie says this is
brand new information yay thanks
it is it is the brain saver books
it's the brain saver books ready ripe
for poaching from podcast doctors like
the other books and everything else and
they won't cite it back to Medical
medium I know I say that a lot but
it's sad
because what's going to happen is
someone's gonna be like whoa whoa doctor
podcast guy that was an amazing piece of
information you must be so smart I'm
gonna buy your Apple Cider gummies and
your diatomaceous earth charcoal powder
you know whatever and all your other
stuff and your whey protein powder and
all that because you must be so smart to
have that advanced information what's
happening is Dr podcast guy's not saying
where you got it from so people could
find out what to avoid and also be
cautious about at the same time
I'm trying not to be too snarky today
you guys
because the people can't find their way
back to heal that's why I'm Starkey
because
it's sad
electricity traveling through the brain
can carry information you won't or don't
use so electricity going through your
brain can carry information you're never
gonna even use you're not even going to
access man it's there for the taking
within the electricity so how do we take
that information out of electricity you
got electricity going through your brain
going through and it's information you
may never use ever ever you're receiving
but you'll never use it a bird chirps up
here you're not going to use that
information a squirrel makes a noise
over here you're not going to use that
information of you know an eagle flies
through the sky you're not going to use
that information anything going around
you your brain could be picking up the
electricity fills up with that
information a horn blows way over here
but you're not going to use the
information
we're trying to tell someone something
that we're getting from that electricity
and at the same time
leaving out information within that
electricity as well so here it is you're
trying to tell somebody like look I
gotta tell you I'm trying to tell you
something I'm trying to understand what
happened happened and electricity has
all this information and in your brain
but you can't get all of it out of the
electricity so you can't even tell the
person everything you wanted to tell
them
[Applause]
this is extremely Advanced unique
information so everybody knows I have to
put that disclaimer out constantly
someone new could come on here and be
like oh
we may feel there was something more to
say yet we don't know what it really was
you ever have something on the tip of
your tongue
it's on the tip of my tongue
it's on the tip of my tongue I gotta
tell you I can't remember what is that I
was gonna tell you something it was
there a second ago I have to tell you I
want to tell you I just don't know what
it is it'll come later it'll hit me
later
maybe it'll hit me later
it has already passed by us our
companion may say
were you going to say something else so
your friend your partner
someone that you're talking to
may say
were you going to say something else and
we may reply yeah I was so busy with
other thoughts I can't remember what it
was
that's because you let the electricity
was harboring the information inside
your brain was holding on to that
information inside your brain but you
couldn't grab it out of there
we're not having a memory lapse it's
information that slipped by inside our
brain's electrical grid that we didn't
access it's not a memory problem it's
not like oh God I got a bad memory right
now I don't know what I was thinking
Maria Lourdes says it happens to me all
the time
it's actually not a memory lapse signs
of research doesn't know that you're
losing your memory
no it's not a memory lapse right there
in that situation there's tiny nuances
and detailed information Susan Denise
says I need every protocol on the book
good grief bless you Anthony thank you
for being here
damage neurons can change thoughts
altering how someone perceives
information
damaged neurons
can change our thoughts we put our
perception can go off because of damaged
neurons Emma says I have been battling
severe depression for over a decade now
this knowledge is everything thank you
for being here
a monitor here Linda Larkin said thank
you for these mind-blowing books so glad
you guys are here I can't wait for you
guys hold these books in your hands
you'll feel it when you have them in
your hands it's really just incredible
that's because damaged neurons mean
altered disorganized and poorly
reorganized electricity so here it goes
if you have an injured neuron you guys a
damaged neuron the electricity
traveling through that neuron is going
to have scrambled information
scatterbrains
as electricity travels through synapsis
and heads to another group of neurons
information in that electricity could
become disorganized before it enters the
new group of neurons so as you've got
one group of neurons and electricity
goes into it it's going to go into a
whole bunch of of saturated contaminated
or injured neurons when that electricity
goes into that batch of saturated
contaminated neurons
it's going to get scrambled up so now
our thoughts
and our emotions everything and when
that electricity leaves that batch of
neurons and heads to another batch of
neurons it's got different information
in it meaning it's scrambled up it's
like
the brain fog brain fog starts to happen
won't the previous books address this
too all the medical medium books
are incredible books this is all new
information with even more information
on the brain packed with brand new
information
so that's why all the books are
important
often people say you know can I just get
one book you can look each medical
meeting book has been life-changing and
saved countless lives out there but it's
additional tools and protocols and I'm
only one human being one little human
being that
you know
can only put the books these books would
take other I mean this these books
if someone wanted to write medical books
with this much information say using
whatever was out there in the world of
medicine now it took them five years and
they would have a team of people citing
every study and what and I think it
would take them five ten years to to
finish a book like this
it's different in this situation getting
the information
both these books you know forget oh
these books take them 20 years
but that would be useless information
thank you
unlike these books
okay so let's go
so it's not just brain tissue that
Harbors thoughts and controls how we
feel and how we physically function
electricity itself also has the power
over our thoughts and physical control
but the electricity itself in our brain
has the power
that's what's incredible
it's part of how we can heal because the
electricity has its own power in our
brain
one job of neurons is to eventually pass
along information to the brain's
billions of glial cells where
information stays stored cataloged and
organized
the glial cells are clogged contaminated
saturated distorted or even mutated from
poisons and toxins a disconnected
breakdown can occur between your neuron
system and the glial cell system so when
your neurons are all messed up
that's one thing electricity going
through them with misinformation or
sorry scrambled up information then if
they get stored in their glial cells and
your glial cells are contaminated so
many people have Metals in their glial
cells contamination in other glial cells
then that's a whole nother problem all
on its own
I'm only look I'm only reading a
sentence here sentence there I mean I'm
still on the same page pretty much this
page and that page I'm working off I've
been kind of in between you're
witnessing history being made these
books are making history it's the first
time anyone has put out two books this
big two books released it once about a
topic like the brain this is actually
the most advanced information so you
guys are witnessing something historic
right now and maybe no one will care and
that's okay maybe long after I'm gone
someone will wake up someday and be like
that was pretty crazy
Advanced unique information that science
has been stealing from they'll dust off
a book a hundred years from now and be
like oh my God
where'd this guy even get this
information wait it says here he talked
he talked to some spiritual Force
read this information it's still
Advanced 100 years later who was this
guy let's go find him oh he died it's a
hundred years later
let's go dig them up
find out how he did it
do some science studies on them
so much information in here the greatest
books of all time as I said you guys
have promised you you will you will feel
that way and you will like tell someone
else because they'll read it and be like
oh my God what is this and you'll be
like it's the greatest books of all time
I have I have uh some personal friends
just like this is these are the greatest
books I mean and I can say and I could
judge it
because the information came down from
above and I could say okay these are
incredible books these are going to heal
people and change their lives
but these
is just
whoa
we just got to another level
these are the greatest books in health
of all time there won't be a podcast
doctor a Health Doctor a health
influencer anybody that can put out
books like these with information like
this it never happened before it never
did you just got to eat better books out
there medical medium books are are
really Advanced information right with
people healing but these books here
exactly
that Jill said the goat
the goat
greatest books of all time and Beyond
Marissa spiritual son
so misunderstanding the brain's needs
doesn't stop at trick supplements
everybody's an expert these days in
brain hacks you notice that
telomeres telomeres
oh
I I actually went to a neuroscience
event and I saw people talking about
telomeres I went on the stage and I did
a whole thing about genetics and
telomeres
kind of a glass of wine
I was in Napa Valley I had a glass of
wine it was 52 000 a glass it was a
perfect price
I'm gonna buy the vineyard with a bunch
of doctor friends
all right
everybody's an expert these days in
brain hacks it's often about how to
master our mind you notice that it's
like master your mind man that's what it
is spend your life mastering your mind
and then boom your triggered back into
it I gotta Master my mind again I gotta
do another course another course I gotta
figure it out I gotta figure out how to
like fix this rewire do whatever
I gotta do something and I'm not ripping
apart all that any tools we can get are
helpful to get us to manage and get by
but the problem is is how do we fix it
though how do we actually fix a problem
so we get rid of depersonalization by
polar anxiety panic attacks depression
anything how do we fix it I want to fix
fix Jeanette says internet on YouTube
unknown Angels please help our best
friend Anthony William to survive the
haters thieves in betrayers the most
underappreciated man in America again no
respect that's actually really funny
thank you by the way Jeanette
it made me laugh Allison podcast doctors
won't know what hit them yeah I know
well you know what it is they're going
to hear about the books Non-Stop
from everybody that's how it works it's
just gonna drive them insane then they
go and grab the book and then they go
whoa I gotta use that in my podcast
or I gotta invite somebody on there who
took it from the book and they'll act
like it's theirs
it's not even mine it's from above let's
respect that and say where it comes from
I'm the messenger
and let's get people to the book so they
can heal right
some of these strategies are how we
think right
I have been doing your protocols for the
last four years and my husband has only
jumped on board this week yeah you are
getting your information out amazing
tell them I said hi please
it's often about how we trick our
thoughts and perceptions trying to
better our lives with how we think right
when we're trying to master our mind
some of these strategies are positive
see I'm being positive I'm not being
sarcastic right there
I know everybody's trying to hack their
brains with some kind of technique and
stuff and I'm being positive I'm not
being negative about it it's often about
how we trick our thoughts you know
everybody's trying to trick their
thoughts trick them trick them out of
something right and perceptions trying
to better our lives with how we think
some of these strategies are positive
and can be very helpful temporarily
because I don't mind trying to manage I
want people to be able to manage
if you're doing stitches and patching up
some emotional physical conditions in
some situations you have to manage it
then you've got to use these hacks they
still don't get to the root of why we're
struggling I want to get to the root of
why I wish why we're struggling and I
said to SOC I want to get to the root I
need to know why everybody's suffering
and the spiritual bachelor's like yes
that's why we're here doing this and
it's in here
it's not about managing and hacks
Michelle oh I've heard doctors say they
already knew medical medium information
laugh out loud really because you've
been around for a long time in the
health field I know a lot of other
people that have too and nothing existed
literally medical media book one when it
came out
all original unique
and brand new and everybody knew it and
there wasn't one paper one study one
doctor that knew any of it and this is
eight years ago
and millions see the little gold emblem
there millions of these copies got
around the world and in every doctor's
office and everything else
so we're in here we're talking about
some good stuff
with these thought techniques out there
eat listen you will witness it again
with these books
and my new podcast episodes you're gonna
witness history being made again with
new information over again like the
blood draw information you guys
I mean it was just absolutely incredible
to blood draw information
and I go into real epic detail about
blood draw in the books
with these thought techniques we may
over compensate to the point that we
exhaust ourselves we try so hard to
control our thought patterns have you
ever tried that hard to keep positive
thoughts to create new references to
focus on confidence Builders positive
thinking right awareness it's all good
stuff new thoughts about how we feel
about our lives and we find that we're
still struggling with our problems why
why are we still struggling with their
problems when we tried so hard to
actually control our thought patterns
keep positive thoughts create new
references focus on confidence building
positive thinking awareness and all
that's good but why
why are we still struggling when we're
doing all that
because no one has shown us the root of
the problem and how to fix it for real
physical issues in our brains and
nervous systems all our energy goes into
trying to correct and battle our minds
by doing everything we can to make
ourselves better people spiritually
emotionally mentally but we don't know
what's wrong with ourselves
Michelle says they couldn't even tell me
why I reacted to eggs
tone man says do you discuss nerve pain
and physical trauma in the books do I
ever
and and I am at your service the books
are loaded with it
Mrs Ferguson's coming downstairs at AWS
Bar and Grill so hang on we have us
hotel rooms upstairs we got the bar
grill down here miss Ferguson
the doorway the doorway is over there
you're heading to the bar the other bar
where's Mr Ferguson he's on the toilet
tell him to come on down he's too sick
today okay what happened he's got a log
Jam
well okay okay well just just be careful
tell him to be careful
you guys look out for
look out for uh imposters these days too
old joke
it's just an old joke it's from one of
the past lives
that we did
all right
you guys there's so much information in
here I'm talking about the brain I'm
talking about static brain
the books are cranked up with
information really incredible stuff
let's go we'll talk a little bit about
something sorry you guys you guys are
all being kind of like I think there's a
glitch
I think there's a glitch you guys are
all being kind of like kicked off right
now
so look there's so much information in
here I can go on and on and on there's
so many different sections so let me
just give you a rundown through the book
we're talking about some great stuff
it's in the brain saver books brain shot
Therapies
that's gonna be really really incredible
the brain shot therapies when you get a
chance
brain shot therapies are for instant
relief
I can't get enough of them
there's the Betrayal and broken trust
one there's mold exposure
that's one right there that's really
cool there's ego shifter
I mean there's the burnout stabilizer I
mean it's incredible what's in the book
really incredible
anyway you guys listen I'm gonna get
going
and uh I'll see you next time hopefully
tomorrow let's do something tomorrow
I'll see you guys soon okay amazing
check out your brain saver copy