we're live right now
we're live
we're live on telegram facebook youtube
tick tock
we're live
you know
everybody's high
everybody's high do you think
everybody's high because it's a hard
world
i would probably say so yeah
if the world wasn't such a difficult
place to live in
i don't think everybody would be high
would you
if the world wasn't so corrupt
right down to the bone
where
there's toxic heavy metals just
saturating people's bodies chemicals
saturating people's bodies
if the world wasn't so difficult do you
think everybody would be high
no
then everybody's got to be high they
have to be high
it's the only way to survive it it seems
right
you'll be high gotta be high on pot you
gotta be high in ayahuasca you gotta be
high on e-cigarettes you gotta be high
on cigarettes gotta be high in alcohol
you gotta be high in caffeine you gotta
be high in prescription drugs
antidepressants you gotta be high on
amphetamines
did you know eighty percent
right around eighty percent of co all
college students and university students
are on an amphetamines
prescribed by their doctors
they have to be on amphetamines you know
there's a black market for amphetamines
for all the students too
so they can take way more than what's
prescribed
right why because the pla because the
world's an easy place
no the world's a hard place but
everybody has to be high
right and then the food
the food
right
god behind cheeseburgers and double
cheeseburgers double bacon cheeseburgers
the hot dogs bacon cheeseburgers they're
hot dogs hot dogs hot dogs making
cheeseburgers again hot dogs back and
forth
sausage eggs pancakes
grease fried grease ice cream we just
got to be then on lots of lots of
comfort foods fried foods pizza pizza
pizza pizza
we've got to be on this high
we have to right
so
restaurant food msg everywhere and
everything right fat and everything
fried everything you name it we got to
be high
so
everybody's walking around high on
something you're either high on wine
you're high not high on some kind of
alcohol you're high on some kind of
prescription drug you're high on some
kind of pot you're high in some kind of
shroom you're high on something and
amphetamine you're high in caffeine
matcha tea and the chocolate you're high
on chocolate but everybody's gotta be
high
that's how this world works
that's crazy
or isn't it right
is the world's a hard place i'm not
shaming anybody you know what's funny
i've never ever ever
for all going back since i was younger
and people were filing into my office i
never shamed one person ever who walked
to that door high on heroin high on
cocaine high on
caffeine high on shrooms high on pot
high on drugs high in opioids prescribed
opiates never shamed a single person who
walked through my door ever
you know what i said
it's a hard world and something must
have happened where the world was so
darn hard that you must have had to
somehow for some reason you fell into
something
so what are we gonna do about it
that's what i would say
and it would come into my office
i can't break my caffeine addiction and
alcohol addiction i can't break my
cigarette addiction i can't break my pot
addiction yeah everybody says pot's good
for you now
it's not
but i can't break this addiction now i
can't break the amphetamines my doctor
has prescribed me because i can't think
without amphetamines
and so
that you don't shame anybody
you know it's hard man you know it is
right so what you do
is you try to work them to a place and
bring them to a place of change
right
if i can't break your caffeine addiction
if i can't break your fast food
addiction or your fat addiction and
i know there's a whole bunch of people
that think their crap don't stink and
they think they're holier than god
they're doing their workout programs
they they know all the google
information about health they're
counting their carbs and their macros
they're they never got sick yet they're
young and indestructible they're working
out and they're doing their weights
right and they don't think they don't
think their crap stinks at all
and
but they're they're addicted too
and they don't know it they're still
jacked up on caffeine they're still
jacked up on other stuff they're still
eating their so-called healthy high-fat
diets where it's just lots of fat
right or they're starving themselves and
then boom and binging on fat starving
themselves and they're eating their
chocolate too they're still and then
they're still doing their alcohol on the
weekends
so don't give me that you're better than
jesus christ
because you're a googler now on there
oh count macros oh i could work out let
me get working out let me because i'm
feeling good enough anyway because i
haven't gotten sick yet so i'm going to
start working out and i'm start doing my
stuff so i'm better than jesus now
you know meanwhile you're still addicted
you're still addicted and in the end
that takes you down to a place somewhere
down the road it takes you down to a
place where it's gonna get you in
trouble one way or another because you
don't know enough you just don't
and
back to everything else yeah the world's
hard it's difficult and it gets a lot of
people in trouble
and then
there's the evil industries
the evil industries nobody knows they're
evil
nobody knows
nobody knows anymore nobody believes it
nobody even thinks it everything's
perfect out there higher than the evil
industries and they're brainwashing
people and brainwashing people
and brainwashing them
and there's all that
you guys right here we're gonna do some
celery juice because that's one way to
make change happen
right there
off the running you guys are live live
facebook youtube
tick tock telegram
i'm excited you guys i'm excited to be
here with you truly proud of all of you
by the way i'm just juicing a little
celery juice
by the way
[Applause]
50 off on the machine
i know what's gonna happen the sale on
this machine is gonna end right
and everybody's gonna be like hey i need
a celery juice or i need a juicer
what do i do
[Applause]
be like i don't know i
pay full price
but by the way the irony is about this
machine you can pay full price for it
and it'll still save you thousands of
dollars as time goes on
[Music]
and that's what's incredible about it
you get a free celery juice book at a
mega juicers.com
when you get this juicer it's 50 off
right now it's the mm 900 hds
guess what all right
guess what people walk through my office
and i would say you got to get on celery
juice
that's what would happen years ago you
got to get on celery juice that's going
to be the start of you breaking that
addiction that's going to be the start
of you turning your life around
that's what it's going to be
because in the end how do you heal
when you're on three addictions four
addictions five addictions six
addictions how many moms
made an appointment with me and brought
their college student son or daughter
into my office and said how do i get
them off of these prescribed
amphetamines or these these amphetamines
my child's getting in school because and
the universities you it's just like it's
open there you can just like buy just
that's what i'm hearing a doctor friend
told me that his son
in a prestigious university can walk
around any corner and just buy all the
black market drugs he wants
right
so he can he can keep with the studies
[Music]
[Applause]
and then
god forbid you're not feeling good
because then they'll just stick you on
open the doctor will stick you on
opioids
right
and then you'll be on that plus
everything else
you know
one of the things
to break these addictions i used to
recommend
would be celery juice
what's what's what's your friend's vice
do you guys know what your friend's vice
is
what's your family member's vice
do you know what their vice is you guys
know
the smoking is it e-cigarettes is it
you know what is it is it alcohol is it
too much
pizza
what is it right
celery juice is an incredible
tool
and a tool to help break
all the addictions
right
i can't tell you how many people got a
second chance
a third chance
in life
fourth chance fifth chance
right
there's nine lives people have right
and just
they got a chance to get their life back
through celery juice
how crazy is that
32 ounces every day
because here's what happens everybody's
brains are getting defunct
i'm just gonna be straight up
about this
everybody's brains are getting this
defunct right
people are getting brain burn out left
and right their brains are just fried
they're just burned okay
so they have to be on the cat being they
have to be on everything because if they
can't they're not on those prescribed
amphetamines and all that caffeine
and everything else if they're not on
that they're just gonna be like what
what what
and and i don't shame them and i don't
blame them it's sad
but everybody's brains are filled with
toxic heavy metals they're filled with
poisons they're filled with msg
they're filled with chemical
fertilizers from people's lawns around
apartment buildings i told you about
schools they saturate all the elementary
schools with pesticide and insecticide
do you know that so you send your
children elementary school and the
classrooms got termite and ant killer
laced in it
so your child sitting there in classroom
breathing in ant killer and termite
killer
[Applause]
setting the stage
for needing to be on amphetamines
prescribed by the
[Music]
doctors celery juice provides these
electrolytes to restore the brain and
battle this
it's a battle
it's a it is
it's a war
actually right
all this crap we're up against
and and what we're losing inside of our
minds
what we're losing inside of our minds
electrolytes
amino acids that are critical
phytochemical compounds
neurotransmitter chemicals
right
our brain cells just fall apart as the
years go on
and then our brains shrink
how do you stop a brain from shrinking
do you know that everybody's brain just
some people's brain is like half the
size as it was did you know that when
they're older their brain is half the
size as it was
their brain is literally it's half its
size
how do you stop your brain from
shrinking you better be putting back in
because it's that boat i talked about
last time you guys
more going out
than coming in
more of the important good stuff going
out that's leaving the station and
coming into the station right
that's important to know
you guys this is the um
this is the mm-900 hds it's on sale just
letting you guys know it's 50 off at
omegajuicers.com
[Music]
you get the celery juice book with it by
the way they they do that it's
incredible
which is amazing you get two free glass
bottles too so you get that as well
[Music]
yeah mega
mm-900 hdf that's your celery juicer
saves money the whole bit
so
what's incredible
we're going to still talk about
addictions we're going to still talk
about how to break them we're going to
still talk about a little bit of
information all around that i'm just
letting you know use whatever juicer you
have by the way if you have a juicer and
you don't have this one use it use it
make your celery juice make your celery
juice definitely
all right definitely
what you'll notice about the mmm 900 hds
the pulp is dry so that's what you'll
notice i'm just letting you know all
that extra juice
is how you save money and the juicer
pays for itself and then pays for itself
and pays for itself and pays for itself
and that's what happens
that's just a fact of life of what this
juicer works this is how this juicer
works it's a medical device that pays
for itself and like i always said you
want to be on this medical device or a
juicer as a medical device could be any
juicer right instead of being in a
hospital laid up on medical devices you
know like i always talk about right
strange ever since i have been juicing
celery
i feel
my nearsighted vision is getting better
in fact
i have to change my eye prescriptions
because it was too strong
diane
mind blowing
definitely
um
i'm just gonna pour this if you guys are
okay with that
so good to see you guys i'm excited
today's a great day
so i'm just pouring some celery juice
right
it's a simple and powerful change
always strain the celery juice i'm just
going to give you a quick rundown on
celery juice real quick a couple of
tidbits that are really important don't
add anything to it you guys know the
drill right
minimum of 16 ounces unless you're
hypersensitive for some reason it with
every maybe you're really toxic really
toxic your liver your body is really
toxic you're loaded with a ton of toxins
right
and then you start with a little bit you
can do four ounces six ounces eight
ounces right so you don't have to do 16
ounces you can start slow and build
yourself up and build yourself up get up
to 32 ounces someday
to change your life turn your life
around right
what i love about celery juice
okay
it gives so much back to us it's an herb
this is an actual herb it's not a
vegetable we have to remember that
because you'll see that out there you'll
see that oh that celery juice trend yeah
ray okay that trend is over no it's not
they hide it
people around they can't keep celery in
stores
they have celery shipments to whole
foods in all the health food stores
there's so much celery going there
they've never seen anything like it
before in our history
because millions and hundreds of
millions of people are drinking them but
there's closet drinkers and the media
doesn't want to talk about celery juice
anymore talked about it for five seconds
it doesn't want to talk about it anymore
because you don't want to talk about
something that brings somebody's health
back and their life back right you know
how corrupt everything is right where
they want to pretend you know
that things don't exist that get
people's lives back their health back
the system set up to make you sick so
remember that the system is built to
actually purposely make you sick
that's the plan
of the system
that's how they make everything go
around right that's how you do it
and celery juice is like this secret
weapon not secret weapon but they want
to keep it secret they don't want
anybody to know what it does and what
it's doing for people
but it's literally getting people's
lives back when nothing else could but
when that happens is you break the
system now
you end up breaking the system less
drugs
less drugs are being sold right less
drugs are being prescribed
you name it you know and the system just
starts to start losing money
and celery has the power to create that
to bring balance back right instead of
everybody just getting sicker out there
sicker out there sicker out there just
then then the medical system making
trillions more trillions more people
getting sicker because that's where it's
happening right well celery juice
is that one
thing
it's at least one of those things simple
things you can do with your own free
will to change that to change that right
um super yoga says love my celery juice
helps clear your mind makes it sharper
does it
ever so
tell you guys a little something so in
my office people would come walking
through the door what can i do what can
i do
how do i get off of all these addictions
get the celery juice going
and then boom their life would start to
change i know people 30 years ago 35
years ago they never quit drinking it
they still drink it
because they know it's what did it for
them they know it's one of those things
that did what it needed needed to do you
know show brown says how much the cost
of the juicer go to megajuicers.com
you'll see it's 50 off on this model
it's an mm-900 hds
and
you won't be disappointed the pulps dry
for a reason that's the way the juicer
is designed so you save money i used to
buy so much more celery to make
the juice right and then now i have to
buy less celery to make the juice
because it saves you money and then that
adds up and then each month you're like
whoa
i just made 50 bucks i just made 100
bucks
each month it's like whoa just another
100 another 200 you know because next
thing you know juicer paid for itself
juicer paid for itself over and over
again it's really cool it's really cool
they give you a free celery juice book
the medical medium celery juice book
right
so
when you talk to family and friends and
people you know
all right
when you talk to them you'll find out
what vices you either see there ask them
like what what are you doing and if
they're honest they'll tell you what
they're doing and you'll find two or
three vices four vices by the way food
prices are going up in the world
and that's why i like saving money with
something that's you know saving me
money so food prices all food prices are
going up
that's what's happening right
so food prices are going up and the next
year they're going to go up more
so what i like about this juicer is it's
saving me money and so that helps battle
that whole food price going up thing
so that's what's cool about it
when people are on two vices or three
vices which is two addictions three
addictions four addictions right
and once you become
knowledgeable
really knowledgeable
about addictions you can pick them off
you can pick them off what you're
knowledgeable about because a lot of
people they're not knowledgeable they
don't know
that too much fat in the diet's an
actual addiction because here's how it
works
the more fat you eat
the more adrenaline gets released
adrenaline's your blood thinner for fat
you're consuming
you think you're smart
you're eating a lot of nut butters
instead
maybe you're plant-based you're eating
lots of avocado oils and nut butters and
you think you beat the the processed
food greasy fried food
animal protein world you think you beat
it
but you didn't
you didn't
because if you keep on pounding the fat
doesn't matter what it is it could be
the healthy fats
i'm not saying you don't have to eat
like never to eat them no
you think you beat the system but you
didn't beat it you didn't beat the fat
i never ever make fun of someone who's
sitting at a wendy's party in a parking
lot in the drive-thru as i'm driving
down or sitting at a burger king
drive-through the whole every time i'm
driving
like every time i'm driving i'll drive
past the burger king i'll drive past the
mcdonald's you'll see the cars lined
right up right right what's that person
getting the person getting the big mac
what's that person getting i'm driving
like you know an unmasked spirit of
compassion like what is that person in
the window ordering right now just come
on tell me tell me for fun because we're
always doing the not so fun stuff
because tell me tell me what are they
ordering uh double cheeseburger what
else what are they ordering happy meal
what else are they ordering right
and so
right but you see the lines with all the
fast food restaurants right
and krispy kreme donuts there's a line
around there
always everybody getting their donuts
can i never say anything bad
not in my head
nor out of my mouth
because there's an addiction they're
addicted
they're addicted
and when i'm driving by the health the
health food restaurants and everybody's
out there eating you think i'm like you
think i'm like that you think when i'm
driving past the fast food restaurants
to begin with you think i'm thinking oh
[ __ ] you're eating all that junk and
garbage no i'm not
that that fool's eating all that fried
food and greasy stuff i'm not saying
that no guess what you think i i would
be and then when i'm driving past the
health food stores and health food
restaurants and everybody's sitting
outside right and they're eating their
healthy bean burritos and everything
else you think i'm saying hey good job
you guys those guys were [ __ ] lined
up at those fast food restaurants and
you guys are the smart ones you think
i'm doing that no i'm not
because you guys
are just as addicted as those guys
and none of you know what's happening
that's what i say
but i don't say
you're smart you're dumb
i don't say oh good job
you're not doing a good job what i say
is
i feel bad
because you think you're doing it right
and you're doing it wrong
you're just as addicted as everybody
else
even though you're being burritos got
avocado on it and canola oil on it and
olive oil in it and all this other stuff
you think you're escaping the whole fast
food thing
but you're not
you're just as addicted your adrenals
are
trying to clean it up every second
you're not doing your celery juice
and your adrenals are just pumping
pumping pumping trying to thin out that
food trying to thin it out with
everything they got
and you know what that high is when that
fat hits
that high is adrenaline when that fat
hits it's adrenaline
ah feels good goes down
cylinder just completely stopped me from
craving caffeine chocolate
alcohol and junk food with no effort
indigestion disappeared best decision i
made
in decades xx thank you ew
laura lorraine sorry lorraine casey
that it's incredible is what it does
right it knocks those out
it knocks those addictions out it's at
least the start
really important
you know
so i was in my office but years ago
phone calls would come in
be like how
we're it's not working i can't break my
son's addiction
they're like well how much celery juice
is he doing every day oh he doesn't want
to do the celery juice i can't get
anthony i can't get my my 22 year old
son to drink celery juice
i can't get my 19 year old son to drink
celery juice i can't get my my 30 year
old daughter to drink celery juice
i can't
i can't you gotta
you gotta try gotta keep on trying
that's gonna be part of how to break it
how to break it
right
so
the bottom line is
overall
we walk around
sick
sad and depressed
mental illnesses you guys are going
through the roof
people are struggling
mentally
emotionally like no other now
right
their brains
are bathing in acid
acid
bathing in fat
their brains are bathing in poisons and
toxins
toxic heavy metals
that's what the world should be talking
about
is the metals in everybody's brain right
but the world is this
is this
place
where purposeful evil happens right it's
on purpose you think it's not you think
it's just stupid people making mistakes
meaning like industries and stuff you
think they're just making mistakes
no
it's on purpose
it's what makes it all go around you
have to be sick
and they want you more than sick
they want you sick
and they want you gone
they want both
that's
what the darkness on this planet wants
and
if we don't get wise to some of it and
understand it
then how do you protect yourself
bottom line
how do you protect yourself talk about
the human body for a little bit by the
way if you guys just got on here it's
the mm-900 hds
tj just said you are so right
you guys we're live on telegram tick
tock
okay
we're live on telegram tick tock
facebook youtube
yeah they want us lemon balm love they
want us to be sick
everybody asks me over and over again
what you sir what you said because
remember the celery juice movement right
and celery juice so i'm asked that a
billion times a day i mean obviously
that's an exaggeration but it's
definitely a lot
and um
and then when there's a sale i got to
tell everybody because i feel like if i
don't then someone just lost a chance to
save 50 on the juicer
they lost a chance of getting like an
incredible book because it's free with
the juicer cmm 900 hds this is a celery
juicer model so it's the celery juice
juicer model mm-900 hds from
omegajuicers.com right
and this isn't metal on metal just so
you know you might be like oh i got a
really good juicer hey and
use it use it but remember this okay
remember this right
all right
okay
there isn't two metal gears in here
grinding against each other this is a
cold pressed juicer without the two
metal gears grinding against each other
okay keep that in mind right this isn't
the centrifuge with all that metal
flinging around too okay
keep that in mind
so
i get it there's a lot of juicer
companies out there and they're like our
cold pressed juicer it's historically
great people love it blah blah blah okay
good glad you love getting all that
metal in you
because you got the metal gears rubbing
against each other this one doesn't
important to know easy to clean pull
this off boom put it in the sink you
clean it in a minute a couple of minutes
and then you're good right
so um anyway it comes with two free
glass bottles too not just the book
and the food price is going up the food
price is going up
this is gonna save people money okay
so talk about what the addictions do and
how it works your brain
starts to get used to the high
the addictive high
it's
one joint doesn't do it anymore
one joint won't do it anymore right
a little bit of ayahuasca won't do it
anymore a tiny bit of shrooms won't do
it anymore you need more
you don't get the same experience
a little bit of cbd cbd oil and i'm not
ranking on cbd oil if you're somebody
uses it and you're somebody that uses
pot or somebody that uses i know they're
two different things unless you've got
thc in the cbd oil but what i'm trying
to tell you is
if you're somebody on any of this stuff
alcohol if you're somebody eating fast
food every day i'm not
shaming you
i'm on your side
okay 100
i don't know what it's like to be in
your shoes possibly right
whatever's happened in your life isn't
what happened in my life
look
you know look at people chronic illness
nobody knows what it's like to be in
their shoe
uh-uh nobody knows what it's like to
feel what their shoe size is like
okay
so with somebody with chronic illness
and and everything they've gone through
with chronic illness all right
so and i get that
what i'm saying is the high isn't enough
that's why people who drink alcohol end
up drinking a little bit more alcohol
and a little bit more at some time in
the life of it a little bit more and
people who start out smoking pot end up
smoking a little bit more and a little
bit more people who do fast food end up
that's not enough i want to order this
now and this down this now now i want to
go to this restaurant and try that
gastro abomination now i want to go to
this restaurant and try that you know
abomination right because there's
there's a high what about the foodie
highs oh i'm a foodie
i'm a foodie
you know i travel around the restaurants
and i'm a foodie you know i like to try
this restaurant that restaurant because
there's this high and you can't get
enough
right everything because the brain
ends up
maxim it ends up maxing out where you
have to trump it you have to ride over
that
you have to ride over that
then it's not enough
a little piece of chocolate once a
week's not enough you need more
chocolate now and then more chocolate
and you need a quarter of a bar then you
need a quarter of a bar every single day
until something inside of you says oh
[ __ ] oh [ __ ] i better stop eating two
chocolate bars a
day i better stop i better stop you know
eating two chocolate bars a day
right
because
something inside here in the brain
here's how the brain works
neurotransmitter chemicals
neurotransmitters neurons and everything
else glial cells the brain works where
you
you have to keep on upping
the ante
to get a feeling like you used to feel
you have to keep on upping it
right it's people there's people that
are addicted to fighting
right they're addicted to fighting and
they start yelling and have an argument
that ain't enough
the next week they start yelling and
having a bigger argument the next week
they start yelling and having now
they're slamming the doors running out
of the house running out of the office
now they're they're they're now they're
having a bigger coral right
it becomes addictive where adrenaline
surge occurs
and then the depression that hits
afterwards
after those fights
it's all part of the addiction can get
you trapped in there
okay same thing when you're bulimic and
you're anorexic bulimic and you're
throwing up your food
it becomes addictive the the there's an
addiction quality to it
if someone had emotional abuse and it
made them bulimic because they had
severe emotional abuse right happened to
them and they became bulimic right
and they're throwing up everything they
eat
they start out just throwing up once
okay
and then they've got a high off of it
because when you throw up
force yourself to throw up
your adrenals explode
they explode
and then whoa my high is coming down my
high's coming down throw up again boom
throw up again
they're self-medicating
somebody with bulimia self-medicating
and their adrenals explode again
i'm gonna go to this fast food
restaurant and eat this big gastric
abomination your adrenals start to
explode
i'm going to get i'm going to get on my
my uh my amphetamine
from my black market amphetamine or my
prescribed doctor's amphetamine you guys
give me a thumbs up if you get a chance
to before i forget if you don't like the
video give me a thumbs up anyway i don't
know
if you like the video give me a thumbs
up
okay
so
that's what happens right so back to the
bulimia
so
one throw up's not enough
the brain
plateaus
now it's throwing up once a day instead
of once a week
but that adrenaline high
now you're throwing up every day
now you're addicted
same thing with an anorexia starving
yourself
the adrenals when you starve yourself
everybody's that's on an intermittent
fasting diet
right
is on a type of anorexic diet did you
know that
when you don't when you withhold from
food all day purposely
right
when you do that all day your adrenals
are exploding all day long
when someone who's anorexic
right that doesn't want to eat and it
becomes such a problem their adrenals
are exploding giving them high
it fills in for missing blood sugar so
i'm on an intermittent fasting diet not
eating anything but coffee and caffeine
and then i'll have a big fat meal at
night um yeah i'm slimming down nice
from it you're just living off of
adrenaline and eventually
that will run out you'll burn those
adrenals out something will happen down
the road right
someone who's anorexic is withholding
from food because they have some
emotional abuse that happened to them
something terrible happened to them or
like i said toxic heavy metals in the
brain there's a reason why they're
anorexic and they don't want to eat but
that they're living off of adrenaline
from not eating and
eventually
it's not enough
so you stop eating longer
you stop eating longer
you want more adrenaline high
and the opposite can happen when you're
eating all that fast food and that
grease
you want the adrenaline high so you eat
more of it
i'm gonna have pizza every night
oh no i'll have something else this
night
addictions
do this right where
your brain
maxes
and then you have to override and
override and try to get the same feeling
again but go further and further
right how many people i've talked to
over the years you're going to start out
smoking a little bit of pot on the
weekends
then they needed a lot of pot on the
and then they needed
lots of marijuana all week long and then
they smoked it three times a day
and their wife was like get the hell out
of here i'm divorcing you
how many friends how many have i seen
that to do that right i've seen i can't
tell you can't count how many over the
years
and and because you you max out and you
have to override
same thing with chocolate
a little square once a week
you need three squares
now you're gonna need ten squares or
you're gonna need two chocolate bars
then you're gonna eat in your smoothies
same with medications amphetamines
right
a little bit ain't enough why do you
think all the college students are
looking in the black market in their
prestigious schools they go around the
corner and they buy it right there
no one says anything
it's possible it's practically passed
out for free
on campuses
because the prescribed dose isn't enough
for all the students
so you need that prescribed dose from
the doctor and then they need a whole
bunch more because you you need to
override to get the feeling you need
again same with alcohol
same with alcohol
but you think they'd be passing out
celery juice passing that around through
all the prestigious universities no
you think they'd be passing all the
celery juice around in the medical
universities no of course not
passing around drugs you think you think
they'd be passing on celery juice
everywhere
no
because nobody wants to fix anything
nobody wants to fix anything so it's up
to us how we empower ourselves to take
control over our lives you know
and and it's up to us to do that for
ourselves
because the system is not going to teach
it's just going to destroy
that's what it does
the celery juice is one powerful tool
that's what it is
it's one powerful tool to really move
the needle it's what it's about
it's about
so
check out the medical mean podcast at
apple podcast and check out the coffee
matcha tea chocolate episode if you guys
get a chance i talked about blood draw
the other day right
check out the blood draw podcast you can
protect yourself because they're gonna
bleed everybody dry in the next one to
five years
they're gonna vampire blood out of you
guys like you've never seen before with
your aches and pains the doctor is going
to be like no let's get more blood work
you know let's get more blood work let's
get 12 more vials let's get 10 more
vials and all that blood
is going to be carried away someplace
carried away
and then you know
bottom line is
they're going to drain everybody make
them more deficient make them more
deficient and people are ready to fish
it they're going to lose their glucose
the glucose deficiencies they're going
to get
and you know
what news flash
i love how they say your brain's made
out of all fat it's not
it's made out of storage stored like
glycogen okay glucose
stored glycogen
without glucose your brain dies within
five seconds
ten seconds
for sure five seconds it starts to die
right your brain has traces of fats all
through it
but your brain's made mostly out of
glycogen that's what the tissues made
out of right
so
what's happening here now with everybody
right
is they're teaching people to be afraid
of sugar afraid of sugar
the critical clean carbohydrates i've
talked about that's medical medium
information the potatoes and the sweet
potatoes and the fruits right
and even peas and and
steamed
sweet potatoes and regular potatoes and
purple potatoes really good for people
for bringing the brain back
what happens is that when they study the
human brain they study the human brain
with overweight cadavers they cut them
open
and their brain had fat in it like a
chicken does
okay
when you have chicken you see all that
fat in the chicken you guys ever see
that when someone puts a big nice piece
of chicken on your plate right and you
see all that fat that yellow stringy fat
all through the chicken
right because they fatten the chickens
up and they fatten them up so you guys
have your chicken right
well the same thing happens to our brain
right
we get a lot of fat in the brain it
builds up it shouldn't be in there
you get fat all around it the brain
starts shrinking and then more fat
starts to show up the brain starts
shrinking right
and
and that's part of how we basically lose
ourselves and get sick throughout the
years
so that's important to know too that's
part of it we lose the gluck we lose the
glucose the glycogen reserve our brain
starts to shrink over time
and
that's important to know
so
on that note when i was talking about
addictions in fact some of you and i'm
going back to this for a reason because
some of you pray like fats are good for
you you need fats brains made out of
fats
right
so the brain study they did for how much
fats in your brain
saw an overweight cadaver
with additional fat that shouldn't have
been surrounded around the brain
just like you get fat around your liver
and you get a fatty liver people get a
fatty brain
important to know
and it had it in in it around it twisted
in it too fat that's not supposed to be
in there bad fat that's not supposed to
be wrapped around your brain when you
look at a cadaver
that that's not overweight the
percentage of fat in the brain is cut in
half
and then you look at a healthier cadaver
the percentage is even lower
and lower
and that's how it works when they cut
open a brain of somebody who's 90 years
old and is still lean after all those
years and didn't consume a really high
fat diet and they cut open that
cadaver's brain there's very little fat
in the brain
right they cut open a 50 year old
that's
pounds and pounds overweight
where do you think all that fat goes
it's just in the skin it's just under
the skin is that where all the fat goes
it's wrapped in and around the organs
liver the spleen
wrapped around the colon wrapped around
the brain
and so i know it's talking about fats
being addicted and we're looking for the
greasy foods and then we're looking for
healthy fats because that's what we want
to eat all the time but we have to
remember
that you got to lower those fats
so you don't kill your adrenals and help
to break the addiction so you can learn
about that information on many of the
lives i've done and everything guys i'm
heading off to ig
all right
and uh we'll talk a little bit more
about glucose of the brain and other
things too i'm gonna head off to ig i'm
gonna turn tick tock back on i'm going
to turn telegram back on
i'm psyched about this this is great and
you guys check out the mm-900 if you
haven't
mm-900 hdfs 50 off if you get it now
it's on sale at omegajuicers.com
it's a celery juicer model just know
it's that model
and
that's the one that saves money i talked
about that and the food price is going
up this is
gives me relief because i'm like buying
a lot of celery because i juice a lot of
celery so anyway you guys
um you get the free seller juice book
whole book the whole bit so all right
see you guys on ig see you guys back on
tick tock see you guys back on telegram
a little while
love