what would you like sir
would you like a shot
okay how many shots
four shots okay coming right up
yes how long have i been a bartender
many years
do i have experience yes i have
experience i do
you don't believe that because why i
just spilled some
that can happen just naturally
say four shots sir
okay
what would the misses like
she would like a shot okay
uh coming right up
here you go here's your four shots
guys we're live right now i'm making
wild blueberry hibiscus iced tea
i'm making wild blueberry lemonade good
to see you guys
and i got the wyman's wild blueberry
juice sale
on the wild blueberry juice which is
mind-blowing ten percent off so if you
order a case or a three bottle
or a case ten percent off right now
which is incredible right with the code
wild wild
then if you get their subscription you
get 10 off the first order anything you
order right
you know how many bottles whatever and
then it's five percent
off your order with the prescription
with the prescription with the
subscription
incredible
so
you know when it comes down to wild
blueberry juice the health benefits are
incredible good to see you guys
coming on incredible right
oh man i know you guys listen they're
working on it they're working on getting
it around the world they are
they are working on it gotta hang in
there for getting it around the world
all right they're working on it
but yeah it's incredible so i just
wanted to make a couple of drinks talk
about
why the wild blueberry's so incredible a
little bit
and
i'm just reading your comments as you
guys are coming up it's exciting this is
really fun i want to have some fun today
right
yeah
it's it's it's incredible so i got the
wild blueberry juice right here the
sales on right now wymans.com
you can check it out right the link is
in the description the link is in the
bio you guys
i never ever could believe when i was a
kid and i was laying in a wild blueberry
field
i know i told you guys this before but i
just i couldn't believe it i was just
laying in the sea of wild blueberries
around me right
and the birds were just flying by above
me
and some clouds would come and the sun
was out and i'd be laying in those
glorious
blueberry field right with blue
blueberries just
being in the sun hitting that minute
beaming
and spirit of compassion telling me the
power they had and how amazing they were
right for the body and health and the
antioxidant
levels
an entirely different beast all together
in the food world because that's what
everybody's up against are up against
oxidation
so everything we're up against is
oxidation right now that's what it is
chemicals toxocapa metals pathogens
whatever it is it's oxidation it's like
oxidizing the body right acids
everybody's acidic and we just sit there
and we oxidize we oxidize we age really
quick
and then we just we're set up for
disease we're set up for sickness you
know that's what happens you love the
juice lifelong amazing
yep
incredible incredible now this isn't the
cultivated blueberry this is the wild
blueberry huge difference right there
all on its own the cultivated blueberry
is an empty
like an empty shell it's it's yeah it's
healthy
but
big difference between wild blueberries
and cultivated blueberries something to
know right there cultivated blueberries
the big blueberries in the clam shells
you go to the store you get the little
clamshell pack
and you open the clamshell right
and you got the big blueberries in there
i mean
they're okay for our health just like
any fruit
but a wild food is an entirely different
situation so what happens is
you can burn
the wild blueberry to the ground burn it
to the ground
right
and it will grow back up it'll grow back
up
you burn an oak tree down
you burn a thousand-year-old oak tree
down it won't come back up
you need an acorn
being carried
by
a bird
or a squirrel you need an acorn
and plant that acorn in the ground in
hopes that that oak tree grows right
when it comes down to the wild blueberry
plant you can burn it to the earth
scorching
scorching flames and it grows back up
and it has survived the tundra
thousands and thousands of years of cold
drought
right everything
and it's that kind of food that takes it
to another level so that's a wild food
and that's what i love you guys you came
here now there's a sale going on
wymans.com
incredible sale right
and
what i love about that what i love about
this there's nothing in here
there's nothing in here no natural
flavors which is msg and poison
okay no citric acid
which is which is poison okay link is in
the description link is in the bio you
guys wymans.com right check it out
there's no citric acid in here
there's no hidden anything in here like
there is in all the other stuff out
there you just ordered yours incredible
angela did you get your 10
you got your 10 off incredible 10 off
the case
you got to do the wild right wild the
code wild
right oh well wild code isn't valid with
the subscription
that's what um
honeydew's asking
it's it's not it's automatic with this
with a subscription automatic
honeydew
if you do the subscription it's
automatically there the discount you
don't need the the code wild
but if you're not going to do the
subscription and you just do you want 10
off
your order right now wymans.com and you
don't want to do the subscription you do
code wild you know wild right
subscription you don't need it you don't
need the code it's automatically there
incredible right
i'm going to make a couple of drinks
with this incredible juice
so
i just want to run down a couple of
things first of all you know i work with
wyman's because i want this stuff to
stick around
because what it takes to harvest
these wild blueberries
in this one little window of the year
this one little window in north america
right up in maine it's one little window
you only get this one shot to harvest
these babies that's it
and then to harvest them
and then to put them in a press
to squeeze the juice out of them
not an easy process
right
to get
a wild medicine because that's what i
call it that's what i call this my
family calls it that's what i call it
see that says i've been drinking it for
eight months all of my friends keep
telling me how pretty my skin looks it's
the antioxidants on facebook incredible
zanette on facebook
antioxidants so what's the difference
why does the wild blueberry antioxidants
make a difference right
entirely different than the clamshell
case you know you get the clamshell
half pine or pint whatever it is right
you get the little pint-sized clamshell
cultivated blueberries
i won't even get those it's not that i'm
a snob
it's not that i'm snob
you know when i go in the store and i
see those i'm like no i'm i'm not
getting that
you know i want to drink
i want to drink that
blue gold i want to drink it i want to
drink that gold and
so because you know what happens is the
the regular cultivated blueberry
doesn't have that anthocyanin level it
just doesn't have it doesn't have that
polyphenol level it doesn't have that
link is in the description guys i'm
going to make a couple of drinks but i
just want to talk about the wild
blueberry a little bit and why the juice
is so critical and the whole bit and why
i'm so happy about the fact that it
exists the fact that they press this
stuff and they put it in the bottle so
when i look at the bottle i'm like
what's in here right
no citric acid no msg no natural flavors
no garbage no hidden stuff thrown in
there
right no fortified
bs
none of that no fillers hidden
underneath at all right none of that so
that's important you guys
it's one thing right there that's
incredible right
not from concentrate nothing's added and
it's not hpp baby no way is it hpp
dang right hpp
bad
and that's what i love about it
high pressure pasteurization is bad and
this isn't hpp
so and that's what i love about it right
there it's incredible serena says
that new one well yeah well this is a
what
i'm gonna pour a glass of wine in a
little bit
invite my doctor friends over
mm-hmm they graduated from the best
medical university
they're here they have their own
practice they're coming over they're
gonna have a glass of wine with me
we're gonna do some wine tasting here
and we're going to see how dry the wine
is
and how good the wine is
so i want to talk about the difference
like when we're talking about
antioxidant power
why like
zanette was saying her skin looks good
after drinking it for eight months and
what's happening with that right
antioxidants stop you from oxidizing
that's the whole point oxidizing means
you're you're dying
that's what we do we spend a lifetime
oxidizing until we're finally
gone
that's how it works right
i don't know what's going to happen once
i start drinking this i'm already
getting kind of silly now just talking i
don't even know when i start drinking
this it could get really bad
all right
i'm gonna get drunk on this stuff
today i'm gonna get drunk on this stuff
all right so we're talking about the
antioxidants right
so manganese
manganese not magnesium
manganese okay
manganese
is the
mineral
trace mineral that connects the dot with
the antioxidant
i'm just telling you right now how it
works
manganese helps to connect the dot with
the antioxidant it helps the antioxidant
work
and so what wild blueberries have in
them
and the wyman's wild blueberry juice has
in it
is
manganese
so it's high in manganese now if you get
a you know if you get a batch of wild
blueberries
and you can get them that one time in
your in that year or you get some frozen
wild blueberries
they have it in there too right when you
press it
and press it
and it's in its potency like this
takes it even to another level right
which is incredible but manganese
is that dot connector for an antioxidant
to actually work
and so
when it's high in manganese
naturally occurring because the wild
blueberry is so high in manganese it's
insane freaking insane actually
because of that
any antioxidants that you got cooking
inside that wild blueberry the dots
connect it when that dot's connected
stuff happens in your life and your
health stuff starts to happen and that's
a big part of it right there
so we're gonna make some drinks we're
gonna have some fun i'm making wild
blueberry hibiscus iced tea and i'm
gonna be making wild blueberry lemonade
i'm excited about this right
it lasts it lasts a long time the
refrigerator you crack it open you do
two ounces a day for your health
that's what you crack it open you do two
ounces a day you do four ounces a day
whatever you'd like to do okay
and i'm going to get some ice too in a
second as well
i think i might need a shot
i'm gonna have this right here
i'm one of those wimps i'm only sipping
my shot right
you ever see that
ever see a show everybody's drinking
shots and
i'm sipping my shot
i'm like a wimp
that stuff is harsh man
there's vodka in that one
there's no vodka in that one it's
straight wild blueberry juice and it's
not harsh it's delicious and it's fun
and it tastes good it's incredible
all right
there's an energy about the wild
blueberry i don't know if you guys have
ever experienced it
i've experienced it in my life i've been
blessed i've been very fortunate and
lucky to actually be walking through a
wild blueberry
field when i was younger
and
you can feel it the energy
and when you lay on the earth with those
wild blueberry plants
they're
humming
the dragonflies are flying around
honeybees are kind of
jumping around
and you got those beautiful wild
blueberries just sitting on top of the
plants
and the wind is blowing through them and
they're kind of all doing this thing
and it's beautiful and it is incredible
experience and you can feel the energy
and the frequency of the wild blueberry
plant with the wild blueberries on
right there right there
on display
for the universe to see
[Music]
it's really incredible
and you lay in that field and it's an
experience all on its own
and when i think about the fact that
that's bottled and put into
our hands is just unbelievable to me
it's
unbelievable lola leona where do i
purchase it there's a link in the
description right there check it out
wymans.com check out the link right
off
which is incredible
10 off
with the code wild wild now if you do
the subscription it's 10 off for the
first order on this on the subscription
and you don't need the code wild and
then it's five percent always it's five
when you're when you subscribe when you
do the subscription it's always five
percent off all the orders
incredible
i'm telling family friends everybody do
the subscription do the subscription
definitely do the subscription
very few companies i work with out there
and i work with wyman's because
for them to do this alone
is unbelievable all right
because
it's not an easy process to put this
stuff in a bottle and have it there for
people so they can
do their antioxidant shot and that's
what i call an antioxidant shot
a lot of people don't understand
antioxidants they don't they don't know
what that means anthocyanins polyphenols
and antioxidants they just don't
understand it out there and i was
talking to a doctor recently
he's like yeah yeah antioxidant i'm like
yeah yeah antioxidant antioxidants it's
what stops our flesh from decaying
antioxidants
okay are a big deal because antioxidants
for our brain keeps our brain alive in
fact
why is there a big wild blueberry on
brain saver
right on the book brainsaver
because the wild blueberry
that antioxidant is so critical for the
brain so critical so i want to make a
drink you guys for some you know have
some fun wild blueberry hibiscus iced
tea let's start there
i'm going to take this glass
and you guys if you can just give me two
seconds i am going to run really quick
don't worry i'm still here
still here you guys
messing around
and i got my eyes right here because i
want to have some ice
i'm going to put that right here for a
moment
guys i'm making a drink we're live right
now
good to see you guys
okay
sorry about that i ran as fast as i
could
to my little freezer and i went and
grabbed a bunch of ice because we're
making drinks if you guys just came on
here incredible sale wymans.com link is
in the description if you can take a
look
and you won't be disappointed ten
percent off on a case or any order right
now ten percent off use the code wild
w-i-l-d links in the description check
it out right if you if you actually
subscribe with their subscription deal
there five ten percent off for the first
order
and then five percent off it's automatic
enough to put the code wild in there
once you do the subscription
all right so
let's make this
drink to start with right
so this is a hibiscus so i'm going to
put hibiscus tea in here
so this is hibiscus tea
see you guys
i brewed it
just a little while ago
here it is right
so i'm gonna put that hibiscus tea in
here
we got it
right so we got our hibiscus tea
that's to start with you guys take a
look i'm gonna drop some honey in here
you can use maple syrup if you want if
you don't want to use honey you guys
doing these drinks is so great when you
have company over here you have people
over right
you can totally do these drinks if you
have alcoholics in your family
if you have alcoholics in your family if
your friends are alcoholics
you can actually
do this right here and they'll really
appreciate it they'll really love it
because there's no alcohol in here
but they'll really love it so i just put
some honey in there and i want to mix
that honey up okay
so easy it's ridiculous
so easy it's absolutely ridiculous
so i'm just mixing up that honey if you
guys don't mind
right
so that's hibiscus tea i just put a
bunch of honey in there i'm mixing it up
this is an incredible drink wait to
wait till you try this drink
it's just so good right
way to you guys wait till you guys try
this try this so i just mixed that up
right there perfect
okay so i got hibiscus tea in here
just like that now
putting in the wild blueberry juice
would you like one
okay
i got a little bit of wild blueberry
juice in there now check this out i'm
gonna drop a little ice in here now
you can put as much ice as you want i'm
gonna drop some cubes
it's an open bar you guys
open bar
and buffet
right dropping some ice cubes in here
look at this
nice
okay
wow
now i'm going to take a piece of mint
right here
all right you guys see on tick tock
there we go look at the mint
here we go i'm going to put a little
piece right here so i'm going to take
this part if you guys don't mind
right i'll pop that right in here
so good
so that's hibiscus tea with wild
blueberry juice in there you guys got to
try it don't knock it till you try it i
mean it's incredible it's so good it
tastes so good right and then incredible
viviacarro bartender i'm the bartender
today how may i help you
[Music]
i got shots right here beats alcohol by
a long shot cold white spring says may i
agree 100
umakali like a pro thank you i'm honored
truly so that's one drink i want to make
that's my i planned on making that drink
because i was excited i couldn't wait to
make that drink
and then i'm going to do some other
stuff too let's make a wild blueberry
lemonade i want to do that as well so if
you guys just came on here
okay
10 off
shop no that's a different one okay
wymans.com that's it right there that's
that's where to go
links in the description wymans.com
okay
now when you press in the code when you
put the code in
to get your 10 off on an order
all caps wild wild all capital letters
and then you're in if you do the
subscription you don't have to put any
code in you get 10 off on your first
order and you get five percent off from
there on out with the subscription it's
insane i mean how incredible is that
lucy does it doesn't it lose nutritional
value once it's juiced and bottled it
doesn't that's the incredible thing
the wild blueberry
right
gets more accessible to the body
when frozen
right or put in a bottle and that's
another thing people don't realize
okay so it actually helps
because what happens is there's a big
difference with the wild blueberry it's
not a cultivated
it's not a cultivated
berry cultivated berries have different
polyphenols they have different
antioxidants the whole entire thing so
it's really incredible what it does
hpp is not good though so
what you have to realize
high pressure pasteurization that's not
this
that i don't trust that i don't like i
do not trust hpp
that's why i always say people if you do
your celery juice don't do hpp don't buy
it like that there's a big difference so
when you look in here
it's not from concentrate there's
nothing in here no citric acid no
natural flavors no msg no fillers the
whole bit let's make another drink
angela how much do we use in the heavy
metal detox smoothie as a sub for two
cups of wild blueberries
now
this is potent stuff
okay
you don't want to throw a bottle of this
in your
smoothie like you don't want to take it
and throw the whole bottle in just like
until it's done you don't want to do
that okay
all right so there's a difference so
with this it's like if you want to do
the heavy metal detox smoothie you could
do two to four ounces throw it in there
four ounces is good boom four ounces if
you want to do a smoothie
you can even get away with two ounces if
you wanted to do that in a smoothie you
can get away with that
if you don't have your wild blueberries
or anything like that
so it's ten percent off on a case
or even three bottles if you want to get
three bottles right if you do a
subscription it's 10 off first order and
5 from there on after the subscription
is cool that's a great thing to do
that is amazing so you guys take a look
at this drink before i move it out of
the way
right there it is i'm gonna bring it
into view
that is the hibiscus one
now let's make the lemonade
let's make a lemonade so see you later
drink i'm gonna move you over a little
bit
all right next
make some lemonade
we need some lemons i got some right
here
i'm gonna cut some lemons and squeeze
some lemons
it's got one lemon right there
i shouldn't be throwing lemons around
while i got all these shot glasses here
and everything else that could be an
epic disaster
so i'm squeezing some lemons in here so
i'm making a lemonade
with wild blueberry juice this is a
great drink
great drink for kids this is a great
drink
for your aunt
this is a great drink for your cranky
uncle
this is a great drink for your mom your
dad
your grandparents
if one of your grandparents is
says they don't want this and you're
saying no no i'm making this for you
just tell them be quiet and drink it
they don't know what's good for them
you know i'm kidding
i'm just squeezing so i'm just making
sure i got some lemon
juice here
right
[Music]
you really don't need much more than
that
nice look at that you guys incredible
incredible
umakali dr nesbit
dr desmond and me are not in good terms
we're not in good on good terms at all
right now
he botched up a surgery really bad and i
actually
was really upset at him because
he took somebody's
took somebody's heart out of them and he
was supposed to
have the
transplant ready and then he realized
he didn't have it in the refrigerator
and it something went wrong and
whole thing was a disaster dr nesbitt is
not
a good friend of mine right now he's
been making a lot of mistakes in his
surgeries lately he says he has a 100
record of
always succeeding but i don't know
plus he doesn't like these drinks
because there's no alcohol in them so
michelle says show us a great recipe
that children love okay the lemonade
let's do it
i'm not someone got me off track talking
about dr nesbitt i'm supposed to be
making lemonade
all right
let's go so i'm gonna put the lemon
juice in here first
take a look you see that you guys
this is really fun we're gonna get some
honey in here now
you guys make sure you take advantage of
the
sale
now i like to put a lot of honey in
there god you make it so good with a lot
of honey in there right i'm gonna put a
little bit more
yeah
god it's gonna be good you see that you
guys the lemon juice and the honey right
there
yeah this is gonna be good look you see
guys on tick tock
look i'm here and i'm mixing this up
so i'm mixing that honey and that lemon
juice up real nice
there we go
i want to just mix it up good i don't
want all the honey at the bottom
you got to keep that in mind right
you don't want the honey on the bottom
so you want to just mix that up good
the honey's dissolving nice
so what you do is you get 10 off on the
case right now put the code wild in
right the link is in the description
wymans.com links in the description
right
if you do their subscription
you get 10 off in the first order but
you get 5 off right okay i just want to
mix that up good
there so i got the honey and the lemon
that's the that's the base right that's
the base
now we need a little bit of water
that's next
so i got some
nice clear water here
you don't need a lot of water
that's nice right there
[Music]
now we're going to get the blueberry
juice
i might crack open another bottle
gonna add some blueberry juice to this
now
i'm gonna crack open another bottle
that's what i'm gonna do
but i also need some ice
something i need
i think that might be good i think i'm
gonna put a lot of ice in here
i'm gonna mix that up
this is an incredible lemonade
go to a lemonade stand and you see this
and
can i have a lemonade yeah sure here it
is it's like a set of lemonade
all right let's get some mice in here
robinson says oh you mean would
subscribe and save on no no i'm talking
about the link is in the description
right
wymans.com
you go to wymans.com
and if you do their subscription plan at
wyman's
it's ten percent off the first order and
then five percent off of every order
from there on with their subscription
it's an incredible opportunity
now if you don't want to do their
subscription at wymans.com right
you can just get 10 off for this month
use the code wild wild
now we're gonna do this next okay so if
you guys give me a second here
here we go
i'm gonna cut this
lemon slice
michelle says thank you anthony i know i
can get the grandkids to drink that and
love it oh incredible
that makes me so happy seriously
so i got a little lemon wedge right here
so i'm going to carve this out
put a little carve here
put that lemon on top
boom
when is the next bombshell podcast
episode coming i am working on them i
really am because guess what
i'm done with the books
brainsaver books
two you guys know
right two books
two brain books
there you go
that is the lemonade right there
oh let's get it in view amazing that's
the lemonade there it is
let's get the other drink out here too
we'll put them both here side by side
hibiscus
tea wow blueberry hibiscus tea
and then
guava blueberry lemonade right there
you know you guys can do
if you guys like anybody who
appreciates wine they appreciate alcohol
in the wine form right
this is an incredible drink you can
actually replace wine with i mean it's
that is exquisite truly the podcast i'm
going to be doing a whole round of new
podcasts
but everybody's going to have to fasten
their seatbelts with those babies
because i'm not messing around
you got to have a stomach for the
medical medium podcast
too much truth
right
once you get off the other health
podcasts
after you've had enough of their their
bs
and you get onto the medical media
podcast your mind just blows up because
you're like what
no seriously
i'm gonna have some some great podcasts
okay
thoughts on substituting juice for
berries in the detox movie
you can absolutely so many times
when i don't have the frozen berries
well first of all i always put the juice
in
the heavy metal detox smoothie when i
make it
i put the berries and the juice in
that's what i do right
so
i see this as a fine wine
right
because first of all it's better than
wine for a lot of reasons
right because it's a wild blueberry
it's an entirely different ratio of
antioxidants the manganese is off the
chart
right
and that's one thing and there's no
alcohol
alcohol destroys
antioxidants
chemical compounds phytochemical
compounds so when people have why it's
like i'm drinking a glass of wine a
night
for my heart or for my health it's like
okay sounds great and all but that
alcohol just destroyed all your phyto
phytochemical compounds in the grapes
you would have been better off eating a
handful of grapes or something like that
right
but when you're dealing with this this
is the kind of wine that i serve when
company comes over people come over
this is it right here
i think
what you got to do is you got to hold
your hand like this right
kind of
move it around a little bit
like you see everybody do
like you see all the rich people do
right all the rich people
you know
these rich people are so weird they're
like their wine is everything they're
just like
honey i think this is a good wine indeed
it's a thousand dollars a bottle
yes
it's kind of dry
hmm
yes
you smell
smell those grapes
take a sip dear i will
[Music]
hmm
very good
that's kind of a dry wine
is this a 1942
10 000 a bottle
i will order twenty thousand bottles at
ten thousand dollars a bottle for my
wine cellar
all my friends come over
i show them how rich i am
we go down to my wine cellar
we walk around and i show them that's a
wine
yes it's a
1937 one
it's a wine from tuscany
that's a wine from naples italy
that's a yes
this glass of wine is about 45 000
right you get people that don't have
money and they have a glass of wine and
they're liking a bar just give me a
glass of red wine
and they're just like yeah
cheers
that's good stuff good [__]
susan what did you do to take care of
your brain
whilst
writing those brain books
a lot of blueberry juice
yeah i did a lot of wild blueberry juice
had it on my desk every single day
and i would just be taking
i would just be like swinging it down
right
oh my god by the way
if you have a carpet
okay
and you're not careful
and you drop a whole bottle like i did
on my carpet when i was writing the book
at like one in the morning or something
and it went down on the carpet expect to
have a blue spot
on that carpet
and don't expect it to go away
either
gianna says my husband
presents me
my wat with your wild blueberry juice
like a wine oh my god incredible
amazing
deer i have a glass of wine here would
you like to have one
right
i have one right here
a little wine tasting
honey wine
do i have the wine
gimmer says that was me i'd buy the
cheapest wine just to get drunk oh i
traded wine for the juice though and
happier than ever all incredible
are you on stitch
so that is
said stitch or is it getter
where is that
it's twitch i'm twitch i'm on twitch
twitch every sing every time that when i
see that when i see someone on twitch it
makes me like twitch
oh my god the juice is kicking in that's
what just happened
that's what just happened right there
yep it's starting to kick in
i might do the robot if it kicks in any
anymore
deborah says hi ew guess what
change last healing is finally happening
whoa
i can now eat cilantro without having to
spit it out immediately
no one food on the planet i hate it most
and it now can help you
incredible now it helps me i still can't
hardly believe it explanation points
can you talk a little more about the new
metal cleanses and brain stable brain
stable nothing i'd rather talk about is
the brain saver books
but everybody gets mad at me when i talk
about it when i bring them out they're
like oh is he going to talk about the
brain saver book again those books are
they're just going to blow your mind
i get a lot of people eat cilantro and
they're like i'll have some cilantro
and they'll just be like
cilantro is awful
and then then eventually you like it
lori says i used wild blueberry juice
and celery force to get me through a
32-hour road trip that's incredible it's
the bomb
i have done that too i've taken the
celery force right i've taken the celery
force and dropped down that wild
blueberry juice and taking some long
road trips too big time
big time
soc stops me from falling asleep if i
start getting a little tired after
driving you know 14 16 hours or
something
he'll just say wake up
he won't say it that way
i say it that way
all right
he'll be like
time to wake up
all right you guys
incredible so we're going to
we're going to instagram
we're going to turn the blueberries
juice is starting to kick in now already
i can tell
we're going ig
did i just say that
we're going to tic toc ig telegram we're
turning that on and that's what we're
doing and i'm excited about you guys
last second though i just want to tell
you 10 off link is in the description
wymans.com
ten percent off on a case
on an order whatever ten percent off and
then if you do the subscription
it's ten percent off for the first order
and five percent thereafter all the time
on the subscription what the heck it's
incredible
incredible we're gonna have some fun
we're gonna go to ig i think i'm gonna
drink all these fast as i can
and i'm gonna be filled up with it and
then i'm gonna be really revved up like
crazy my brain's gonna have
crazy amounts of antioxidants and
everything else and we're gonna be on ig
we're gonna be on telegram i love you
guys