wild blueberry cultivated blueberry wild
blueberry are you eating all the
cultivated blueberries that's what you
do I'm getting some blueberry for my
smoothie I picked up some blueberries
and they're cultivated blueberry meaning
they're not as powerful they're not as
good for you they're not a lot of things
big difference between cultivated
blueberry and wild blueberry thousands
upon thousands of years of
adaptation literally thousands of years
Native Americans used to burn around
fields of wild blueberry because what
would happen is when they would burn it
all down the blueberries would come back
up everything else would be gone that's
a way they used to manage the wild
blueberry crops back th for thousands of
years anyway you guys we're live right
now and I'm making a whole bunch of
different drinks which is going to be
really fun I am also going to open up
aw's bar and grill in a little while too
that I'm going to do but I'm just going
to pour a couple drinks as I need more
drink myself I need a shot for myself
really quick so I want to tell you guys
okay that this talk about the wild
blueberry is really important because
don't you want the best of the best
inside your body and I understand if you
can't find a wild blueberry somewhere if
you have no access to it but if you have
access to it what an incredible support
system for our body especially when the
earth is getting crazy times are getting
crazy people are so stressed out people
are over the top stressed out and stress
we need adaptogenic we need things that
have anth sinins things that have powers
in them and that's what we need when
we're under
stress our tender give me another that's
just a start right there I just needed a
shop right off the running but I'm going
to make a lot of different drinks we're
going to open up the medical medium
cooking show today but we're also
opening up aw's bar and grill and we got
a lot to talk about let's get into it a
little bit just let it hit let it h all
right all right I'm just G to have
myself quick little drink while we're
talking about wild blueberries versus
cultivated blueberries this is going to
be an entertaining show meaning I'm
going to be entertaining myself you guys
might not be entertained but I'm going
to be entertained here we go I love the
sound of pouring drinks with the wild
blue the big difference it's a different
sound here's a goblet a
goblet this is a great way to also you
know when you're you don't have to have
alcohol you don't have to poison your
body with alcoholic beverages you don't
need to you can do something better than
that you can be better than that you can
you can break the vices you can break
the addictions if you get this stuff
right here and you're pouring this for
the holidays or with
friends and we'll get a little close-up
on this too cuz I love when the close-up
camera is on this we got a goblet right
here let's just see if we can get a
little closeup of some wild blueberry
juice going in there nice let's fill
that up I'm going to drink that every
bit of it I'm all of a sudden getting
tipsy from all the wild blueberry juice
I just want to pour a few drinks here I
got this goblet here I got this what
else do I have here's a nice little
daquiri glass a daquiri I would have can
I have a daquiri please is that okay can
I have a
daquiri how about that oh hold on guys
all right got a lot to talk
about um let's crack open another bottle
that's all right here you guys I'm just
waiting for you to come on too if that's
okay we're going to be making a lot of
different woo get that in there we're
going to make a lot of different
drinks I'm serious spiced apple cider
wild blueberry we got all kinds of
things we're going to do this is going
to be a fun fun show so let's get into
it let's get into the nitty-gritty and
what we're talking about versus wild
blueberry difference between wild
blueberry and cultivated blueberry I
didn't want to get any cultivated
blueberries I just didn't want to I
didn't want to go and get those because
every time I see a cultivated
blueberry every time I see it in the
store or I see somebody using it I feel
bad there's just something that comes
over me because it's weak it's weak I
support it I like blueberries of all
kinds but it's not the same blueberry
it's not that adaptogenic power it's not
that high antiox oant rate it's not any
of that the anthocyans are different
it's not the same thing so I'll give you
little differences here a wild
food can survive on its own through
drought through floods through freezing
Tundra cold the cultivated blueberry was
a blueberry that wasn't just growing in
the wild so it's not like hey you know
these blueberries have been around for
thousands of years not true the
cultivated blueberry was a spinoff a
spin-off a cultivated spin-off from its
cousins the wild blueberry big
difference with the wild blueberry
versus the cultivated blueberry so I
want to give you one thing that's really
interesting
okay what happens if a disease hits a
crop if a disease hits a
crop the crop can get annihilated and
we're going to have disease hitting
crops in the future because of all the
gming all the heavy heavy GMO right all
of that just to begin with but crops are
not going to be able to be strong enough
they're not going to be able to sustain
a massive blow and that will be coming
in the future with crops so the
difference with what I'm saying is like
a cultivated crop like say the
cultivated a blueberry if a fungus comes
and eventually becomes strong enough and
hits a sensitivity in the crop and takes
out an entire cultivated blueberry crop
worldwide which it can it can do that
for virtually any crop by the way if it
does this the whole crop goes that's how
it works the difference with wild
blueberries is there are hundreds and
hundreds and hundreds of different
strains of wild blueberry plants in the
same crop in the same like if you look
at a wild Blueberry Field this is
important to know there are hundreds of
different
Geniuses oh I just saying say it that
way there are hundreds of different
varieties hundreds of different strains
they all look the same almost it's all
wild blueberries it's all sitting in the
field the difference
is that there are different plants even
though it's the same plant all within
that field that means that if disease
comes to the wild blueberry crop it may
only take out one or two species of
plant amongst the the entire field of
wild blueberries if a disease comes to a
cultivated crop it'll wipe the entire
cultivated crop out that's how it
works so what I love about wild
blueberries is because it's a
spiritual fruit very spiritual a lot of
reasons for that it's a survival
mechanism it also feeds animals and
keeps animals alive so here's another
thing too the cultivated blueberry and
done and gone it's not there for
wildlife it's not there for the survival
of wildlife too the wild blueberry is
powerful if it stays there and the cold
comes and it freezes on the vines they
sit there Frozen and just available for
the coyotes for the foxes for the Bears
for the deer for for mice for all forms
of wildlife so the the wild blueberry is
actually feeding all all these different
creatures and different animals
something a cultivated blueberry won't
do they pick the crop it's done that's
it wild blueberries are growing wild
they're all through the forests they're
all on the plains they're all in
different areas in this world and even
if you harvest them there's always wild
blueberries somewhere in those fields
left over or somewhere on adjacent or
somewhere on the outskirts of the fields
feeding all kinds of different Wildlife
Birds animals beer deer everything gets
the Bears it gets everything fed and
that's what's incredible about it all
along so when I think about it I think
about the W blueberry I always think
about what it's doing for nature what
it's doing for animal life what it's
doing for that and that means a lot so
what happens is when the winter sets in
it's getting cold the snow starts
falling these wild blueberries are
floating around in all kinds of
different places for all kinds of
different animals to survive on deer
push through the snow
right they push their snoots through the
snow and they actually get these wild
blueberries and they use them for
survival it means everything to keeping
deer alive through a whole winter
keeping any kind of animal alive through
a whole
winter so this is just one aspect of the
wild bluebery now what it's doing for
our bodies as far as like the
anthocyanins and how it's the anti
oxidizer is a whole another level of
power all on its own so we're oxidizing
that's what we're doing we actually
oxidize so when we age we're oxidizing
when we age that's how it works so every
free radicals and toxins that are
floating around our bodies oxidize us
aets that are actually flowing through
our body oxidizes us so everything's out
to get us toxins and poisons and
chemicals and toxic heavy metals that we
get exposed to are all there to oxidize
us right age us or age our organs or
kill our organs or break our organs down
so so that's what that's what it's like
here on planet Earth the chems coming
out of the sky the smoke and the fog all
the burning the excess burning that
happens all around the world right those
massive fires all the fire [ __ ] and
they're dropping off all all on you know
onto those fires all this stuff blowing
around the DDT that's floating around
the planet because DDT is still used all
around the world all the pesticides
herbicides the fungicides it's on the
the clothes that we're wearing brand new
clothing items are dous with flame
retardant DED with fungicides right so
we're exposed every single day fabric
softeners we're exposed to detergents
we're exposed to plugin air fresheners
we're exposed to fragrances perfumes
colognes you name it all of this stuff
is oxidizing us that's what it does and
it increases that oxidation level and
that oxidizing makes it so everybody's
running out and getting plastic surgery
that's how it works why are they getting
plastic surgery some people are getting
plastic surgery because they want their
nose in a different spot some people are
getting plastic surgery I'm not harping
on that I'm just saying they're getting
plastic surgery right because they want
some changes but most people are getting
plastic surgery because their skin is
starting to fail them because it's
oxidizing and that's part of the aging
process somebody can age faster well
they're oxidizing faster someone can age
takes a little longer it's taking a
little longer for them them to oxidize
one way or another it still doesn't even
mean they're not oxidizing internally
with different organs in different parts
parts of their
body but the world and the stress and
the pollutions and the pathogens and the
toxins created by
pathogens and the lawn treatments and
the mosquito spray and the pesticides
herbicides and the fungicides and all
the junk that's sprayed on our food and
everything puffing through the air from
everything from gasoline at the gas
station you inhaling from the fumes to
exhaust fumes you breathe in and Diesel
fumes you breathe in when you're out on
the street whatever ever it is we are
actually getting challenged to oxidize
and age quicker both in every single
aspect of our organs including our skin
and everything else in our body and then
we get degenerative we actually age
faster in so many different
ways now the whole thing about this is
really important to understand is
everybody everybody is trying to eat
better the best they
can everybody's trying to do something
for themselves now you'll see it it
maybe not everybody okay but almost
everybody is trying to actually choose
something differently that they consume
eat something differently that they
consume take something differently that
they can consume put something on their
skin put something on their body right
because everybody cares about what's
going inside their body now it's not
like years and years and years ago where
people really weren't caring about that
and they just did whatever and they
still do that now even people who take
care of themselves are still poison
themselves still drinking alcohol
they're still doing that and other
things too but regardless they're trying
to counter it right you'll see somebody
guzzling down caffeine drinking a bunch
of alcohol in the holidays eating a
bunch of rich chocolate and then in the
end they have this green juice in their
hand or they go to the health food store
and they grab a green juice from the
health food store a bottled one or
something and they're after their yoga
practice or their yoga class or whatever
they're actually drinking
their grain juice but at the same time
they're doing a lot of other things that
are actually harming them but they still
do at the same time care about what
their body is telling them caring about
what they're putting inside their body
and so what I like about the wild
blueberry is it takes it to a whole
another level a whole another level of
taking care of yourself and that's what
I love about it I remember being a child
in laying in the wild blueberry Fields
the fields filled with wild blueberries
and I would just lay in I would I would
turn purple and blue because my body
would be laying on top of the crop just
laying on top of those wild blueberries
and I used to go into the wild blueberry
Fields when I was younger and I used to
sit there on my knees hands and knees
and I would crawl through the field and
I would eat and eat and eat and eat till
I couldn't eat another one and then I
would fall just flip over on my back and
just lay there stuffed with wild blue BL
berries and as I was doing it I was
doing a lot of different things with
that like for instance there would be
like wild roses growing in and out of
the wild blueberries so Spirit of
compassion would say eat the wild rose
petals while you're eating the wild
blueberry so I'd make a mixture and I'd
Crawl Through the field making mixtures
I would take the wild blueberry and then
I would take some rose petals with it
put it there mix it up and I would eat
that like that right and I would do this
kind of thing and the whole time you
know my face is turning blue my body's
turning blue I'm squishing on them I'm
rolling in
them and it's really an
incredible spiritual
moment and I wish everybody could have
that opportunity but I know that that's
not easy it's not an easy opportunity to
have but I remember when I was younger
that I thought if this stuff could be
bottled up and to make it clear I don't
own Wyman's I don't have a percentage of
the Wyman's blueberry company and I want
to make this clear this is critical
because I heard somebody out there might
say like oh he's just trying to sell his
blueberry juice and I need this to be
absolutely clear with everyone I don't
have a share in the Wyman's
company I don't have a percentage of the
Wyman's company I'm not an owner I'm not
a
partner and that needs to be understood
I endorse Wyman's because it's the best
stuff there is and these guys do things
people don't do and this juice is insane
it's just insane and so I want people to
know that right CU it looks pretty
intense I got I you know I actually
purchased a bunch of cases I have all
this stuff right here in the counter I'm
going to make a bunch of drinks for you
guys I think I'm going to make four
different killer beverages out of this I
hope hopefully I do it right I do it
right but I want you to know that you
know I'm not an owner of the Wyman's
wild blueberry juice company or wild
blueberry company but I support these
guys I do I stand behind them and their
product I endorse them and rightfully so
because of what they do they got a heart
of gold and their stuff is amazing if
you can't watch this live on IG cuz I
see that everybody's getting kicked off
of IG and I see that right there go to
medical.com and you probably won't be
able to see me say that cuz cuz you've
already been kicked off or go to YouTube
or
Rumble IG is just keeping it like
kicking everybody off and just keeping
it down to like whatever they're doing
today all right so let's go into some
wild blueberries a little deeper and
stuff talk about something that's really
incredible all
right so you can burn down a wild
Blueberry
field and anything in that wild
Field anything won't come
back so as spring comes what will come
back instead are the wild
blueberries that's the kind of power
they have the adaptogenic power we're
talking about a survival mechanism that
if the Earth was
blazed if the Earth was blazed the wild
blueberry would come up and what really
crazy really crazy that if some
massive catastroph
catastrophic event happened where some
solar pulse solar
flare a huge ball of fire just balls out
of the Sun and barrels down towards
us whatever happens or if the planet
gets scorched for some
reason the wild blueberry will come back
up everything else will be
gone all the oak trees will be gone all
the acorns that grow oak trees would be
gone it's important to know all the
birch trees all the cherry trees all the
cedar all the
pine everything would be
gone just
annihilated and gone and what would
happen would be the wild blueberry would
just start coming up out of the earth
and would just start to grow and come up
out of the earth an oak tree won't
that's gone for good if the planet gets
scorched for some
reason if there's a nuclear war and the
planet just gets burned to the
ground the wild blueberry will be the
first to Peak its head it'll be the
first to come up you have to realize
what that is
and so what I like to think about is
that power it has and then I like to
think about that power in me like I want
that in me that's what I want I want
something that if it gets nuked it comes
up out of the ground I want something
that if it literally gets burned because
of some crazy event the moon crumbles
and starts to fall apart some Earth gets
thrown off its
axis something
happens or some alien race decides to
blow up the moon which by all means they
have power to do that and anything or
anything and the Earth was destroyed
over it the wild blueberry would still
come up out of the
ground that's what I'm talking about
it's that kind of power so I think about
that as I'm drinking and consuming the
wild blue bries so when I was a kid I
always thought about would it be amazing
if for some way somehow that can be
bottled those wild blueberries that are
once a year on that field in those
fields can get squeezed down and pressed
you know like pressed like oldtime apple
press style like
pressed and get pressed down into a
juice and gets put in here here like
that would be the biggest dream come
true for the health of people like to me
that would be the alltime greatest
dream to have that resource and have
that so I want to make a bunch of stuff
I to make a bunch of drinks I can talk
about the wild blueberry forever and I'm
going to continue as we're making drinks
and doing things but I can talk about
the wild blueberry forever now you know
I talk about it in my books the whole
bit now remember I just want to say
there's a sale if some you guys I saw
somebody mention that on there so check
it out W blueberry a whole case $20 off
for a whole case if you buy a case of
the W blueberry juice it's $20 off it's
a case of 12 keep that in
mind case of 12 I have to look here I 1
2 3 four bottles 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 over
there corner it's a case of 12 for $20
off meaning $20 off the price of the
case so just think about that if you're
checking it out and there's a Code use
code wild2 so code wild 20 w l d wild
and 2020 link is description link is in
the profile check it out if you guys
just came on here this is the medical
medium cooking show medical medium or
Anthony William aw's Bar and Grill is
going to open later and I'm making a
bunch of different drinks so I'm
actually excited about this and I'll
talk about like killer points about the
wild blueberry as we're doing this let's
start cranberry oatmeal cookies but I'm
going to replace the cranberry oatmeal
cookies with some wild blueberries dried
wild blueberries I'm going to do that I
can use a few Frozen wild blueberries
too in those cookies but I'm going to
try the dried one so I'm excited that's
on the menu here I just want to drink
all of this right now but I can't I
can't I got to keep it together and not
drink everything so let's get started on
this the oatmeal cookies all right let's
get the ingredients ready got my little
measuring cup right here all right one
and2 cups gluten-free rolled oats I'm
going to go with three cups so let me go
find those right
here I want to get some cookies in the
oven are you guys okay that that I'm
like I'm excited to do that I want to
get some cookies in the oven so we got
this here perfect yeah but I'm going to
start moving these drinks around that's
what I'm going to do okay now let's just
hope that I don't have an accident in
here because I got this funny feeling
I'm going to knock over something and
something's going to go knocked over
somewhere and it's probably going to be
a big old glass of wild blueberry juice
and that's what's going to happen so
there there we go okay I got two cups
I'm going to put three cups in here cuz
I'm making a big
batch why am I making a big batch and
not a small bat just because I'm going
to tank the crap out of these cookies
because I am hungry so I'm going to do
one cup of gluten-free oat flour but I'm
going to do two cups of gluten-free oat
flour so here we go I got a cup right
here
two cups of this there's
one
boom all right there's
two here we
go what else is going in here now this
is all the dry I want all the dry
ingredients in here first cuz I want to
mix up all the dry ingredients you guys
see this right here got it right I got
the split screen going okay next is 2
tablespoons of coconut sugar which I'm
going to do four tablespoons of coconut
sugar all
right I got my tablespoon right here I'm
pretty excited about this you guys we're
going to have some fun today hang around
if you want so we're going to put two
we're going to put four of coconut sugar
in here this coconut sugar that's good
it's good it's good it's good it's good
all right we got that in there I'm going
to mix all this up soon let's see what
else I want some baking powder so I'm
going to go with 1/4 teaspoon which is a
I mean a half teaspoon which is one
teaspoon of baking powder
boom get a little bit of that in
there all right and then I want a half2
teaspoon of bacing
soda got that right
[Music]
here okay getting excited about this all
right so then I want a little bit of
cinnamon a little bit of nutmeg cinnamon
and Nutmeg I'm going to put some
cinnamon in here nice that's going to be
great wonderful
trying to train myself to say wonderful
lately little nutmeg wonderful it's
wonderful it's wonderful you know how
when you look for words how many times
can you say amazing amazing right okay
there we go I'm looking for like
wonderful okay now I'm going to mix this
before
I put the wet ingredients in so take a
look you
guys first the first kitchen kitchen
accident get this in
here all right let's mix this
up that's good that's
good all
right mixing this up you guys these are
the dry ingredients and the reason why
you want to mix that up I'm just going
to be straight out about this cuz if you
put the wet in with this and it's not
mixed it's going to be a heck of a hard
time getting this stuff mixed up been
down that road before I've made these
before do you guys have the ingredients
on hand you guys want to make them with
me this would be cool let's hit the wet
stuff now let's get some maple syrup
going on in here so this thing calls for
um here we
go this recipe calls for 1/4 cup of
maple syrup I'm going to do a/2 cup of
maple
syrup let's do a/2 cup maple syrup there
we go where are we here
making a mess already
unbelievable do you guys ever get
irritate
it like you know what I mean when you're
like you make a
mess just
like I tell myself I'm not going to do
that this time I'm going to do some
applesauce now third of a cup of
applesauce but I'm going to do a full
cup of applesauce I'm going to put a
little bit more in
here all
right
H yeah let's do this I got some
applesauce can you see that you guys I'm
going to do a third I'm going get this
2/3 cuz it's double batch I'll do 2/3
and then I'm going to put a little bit
more yeah that's nice that's nice
good
okay all right and then we're going to
put some orange zest in there
zest is that what it is orange
justest okay now I'm going to mix the
wet ingredient in but I don't have to
worry now cuz you can mix it up but you
don't have to freak out because the dry
ingredients were mixed up right I can't
wait to talk about the wild blueberry a
little bit more about the power it has
why it's so important to healing and
guess what that's right the wild
blueberry is in the hmds for a
reason do you know that it's a powerful
powerful binder
for the people that go he never talks
about binders he never talks about yeah
because the wild
blueberry is the most powerful of the
binders right all right so I'm mixing
this up now I want to get a little bit
of the
orange zest in there so what I do is I
take an orange I hope you guys are okay
with this can I throw it around a little
bit and what I do is I just peel it back
with a knife if you're okay right now
get a zest
greater what is it a zest tool this is
the way I do it now if you have somebody
that doesn't really like you orange zest
you don't have to do this if you don't
want to I like it so I'm going to get
some nice big pieces
here now try to keep the don't get down
to the pith too much take a look you
guys don't get down to the pith you see
this like try not see there's a little
pith almost in that right there don't do
that too much because the pith is a
bitter you don't want a bitter cookie
you just want to get the
outside so see that right there that's
actually a good one right there check it
out okay that was good all right that's
good that's good because you don't want
to go too deep so I want to show you
this right
here every time someone's like I do a
smoothie I do a smoothie I put um
blueberries in my smoothie I'm like
blueberries what kind of blueberries do
you put in there I just blueberries you
know I just bought them and it's
cultivated blueberries and it's like
okay well that's not going to help you
know what happens a lot of people don't
realize it and they do their
hmds with the cultivated
blueberry big big big big big problem if
that's the case if that's all you have
then what I recommend I'm going to cut
that up right now what I recommend is
when you do your
hmds you use a Blackberry you use a
cultivated black Blackberry a cultivated
Blackberry is getting much closer to
what say a wild blueberry could do it's
not the same thing it doesn't do the
same thing but the but the Blackberry if
but is better than the cultivated
blueberry I'm just going to tell you
right now this is important to know so
many people do their hmds and it's got
the cultivated blueberry and I feel bad
because it's not it it means that you're
not getting that maximum maximum
you know you're just not I want to just
I want to cut this down a little bit
more this is an important tip by the way
for hmds I want everybody to know by the
way the juice is coming to Europe soon
so I know that I saw um a comment right
there saying like we can't get it we
can't get it out here you're going to be
able to get it out there pretty soon
you're going to be able to get the
Wyman's wild blueberry juice out there
in
Europe overseas out
there
I'm not kidding you
are if you guys don't mind just going to
do a little bit more of this little zest
chop there you go it's looking pretty
good doesn't have to be
like so crazy
but all right nice that goes
in right
there you guys see that take a look how
does that look great let's mix some of
that in there these are going to taste
so good now I also got some cranberries
I can put in but I'm I'm going to go
with the blueberry instead so let me
find my
cranberries just so you can see them
take a look right there you guys see it
on the split screen all right these are
the
Cranberries okay and you can go with
that but today I'm not going to go with
the
Cranberries shame on me for not going
with the Cranberries shame on
me
shame right okay this is what I'm doing
here
whoa whoa whoa whoa check it out you
guys I'm putting the Wyman's wild
blueberries in here that's what I'm
doing I shall open up the package do I
know how to do that yes I do let me get
some of these out these babies this is
what I'm talking about right here I
don't know if you guys could see that on
there these are the wild blueberries
dried
ones oh that's good I'll see you guys
later I'll see you guys later I'm going
to go over here and just
relax I eat those all day
long all right let's go let's get going
come on you guys let's go what are we
doing just's a lot to do let's put a few
more in here
nice take a look you guys you know what
I love about
these check them out go to Wyman's right
and check them out what a live about
these take them anywhere you anywhere
you want you can take them with I got
them in my car I got them in my glove
box I got them in my pockets like this
is like incredible to have on hand all
right let's mix this up
I also
take a juice
too in the car so I usually have that as
well all
right I might add a few more of these
because I can't help it there we
go this is just too great oatmeal
cookies we're on the way just that at
aw's Bar and Grill which we're going to
open up later I don't think they like
oatmeal cookies but we shall
see good point all right I got some
guests arriving pretty soon are you guys
okay with
that but I do have guests on their way
this is done this is
ready actually ready for cookie doing
cookie making cookie prod ucing let's
go hand I got the oven on at
350 ever since I had I can't tell you
how many people I've heard this happen
to right have you heard that happen
where you so many people there's a lot
of people testimonies comments people
talking about it where and even have
family members where they have a little
bit of the wild blueberry
juice right and they feel better shortly
after I've seen people where their
migraine goes away people have told
their stories where their migraine goes
away there's people out there that said
I got rid of my
UTI because I was doing a bottle of of
of the wild blueberry juice a day during
UTI and I got instead of cranberry
they're doing the wild blueberry juice
and they got rid of their UTI like
there's a whole bunch of stories out
there and people what's happened when
they're doing their wild blueberry juice
headaches is a big one right there
people that that actually are prone to
headaches and they're about to get a
headache and they're coming down with
headache and they do the wild blueberry
juice and it just shifts it it's
crazy all
right so
good let's do this now let's um let's
get together here and make
a I'm just getting a little water right
here so I can dip my hand in here if you
guys don't mind here we go and I am
going to do some now you can do your
cookies anywhere you want right but I'm
going
to make them kind of small preheat your
oven to
350 now I'm putting some moisture on my
hands so they don't stick to my hands
I'm making them kind of small and I'm
flattening them out a little bit take a
look I don't want them super
thick okay I'm going to pop these on
here can you see
that can you guys see that you can make
these babies big I made a huge oatmeal
cookie it was crazy how big it
was I was just like is this okay when I
was doing it I was like is this okay can
I make an oatmeal cookie that big that
one's actually kind of big though uh-oh
these oatmeal cookies are getting bigger
and
bigger you know what's really really
weird is the health movement still isn't
caught up on the wild blueberry and what
it does the power it has how good it is
for you the cultivated blueberry is not
in the hdms for a reason it's not in the
HD hmds for a
reason
woo Big Show ahead of us I better gear
it up and get it
ready it's not in there for reason
doesn't do what the wild blueberry does
results Details Matter but they really
do it's not a joke details really really
matter okay you guys see that right okay
let's get this next one in how's
that all right let's do a few more
cookies now I don't want to be like a
hog but I'm probably going to eat all of
these on you guys pretty fast when they
come out of the oven
okay
yep make a few more right
here a lot of people would do a
blueberry smoothie they'll have a
protein smoothie and they'll put
blueberries in there and they'll think
they're doing themselves the greatest of
great but they don't realize they're
doing the cultivated blueberry inside
their their protein smoothie and so
forth
this is a Great Cookie for the holidays
I just want to forew war everybody like
a little holiday shout out shout
out this is actually the thing is with
these cookies though right you don't
feel this guilty guilty thing going out
you know going on like that you just
don't feel this guilt come over
you you know when you eat a whole box of
cookies how do you feel how how does
everybody feel when they eat a whole box
of
cookies and you know these you know the
cookies aren't good for you have you
ever done that in your life have you
ever had a whole box of donuts a whole
box of cookies like is that just my
imagination and I just always thought
people did
that but they don't did you ever do that
in your life do you remember a time when
you totally tanked a whole crap load of
cookies in the whole
bit the difference is with this you
don't have to panic
like there's no panicking there's no
like wait a minute is this like bad that
I had this many
cookies all right some of these are
coming out really good some of these are
coming
out yeah we got a lot to do you guys I
want to get these in the oven and then
we're going to make some drinks we're
not going to do it with
alcohol what's what's incredible about
this I'm telling all my friends family
that you should have this wild blueberry
juice there and ready so you don't have
to do the alcoholic beverage
thing have it at least for different
members of the family that don't drink
if you're a drinker have this here so
that different members of the family
don't have to
drink give them an option you might have
somebody that's a recovering
alcoholic you might have somebody like
that in the struggling in the family and
you can give them an OP option and be
like whoa check this
out all right let's get a little bit
more in here one more and we'll get
another one you guys see this it's
coming together it's no
joke if the planet gets
scorched if the nukes are lit out of the
silos
someday something crazy
happens the wild blueberry will be the
first to come up first to come
up it will be the
first form of
life that comes
up that's what people don't
realize and that's an
incredible incredible
amazing I don't know how good those wild
blueberries would be at that point a
planet after some
catastrophe all right I'm going to put
pop these in the oven here we are I want
to give you a closeup on these really
quick you guys these are my cookies this
isn't cookie dough by the way you know
what I'm talking about this is a new
recipe at Medical medium.com Medical
medium.com
you can watch this show live right now
at Medical medium.com it's streaming
live on the website as we speak keep
that in mind guess what's not in these
cookies no overt fats no overt fats are
in these cookies isn't all this oil this
isn't all this different oil there isn't
you know Crisco there isn't all kinds of
junk and garbage in here this is clean
this is pure and these are cookies we're
making don't those look like chocolate
chips but you don't need chocolate chips
in here you just need those dried wild
blueberries in here that's what I'm
talking about let's get it in the
oven all right guys I'm over here don't
worry I have it left don't worry boom
they're in there
350 on it Trudy says what is
hdms
hmds check out medical medium check out
the books check out medical medium.com
check out the blog
post hmds heavy metal detox smoothie
that's what it is the heavy metal detox
heavy metal detox smoothie right there
in the brain saver books we got a lot of
drinks to make just showing you real
quick all
right there's a wild Blu-ray on the
cover you guys want to know what a wild
Blu-ray looks like up close what a wild
blueberry looks up close you get it on
the split screen right there you'll see
it that's what one looks like that's a
like a
defining what you'll see is the little
cap on top the little crown on the
blueberry is different than the
cultivated Crown it's a different
species altogether because it's so far
from the cultivated the cultivated was
is so far from the wild they are not the
same thing and I still see it out there
people are just doing regular
blueberries I'm like are you kidding by
now 2020 whatever we're at right now you
mean to tell me we're still just doing
cultivated blueberries we're not trying
to do the wild blueberries like when I
think about that it's insane to me it's
insane let's go on to the next
rink sparkling wild blueberry juice and
lime let's get into it okay cup of wild
blueberry rry juice let's
go yep on this one and some sparkling
water too let's get that out as well all
right I'm going to use this measuring
cup where am
I okay one cup of wild blueberry juice
let's go hold
on I can't wait to open the bar in a
little bit
seriously okay one cup of wild blueberry
juice okay is it audio slow no what is
going on yeah that's just yeah that's
just uh that's IG that's all that's all
I'm surprised any of you guys can even
watch this right now um let's go with
one
cup Instagram messaging with
audio or it's messing with the messaging
it's messing with everything okay let's
go one cup right there
let's keep it up 1/4 cup of sparkling
water whoa glad that didn't blow up
nice here we
go 1/4
cup sparkling
water
[Music]
okay
H very
[Music]
interesting very very interesting
here when you're live you never know
what's going to
happen all right I don't know if you
guys saw that did you see that do you
know what happened do you guys know what
happened just now or did I just get away
with that without you guys
seeing did you guys catch that you might
want you might want to watch this entire
video from the beginning and get to this
point and be like what the hell was he
talking about and what did he just do
what did he just say the craziest thing
just happened I'm not kidding was
actually like weird never had that
happen before during a
live like I don't know
all right let's get a lime
going half a tablespoon of lime
juice whoa there lots of lime juice
coming out of this one look at
that there oatmeal cookies cooking up
nice I'm hungry today too all right got
the lime in there that was Pat that lime
that was not a joke
wooo all
right this is going into a champagne
glass right
here this the sparkling trying to find a
good spot for it this is sparkling wild
blueberry juice and
lime
okay
what is going
on is someone messing with
me okay okay okay okay okay I'm on it
I'm on it here all
right someone playing a joke on me man
the
heck something else weird just happened
like really really weird
weird it's like
what you guys aren't seeing it some
weird shits going
down in all kinds of ways all right we
got that filled up I just want to do a
little lime work real quick so I'm going
to cut this lime as you can see I'm
going to cut a nice little piece just
like
this
right
you guys okay with
this I'm in a fancy restaurant I'm out
on the balcony at a fancy restaurant
$2,000 per
seat and that's not the meal you have to
pay for that later it's another
$2,000 honey I have a drink for
you at our wiy we do it this
way either way you guys check it out
this is incredible instead of
alcohol we got
this medical medium is the only only
person I'm doing third person right now
medical medium is the only person on
social is not allowed to say the word
alcohol not allowed to say the
word Wana not allowed to say
not allowed to say the word Wana kid you
not not allowed to say the word
it not allowed to say words still just
not allowed to say any words guys have
no idea all
right can I have a sip of this in a
little while let's see that we'll do a
sip of a little wild blueberry Apple
ciders next coming right
up coming right you guys I'm under
pressure I feel some stress cuz I have
to open up aw's bar and grill soon
because I got a a a [ __ ] load of like
angry people that want to get into here
and have drinks and so forth wild
blueberry Apple ciders next okay one cup
wild blueberry
juice one cup of wild blueberry juice
coming right
up it's going in the pot can you guys
see
this
yeah one cup wild blueberry
juice yep there we go let's get this in
here you guys see that you know you can
make a mess with this stuff don't wear
white there's a reason why I'm wearing a
blue shirt today because I know this is
going all over the place and going to go
all over me so that's
why all right what's next in this you
guys this is going to be killer this is
the wild blueberry apple cider one cup
of fresh apple
juice yeah that's fresh apple juice
right there that's what I'm talking
about apple juice fresh apple juice is
so good for you are you kidding are you
freaking kidding fresh apple juice is
amazing for you too in different ways
different ways all
right that's right that's going in here
as well if you guys don't
mind look at that I'm just going to dry
this cuz that's going to go on the
burner and that's going to be a smoking
on that burner uh-huh turn that burner
on all right what else is going in here
one to three tablespoons of raw honey I
choose maple syrup
today why am I
yelling do you guys know why I'm yelling
okay if you guys just got on here $20
off on a case of the wild blueberry
juice right now
$20 off on a case of 12 of the wild
blueberry juice right now I'm just
saying I'm just
saying boom maple syrup done in one
cinnamon stick
take a look at these cinnamon sticks
right here I'm going to put this big one
here I like this one that's a big one
right there look that's a beauty that's
going in
there what I love about the wild
blueberry juices it's actually
incredible for emotional support
emotional support for an evening out
emotional support for an evening with
family because it's providing brain help
for your neurons think about that for a
minute right there so the wild blueberry
juice is going into the brain it's
mainlining into the brain and it's
providing all this kind of anthocyan INF
filled glucose phytochemical compounds
for your neurons specifically when you
hear people say why do you eat so
healthy why are you actually eating so
healthy like forget it it's Thanksgiving
just eat whatever just eat whatever
everybody's eating eat all the butter
and eat everything else why are you
sticking to your medical medium protocol
why are you eating medical medium stuff
why are you eating a salad with spinach
why are you having spinach soup right
now everybody's having turkey all that
pressure all that stress the wild
blueberry juice kind of throws that all
aside because people in the family they
see that wild blueberry juice like this
they'll see it like this and they'll be
like what is that why is that are you
drinking are you actually loosening up
and you're drinking families actually
feel like you're loosening up and you're
actually like partying with them they
won't be so like antagonistic to your
lifestyle of healing and your lifestyle
of eating the way you're eating and your
celery juice drinking that they probably
can't stand anymore or whatever it is
that's happening with you know different
people in your family and different
people around your
nucleus in your world and then what
happens is you bring this out you break
this out and something changes
emotionally something actually just
Alters their way of how they feel in the
Moment by looking at this stuff I know
I've done it I've done it I've seen it
I've had friends do it they crack open a
bottle of this they drink it they crack
it open and they're like yeah I'm not
not going to have alcohol I'm just doing
this I'm fine with this right now and
something changes and shifts it's
unbelievable the pressure the family
pressure upon them all that peer
pressure and everything else during the
holidays about eating and what you're
eating what you're doing you have Eating
Disorders you have done what are you
doing why don't you eat whatever you
were eating why don't you eat what you
want aren you enough of this healing
stuff just just do what we're doing
you've heard that stuff right before a
lot of people have heard that before and
you break this out and boom something
changes it's crazy how it
works all
right all right over there on YouTube
Max I didn't realize before how people
need to see you drinking with them they
need to see you poisoning yourself with
them and when you take out the wild
blueberry juice and you say I'll drink
with you I'll freaking drink with you
yeah I'll do it I'm here I'll drink
that's right and you bring out this and
they're just like yeah no problem
they'll have some alcohol right they'll
have some type of alcoholic beverage is
what they'll do you know what I mean
they'll do some kind of alcoholic
beverage is what they'll do right yeah
uhhuh what am I even looking
for they'll have some kind of crazy
alcoholic beverage and that's what
they'll be
doing and you'll have this they'll have
wine and you'll have this that's how
crazy it
is right I'm just actually
making making a pink Champagne they'll
have pink Champagne just like I have
right there and then you're going to
just throw this at them and you're going
to be like yeah I'll drink with you damn
right okay I could do it uh-huh you
don't like it you don't like it huh huh
you do like it that's why you do like it
you like me drinking with you that's
right they're going to have that pink
champagne and they're going to be like
everybody have a toast oh who's the
loser that's not drinking right now and
you be like screw you man I ain't no
loser I'm drinking the stuff you're
supposed to be drinking everybody will
be happy that's the way to do
it that's the way to do
it all right what else is going in here
we need a spider I need a
spider one spider which I actually just
had a little while ago I actually had a
spider look one
spider and we're going to put these
dehydrated spiders right in there we got
that whoa did I just th that all right
four to five cloves four to five cloves
one two three four got the cloves in
there okay all right half piece of
Ginger thinly
sliced Ginger is coming right up almost
lost that one
yep I'm going to have another shot of
wild blueberry juice because that's how
I get the energy to do this you know
this is the that's where I get the
energy to do this that's
right how many hours of sleep did you
get last night I only slept 4 hours last
night and I haven't even sat down to
think I've been going all day on 4 hours
of sleep I didn't get 4 hours because I
couldn't sleep I got 4 hours because I
was working on stuff and it just got
crazy and next thing you know it push
came the shove and I was only getting 4
hours of sleep and I knew it whoa these
cookies getting
close
almost almost all these recipes can be
found at medicalmedium.com there also in
the email we sent out this week make
sure you are on the newsletter so you
can receive them just letting you
know all right so I'm thinly slicing
some ginger about a/ inch of it so you
don't need a lot you don't want this a
ginger all about just Ginger and that's
it okay there we
go okay and then that's it this is
actually going on the stove I have the
stove right
here I got it on I'm going to put a top
on it get it to a quick simmer really
fast now we're making the wild blue well
actually that is the wild blueberry
apple cider get with it that's the wild
blueberry apple cider let's go next one
wild blueberry orange
sangria this should actually be
fun
okay three cups pure wild blueberry
juice let's knock through these three
cups of pure wild blueberry
juice yeah yeah wave World said can you
please show the bottle
again I can at least do
that is there any way to show this
bottle can you see it up
close it's incredible stuff I can't
can't say enough about the wild
blueberry and you know people are
starting just starting to talk about it
after all the years and all the books
getting out there they're just starting
and all the work I did they're just
starting to learn about it and it's true
it's true people are just starting to
like they're just starting to say
blueberry
wild
blueberry it's almost like it's like it
kills them to have to say
I've totally been screwing up my whole
career in health pushing the blueberry
on everybody the cultivated one it's
like because it hurts it's like I don't
want to be told I was wrong or stupid in
the health realm I'm a guru and should
know better so I better not utter wild
blueberry it's like I screwed up all
these years and didn't tell people it's
the wild one that counts cuz I didn't
know it's like all the gurus don't want
to say it they don't want to say it it's
painful and it hurts it's like I [ __ ]
up bad because I thought the cultivated
blueberry was where it was at you know
it's just like it's crazy how it
works that's cooking right there I want
to do three
cups
so use the rest of this
bottle
let's find another bottle that's that's
tapped open here remember doing three
cups
okay that's
two let's go with a third
cup
yep so good can you imagine the holidays
and you're doing
this talking about
being on the Forefront
man all right we're supposed to be
having some fun today let's step it up
and Notch 2 and 1/2 cups freshly
squeezed orange
juice do a little orange juice shake
right is freshly squeezed orange juice 2
and 1/2 cups let's go let's go let's go
what we got got two cups right there
we're going to do now a half2
cup I had exactly that that's right look
at that two and 1 half
cups
incredible
yep all right what else are we doing
right here we got to finish this up up
on this one we need some maple syrup two
to three tablespoons of maple
syrup why am I having a hard time
opening that there we go two or three
tablespoons of Maple Syrup can you guys
see this right here let's get a little
bit of it
one
two
three don't you hate when people do that
you're a kid it's like it's always about
some kind of like challenge when you're
a kid it's like on a count of three jump
in the pool one 2 3 go it's always 1 2 3
go okay we need to c one cup of
sparkling
water all right uh regular water well
it's optional okay sparkling water is
optional I'm going to put a little bit
in here some sparkling water you don't
have to have it in here but I'm going to
put a little bit
in
nice all right hold on you guys this is
actually like cooking cooking this is
simmering let's bring this down let's
bring this down all right let's just
finish this one up and we'll pull that
one off all right okay two
apples one
apple
two
apple I don't have pairs of rep peaches
today forgive me please forgive me
seriously if you guys can forgive me
only got apples
here all right Denise says wow sparkling
water I'm going to serve this for
Thanksgiving oh you won't be
disappointed I promise you won't be
disappointed apples look how I cut these
apples ready check this out ready for
this cut them thin
okay just like this you guys see this
nice can you guys there you
go careful when you're cutting your
apples like this it's a great way to cut
them for this look at this going to do
two
apples hold your horses sucker's
hot
yep uhhuh on here it's going to pop this
here for a second cool down cookies
[ __ ] yeah these are
done almost really messed that one
up them cookies man five more minutes
those cookies would be in like toasty
land and that would not be good where do
I put these cookies right you guys hang
on
hang
[Music]
on hang on you
guys that's what I'm talking about take
a look dying for one of these you guys
see this is that sick give you a little
closeup here
IG you check that out there's no lard in
here there's no fat there's no oil in
here there's no grease to give you
pancreatitis there's no pork in here
there's no oil there's no vegetable oil
there's nothing like that in here you
don't even have like nut Butters in here
or anything like that this is right here
no overt no over overt fat it's free
from overt fats and what's incredible is
it's easy on the digestion this right
here is so good if you're somebody
that's trying to lose weight during the
holidays or trying to lose weight before
the holidays or you've been you've been
tanking food and you're gaining weight
during the holidays this is the kind of
food you make then if that's if you're
going to be eating all kinds of other
crazy stuff out there this is what you
do check it out right there I'm going to
let this cool down over here I got to
finish up these
drinks
all
right what the heck was I
doing let's get these
apples what Incarnation was I doing what
in creation am I
doing I'm cutting these apples I'm
making the
sria okay let's get another app
going see this right here I'm taking the
pits out right the pits kind of usually
fall out of
here okay nice
nice nice get the pits Little P I mean
the
seeds I stand correct
it it's the one thing no one realizes I
go through it's why the books don't
contradict it's why eight gigantic
medical Bibles can be put out and
they're not
contradictive that's why lives and
lectures and and podcasts aren't
contradictive like dicted like everybody
else in the health scene it's because I
get stand corrected by a voice I hear
and it's the biggest pain in the butt
ever if I call this a pit in here I get
corrected by the voice that says it's a
seed and that's why the books no one can
touch the books
there's no authors out there in the
health realm that can actually do
medical books like this with information
that's detailed and not have some kind
of problem they don't do it they just
write eat better books and they
contradict themselves in every sentence
or every book if your screen is Frozen
on Instagram please take screen
recording of it if you got no sound same
thing send it to Via
DM and then go to YouTube or Rumble send
it to my DM if you can so we can file
some
complaints all right let's get some more
of these I'm putting more apple slices
here so let's get
going all right there we go two nice
apples are going in here and then we're
going to get some strawberries out
here great is that let's pop these in
you guys see this this right here see it
going
in
look apples are going in here what I'm
doing is I'm each individual slice I
want the juice to go in between the
slices and I'm going to mix them up a
little bit
too I got an oatmeal cookie with wild
blueberries calling my name I can't wait
I cannot wait all right we got the
apples in here let's go with
strawberries now
you guys don't
mind strawberries so here's what I'm
doing with the strawberries I'm going to
move this over I'm going to cut these
tops off someone yelled at me that one
time what if you remember a long time
ago you can eat the strawberry leaves
you think you're so smart with that one
do you you can eat the strawberry leaves
aw you don't know anything about plant
Foods you're not really a plant food
person you're not really a plant-based
person because you didn't know the
advanced raw plant-based knowledge of
you can just eat the strawberry leaf
with the strawberry it's so Advanced you
guys think you're so
smart think you're so smart but what you
don't know is something Spirit taught me
once
again okay is you can eat the strawberry
Leaf that's on top of the strawberry
when it's out of your freaking
Garden but you can't eat the strawberry
Leaf when it's in the package that was
in the store because
bacteria gets trapped in between the
strawberry Leaf even if you wash it and
the
strawberry and so you go there you're
eating your strawberries you know from
the store and all the bacteria is packed
in between the leaf and the top of the
strawberry everything from anything from
traveling along with other like meats
and chicken and God knows what and the
big trucks and the big Carri
in the 18 wheelers drippage everywhere
and that salmonella can go right between
the leaf of the strawberry and the
strawberry so what I do is these aren't
grown out of my garden I'm not going to
eat the little strawberry top Leaf I'm
going to cut the darn thing off even
though I've washed
these I love when people love to try to
teach me stuff keep on
teaching the smell in this house is so
freaking amazing it's wonderful it's my
new word it's amazing the recipes are
off the chart this is like crazy how
good this is all right let's get a few
more strawberries if you don't
mind yep I mean I'm smelling everything
under the sun right now smells so good
it's a festival
smell it's got such a great smell to
it wish you guys were in here right now
sure you are here okay festive holiday
smell an aroma
so great let's get some more
strawberries in here look at this big
one right here okay we still have some
orange uh slices to go and we're putting
this this is this is so good all
right all right you guys can watch this
a little bit slicing these
up here we go all
right
nice okay a little bit
more what are you guys doing for the
holidays I mean if a lot a lot of people
I got a friend that's just on mattress
Island and they're just chilling out and
they're just you know doing their own
thing because they they're not in a
place right now with everything with
their severe chronic
fatigue they just started their healing
process the medical medium
information just started it recently
starting to heal but they don't want to
push themselves too hard all right we
got the strawberries in there now let's
go with
orange is this the orange I want is
it is that the orange I
want okay orange slices coming right
up chill out you guys chill
out chill out it's going to be okay
don't worry aw bar grill is opening
anytime soon please contain
yourself if you
can yep we're going to open the door
soon you guys got a lot of guests that
are
waiting
okay text 369 champ
yo
bro Anthony people always try to say to
me that one guy you Mah doesn't have all
the answers and you know what I tell
them he doesn't but he has access to all
the answers the
Fist and a
heart then if I don't have the answers
then why am I the only one on the planet
that
realize the blood draw crisis they're
drawing all this blood out of people who
are chronically ill and literally
killing them they're not monitoring it
20 vials 10 vials 13 vials 7 vials
pregnant women getting seven vials five
vials 10 vials taken out giving their
babies hemorrhagic shock in the
womb and they lose their baby but nobody
knows why because they had five vials
seven vials 10 vials taken from them
while they were pregnant over and over
again that's mm
info nobody knew Epstein bar caused
multiple sclerosis took that info from
me later after I published it 8 years
ago 9 years ago actually almost 10 it
was already pre-published in the phase
way before it was even released medical
mem information is at the Forefront of
the chronic illness world and science
takes the info day after day after day
and they don't cite it back but we're
keeping track we're keeping track and
we're going to release that down the
road and we're talking to some people
and we're going to release that down the
road about all that has happened
throughout the years
Rowan this isn't live this is live dude
I'm live right now did you hear me if it
wasn't live would I be able to say this
isn't live or is that just kind of some
psych out Trick what is that how am I
saying that if it's not live you said is
this live I was saying it's live it's
live let's get the orange in
here all
right need a wooden
stick let's go
I'm just talking about a couple of
things Tex I'm just mentioning a couple
of things just the blood draw has been
on my mind lately this is the wild
blueberry orange
sangria this is a fun recipe for you and
your family during the
holidays
hi I'm
Martha and I want to show you the
sangria that we have in our household
welcome to my $10 million house I'm
going to show you my multi-million
dollar kitchen and I'm going to make
sure that
you enjoy the festive holiday with us
here at Martha's
Holiday
Fest I'm not making fun of
Martha making fun of anybody
just having
fun that's
all all right that's insane right there
I just want to show you guys this right
here you see that on IG check it out see
that right that's
insane if I didn't have all the answers
they used to call me the Epstein bar guy
oh he's just the EP bar guy he's insane
now every single person in Health it's
like you got epine bar you got epine bar
epine Bar's causing fibro you got epine
bar it's it's
insane Jolene are you the reason Snoop
Dogg gave up his weed I'm not allowed to
say we
D was
forewarned no one in the health realm
and health World get sold you're not
allow to say that
buddy it's really really actually
insane all
right Tik Tok turned off my live stream
option by the way we are fighting to get
it back you guys remember when medical
medium had almost a million followers on
Tik
Tok multi-million views per video
putting out information Forefront
information I have to admit I'm guilty
of playing the drums on a couple of
different episodes or different videos
on Tik Tok I was playing the drums
and remember and they completely deleted
my account and they held me back from
getting it so then after a year later we
were able to open up a new account and
they just turned off my
live my live stream option they said
they banned
it that means you're doing powerful
stuff in the world and that means you're
moving mountains and that means you're
changing the world and that means means
500 million people we already know out
there in the world are drinking celery
juice and that
means that heavy metal detox is the
number one word phrase in health right
now because of mm
info and millions and millions of people
are doing the hmds because you're
changing the rules and changing the
world and changing
everything and they don't like it all
right all right enough for the
fun okay you guys I want to serve this
baby right here so let me just move this
aside for a second I got some cookies
going on there lots of do you guys stick
around I'm opening up aw's bar and grill
which it's getting me kind of
nervous getting kind of nervous to open
up aw Bar and Grill because what that
means is I have to serve I have to serve
and it's really hard to do everything
all at once but we're going to try to
pull it off all right what do we have
here
okay I'm going to pour this into
something I think I'm going to choose
this
here I think I'm going to choose this
here yep yep yep all right h no don't do
it this way do you ever do that did you
ever do that where you're like no I need
a scooper something's wrong here okay
all
right see I'm
notorious for
like making a mess that's just what I do
whoa whoa I just saw a huge cinnamon
stick go down in there you guys okay
with this you're supposed to strain this
but I decided to have a massive cinnamon
stick inside
mine because that's just what I wanted
to
do all
right by the way Samantha Sammy the Rd
registered
dietician registered
dietician is going to be coming on the
show at some point not today but coming
on the show some point because she wants
to clear the air she says that the
medical medum community knows nothing
about anything and she said that medical
medum community knows nothing about
protein so Sammy will be making an
appearance and talking about protein and
so forth um I'm going to give her a
chance to talk and tell you guys how she
feels but this is the wild blueberry
apple cider right
here and this is it right here you guys
all
right that that sucker's hot that
sucker's
hot
yeah that sucker's real
hot no no that sucker's so hot yeah no
that's not
good you know I mean I do things to
myself but I don't want to burn my
tongue off all right I'm going to serve
the
sangria yeah
correcto oh
sangria
sangria all
right
Singa that actually almost that actually
almost oh
yeah what am I
doing I'm going
to somehow
scoop the
sangria into the
thing so I'm going to do I'm going to
take
this uh yeah I'm going to scoop the sang
Reade here look at that oranges and
apples
woohoo
yeah all
right yep there we go boom diddly boom
that's just
insane
Can I taste the sangria if you don't
mind it's not alcohol free this is a
crap loser I can promise you this you
guys I know fool I know I fool around a
lot it's because of a lot of reasons one
is because the chronic leel they don't
feel good I want to make them happy I
want to serve in any way I can
serve the other thing is right is MM
info is so serious so deep it comes from
above the eight books packed with
information really intense all about
condition symptoms diseases what causes
them all that it's serious people
struggling is serious I try to kind of
lighten it up a little bit and um that's
why I just love to do this
show I'm serious that is
insane seriously that's insane
okay W blueberry
latte crap I got to make that I got one
more to
go one more to go one more
down okay let's
go all right you
[Music]
guys
so
ah
Shake It Off I can't end up on the
floor all
right I got to rinse
something okay just hang
[Music]
on all
right okay all right so now what I'm
making just so you know is a wild
blueberry
latte
3/4 cup of
water yep 3/4 of a cup of
water goes in the blender right
here you guys this latte is insane I'm
not kidding you can use unsweetened
almond milk you can use coconut milk
unsweetened coconut milk you can use
unsweetened oat milk I am
using unsweetened almond milk right
here
yep okay so what I'm going to do with
this is I'm going to put a/4 cup nope
I'm going to put a half a cup of this
almond milk in here and I'm going to
figure out how to do it without making a
killer mess half a
cup of almond milk right there goes in
here
ready amazing
you know where this almond milk came
from it came from my
juicer didn't come from the store with
all that stuff in there
okay4 cup W blueberry
juice4 Cup wild blueberry juice boo boo
bo boo
boo4 Cup wild bluy juice
am I going to say that again all right
one and two tablespoons of raw honey or
maple syrup I'm going to go with maple
syrup I'm totally into maple syrup just
lately lately I'm totally into maple
syrup if you guys didn't hear that I'm
totally into maple
syrup all right one or two tablespoons
of
maple
whoa that's nice
I can't believe I dodged that laugh
attack that laugh attack was really from
deep within and it was going to take
over and ruin everything I'm going to
blend this right
now that was no joke that laughing
attack it reminded me of Amazon the
laughing attack on there it was just oh
was awful it was
awful let's click this
on we're
on
[Music]
going in here hang
on four
walls trapped ins
[Music]
forever
okay if I ever get out of
here all
right the
rain okay guys I'm heating this up so
I'm going to show you what I'm doing
right
here okay what you see right
there this is the latte so blueberry
latte this is by far probably probably
one of my favorites without a
doubt by far one of my favorites I got
it on the heat right
now so we're getting ready I'm going to
steal a cookie any second I'm going to
steal a cookie any
second grace [ __ ] over there on
YouTube that laugh attack on Amazon got
me through a really tough day thanks
[Applause]
oh oh
hey deie Barn girl just
opened
crap all right guys come on in come on
in let's
go come on come on I you
guys come on
in come many you
guys oh I hope you don't drive me
[Applause]
nuts all right what can I do for you is
there anything I can can do for you I'm
starting to getting nervous already I'm
actually nervous right
now you guys are really in my
face something
fierce this is actually going to be
harder than I thought with you guys here
aw Bar and Grill is open I have to make
a phone
[Applause]
call yeah 911 yeah Emergency Services
yep
yep can you send somebody here sure uh
Mrs Fergenson she fell down the stairs
again she's at the bottom step right Mrs
Fergenson hold
on
[Applause]
Ferguson Mrs Fergenson slipped on the
bottom step it was wet we weren't open
yet and she came downstairs it didn't
dry she's crying about her back she's in
agony please send
somebody yeah it's Fergenson just hang
on
[Applause]
um you guys um just just just just bear
with me for a
secondo down here in the bar under the
bar I got lots of the beverage as we
speak what would you guys like what
would you
like okay let me just get you all set up
[Applause]
here okay all right um
this isn't going as good as I want it to
I want it to be prepared I'm not
prepared let get it what would you like
the hot dog the chick d right there
um would you
like yeah yep yep oatmeal cookie you got
it oatmeal cookie how about you uh sh
right
there okay that's
[Applause]
interesting
lost that cap aw's Bar and
Grill okay um I got to work and do aw's
bar and girl at the same time this is
really hard um would you guys like a
little cookie right
[Applause]
here yeah aw's Barn Grill yeah oatmeal
cookies that's
right siloc ibin no no no no no no
there's nothing of that in our cookies
no these aren't Edibles no no no no no
these are actually just regular cookies
but they're not regular cookies there's
in junk in them or anything just hold on
a second right here yeah oh hold on
another call coming through aw bar
[Applause]
gr hey no
no what you didn't see the sign outside
we're open you coming in great all right
you guys we're under staff I clearly
can't handle it
all Cookie is insane oh crap you guys
want
[Music]
some
guys calm down calm down calm
down calm down stop stop calm down no
calm yeah you got it just plenty for
everybody it is plenty for
everybody all
right yeah don't
wor come
on is it enough all
right
good hold
on is he get enough right
there
[Applause]
right
here all
right I'll put this here for you okay
all right about
that all
right all right you guys I just want to
show you a couple things you guys can
can is
up the cookies are really good this is
getting
ready all
right hold
on one cookie two cookie three cookie
four five cookie six 7 eight
cookie
whoa yep I'm sorry but that cookie was
so
good oh my
God are you kidding are you freaking
kidding me oh my God you guys seriously
right
seriously I don't know what to
drink I I don't even
know this is
ready
M you guys did I tell you did I tell you
how to eat a cookie if you're at a fancy
fancy
Gathering if you're at a fancy Gathering
you get invited to a mansion like really
rich people I've been invited I've been
invited to some huge
mansions cuz over years I've helped the
most power powerful people in the
world
right I won't name names I've helped
some of the most powerful people in the
world right been invited to Mansions
right and one of the things I do is I
you got to point with your cookie when
they when they speak to you you got to
point with your cookie and you got to
talk like I what do I think about that I
don't know I don't really know what I
think about that
another thing you want to do is you want
to take a piece of your
cookie and you want to put it in your
pocket because you know if it's a
wealthy person's cookie in a
mansion you want to kind of like steal a
couple you know you want to take a
couple and you want to put them in your
pocket I've done
that and then when I leave I got a bunch
of those fancy cookies another thing you
do if you're eating cookie in a mansion
a whole bunch of rich
people take a piece of the cookie you
put it in your
hand right as you're eating the cookie
everybody take your other hand you
go another one
here two servings all
right okay this is ready this is ready
this is getting poured
that's getting pour I need a um oh yeah
that's this correct me if I'm
wrong this is so good all
right I'm going to try to pour
this it just might be kind of a not so
smart thing to do but I really don't
know it's not so smart it's it's
actually
smart I don't know I don't want to go
too
high get
ready all
right hang
on all
right
I just want to get some more of this
almond milk in
here yeah that laugh attack totally
totally I I I was able to shut it down
somehow yeah just going to pour a little
bit in
there that's okay little extra you good
pour what you want on top right you guys
see this let see this right
here okay put it on the I'm going to put
it on the griddle I'm going to get that
hot we're going to fluff that
up and we're going to finish off these
drinks oh man I feel like an attic with
these cookies is so
good
incredible what do you guys think did
you ever have these
Yeah the code is wild
20 $20 off a case of the wild blue
Braes wild blueberry juice is such an
incredible gift for the
holidays incredible thing to have for
the
holidays all
right
sorry I just need a little bit more of
this bartender give me
another Mr William would you like
another Mr
William we are happy to serve you
here thank
you so
good oh
nice are you guys okay if I dip a
cookie so this is the
sangria oh this is the hot apple cider
this is the hot wild blueberry apple
cider let me just taste it
first okay hands down that's my
favorite
I call that that's my favorite I'm going
to dip a cookie in
there here's a
cookie oh
nice
nice you guys see this up close I'm
going to crack this cookie open
here see this cookie yeah that's what
I'm talking about right there I'm going
to dip that right in here
whoa
I better not do that over all these
cookies or somebody else wants a cookie
later I don't know if they
want I don't know if they want me
dipping my cookie over those cookies
right now look at guys
man you see this that's so
good you see what I'm
saying I see what you
saying that's just wrong that is just
wrong
that is so good there's got to be
something wrong with it I mean could
that be good for you could this could
this be actually good for you it is but
it doesn't taste like it's good for me
it doesn't taste nowhere near like it's
good for
me
yeah all
right
that's what I
thought watch this you
guys okay hang
on okay hang on hang
on
yep hang
on see this little thing
here
okay this thing's really
weird
whoa I'm froing this up you guys see
this
wonderful that froth this up
multitask are you guys hanging in
there m let's do
this move this over for a
second are it
okay I'm making the wild blueberry
latte
grou you okay okay sorry guys I think
that just got away from me a little
bit I didn't even know where I was
anymore this goes right on top it's like
this this
is
right now that when you when you dip a
cookie in that forget it little cinnamon
on
top yeah whoa all right take a look at
that you guys see
this now I'm going to dip a Cookie in
here
all
right
nice okay that was
it that was a
climax right
there that was it that was the serious
stuff
yep all right I want to show you guys
all the drinks got the
latte first of all you got the
shots got the
sangria right you got the apple
cider
right you got the
Mimosa is that what it
is you got the
Mimosa right you got that
the champagne
Mimosa it's a sparkling wild blueberry
juice and lime is what it is it's not a
mimosa what is a
mimosa all
[Music]
right Dr fawn
do I know you Dr
fa my name's Dr
jobie
$47,000 a sip
inflation of wine from my Winery in Napa
Valley I bought a Napa Valley
Winery that used to be $4 million to buy
it now it's 150 million to buy it and we
bought it me and a bunch of
doctors me and a bunch of doctors went
in on it and we got a
winery so our wives can sniff wine and
drink wine and be married we could all
get Gatherings
together it's really
good anyway
guys I think we did
it Greg Ruby girl over there in IG you
are such an amazing bartender
aw I don't think I did that great of a
job this time
around Julia I don't think I did that
great of a
time next time we do this I'll do better
I'll be a better
bartender all right you guys once in
next
book link is in the bio link is in the
description just so you
know take a look at the
cookies you guys seriously I had the
best time today I wouldn't trade it for
the world link is in the bio link is in
description you can check out the
blueberry juice stock up for the holiday
stock up for
festivities Wild 20 is the code code
wild
20 at Wyman's $20 off a case a 12 1 2 3
4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
12 all right guys for a last shot to
go you ever see people totally [ __ ] face
they in the bar and they're like one
more of the road one more the
road and then and the girls are like
yeah and the dudes are like
yeah I'm
buying on the house one more for the
[Music]
road one more for the
road
yeah you driving me home tonight you got
my keys one
more bartender give me
another coming right up Sir Anthony over
here in Britain coming right
up bartender give me
another sure
thing
indeed why do they say indeed over there
so much
indeed
cheers one more time that's it one more
shot one more shot going down a hatch
this is when everybody gets stupid when
they drink they just get so stupid
they're like alcohol poisoning
themselves right they're like alcohol
poisoning themselves it's like no don't
drink another shot of that
whiskey don't drink another shot of that
tequila are you
crazy I no more vodka in and it's like N
I want more I don't care you hurt my
feelings it doesn't matter I don't like
you anymore they're all like lost your
senses they're all like just so drunk
they're
like yeah what do you mean that's not
what it was we had a relationship no
everything was cool yeah man no
everything's fine oh I love you man I
love you yeah totally yeah huh what's
going on oh I got to go to the bathroom
oh oh my God
ready
woo that's right all right you
guys love you when you drink a
bottle when you drink a bottle of
this you're not going to feel like total
turd the next
morning like when you drink
alcohol you're not going to last one
bartender give me
another yep friend of mine told me that
he paid $37 for just a shot of tequila
in a bar $37 for a shot of
tequila he told me the reason why cuz
the worm was at the bottom of the bottle
there was a worm at the bottom of the
bottle I said dude you don't want to be
drinking that with the worm on the
bottom in the bottle that's
disgusting all
right you guys am I drunk off of wild
blueberry juice is that
possible
no it's not possible cuz I'm not I love
you guys instead I'm just packed with
energy and I'm going to go go go go go
go go go is what I'm going to do
actually my ass is just going to clean
up this mess is what it's going to do
I'm going to need this energy to be
cleaning up this freaking mess this is
what I'm going to be doing I got blue
teeth right now
saw saw somebody say that you got blue
teeth yes I do have blue teeth indeed I
do for about 5 seconds and then it goes
away all right you guys I have another
cookie I'll see you guys later love
you wait hold
on go to telegram anyway give me a
thumbs up and a like if you like this
video and go to telegram because I'm
leaving messages audio messages on
telegram yes go to
telegram
definitely go to
telegram okay recipes are all at
medicalmedium.com see so many options
for the holidays the website is packed
for all that y all right bye guys love
you