we are so honored to meet you my
goodness my daughter Lauren I'm Jackie
this is Laur what's going on nice to
meet you we've been doing her stuff she
has epilepsy petite M epilepsy and uh 15
years of a journey four different world
renown neurologists all the same thing
keto diet no changes long story short is
that she did the Smoothie first she
liked the taste does probably half of it
then this past June she started to do
the celery
[Music]
and we are now off what four
medications 100% and then and then
slivers of the last two my God we are
almost we almost home she almost has a
normal life that's incredible I'm proud
of you I'm proud of you okay 1 2 3
[Music]