thank you for saving my life I'm I don't
want to get too emotional but I'm so
grateful to you and for a while I
couldn't write and my passion was
writing you couldn't even write it was
just the brain fog wasn't coming to me
the way I thought it would so um I wrote
you something you're a writer you're a
of course you're a writer now I can
write again and I just wanted to thank
you for that so I this is for me you
wrote something yeah it's just a little
thank you not a little thank you note
this is amazing what do you mean
hopefully you can read my handwriting
but I will okay Lauren I will thank you
you're working with everything you're
doing good stuff you're healing you're
already moving forward okay
[Music]