this is a recipe in the medical medium
book
so this is the new addition revised and
expanded
this is one of the recipes and
today's episode right here we're going
to be making this recipe
i'm excited hope you guys are with me on
this so i got some different stuff here
and you haven't gotten that book yet
it's on amazon you can find it there
this is the new edition
45 recipes and description
is in the link so the link is in the
description i always
but i want to tell you this you guys
what's incredible about this book is
i added a book to it so i just want to
tell you that
so it's so packed with information so i
expanded the meditations chapter
i expanded the angels chapter
i expanded my story me adding in more
private information that i haven't
shared with anybody
in the origins of medical medium since i
was a child since age four
and i got the the chapters are packed
they even have information about the
plague we're dealing with today
and that's just to start i mean i mean i
could sit here all day with this that's
how packed it is
anyway we're gonna make the sweet and
sour stir fries what we're doing
and it's out of the revised and expanded
medical medium book new edition so i'm
excited
so i'm gonna get my things ready and
show you i got the bell peppers i know
some of you are like no
not i can't do a bell pepper it's gonna
it's gonna hurt me it's not gonna hurt
you this is really good for you
i got the orange bell peppers i got the
red bell peppers which you don't want is
a green
bell pepper green it's not ripe so you
got to remember that
green bell peppers are not ripe
that's the whole ticket right there
right you want to eat
ripe food and green bell peppers aren't
so keep that in mind because somebody
will have a green bell pepper
and it's not going to feel good in their
stomach because unripe food
doesn't feel good it just doesn't i mean
can you imagine eating an unripe mango
you just
really hard mango or an unripe avocado
where you can't even you guys like
avocados well
if your avocado's not ripe right are you
just gonna eat it where it's hard as a
rock where you can't get a knife through
it
so but a green bell pepper is not ripe
and that's what you want to avoid but
the red ones are ripe so i got some
carrots here too so i want to show you a
few things
i'm working with i got some carrots i
got some peppers i got some green onions
these are scallions
with the green onions there i'll you
know you can call them green onions i
call them scallions that's what i like
to do
i got some garlic right here i got some
ginger so letting you know maybe you
guys have some of the stuff
in your kitchen right now and
i got some limes because we're going to
need that got some other stuff too
over here
i got some beautiful asparagus so
that's going to be in the stir fry this
is sweet and sour stir fry that's what
i'm making
i got the brussels sprouts right here
too you can use broccoli the recipe
calls for broccoli but i had these
beautiful brussels sprouts
and that's a cruciferous i want to use
for this um
renita says i can't eat any peppers they
cause joint pain for me
well make sure they're not green peppers
make sure they're never green
make sure they're they're red and make
sure that have you ever had a piece of
red
bell pepper by itself like a piece
or was it peppers and something else was
it peppers in a sausage
grinder with cheese was it peppers
in a chicken grinder with cheese was it
was it
peppers and eggs was it peppers and
butter
what was it that you were having was it
was it gluten
was there like was there was it a pepper
sandwich with all these other things and
then gluten was involved and
keep that in mind just we can do some
self-diagnosis a little self-diagnosis
there like
could a little piece of red bell pepper
be the problem
or is it whatever that pepper was in
that was maybe the problem what was
going on was there vinegar in there so
that's another thing too because the
true cause of joint pain
is viral stuff so that's the joint pain
so it's viral stuff i talk about that
with ra
rheumatoid arthritis i talk about the
epstein-barr virus being
the joint pain maker it hurts the nerves
swells up joints too so keep that in
mind
but hey you can stay away from the red
bell pepper and the orange bell pepper
of course of course try something else
keep it out of the stir fry how about
that
lorraine lawson wow green bell peppers
are not ripe
yes they're not ripe exactly totally no
wonder why no wonder i thought peppers
affected me at one time
i stopped eating them but love the red
and orange ones
the green bell peppers so another thing
too somebody might
get a pepper meal of some kind like a
dish or a condiment and it's got
green and red and other things in it or
or but the green
pepper is what causes problems anything
unripe can cause trouble so keep that in
mind
um hi from michigan glad you guys are
here
so yeah so you have you have a lot of
joint pain elena
so some look if you someday you want to
venture into knowing what the joint pain
is and learning what that joint pain is
you can always get this right here in
the future it's on amazon
but you can wait until the book comes
out get it free at the library if you
want you can do that so you guys i'm
making this if you just came
on i'm making the sweet and sour
stir-fry
so jalapenos if you do green out
jalapenos
you can have a problem look for red
a green jalapeno is unripe it's an
unripe pepper
you don't want an unripe tomato you
don't want an unripe
pepper you don't want an unripe avocado
you don't want
a prawn ripe banana on ripe mango
you know you don't want that for sure
you know people are so there's there's
health advocates out there or health
so-called health experts out there
that hate the banana so much they don't
like bananas because they're like sugar
sugar but then they'll recommend
an unripe banana so they'll put that in
their book or they'll put there on their
podcast where do an unripe banana
that's the worst thing you can do you
don't want unripe
bananas on ripe fruits you don't want to
eat an orange that didn't turn
orange you don't want to eat a green
unripe orange where it's green
on a tree you want food to be ripe
that's the key
and that's something that people get in
trouble with in general because they
won't
they won't know what they're doing those
jalapenos when they're green
they're on ripe so keep that in mind too
green bell peppers are so yummy though
yeah you know
alex if you still want to eat them you
could still have green bell peppers
you can you can so i'm making some food
now i'm going to start making this
stir-fry
i'm excited what's the name of the book
please i just saw that
this is medical medium okay secrets
behind chronic
mystery illness and how to finally heal
and this is the new edition so revised
and expanded
so i cover chronic fatigue syndrome
lupus
ra multiple sclerosis lyme disease this
is the book
that blew the roof off of lyme disease
and millions have healed because of it
so this is the truth about lyme and how
to heal it
so it's in this book here that's just
some of the stuff in here there's
recipes the 28-day cleanse the famous
28-day cleanse that's turned lives
around brought people back
from the grave i mean brought people
back
they were literally in wheelchairs
suffering in bed
and the 28-day cleanse has brought so
many lives back
and this is the book so jim
kathy says i've had the all cat blood
test
that says i'm highly reactive to bell
peppers or bananas
how can i do your cleanses when they
call for banana well
um look i talk to doctors all the time
about that test and the consensus is
between lots of doctors i know
plus information that i've learned along
the way about that that the test is very
inconsistent so it'll tell you that
you're sensitive to a lot of different
things but what it won't tell you
is maybe something that you should be
sensitive like you should keep out of
your diet so
does that test tell you to stay away
from eggs because eggs
feed all manners of illness that feeds
pathogens viruses bacteria
so if you have any kind of condition at
all eczema psoriasis
cfs lupus aches and pains tingles
numbness vertigo dizziness whatever it
is
you know ringing in the ears utis
chronic sinusitis whatever you have
going on
eggs will feed all these bugs and what
the alcat test
never understood or never knew the
makers of it okay
was they never knew what causes sickness
so
the creators of the alcat test don't
know what causes cfs or lyme disease
unless they learned it from medical
medium information like so many doctors
have
but they didn't know what causes any
sickness and illness so
all of a sudden now they're experts at
what foods you should stay away from
you know that's interesting too so
they're experts
but meanwhile they can't get anybody
better that's got the ms and they can't
get the people better with lupus and
they can't get the people better with
raging eczema psoriasis where they can't
wear clothes
and they're suffering all night
scratching their skin off and it's
bleeding everywhere
well they can do an lcat test for that
eczema patient or that psoriasis patient
but they sure as heck can't stop their
skin from tearing off and then bleeding
all night long in agony and needing
drugs to try to calm the pain down
well they can't fix that so what i
kind of like what i've learned through
the years is when
you know something works and you've seen
it work and
the results are there and millions have
healed from the information
that's kind of the leads you kind of go
with because the makers of the alcat
test
well they can't save that person with
severe eczema
and they can't save that person in the
wheelchair that needs to get out and
recover further that mass and they can't
save that person with neurological lyme
and their life is falling apart all
around them and
and they can't save anybody there they
can tell you that you should stay away
from a banana and they should tell you
they can tell you that
mandy i had those food sensitivity tests
two years two
um two years ago and was told i was
highly sensitive to bananas turnout
that was incorrect once i found the mm
information in 2017 i eat bananas every
day
every single day and they have helped me
heal being being
so high in lysine correct 100 mandy
right on so true and that's the mistakes
out there
once again you got a whole bunch of
hackers
this is how you know this leads into
something i've been thinking about like
just recently but this leads to a whole
bunch of hackers in health
right and they got all these different
ways of doing stuff
meanwhile they don't know what's wrong
and they're kind of like just they're
shooting blanks everywhere it's like hey
stay away from that banana stay away
from that tomato
stay away meanwhile they don't even know
why anybody's suffering and i don't know
why you're sick
and a whole bit um lunell
you going good this evening going great
i'm here so let's talk about this let's
get this going and i want to cover some
cool things
um i just want you guys getting better i
want you guys healing
so i'm going to slice up some carrots to
start with okay
so i'm going to thinly slice up some
carrots i got them right here
so this is the sweet and sour stir-fry
um look i understand it's it's easy easy
to get tricked
into the owl cat it's easy to get
tricked
into food sensitivities because
you know one of the things is that
what food sensitivity tests change
they change literally by the hour so you
can get some
blood drawn right you can do even some
saliva testing or blood drawn
okay and you can do it an hour later
if you went back to your doctor an hour
later and had a new blood test
drawn it would show different
sensitivities to different foods in one
hour okay a day later
the same thing all of a sudden now your
food sensitivity says
tess says you're allergic to cilantro
now oh you're not supposed to have
parsley
oh stay away from strawberries oh forget
asparagus that's a bad one too
here's what's funny you can get that
test done and get it done a month later
and here's what your doctor will do
your fancy doctor will go hey some new
sensitivities showed up on your test
this month
since last month you're not just now
sensitive to some bananas
but you're sensitive to some cilantro
you're sensitive to
some parsley and this is how ridiculous
it really is
and how it consistent if they did a
blood test an hour later
after you went to bathroom okay
or ate something all of a sudden that
test would change
isn't that incredible um
karen todd says finding your books gave
me my foot from being amputated due to
severe infection that spread throughout
my body
thank you for all you do for us karen
you know like
look i understand because
it it's the people that haven't suffered
and they haven't struggled and they
don't know what it's like to be down
there
in that in that spot they don't know
what it's like to have that kind of
struggle or suffering right
and um i'm slicing these carrots by the
way thinly slicing them
and they don't know what it what it's
like to be there
they're easy to judge quick you know
they're easy to judge quick they'll be
like
no don't listen to the m make sure
you're on apple cider vinegar make sure
you do two tablespoons of apple cider
vinegar every day
that'll help your foot you know you hear
all this kind of information out there
and what's sad is that information can
get you in trouble and when you're
when you're in a situation that's really
really tricky and exactly maybe about to
get
your foot amputated or something every
little bit
counts every little bit counts
it really matters then but if you're
you're you're fairly healthy don't have
much going on
maybe just a little anxiety and a little
fatigue right
and you're fairly healthy um
you know you can you can play around
with all these different things
but you know what it really counts is
when yeah when when
when it matters matters the most um
elena says i am 70 healed thanks to
anthony
incredible incredible you know
just keep on working at it um rebecca
says brand name
of your skillet you can find it on my
directory medicalmedium.com
so medicalmedium.com go to my my
directory
and you'll you'll find it there okay
supplement
the link you'll see like supplements in
there you'll see
the kitchen store okay so it's it's
under the kitchen store it's a non-stick
ceramic frying pan
great glad you guys are here what i'm
doing is putting some carrots in here so
i think i got enough
because this is a nice good sized pan
right there
all right and now i'm going to do some
brussels sprouts
i'm going to chop these up a little bit
so look you guys one cup sliced carrots
we're going to do one um
we're gonna do around two cups one to
two cups of
brussels sprouts now recipe calls for
broccoli
but i'm gonna throw these really nice
brussels sprouts in here too
that's what i'm doing now so let me get
these in here so this can start cooking
um so you know like there's a lot of
hackers out there health hackers you
guys hear about biohacking have you guys
heard about biohacking
right and
it's really not a good term bio
biohacking
because really what it means it's a lot
of guessing games
so biohacking is really just hey i'm
gonna try to hack my body
i'm gonna try to trick out my body i'm
gonna try to psych out my body
i'm not gonna know what my body needs or
hear what my body needs
i'm just going to kind of guess with a
bunch of crap i find out there and then
i'm going to try to hack my body
whether my body likes it or not
you know so the bio hacking thing is
really kind of a tough one for me
because when i hear it i hear
really hey i don't know what's wrong
i don't know what my body needs i don't
know what i should do
but i'm just going to try to like hack
it and what i noticed with biohacking
is all the bio hacking
all the bio hacking is
really adrenaline based stuff
so it's like oh you got all these health
experts
and they're all bio hack experts okay
but really what they're doing
is they're teaching people how to get
adrenalized
they're teaching people how to live on
adrenaline
so health experts should really be
called how to get high on your own
adrenaline
not you know let's bio hack and find
some answers that way
because bio hacking's really like a lot
of stuff thrown out there these days
it's like
lots of cacao make sure you're doing
your cacao make sure you're doing your
apple cider vinegar
make sure you're doing you know lots of
your coffee drinks do your matcha tea
try that that's good for you so
biohacking can
you know and then there's also it goes
beyond that right so you guys i'm
putting brussels sprouts in there
biohacking is like not just caffeine
which
really that's a big one for biohacking
get everybody on caffeine
get everybody on chocolate right but
biohacking is also
high fat get everybody on a high fat
diet that's already been on a high fat
diet
who's already gotten sick from being on
a high fat diet all these years
and then we say hey get on a high fat
diet
you know that's another thing too so but
i want to talk about that a little bit
like
what happens is when you do a high fat
diet
because that's what everybody does
you're burning out your adrenals faster
than they should be
you're using your credit card your
adrenal
credit card something that's really
important to know
see your adrenals are only good
they're only as good as how you treat
them and take care of them
and we waste them throughout the years
so a lot of the biohackers actually all
of the biohackers out there
are really just about wearing down your
adrenals
burning them out and one way to do that
is the high fat diet so what happens is
when you're eating all this fat
which you're not going to find in this
dish by the way when you're eating all
this fat
what i call radical fats your blood gets
thick with that fat and then your
adrenals
have to spit out all this adrenaline
pump all this adrenaline out to thin
out your blood so your adrenaline
becomes a blood thinner that's really
important to know
the reason why it's trying to save your
brain
your brain sends a message to your
adrenals
save me that's what your brain does send
adrenaline
fast because this person
actually dumped a ton of fat inside the
body
the fat's going to head up to the brain
and and take the oxygen away
so here's what happens when you're doing
the high fat diet you take
oxygen away from your blood
you lose oxygen out of your blood that
means your brain gets less oxygen
so your brain your nervous system sends
out a signal an alarm bell that alarm
bell
goes right to the adrenals the adrenals
then floods your bloodstream with a lot
of adrenaline
every time you eat your big fatty meal
okay because the health hackers and the
biohackers they want you to do that
every time you do that what happens is
your brain is begging for help from your
adrenals
so it's looking for help your adrenals
release all this adrenaline the
adrenaline thins out your blood
so your brain to save your brain to
protect your brain
it ha your adrenals have to release all
this adrenaline to thin out your blood
so the fat doesn't kill the brain
happens every day every meal you have
you have the bacon and eggs in the
morning
your adrenals are pumping you want to do
a carnivore diet adrenals are pumping
i'm not anti
i'm not anti-animal protein you guys i'm
not anti-vegan plant-based
i'm just telling you what happens
because you could be vegan you can be
plant-based
right and guess what you're on a
high-fat diet
um tiffany says i'm so confused you
didn't use any oil
no oil needed in stir fry you got a hot
pan
right here hot ceramic pan i got the
carrots in here i got the brussels
sprouts i'm cooking them down a little
bit
i got the heat on i just put a little
water a little touch
just a little water in there that's all
you needed to do
so i'll give you guys a little recap
this is really important to know
when you're told to do those high fat
diets which everybody's told to do
okay what is happening is your brain
is crying for help sends a signal down
to the adrenals
the adrenals release all this
epinephrine
to thin out your blood so that the fat
doesn't rob oxygen
from your brain right now you're on an
adrenal high
so now that's a lie a lot of people are
like whoa i just had that
i just had the animal protein i'm
starting to just i feel better now
i feel like myself what's happening is
you're getting the adrenaline surge
or say you're plant-based say you're
plant-based
okay say you're vegan i just ate a whole
pile of nuts
i just ate a whole bunch of macadamia
nuts i just ate a whole
whole pile of peanuts i just had a
two tablespoons three tablespoons of
peanut butter on my smoothie bowl
i just had some almond butter and almond
milk you know
i just had some butter some
if ghee if you're into animal protein i
just had some butter and so what's
happening is
just so you know you can be plant-based
and vegan
and you can kill your adrenals over time
now hey hey hey
sounds a little too much right you're
killing your adrenals
how can that be just because you're
eating a high fat diet whether it's
healthy
or not how can that be i mean this
doesn't sound right you guys i just cut
the bell pepper i showed you this the
other day
i cut the top off right there and i'm
just taking out the center
that's all and i got the bell pepper
you might be thinking it's kind of harsh
isn't it he's
he's saying that we're killing our
adrenals on the high fat diet
you know how's that possible well here's
how it goes
your adrenals don't die quick and they
don't die too easy
so they hang on because they have to
because that's how we stay alive
it's our adrenals that keep us alive
that's a big part of how we stay alive
right cutting up some
bell pepper here but here's what goes
wrong you keep on doing it you keep on
doing everybody has different levels
they have a different adrenal strengths
different levels of tolerance
some people have weaker adrenals some
people have one
one adrenal that's stronger than the
other right but then
you also get someone where it hits them
pretty good along the way
they don't know it until they have their
baby yeah
hard pregnancies are from weak
adrenals throughout the years from high
fat diets
from caffeine from chocolate okay
all right from from uh and
hard child births hard pregnancy
hard child birth because here's what
happens it's
in order to have a baby your adrenals
have to be supersonic they got to be
powerful
they got to be strong so a woman's
adrenals are not like
men's adrenals and men don't know this
so men health hackers and biohackers
all over the internet out there they'll
just tell you do lots of caffeine that's
how you do your matcha tea
do your cacao do your high fat diets but
they're not the ones that are going to
have that hard childbirth potentially or
the second baby being really difficult
because the adrenals start to weaken
over time
so what happens is you need
your adrenals working top notch
when you deliver a baby when a baby
is born when you birth a baby so it's
very important to know this
but there's a lot of women right now and
young women they're saying that was a
really difficult labor
the labor went four hours why the labor
went
seven hours how come the labor went two
days how come like why does it have to
be that hard
labor to go two days and
um and what they don't know
is all those years even if it was two
years even it was three years
of the coffee drinks the matcha tea the
energy drinks
the chocolate chocolate every week
all the cacao cacao nibs whatever
chocolate bars whatever
all of that beats down the adrenals and
here's another thing that kills the
adrenals for women so they have
difficult child births here's another
thing
intermittent fasting epic disaster
for childbirth okay years of
intermittent fasting
breaks down the adrenals because you run
on adrenaline all day
you withhold food so your adrenals have
to release adrenaline
to replace glucose so now
glucose has to be replaced that's your
blood sugar glucose right
so you have no glucose going on you're
intermittent fasting
right and you're going without food
you're on caffeine all day long
and your adrenals are flooding all day
long your adrenals are flooding all day
long see and they start to wear down
so then you got so here's what's
happening biohackers are teaching women
women biohackers too men biohackers are
teaching women
to intermittent fast the wrong way okay
to get all jacked up on caffeine
and to do high fat diets when they do
eat the combination of all three
is an epic disaster for child for for
for delivering a baby okay and
and so that's very important to know
it's also an epic disaster for future
hair thinning and hair loss and what
you'll find is women
end up getting hair thinning after
having a baby yeah
because it's just too much too much
happened to their adrenals
in the years before they had their baby
too many things happen to their adrenals
and the hair started thinning and then
they get the sunspots and the age spots
everywhere
and then they get they they get the weak
adrenals and then they lose energy and
then they need more caffeine and more
caffeine and more caffeine
so chopping up some
orange bell pepper here so bio hackers
and health experts really shouldn't be
called
health experts well actually they should
be they're health experts to how to
trash your adrenals
weaken adrenals shorten them for the
long haul
make life more difficult for millions of
women and
even some men in some ways in different
ways but
especially for women especially for
women
you need your adrenals to be on point
for threatening events
hard times a divorce
a bad breakup a betrayal car accident
you know you can't lift up a car
you know out of a ditch off of somebody
that's trapped under it
when your adrenals have had 10 years of
caffeine 10 years of high fat diets
10 years of intermittent fasting you
won't get that car off that person
underneath that car
you will though if you protect your
adrenals and keep those adrenals strong
and not get tricked and fooled by
biohackers
so something really important to know
um i got some red bell peppers here i
got some orange bell peppers i got some
brussels sprouts in here too and i got
some carrots i'm making a stir fry it's
called sweet and sour stir-fry
if you guys just got on here it's a
medical medium new addition right here a
recipe
right out of this brand new book coming
out that's the recipe i'm making
so i just want to let you know and
here's the other thing
your adrenals are what creates the most
important hormones
so everybody's worried about hormones my
hormones my hormones my hormones doctor
says worry about my hormones
doctor says she's worried about my
hormones my reproductive system
my hormones maybe my hormones are off
that's what you'll hear right
your your adrenals are the hormone
makers
the liver is the second hormone maker
but the adrenals
that's the big one that's your estrogen
that's your that is where that's where
it's happening right there
it's those adrenals so that's your
testosterone
you need that testosterone that's your
estrogen those adrenals
are what's cranking that out every day
so when you're worried about hormones
and you say well my doctor says my
hormones are off
my nutritionist said maybe my hormones
are off you know
you know all that well guess what at the
same time your nutritionist is going to
tell you to do the high fat diet tell
you
matcha tea is just fine eat lots of
chocolate it's good for you studies say
and they're going to tell you that and
then they're going to tell you with all
that and the coffee and the coffee
drinks and
the chocolate and the intermittent
fasting they're going to tell you to do
with all that combined and then they'll
say hey you know what
and all that's going to be killing your
adrenals which is going to mess up your
hormones more and more and more and more
but then they're going to say why don't
you do some hot yoga
why don't you do some hot yoga that's an
adrenal destroyer
right there i got nothing against yoga i
think it's great i think you know i
think it's great
hot yoga it's ridiculous it's actually
the adrenal crusher
what hot yoga does if you do it long
term will make sure that when you do
want to have that baby
that's going to be a hard birth okay not
everybody because their adrenals are
maybe stronger than someone else's but
eventually it catches up to everybody
and it catches up to them later on in
life in different ways
maybe fatigue maybe aging faster
maybe you know sensitive nervous systems
from adrenaline pumping through them so
much
so health experts and biohackers are
really
adrenal destroyer experts
they promote everything that destroys
adrenals shortens women's lives as far
as aging them faster
making life more difficult and then
they'll tell you to do the saunas
with a really high temps you know really
high temperatures they'll say
do the saunas high temperatures true
130 degree 150 degrees stay in there for
40 minutes
whatever and what you'll do is right on
the edge of hyperthermia
your body goes into shock and goes into
crisis
and then you and then that high comes
out because your adrenals are flooding
in for dear life
your brain's saying you're cooking my
freaking brain
your brain is telling your adrenals god
help me you're cooking
my brain so you're sitting there being
told to do these really hot
hot hot yoga you're doing the real hot
saunas
you've got the temperature really high
you're told to stay in there longer
and what's happening is your brain is
starting to cook
and then it's calling for adrenaline to
save
its life which is your life so
the adrenals are flooding all this
adrenaline by the time you're 30 minutes
40 minutes into your hot sauna
which is another brainiac really silly
idea
and then your adrenals are now like
you're wasting them and
wasting them and then you feel high
after that sauna that really hot one i'm
not talking about going into the
infrared sauna for five minutes 10
minutes 20 minutes
you know at a reasonable temp i'm
talking about
you know not even like 105 whatever you
know
the point is is you're going in high
temperatures in these saunas now
and what you're doing is you're getting
high off of adrenaline so
biohackers and health experts are
experts
at destroying your adrenals shortening
and aging your life
setting you up for misery later on when
you're in your 40s
so when you're 22 and you're doing your
hot saunas and it sounds like a great
idea and you got these cool guys and
cool people whatever
and telling you what to do you do this
hot sauna you crank it up
and now you get high afterwards they're
still robbing
and stealing they're vampires that are
robbing
and stealing your adrenaline reserves
breaking down your adrenals and
yeah saunas are very healing when you
use them right
but see biohackers and health experts
they don't use a lot of things right
they don't
and the same thing with cold plungers
and cold
and you know cold plunges okay that's
another thing too
any kind of cold shock therapy all right
it's any kind of cold shock therapy i'm
gonna get some asparagus in here now
anything in the hypothermic realm so
when you sit there and you freeze
yourself
what you're doing is you're putting your
body in shock and then your adrenals are
now cooking again they're cranking
your adrenals are now flooding again you
see how it works
so now you're killing your adrenals
again because your brain's saying you're
freezing me
see so when you do the cold plunges
and the cold therapies your brain is
saying
okay now you're freezing you're freezing
my ass off is what your brain's saying
send out the adrenaline army send out
the adrenaline reserves
because we need adrenaline here because
you're putting me in shock
so it's not just the heat it's also the
cold
see it's life threatening in the entire
brain
so how do you use this karen how do you
use the sauna correctly you can use an
infrared sun you can also use a steam
shower steam bath sauna steam
so you can do that but you don't cook
yourself you stay in there
for a little while you need to do 15 20
minutes do 10 minutes
keep the temps reasonable don't keep
them blaring
and don't be a hero because the
biohackers
what they do is they don't care about
women's health really
they're usually men and they usually
tell you
to just push it to the limit push it to
the max and that's what they do
and so they'll end up saying they won't
do something they won't be protective
over women they won't be like no be
cautious keep the heat at a reasonable
rate just be in there for a certain
amount of time check out how you feel
you won't hear any of that you'll hear
here's what you do here's the new trend
here's a new fad
crank it you know and do it every day do
your sauna crank the heat up
and and then people get damaged
they get damaged later on you might not
sense it in the moment you might not
sense it in the first year or two
you'll sense it later on and then your
adrenals are cooked
things are actually you're in a lot
difficult situation with your health
and if you're somebody with chronic
illness if you have anything going on if
you have fibro or cfs me or anything
lupus forget that symptoms how about
symptoms you know feel good you got
fatigue you got ace and pains
you know your feet hurt your back hurt
your neck how you've got teeth that hurt
your neck hurts right
any of that you got to be careful you do
the sauna carefully
do the infrared one you can do a steam
sun
carefully so you be mindful
which leads me to the next thing i have
to tell you guys because that just
reminded me about something okay
everybody's so spiritual you know
everybody's so spiritual everybody's
you know into self-care everybody's
honoring their body
right like you hear it now everybody
hears it everybody's talking about it
everybody's honoring their body
everybody's so careful
on that level where they're like hey i'm
honoring my body
i'm using my intuition okay everybody's
so spiritual
right and meanwhile
they're not listening to their body
they're not
you know being spiritual is about
letting some things go like vices
and it's okay if you can't let a vice go
it's all right
that's okay i get it some people need
devices absolutely
they need them to survive life is hard
i'm putting green onion in here
scallions but
there's a lot of people these days
they're acting like spiritual experts
acting like they're so spiritual
and they're literally intermittent fast
intermittent fasting they're on caffeine
all day long they're doing all this
caffeine on their body they're doing
chocolate all day
and being spiritual is living without a
little bit you know what i mean
being spiritual is learning how to let
go of vice
and then feeling what that feeling is
being spiritual is being able to like
give your body something truly back so
instead of saying everybody's honoring
their body you know what own it
okay just finally own it you're not
honoring your body
totally be straight out be honest please
okay you know what i mean because
if you really were to honor your body
you'd break out of the caffeine
addiction
let it go and fix what's wrong
the caffeine hides everything so it's
hiding everything for everybody it's got
them on a big high
and look look i'm not judging anybody i
look i know some people
had some hard lives hard lives and
that cup of coffee pushes them through
their day okay
and i got friends with hard lives and
you know they were like look i'm working
on it i'm like totally i totally get it
it's just that some of the friends i
have
they're not saying how down they how how
they got it all down they're not saying
how spiritual they are
acting so spiritual they're not
pretending on their youtube channels how
spiritual they are
you know they're straight out they're
saying i got a lot of work to do you
know they're humble
i got a lot of work to do i'm trying to
honor my body
but i'm just not there yet you know
right now life's hard i'm pushing
through each hour man
anthony i'm pushing through hour by hour
and i know i need to work on stuff and
at least i know
and that's the key right there but
what's happening here is people are
being told
things are good for them now everybody's
saying hey the caffeine caffeine's good
for you everybody's saying the coffee
drinks and the chocolate is so good for
you
and then everybody's like i'm honoring
my body
i'm being so spiritual i'm you know i'm
i'm a health expert now
and come on let's just be real a little
bit
because if you removed that caffeine
you would notice depression starts to
kick in you'd notice that fatigue starts
to kick in you can't do your workouts
anymore
you know that anxiety would start
kicking in and that's when you honor
your body
that's when you're spiritual because
you're without your vice
and you're honoring your body and you
start
and you start you know and you get off
that high fat diet and you realize whoa
wait a minute what's wrong here honoring
your body is
finding out what's really wrong too it's
it's about hey
i got a problem i can't focus and
concentrate without my caffeine
how do i fix this you know i can't
function without my caffeine i can't do
my two hour workouts now every day
because without my caffeine
or how about this i got to keep my
caffeine in order to function
i know it's not good for me i know it's
a drug
you know i know everybody's trying to
pretend it's good for you now
but you know honoring honoring you
honoring your body is really about being
self-aware for real like really
self-actualized
really self-realized it's about saying
hey
you know i know i need work you know
it's about a little bit
humbling a little bit about knowing you
need some work
i've just seen a lot lately people think
they got it all down
spiritually they got it all down where
they're talking the good stuff
they're talking about they're honoring
their body they're talking about
that whole thing they're saying how in
their intuition is off the charts and
their intuition is so strong
right i hear that a lot but
you know what
they need some work anyway they need
caffeine for energy
because there's some problems okay so
look i'm going to make some sauce right
here so i'm going to do that now
so i got a stir fry going i got some
asparagus on here
i'm going to start with some pineapple
juice look this is a pineapple juice
right here
it's a really good organic one so
i got that now i don't have a fresh
pineapple
to juice so i'm going to use pineapple
juice that's what i'm gonna do right
here this is unsweetened pineapple juice
just so you know
so um so anyway
okay let's see so i got some i'm gonna
do one cup
put that in here that's going
all right two tablespoons of lime juice
i'm gonna cut some limes get that in
here this is the sauce that goes on the
stir fry
look i'm not judging anybody life is
hard
life is hard a lot of people been
through hell and back
but i know a lot of people that got it
easy
out there got it real easy you know
everything taken care of
they don't have to worry about money
they don't got to worry about jack
right and they're out there saying how
spiritual they are
and how they're honoring their body
while they're living off caffeine 24 7
and they're not being honest and they're
not honoring their body
you know and these are health experts
i'm talking about if you want to be a
health expert
you don't have to be perfect okay you
don't have to be perfect as a health
expert that's not it
you don't but you got to be honest with
yourself
that's that's a good sign of a health
expert like a real one
being honest with yourself and i know
you guys are honest with yourselves
i know that i know that i mean you guys
are like salt of the earth
you guys are like nothing i've never
seen i've never seen out there like you
guys
okay but you know
but the thing is is when you're a health
expert and you never suffered or
struggled
never had any problems you're young and
everything's taken care of for you and
you're out there promoting the heck out
of a
a caffeine product and it's keeping you
running around like crazy and it's
hiding your anxiety and it's hiding your
fatigue
and it's hiding your depression and
you're telling another hundred thousand
people or fifty thousand people that
they should be jacked up on caffeine too
it's not really honoring your body or
others
or teaching them how to intermittent
fast wrong getting some lime juice here
okay two tablespoons of lime juice in
this
i'm gonna put some grated ginger in here
you know when you're a health expert
you're supposed to protect people right
that's what you're supposed to do and
you're supposed to give in
a little bit right give in
be honest be truthful
about what you're doing it's like
protecting people is the number one
thing that should be in your soul and on
your mind as a health expert
that's the critical thing that you gotta
be
and it's hard to protect people when
you know you're training them to be
jacked up on caffeine
training them to lose their adrenal
strength so they have difficult
childbirths later
training them for all these things so
i'm going to put i got it next thing i'm
going to put a little
tomato paste in here that's what i'm
doing now
get a spoon
so right now i have a cup of pineapple
juice in here
all right so i got that i'm going to put
some tomato paste
a couple teaspoons in here or a couple
tablespoons of tomato paste in the sauce
there we go
so i got that in there now i'm going to
grate some ginger that's going to go in
here too
and the whole biohacking thing is really
kind of
interesting when you think about it it's
really a guessing game
and i noticed all biohackers these days
just want to make sure that whatever
they're offering for advice most of it
means killing your adrenals
that's what it means you know maybe
maybe it doesn't matter right who cares
i mean should we really care just let
people do what they want to do
let them do what makes them happy let
them um let them get the hair thinning
you know all the women getting the hair
thinning let the age spots happen let
the wrinkled skin happen real fast the
wrinkles
when they shouldn't be happening
menopause symptoms coming on faster
right losing precious hormones critical
hormones for the whole body
so that you're not in the doctor's
office every single day
you know all worried about the hormones
right
so i don't know i mean shouldn't we care
or what about if you get you have an
experience someday you pick up some bugs
you pick up some epstein bar
i got some some grated ginger in here
what if you pick up a new epstein bar
and you get really sick
and your adrenals can't handle it
so i'm going to do some garlic too i'm
going to mince up some garlic
you want your adrenal strong you guys
you want your adrenals strong for what
gets thrown at you in your lifetime
and so adrenal robbers which are
basically vampires in the health field
now there's tons of them out there tons
of vampires in the health field now
they'll teach you how to rob
and kill your adrenals right they'll
teach you that matcha tea is good for
you all that caffeine they'll teach you
cacao is all good for you so you
just ruin your adrenals so they're the
real thieves right
but i'm going to put some garlic in here
too you guys
then they'll go on podcasts
talk about all the scientific studies
well you know
last when i checked no one ever got
better from a scientific study ever in
chronic illness
so i guess you could wait for another 20
years for scientific studies to come out
to get you better but we've already
waited 50 70 years
for scientific studies to get everybody
better at chronic illness but
but last i checked there's no study that
fixes anybody
um can you show me a study somewhere
that gets somebody out of a wheelchair
with ms
okay so let's do i put the garlic in
here that's great
that's in here maple syrup's next so i
got two tablespoons of maple syrup
that's in the sauce and we go with one
tablespoon of arrowroot
powder which i have right here just so
you know so one tablespoon
of arrowroot powder in the sauce
got that
i didn't know a scientific study can
stop somebody from having the worst
preeclampsia
i didn't know a scientific study can
stop somebody from having pcos
didn't know
really didn't know and i didn't know a
scientific study can
stop somebody's encephalitis brain
inflammation from mecfs
or stop their vertigo or stop their jaw
pain
and their trigeminal neuralgia there's
not one scientific study that's ever
stopped anybody's trigeminal neuralgia
so you guys this is the sauce i just
made right here a little tomato paste
some maple syrup some arrowroot some
garlic some ginger
okay cup of pineapple juice and i'm
turning it
into here or pouring it into here okay
and i got the heat up here
this is stir fry got the asparagus in
here
got the carrots got the red bell pepper
got the orange bell pepper
i mean have you guys have you guys found
a scientific study to
fix your depression or have you found
one to fix your anxiety
just wondering crippling anxiety
i haven't seen a scientific study that
fixes anybody's tinnitus
it's a whole other thing so i got the
stir fry here i'm just going to wait
i'm going to crank up the heat a little
bit more get it cooking
but all those adrenal highs all those
adrenal highs everybody's doing
it's incredible almost every single
person
almost every single person is on
caffeine every single day
every single day and adrenal high
adrenal high
everybody's intermittent fasting not
everybody but a lot of people
almost everybody right in the health
scene and they're killing their adrenals
that way adrenal high adrenal high
because when you go without glucose
your adrenals replace the glucose and
flood flood flood flood and it makes you
do more chocolate more caffeine more
coffee drinks more matcha tea more green
tea whatever more energy drinks
and you're just doing the intermittent
fasting like that so there's more people
doing that more people doing
the hot saunas but i'm talking about the
hot saunas right long
long time in there 40 minutes more heat
cranked up until you go into that crisis
and then your
adrenals flood like crazy and you come
out like oh my god i feel so good i'm
high
and you're totally high on adrenaline
and then you know you do the apple cider
vinegar and you kill your stomach glands
with the apple cider vinegar
you kill your stomach glands and
once you kill your stomach glands you're
going to need adrenaline too
to help digest your food so then people
do this thing where they don't get it
but
once your stomach lands start getting
eaten up start getting eaten up and
weakened from apple cider vinegar eaten
up and weakened from caffeine once those
once a stomach lands the things that
make your gastric juices and your hcl
once they start weakening then you're
going to need more adrenaline to
try to digest food and try to get
peristaltic action
you're gonna need more adrenaline
so basically i guess the talk today
is information today the trendy stuff
that's happening in the health experts
in the biohackers today
are really promoting how to kill and
destroy your adrenals
which inevitably will shorten your life
make your life more miserable later on
and you'll never be able to connect the
dots
why is my hair falling out i'm a woman
it's not supposed to fall out why is it
happening
wait my hormones what my hormones are
all messed up
um let me go to another doctor it's
because you're adrenals
um huh i can't digest my food good
anymore
how come your adrenals stomach lands
and then you start getting sick with all
kinds of different conditions because
everybody's getting sick
everybody's getting sick so i'm making a
stir fry right here
everybody's getting sick everybody's
getting a symptom no one's escaping
that unless you know what to do and how
to heal but the health experts today and
the
biohackers they're just out to basically
rob and steal
theft and basically rape and pillage
your adrenal glands
all for what so they can still they can
do their caffeine and feel good about it
and i know look i'm all for yoga big
time i think it's i love it i think it's
great
but hot yoga just be cautious
you know just be cautious because
it's it's an adrenal surge you lose a
lot of adrenaline you weaken the adrenal
glands from doing it
but what do i know the hell do i know
right i mean millions of people getting
better
all around the world 35 years experience
teaching doctors
that information it heals
advanced information that's now that i
published first that science research is
stealing
um what do i know st mason says but i
would love it if
anthony could clarify on cold showers
cold showers are fine
it's just cold showers are fine i just
wouldn't um if you're okay
if you're struggling with a condition
you're not well
you got some fatigue cold showers aren't
great meaning
freezing cold showers where you shock
your body staying in there too long
like bringing your body temperature down
not a great thing okay
you don't want like ice cold do a cool
shower where you feel a little bit of
that shock right
just don't go ice cold don't be jumping
into
you know like the ice and and staying in
there too long because you're gonna be
on adrenaline
straight adrenaline when you're in the
shower right and you just flip it to
cold
and you're in the shower and you flip it
right to cold okay
and that hits you and you go like this
you're like
is the waters hitting you your adrenals
are flooding
that's what's happening they're going
crazy and you're getting adrenaline
surges adrenaline high
you don't want to do too much of it you
don't want to get let it get out of
control and if you got some health
issues of any kind
probably wouldn't do it at all
what's wrong with hot yoga i'll tell you
what's wrong what happens is when you're
pushing yourself in that kind of heat a
lot of studios keep it
really really hot on hot weather days
on top of it so outside of the studio
could be like a 90 degree day where
depending on where you are during the
summer or whatever it is
so it's already your body's already
elevating at a much higher temperature
your body's trying to cool itself
already
then you're going to do hot you go into
a hot yoga studio they got it cranked up
and you're sitting there for an hour
session sometimes hour and a half
session i've seen hot yoga sessions two
hours i've seen them
even less or whatever but what you're
doing is you're going into
hyperthermia so now you're go but but
your will your free will is making you
do it like i gotta do this i gotta push
through with everybody else to this hot
yoga
you can't stop me i gotta do it i gotta
show everybody i can do it too
so everybody's in there and everybody's
like and they're breathing and they're
doing their hot yoga
meanwhile your brain is saying you're
cooking me baby
you're cooking me so hey i need
adrenaline so now your
your adrenals are surging and purging
and purging by the end of that whole
session
you're high on adrenaline because your
brain almost cooked because you had to
use adrenaline
it's hard on the system then you end up
getting that
that adrenal fatigue hormone imbalance
imbalances later
you get if you're if you're young and
you're trying to have a baby
you're you're there's a good chance
you're going to have a difficult
childbirth
because you need all the adrenaline you
can to have a smooth
childbirth weak adrenals means difficult
child births
28 sarah holly 28 day cleanse heal the
adrenal glands
question mark i'm on day 22 and i feel
tired yes
very good meaning it's it's good so
you're you're
you're tired anyway is that the first
time you've ever been tired
or you're dealing with adrenal gland
issues and you're usually tired on and
off
so you just you know you're you're
working on healing
that's an incredible sarah an incredible
start and i'm proud of you
28 day cleanse you could do longer term
you can do it longer you can ask your
doctor too
how long your doctor wants you to be on
it if you feel for your health
healthcare practitioner and so forth but
the 28 day a lot of medical doctors know
about medical medium information
thousands of them across the country use
medical medium information the books and
everything in their practices
but but the 20-day cleanse is one aspect
but
looking at where your condition is like
say it's adrenal fatigue so
if you were diagnosed with adrenal
fatigue or do you have neurological
fatigue
too which is your nervous system being
affected by a little bit of epstein-barr
because adrenal fatigue is one thing but
you can have also
chronic fatigue which is neurological
fatigue
which means your fatigue for other
reasons besides your adrenals even
though the adrenals could be part of it
that's when it's important to have like
you know
like in here there's an adrenal section
in here shows supplements and protocols
and dosages
i mean you can talk to your practitioner
and show your practitioner's book in the
section in there and you can see there's
more you can do so not only can you do
the 28-day cleanse right not only can
you do the 28-day cleanse
but you can do supplements too and in
here i have them all listed in here too
supplements for the for the adrenals and
here and you can take a little bit at a
time and start
reinforcing your adrenals that way if
your fatigue persists
you might have some neurological fatigue
which is some chronic fatigue syndrome
from epstein barr
that's happening then you want to go
anti-viral which these books provide all
that information you can take them to
your doctor so forth and talk to them
about it
see you guys got the stir-fry here but
we're talking
about a lot of stuff so i'm going to
actually put this on a plate
so just letting you know here that
i'm gonna put i'm gonna plate this right
now probably not even showing you guys
[Music]
so that's the stir fry this is the sweet
and sour stir-fry it's a recipe
that you guys this is the first time i'm
showing this recipe the whole day
exhibiting it
this is in the medical medium book okay
the link is in
the description right there it's a
healing recipe it's got some red bell
peppers in there it's got the carrots
it's got the sweet and sour sauce in
there too it's
garlic ginger asparagus it's got some
brussels sprouts
that's the dish it's right here
so there it is i think mine
here versus mine that was made here when
i made this i think i chopped it a
little differently
but that's the recipe right there
listen you guys your body wants to know
you're in it with them your body wants
to know you're on the same page
your body is always up against what we
think
we should do or what we get told what we
should do out there
if we're told caffeine's okay our bodies
like its pants it's like wait a
minute
wait a minute you're going to dump all
that caffeine in me you're going to do
that to me what do you mean the
communication breakdown between your
actual body
and your free will and your will to do
things
you see what i'm talking about that's
where the problem is so
it's like that's why i kind of like it
pains me to see a little bit out there
when people are like so spiritually
connected and they're so they got their
health down so good and their intuition
so great but their bodies like
freaking out saying why are you killing
me man
why are you killing my adrenals who told
you to eat a chocolate bar every single
day
90 child who told you to eat cacao nibs
every single day like that
good or something with all that caffeine
your adrenals are just getting toasted
it's like who told you to go into a
sauna for too long
with such a high heat like who told you
to jump into ice and
and freeze yourself to hyperthermia
level to your adrenals freak out who
told you to go into a
yoga studio with the heat being at 105
degrees
on a 100 degree day outside during the
summer time with your body going into
total hyperthermia like who told you so
your adrenals have to clean up all the
mess your body
your body is just like freaking out and
it needs those adrenal reserves for the
long haul who told you to intermittent
fast what it was some brainiac idea from
somebody to make sure you're jacked up
on caffeine all day and no food
and then you eat a high fat meal at the
end of the day which also kills your
adrenals
it's never ending throw in a whole bunch
of other stuff too
and then while you're intermittent fast
and then have chocolate at the end of
the night like two on top of it
so maybe even chocolate ice cream you
intermittent fast all day long and then
boom you have your big fatty meal at the
end of the day and then you have some
chocolate or something else or maybe
some weed
so now you know some weed at the end of
the day smoking weed
i'm not judging anybody people do all
kinds of stuff
i'm just saying our body what it wants
to do
could be a lot different than what we
want to do you know
like our body might be thinking a lot
different than
what we're thinking right heather says
that's a crazy diet
our body's thinking differently you see
what i mean so
think about that so i mean
and that's the other thing but there's
all these biohackers every day out there
now
health enthusiasts and influencers and
health experts and
whatever you want to call everybody now
and they got big ideas and it's the same
old crap everybody else is selling and
it's the same old
that everybody else is selling and it's
the same old stuff it's called kill your
adrenals
seven ways to sunday that's what it is
like kill your adrenals seven ways to
sunday that's it
that's what it is and
that's what's going on out there you can
intermittent fast your adrenals to death
you can caffeine your adrenals of death
you can break down your stomach glands
you can do the apple cider vinegar all
the time too and make sure you dissolve
your teeth
and then no one cares about getting the
toxic heavy metals out because what you
can't see you don't know was there so no
one cares about the toxic heavy metals
and those are in there causing wreaking
havoc left and right
causing people's depression and anxiety
and bipolar and depersonalization and
ocd
and but everybody's too busy just trying
to rob and steal and theft everybody's
adrenaline
and vampire the hell out of their
adrenals and kill them faster
and making sure that young women have
really difficult second child births or
first child births or third ones where
it's epic disaster because their
adrenals are saying
dear god i just did 10 years of caffeine
and 10 years of all this other stuff
and no one protected me and told me
about it and now i'm just crapping out
while i'm trying to have a baby
and that's what the adrenals that's what
they do and that's why some women will
be in labor for two days because their
adrenals can't cut the mustard
because they've been doing caffeine for
the last five years
six seven years and every and these
podcast doctors are sitting on the
podcast they'll be like much
tea is good for you yeah i drink it
every day oh it's got antioxidants every
woman should be drinking their caffeine
every single day
and that's how it works but like i said
what do i know right
you know what do i know it's a you know
it's
it's funny because it's like
the key is let's just be all straight
out and honest about it
let's just be open about stuff
and let's see the reality of it see
let's
i'm tired of hearing people say they're
going to speak their truth or they're
speaking their truth or
truth truth or whatever it is and it's
not really truth
i just like to do real truth that's what
i like to do like real truth
and there's a difference between real
truth and bs
truth or fake truth there's a big
difference
and yeah i'm the only one going against
the caffeine industry
right now pretty much yeah i'm the only
one
telling it like it is about all this
other stuff but
isn't it about like making sure that
you're protected
you're safe your life gets better you
know the truth
you can make the choice to heal when
given the knowledge
isn't it about making sure that your
life is precious and everything in your
life and everything you do
matters i don't want that robbed or
stolen from you
or ripped off from you i don't want that
taken from you
you know what i mean like why would i
want that it's like
and be cautious
be cautious look out
renata says what's hard to convince
people to listen to this info
what's hard is to convince people to
listen to this info
it's heartbreaking how stubborn some
people can be i was told today
just chill out nutritional yeast
tomatoes
so just chill about nutritional yeast
have msg too nutritional yeast
it can make or break somebody's healing
process i just want you guys to know
that
it can um it's highly toxic
and what nutritional yeast does it
interferes with the brain chemistry
it interferes with electricity in the
brain neurotransmitters in the brain
it's one thing what nutritional yeast
does
another thing nutritional yeast does is
it weakens the immune system it doesn't
build the immune system
so if you got fibrocfs eczema psoriasis
depression anxiety
whatever you got going on utis bladder
infections kidney infections
whatever you got acne yeah acne
your immune system lowers down and you
get acne every time your immune system
lowers you get acne
tomatoes don't have msg by the way but
anyway all
what happens is that nutritional yeast
can make or break your finish line
your healing to the end your finish line
maybe
you don't have any issues you're eating
it all day long because you got nothing
yet
everybody is going to get sick who isn't
sick now
that's where we're heading everybody
gets something
everybody gets something and some get
many get much
more than just something um
people who aren't sick will spout out
where's your study
they don't want to know like your track
record of how many people healed in the
world doing your info
or they don't want to know what celery
juice does for people and why it's the
biggest
the biggest out there as far as how many
people are doing
it there's no trend or anything else
that overrides it but you know why you
don't hear about it every minute celery
juice even though everybody's doing it
500 million people in the world are
doing it right now the reason why i
don't hear about it
because it makes no one money it makes
nobody money
and all the other crap makes people
money collagen
coffee caffeine whatever it is makes
people tons of money right
so because it makes them all money you
hear about it every minute
every single minute um
so yeah so people who aren't sick
they'll they'll be spouting out like
they haven't figured out that science
doesn't have the answers yet
if you're sick did a scientific study
fix your fibromyalgia i'm just curious
did it fix your trigeminal neuralgia
did it fix your ra did a scientific
study fix anything
did it fix something that you got
kind of curious right are you still sick
do you still get bouts of it are you
still
dealing with something because there's
no science study
that has ever fixed somebody's eczema or
psoriasis
ever got it better ever
think about that just think about that
for two seconds
like oh my god but you'll hear a bunch
of people who aren't really that sick
yet or maybe they're just
a little mentally sick but they're not
they got other problems meaning like
they're
struggling with some kind of hardship
mentally and emotionally maybe there's
somebody that
you know maybe there's somebody that
doesn't have physical symptoms
really but they have a lot of emotional
turmoil
and they don't know what it's like to
physically hurt physically
suffer physically be weak and sick
physically have
ailments and pain and teeth killing them
and on
opioids because they can't even chew and
they don't know what that's like
you know it's a whole nother game
um brenda says brenda king says i want
to know how to reverse thinning hair
cleanse the heel is a great place
start right here so cleanse the heel
there's a hair thinning protocol in here
the whole bit
look into it bring it to your doctor if
you need to get it free at the library
if you can't afford the book the book's
inexpensive it's on sale on amazon.com
right now
16.99 but if you can't afford it because
i know a lot of people can't afford even
sixteen dollars right now
um or hard times just get it free at the
library if you can okay
i mean i just want you to have it and
that's all that matters
it's all that matters free free free
opinion on collagen yeah you can't eat
collagen to fix collagen you can't eat
collagen to create collagen you can't
eat a sheep's eyeball to fix your
eyeball you can't eat a human eyeball
to fix your eyeball you can't eat kidney
to fix your kidney can't eat liver to
fix your liver
you can't eat brain to fix your brain
you can't eat a cow's brain to fix your
brain you can't eat a human brain to
fix your brain it doesn't work what's
really disturbing about the collagen
thing
it's such a psych out for people it
really insults people in a way that's
unbelievable
how dare you think you can eat something
to actually fix something but eat that
very thing
it doesn't happen it doesn't exist it'll
never happen
you can't eat brain to heal your brain
bottom line and that's something to
remember
you have to eat other foods to build
your collagen you have to create
collagen through using foods that create
that actually help you build collagen
the process in your body to create
collagen
comes from leafy greens it comes from
fruits it comes from these foods here
these healing foods asparagus it comes
from these healing foods
that's where it comes from it's so
insulting to trick people out
maybe the system thinks people are so
dumb or something out there maybe
the evil system that just you know banks
trillions of dollars on stupid ideas
thinks people are that gullible and that
stupid i don't know how how it happens
um maria says laugh out loud i healed
six symptoms with you
before you i spent thousands of dollars
to see naturopathic doctors and spent so
much on tests
and they never helped maria thank you
for being here i'm proud of you for all
the work you've done
um my heart goes out to you and go
through all these symptoms the same with
anybody there you guys if you're
struggling symptoms
um there's pressing prints you're here
today
i see that um
margaret valentine you're here today
amazing
yeah i mean that caffeine can age you
quick it really can
that's what does the wrinkles faster
it's why that's why everybody's running
to get botox that's why everybody's
running to get teeth implants and
veneers it's why everybody's running
into
you see all the guy doctors out there
like the guy the guy doctors that are in
the public eye none of their teeth are
real
they're all like replaced um they burned
out their teeth
reserves a long time ago with vinegar
and caffeine and coffee
and so when they're 50 years old they
got no no real teeth at all they got all
these implants and they got veneers and
they're shining sparkling teeth when
they're doing their interviews and
podcasts and everything and they don't
got any of the real teeth but they'll
tell everybody to keep on drinking
caffeine and take your apple cider
vinegar so you can lose all your teeth
anyway
um
you guys i'm heading over to ig are you
coming
are you guys coming over ig and tick
tock i'm going to do ig and tick tock at
the same time
um probably like 15 minutes i just got
to get the kitchen ready just give me a
chance to get the kitchen ready you guys
i want you guys to come over come on
because i might be talking about some
other stuff
i don't know all right
uh god bless you thank you for being
here today
laura i just saw that laura how to help
with ms
ms epstein bar virus causes multiple
sclerosis
um and toxic heavy metal combined so
it's epstein-barr toxic heavy metals i
put that information out there
years ago um take the book to your
doctor
your health care provider your doctor
have him take a look
okay this is the cleanse to heal and
then there's
um if you want you can just wait for
this to come out pretty soon it's coming
out actually
really soon i don't know if it's a few
weeks but it's coming up
and the link is in the description whole
multiple sclerosis chapter in here you
can take it to your doctor
thousands of women and men took this
book
original book this is the new edition
got to keep that in mind the new edition
they took the original book to doctors
when they had multiple sclerosis
and it helped them recover
nina says just found out my daughter and
i have the mt
mthfr gene mutation our metabolism is
one slow any ideas what diet we can eat
nina i don't have time right now to
actually go through the whole mthfr
the whole mthfr mess up that's out there
um maybe i'll do a podcast on it medical
medium podcast at apple podcast
so i'll do it i'll do a gene mutation um
podcast on there my book liver rescue
has a whole bunch of information on it
okay cleanse the heal has information on
it just letting you know
about about the gene mutation so if you
want to learn the truth about it
it's it's it's a lot of intense
information um
but it's there and and what to do take
it to your doctor have them have them
take a look at it so they can learn the
truth about mthfr
uh it's not exactly what they think or
how it works out there it's much
different um anyway
i love you guys i'm heading out to ig in
about 15 minutes i got to clean up the
kitchen
get some food prep going i'm going to
make some food again
tik tok and ig at the same time love you
guys
bless you take care