how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about food Wars
both sides of the food Wars are
brainwashed meanwhile they're all still
getting sick no matter what food belief
system someone belongs to whether
plant-based or animal-based or even
everything in moderation they use
science to attack anyone who doesn't
share their belief system everybody's
fighting both sides are at War and their
eye isn't on the ball about what creates
chronic
illness as soon as vegans or people
eating plant-based get sick they tend to
run back to animal Foods when people on
already animal base diets get sick most
of them tend to stay with animal foods
and keep searching searching and
searching for other reasons they could
be sick or suffering there are not a lot
of vegan families and plant-based
families where the children are born and
bred vegan and stay that way nearly
everybody is raised on animal protein
diets nearly everybody on this planet is
raised on animal protein in some shape
fashion or form and now that's why most
people who go plant-based or vegan and
they get sick they end up running back
to animal protein they go back to their
roots to where they came from they get
scared they get scared into it by
practitioners doctors and family members
they get scared into it by themselves
they start thinking I'm lacking
something they start thinking they're
missing something something they get
from animal protein something they get
from some kind of animal product and it
must be the answer to why they're sick
even though they came from animal
products that was their diet originally
they were born and raised on it and
after they went vegan for a little while
they're still sick or they're getting
sick they run back and they're like I
must be missing something maybe I should
start eating liver now and then they see
something on social they see a video
they see some material they read out
there and it says they should be on beef
Hearts that's where the nutrients are so
they get really confused and now they're
searching for the best beef Hearts they
can find one of the interesting things
is both sides the animal-based and
plant-based believe that protein is the
answer for everything so when anything
goes wrong or any kind of Health
struggle at all happens or any kind of
deficiency they see in their blood work
when they're at the doctor's office they
instantly think protein and their
practitioners and doctors Healthcare
Providers say protein too so they think
protein is the an answer for everything
this partly comes from people being
raised on animal protein just the word
itself protein vegans and plant-based
people won't adopt this way of eating
unless someone convinces them in a
confident manner that there's protein to
be had that there's protein in a
plant-based diet which there is but both
animal-based and plant-based folks are
brainwashed to think it's all about
protein because protein protein sounds
scientific both sides have to feel like
their diet belief system no matter what
kind of name it has no matter how fancy
it is that it's science-based and you
can get enough protein both sides are
also conditioned and brainwashed for
confrontation they get into a
fight I got my money on Old
Nessie who you got your money on Albert
I got Alber is going to win I got my
whoa no get get back in the pen no
there's still
fighting before plant-based people
revert back to eating animal protein
diets they got to fight in them first
they fight back plant-based folks don't
just look at animal-based folks and say
hey look we're all sick instead each of
them get their weapons out they find
their weapons of choice in the form of
studies research papers both the
committed animal protein people and the
committed plant-based and vegan people
call themselves researchers now they're
all researchers they spend a lot of time
on the internet looking around for
information they throw articles at each
other's faces articles that they feel
are based on science they say this keto
study says when it isn't even a real
study it's just a survey or a uniformed
observation or Theory theoretical paper
put together by somebody or anybody in
health with limited experience on the
issues or the subject and if they do
reference an actual clinical study how
reputable was it who funded it was it
based on a handful of paid participants
from the same age and background
monitored over a very short time span
leading to gross generalizations and
misinformation where was the study study
done was it even done the reality the
bottom line is that both sides are
brainwashed they're brainwashed that
they can trust the science behind their
diet they're brainwashed that protein is
everything they're brainwashed to
confront each other and fight each other
both sides of the food Wars are
brainwashed that intermittent fasting is
healthy both sides are brainwashed that
caffeine is good that adding quality
salt to food is good that apple cider
vinegar is good does that ring a bell to
anyone both sides are brainwashed that
you can fix all your problems through
breathing techniques or through
manifesting both sides are brainwashed
that chocolate is plant medicine that
it's good for you both are brainwashed
that they don't create any waste with
their food decisions and diets this is a
good one right here both are brainwashed
that they're diet belief systems are
sustainable and are all about
sustainability both sides are
conditioned to run to the conventional
doctor for antibiotics the moment they
get sick both sides are brainwashed to
believe that autoimmune symptoms a
result of the body attacking itself
here's another good one both sides are
brainwashed to believe that their genes
dictate why they're sick here's another
both sides are brainwashed to be afraid
of fruit so much so that even if they do
start believing fruit is okay to eat a
little more fruit each day all it could
take is one whistle from a food Brigade
that sends them right back into Fruit
fear once again here's one of my
favorites both sides have B12 iron and
calcium deficiencies while both sides
are brainwashed to believe that only
plant-based and vegan people are at risk
of these deficiencies not the animal-
based people both sides are worried
about vitamin D deficiency both sides
are vitamin D deficient and both sides
believe vitamin D Mega doses are the
answer both sides believe in fermented
foods both sides believe that all your
problems stem from your gut and both
sides believe that the brain is made of
fat and you need fat in your brain to
survive this is a great one right here
both sides believe their blood tests are
all accurate here's one for the record
books both sides unknowingly get too
much blood drawn when they get a blood
test both sides believe that a diet of
processed foods mad eating habits and
fried and greasy Foods was the sole
cause of any symptoms before they Chang
their diet when really there's much more
to it this is an interesting one both
sides believe their food choices now
make them spiritually
enlightened and my favorite both sides
believe they're very much different from
the other side that they're opposites
when they're not the funny thing is they
are the same side the same belief system
they shop at the same markets to get
their food and the only difference is
that one eats meat and one doesn't still
the battle each other they fight each
other they face off against each other
and both sides use flawed science fake
science underdeveloped science and
broken science to back up their
positions Animal product science doesn't
believe in plant-based science
plant-based science doesn't believe in
Animal product science these science
entities are against each other and the
conventional mainstream Medical Science
entity does not support any of the
sciences that either plant-based or
animal-based Believers are projecting I
could just hear it now I know people are
going to be like no that's not true I
believe in science and my science is
good and big science believes in my
little science and my science is more
important than the plant-based science
and plant-based people are going to be
like no my science is more important
than your science that's a science to
believe in you don't need to eat meat
and then the meat eater is like you need
eat meat and but yet they're all the
same on top of everything food War
Battlers go for the emotional side vegan
and plant-based Believers tell Animal
product Believers that they're killing
animals destroying rainforests clueless
that animals have souls and making their
children eat dead
animals Animal product Believers tell
vegan and plant-based Believers they're
causing malnutrition in their babies and
children starving them of protein not
preparing them for quote real life and
keeping them away from
moderation no matter what food belief
system someone belongs to whether
plant-based or animal- based or even
everything in moderation they use
science to attack anyone who doesn't
share their belief system that any group
can find Science and data to back up
their position that science hands out
the weapons to both sides of the battle
should make us question that very War
meanwhile this whole time everybody's
fighting both sides are at War and their
eye isn't on the ball about what creates
chronic
illness when a person or a person's
child gets sideswiped or blindsided by
health
challenges and medical science and
research doesn't have an answer and
can't understand why they're sick
whatever belief system they've consume
themselves with starts to break apart
whatever diet whatever diet belief
system whatever Trend whatever they
believed in that science backed or
alternative science backed it all just
Falls to
Pieces it doesn't matter what study what
research paper what trend they first
believed in it doesn't matter what study
that convinced them to go a certain way
it doesn't matter what podcast doctor
doesn't matter what book they read that
seemed like it was backed up and
supported by science it all just starts
to fade away because when they get
chronically sick and there's no answers
it all falls apart when someone gets hit
with neurological Lyme multiple
sclerosis chronic fatigue syndrome or
they're dealing with some form of
anxiety that's crippling them depression
they got the worst brain fog they can't
function they can't be productive
they're struggling or they got bad bad
bad digestive problems they're
constipated they're bloated they're in
pain or they have vertigo and dizziness
where they feel like they're on a boat
and they're rocking back and forth or
they're just vomiting because they have
vertigo or they got tingles and numbness
bad migraines where they can't live
their life because the migraines ADHD or
OCD crippling
OCD autoimmune or eating disorders when
those things start to disrupt their life
any doubts someone has had in the back
of their mind about a plant-based diet
or veganism starts to grow like
weeds the doubts usually take over fast
and once again that person goes into the
Land of the
Lost they go searching all over again
just like they were when they first
started searching at the beginning
looking for a direction and making a
decision to go vegan and plant-based
from the beginning some still hold on
they hold on to plant-base and veganism
beliefs and they fight for a little
while in that lost land while they're
sick they'll see their functional
medicine doctor or their plant-based
naturopath and they'll fight for it
until a family member or friend ignites
that tiny doubt that was in their head
and the doubt grows and grows into a
mean
nasty monster they defect they change
your diet belief system and poof unless
someone finds medical medium
information they don't know why they're
sick so they believe it's caused by
their diet it's not just a rookie thing
in health to believe that diet is why
you're sick it's an entrenched
conditioning an entrenched belief system
among long-term diet Believers too
people who commit MIT to their diet
belief systems believe that their diets
beforehand were the sole reason for any
symptoms they experienced instead of
understanding pathogens heavy metals and
chemical exposure as the source of their
symptoms foundational landmarks of
medical medium
information part of the brainwashing
mechanism that's out there is when
symptoms arise and come up as they're
already following a a belief system if
it's plant-based they'll fall through
the trapo of believing they got sick
from the lack of animal products if they
get sick on an animal-based diet on the
other hand they won't blame their diet
totally they'll be more apt to blame
factors like stress or unhappiness
they'll be more afraid of fruit than
ever before they'll feel like maybe
there's a spiritual or genetic reason
why they're sick each side plant based
and animal-based has its underbelly
exposed plant-based Believers are more
susceptible to getting slammed about
deficiencies because they've long been
fed doubt about whether a plant-based
diet offers them all the nutrition they
need both sides are susceptible to fear
both sides get sick with the same types
of symptoms and
conditions once they become sick both
plant-based and animal-based believers
start worrying about the
microbiome bacterial overgrowth in the
gut metabolism issues nutrient
deficiencies candida leaky gut fructose
intolerance histamine problems food
allergies oxalates gene mutations
autoimmune or whether they're exercising
enough they're clones of themselves it's
a constant revolving door of trying to
get improvements from mixing and
matching flip-flopping guessing games
try this try that eat this differently
eat that differently but yet eat this a
little differently than that it's a game
that occupies you while your body is
fighting for temporary results and
fighting for its life temporary
improvements and temporary relief come
for some people but it's back into the
game again the guessing games they don't
stop some practices can be supportive
some not you can't be sure which or
which because you can't read the signs
and symptoms that your body's providing
you because whether you believe in
plant-based or animal-based you don't
know why you're really sick the game
could go on for so long and go on and on
and on it could go on forever in a
person's life 10 20 50 years until they
can finally find a way
out healing from a symptom condition or
disease isn't about choosing sides it
isn't just about going plant-based or
animal based or everything in
moderation recovery isn't going to be
Reliant upon a scientific study we may
have that
illusion in the end healing is about
understanding that we've been tricked
all along the way duped the wool has
been pulled over our eyes we've been
bamboozled healing is about learning
that all sides are continually
fold once you learn why you truly became
ill opportunity opens up the light does
appear at the end of the tunnel and
health freedom is
possible original published medical
medium information gets stolen and
poached by podcast doctors social media
doctors influencers and medical clinics
medical medium information has never yet
been proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion