this is the book right here i got my
copy
medical medium secrets behind chronic
and mystery illness and how to
finally heal and the first edition
millions have healed this is the new
edition
right here in my hands i'm beyond pumped
beyond excited this is a special day for
me because i know how many people are
going to heal in the future i'm really
excited i'm going to talk a little bit
about it but i'm making
also the spinach soup which is a recipe
from the original medical medium book
but a recipe that's powerful that's
helping people heal around the world i'm
really excited about it
but this is it the revised and expanded
medical medium
go to amazon.com barnes and noble um
you know yeah it's in target coming up
soon too so whatever you guys can find
in different places
uh i'm really excited valerie can't wait
to get
the new book i mean i couldn't believe
when i got this
this is a really it's a heavy book the
one thing about medical medium books
they're so packed with information that
they're
they're heavy so yeah that that's true
they are heavy because it's a real book
it's not a joke like a lot of books out
there in health
they're just there there's no meat to
the bones you know what i mean there's
no meat i just opened it up i went right
to the gut health chapter right here
this incredible gut health chapter i
just opened it up to
and um that's the gut health chapter
right there
sure if you guys can see it i'm not sure
if it's whiting out right there
but i'm really pumped out i'm really
pumped up about this i can't say enough
and i'm gonna make the spinach soup too
um too heavy to hold michelle
i mean they're medical medium books are
heavy
dr faun md you're excited about the new
book
oh wow that's really funny
um yeah so i can't wait so i'm gonna
talk about a few things inside here
uh i'm on day six of celery juice kelly
says
proud of you amazing day six of celery
juice
my juicer is over in the corner i don't
know if you see it over there in the
corner right there i haven't cleaned it
yet
it's still got it's still got pulp in
the machine
um and see veronica i'm sharing a recipe
by the way yes
the spinach soup recipe you see my
blender right here
you guys see my tomatoes okay you see my
cherry tomatoes here too
teresa i never thought i would like the
spinach soup recipe but it's delicious
it's it's my favorite like i'm gonna
make it that's my dinner
right there so let me read you guys a
quote right here and i'm going to answer
questions too along the way too
so there's a quote right in the
beginning of the book when i open it
right there
see my little postage note they're
starting the postage notes
whether you come to this elevated and
expanded edition of medical medium as a
new reader
or as a seasoned follower of the book
series
know this there's already a track record
of established there's already a track
record established
of the power of healing this book has
provided
people from around the world who've
tried everything
medical research and science had to
offer have found this information to be
a sanctuary
they found that it has allowed them to
rise out of the ashes
and when this book came out okay the
first edition
there was very little information out
there for the chronicle for anybody with
fibro anybody
with chronic fatigue lyme disease gut
problems
there was really very little information
out there this was that sanctuary that
came out right
and the new edition is packed with more
information so you don't want to
miss out on this but when this book came
out
it exploded the truth about
the epstein-barr virus and what it
causes so if you're somebody dealing
with hashimoto's thyroiditis
hyperthyroidism graves
hypothyroidism that's epstein-barr that
causes it if you're somebody dealing
with
rheumatoid arthritis or fibromyalgia
chronic fatigue syndrome amne or
cfs or plain old cfs or however you're
feeling
that's the epstein-barr virus and that's
just some things right there and
so i broke the truth about epstein-barr
out there and it has saved millions of
lives around the world
it's the most popular book series in
health
globally for going on close seven years
now
and this book right here broke the truth
about epstein-barr and why does that
matter
like who cares you know who cares about
breaking the truth about epstein-barr
out there like
why should it even matter because
because it gave
people the answers of why they were sick
that didn't exist before the mm
information
everybody was on the merry-go-round and
chasing phantom ghosts for answers like
chasing theories and chasing all that
guessing games everybody was running
around the musical chairs
and so millions of women around the
world and they're still doing it that
don't know the medical medium
information
they're doing the musical chair route
where they're like okay this doctor here
and then this neurologist here or what's
my
ringing in my ears and my dizziness and
my body pain
and my burning skin and and my tics and
spasms and
and that's just a few things and nobody
knew like
what was the cause what what's going on
why do i have a problem with my thyroid
and
and all that sherry says couldn't put
the first edition down
when i first read it i'm sure this will
blow minds and hearts
of all that receive it it sherry this is
you know i'll tell you dr sherry green
thank you for being here
this is amazing this book is really
really special
and you know before the truth came out
about epstein-barr everybody
thought epstein-barr was the kissing
disease where
you caught mono and then it went away
and then it was gone
never to come back again never to cause
a problem
it it and that's what best of science
thought
all the doctors thought that science of
research thought that
they just thought that you caught mono
and then
it disappeared and you were better and
you would never have to worry about
anything ever again
the whole reason anybody's talking about
reactivation of epstein-barr
right now today is because of the
original book here
and that's how incredible that is so now
out there
you'll hear out there reactivation of
epstein-barr
and you'll hear that and that's from
this book no one in science or research
no one anywhere no doctors knew
epstein-barr
caused an aftermath problems
later on which lead to lyme disease
so this book brought that truth
to light and the thing is
is that epstein-barr causes symptoms
later on
so you get your mono whether you know
it's mono or not
or if it was diagnosed of mono or not
you get it
it goes away and then it comes
back on a rainy day and it comes back
with some vertigo
some dizziness some focus and
concentration issues a little bit of
anxiety
sometimes some depression migraines it
comes
back with all these different conditions
and symptoms
and everybody then goes looking for
answers and they're spending thousands
of dollars and they go to
alternative doctors of all kinds right
and they go to
every kind there is and they look for
answers and they don't find
them this book has changed the world
with this and it's so
it's so special science of research just
started talking about
epstein-barr now being linked to
hashimoto's
ra and fibromyalgia and lyme disease and
that's because science research follows
the lead
of the medical medium books so
i love when i hear out there someone say
where's your scientific evidence
well that's funny because science
research they take the medical medium
information and they use it later so i'm
the source for science research and
chronic illness
it's the medical medium books and that's
where they get their information
so i am the source for science and
research
include that involves lyme disease
science research for hashimoto's science
research for fibro
for all these things because it stems
from the original publication of the
medical medium book which was published
before
medical research and science even
started spouting out that fc bar has
anything to do with anything
so it's really exciting so you guys the
book is packed
it's a thick book it's a heavy book for
a reason
get ready to get mind blown when you get
into this book i'm going to talk about a
little bit about it i'm going to talk
about triggers today
so i know you guys are up against
triggers
and i do want to talk about triggers to
lyme disease triggers to other things
too
um other conditions and in this book
i talk about the plague we're up against
right now of why everybody's in lockdown
where everybody's going around with
masks on i talk about
that plague in the medical medium book
which is really cool
it's got way more information than even
cleanse to heal for specific
conditions for specific conditions so
this book is that pact
um and look i i can't cover what's in
this book
in one moment right here it's not
possible it's
that there's that much but i'm gonna
make the spinach soup i'm gonna talk
about lyme disease i'm going to talk
about triggers to chronic illness
this is going to be interesting i'm glad
you guys are on there
i saw lorraine l's on there um paige is
on there great to be on there
great great you're here incredible um
and yeah i'm glad everybody's coming on
here it's so important
so spinach soup is a powerful healing
tool i'm gonna start making a little bit
of it just
start giving you some at least the
ingredient ingredient so forth and how
it works i'm gonna put the book down for
a second
and um you know you guys the more and
more
trendy stuff i see out there that's bad
for us
um causing people to stay sick it's just
so disheartening i mean i can't believe
people are still talking about colostrum
they still think collagen is helpful i
mean these are things that are not
um
donna says i didn't know i was infected
by ebv before i read the book
then i did a lab for ebv
and igg yep and found that i had lots of
antibodies
i have graves and all the doctors told
me that
my autoimmune disease was caused by my
immune system going crazy and
donna what happens is that's what they
do they'll they'll blame it on your body
attacking itself they'll say that your
immune system is
attacking the organs and the the amazing
thing about this book is
i release the truth that that's not
accurate that the body
does not go against itself because the
minute you take that into your
consciousness
the minute it's all blamed on
you and your body it can go even more
wrong because
all of a sudden you're sick why am i
sick why do i have a condition
and now you get told by medical research
and science that tells doctors
that your immune system went haywire and
it's attacking your
organs and your glands and
that's not accurate that's not what
happens instead
it's about the epstein-barr virus that's
causing the inflammation
and your immune system's protecting you
and not causing a problem at all
it's there to protect you it's there to
look out for you
and this is this is the
the problems that happen out there where
people just they're
they get told that their body's
destroying itself they get told that
their bodies against them
and that's really disheartening very
damaging
doesn't allow the body to heal doesn't
allow us to move forward
doesn't allow us to get past their
illnesses because once we consciously
take that in
it's like wow my body's killing itself
hey
my body's hurting itself so there's no
way to fix this
uh what's the other answer it's genes
and
or maybe i'm thinking myself sick maybe
i'm creating it so that's the next thing
that occurs that's all wrong
right and your body is so beyond
intelligent
your body is that unconditionally loves
you
your body knows what's going on your
body doesn't attack
itself there's a real problem to why
we're sick
and that information i released in
medical medium book one to start with
years ago this is the new addition if
you guys just came on it just came out
i mean it's out in probably i don't know
four or five days or six days now so
it's the amazon.com has it
um barnes noble has it but i got my copy
i just got my copy all right and you
know i think i saw somebody online that
had a copy or an early copy they must
have got it from their local bookstore
and they had a copy before i did which
was really funny i laughed so hard
and um it's like i don't even have a
copy and they had a copy first
and uh that was so great to see that
that made me so happy
so anyway you guys um you go to your
local bookstore too okay
so educating myself good to see you
the tattoo truth bomb was awesome
you know you guys that you want to say
this one thing about that the tattoo
thing
in order for the ink to actually show up
and pop like show up and make a good
tattoo
all right they have to put toxic heavy
metals inside the ink
all right so wherever the ink is if you
want to get that scripture on the side
of your ribs or
wherever you get your ink you want to
get the butterflies on your ankles
whatever you're doing
wherever that ink is it has to be filled
with toxic heavy metals in order to
reflect light to come through the skin
so you can see it really well so that's
how it's done
so the light shines on the tattoo the
ink
underneath the skin reflects off the
toxic heavy metals
even the best vegan ink the best cruelty
free ink the best steriling the best
non-toxic ink whatever they say
there's metals in it so that the light
when it hits your skin if you get a
tattoo on your hand it hits the skin
it goes into it the light then reflects
off of the ink and pops back and that
because if they didn't put toxic heavy
metals in
ink you wouldn't see your ink it would
turn into a blob
literally a blob and that's why ink
fades throughout the years because the
metals leach down and they
drop deeper into the derma and the metal
stop having that reflection ability and
i didn't even say that part when i was
talking about the tattoos
i didn't even say that part that the ink
as it settles
deeper into the derma and then goes into
the bloodstream the metals
go into the bloodstream you lose the it
fades the reason why it's fading is
because the metals are
leaving the ink so so then this so that
so the light doesn't reflect so strong
and i didn't even say that part i was i
was
i was bummed out i didn't tell you guys
about that part too because it's such
good information
but um the point is don't get rid of
your ink and tattoos don't do that just
do the
you know do what i tell my friends and
family if you want ask your doctor if
it's right for you
do the heavy metal detox smoothie and i
talked about that here's the spirulina
and the barley grass you guys know i
talk about that
the you know and that's what i would do
i tell my friends and family
joni just bought it on amazon for lime
best
lyme disease uh book
there is hands down it's changed the
course of lime i want to talk about that
a little bit of
what it's done kim says i have all your
books i'm honored
kim thanks for like being on here and
thanks for for
for uh commenting so anyway
i'm gonna go into lyme disease in a
little bit so let me just cover up
steambar
um incredible
glad you guys are coming on so look i'm
gonna pop a little
spinach in here too
maybe some tomatoes as well you can make
your spinach soup
i just want to at least start this a
little bit
30 years ago i got ebv then set a
megalovirus i talk about cytomegalovirus
diagnosed with cfs meniere's meniere's
which is vertigo
diverticulitis i see and finally
chf i'm exhausted and need help
sandy i completely understand and that's
that's that's what millions of women
when they discovered the medical medium
books and discovered this first book
here they were in that situation and
they needed to learn about the epstein
barr
they needed to learn how to learn how it
worked and they needed to learn some of
the foods
and if you guys can't get the book right
now on amazon.com like you can't buy it
maybe you know because you don't have
any money
or whatever just wait for the book to
come out for a while right and go to the
library
and ask for it or go straight to your
library and ask for it
so that they get a copy or something
like that or
so where people drop off their old
copies to the library
they'll they'll buy some extra copies
and they should deliver that's what we
do we'll
you know get copies and bring them to
libraries
anyway so let's go into this a little
bit i'm just going to pop a couple of
tomatoes in here
just to start with and we'll talk about
epstein-barr and talk about
stuff that's in the book so powerful
information
so i'm putting putting some tomatoes in
here because this is the spinach soup
you can do cherry tomatoes which i have
right here but
i'm in the mood for some of these these
beautiful tomatoes so i'm popping these
in here
do another one okay
so
so there are over 60 varieties of
epstein-barr i talk about it in medical
medium
secrets and i talk about how these are
mutations of the virus
as the years go by these the viruses do
different things
some viruses cause a little bit more
fibromyalgia some cause hashimoto's
thyroiditis
and different levels and they're
different aggressions of the virus
okay and that's what makes this all
different really what kind of virus do
you have do you have
you know epstein-barr which variety do
you have
how long have you had it you know you
know and these are the things that make
a big difference how many toxic heavy
metals do you have
um you know how many toxins overall
how's your liver the condition of your
liver all these things matter
and with epstein-barr what it likes to
do is it likes to start out
by incubating or going
dormant in the liver but epstein-barr
never really just goes dormant it lives
in us
and stays alive as our immune system
keeps it in check
and then we get triggers along the way
that become the triggers for the epstein
bar that's sitting inside of us
so like heartache betrayal
broken trust broken promises
these things hurt us really bad
emotional
abuse emotional hardship of any kind
all those are triggers so there's a lot
of emotional triggers from what we go
through hard times
and then we go into fight or flight and
our adrenaline is pumping and our immune
system drops
divorces breakups and relationships
and and then also we pick up epstein
bars people
pass around epstein bars in all kinds of
relationships because that's just normal
that's life it's like you get into a new
relationship and then
you got somebody else's epstein bar who
also had somebody else's epstein bar and
somebody else's epstein bar and said now
i've seen bars are like
they travel that way you know they can
travel in restaurants you go into
restaurants and you're
eating food in restaurants epstein bar
travels to restaurant food is probably
one of the big ways it travels
public bathrooms it can travel that way
and so
the whole population has an epstein-barr
r2
so that's the other thing so we all have
ebv in our system and that's just
the fact of life here the way of life
here in on planet earth and then but
that's okay
because when you know what to do to take
care of yourself and you know how to
stop it from causing problems you know
how to fix it when you have a problem
that's what matters it's it's not about
the fact that we pick
epstein-barr up easy whether it's a new
relationship
a new friendship um you know some
restaurant food somewhere from a chef
cutting their finger or
sweat dripping off a chef's you know
forehead and dropping it right on your
salad
which is really an easy way to pass ebv
um either way when we pick up new
varieties
and then they're in our system and then
they become a problem
later on we can do something about it
and that's the whole point
even if we didn't get fibro yet or
eczema yet or psoriasis
or we didn't get another condition lyme
disease or we didn't get cfs or focusing
concentration issues or something or
dizziness or
some kind of mysterious symptom even if
we didn't go
there yet we can take care of ourselves
and we can clean abv up out of our
system because everybody has it
and eventually they get something if
they don't take care of themselves you
know someone might be young and seem
strong and indestructible now
they're on instagram they're on social
media they're on facebook
they're on youtube and they think they
got it all down
and they're doing their their you know
foods and whatever it is in their
lifestyle and
boom they're 38 years old years later
and then
now we got ebv we got symptoms and they
doubt everything and now they don't know
what to do and i got all kinds of brain
fog
and back pain and all kinds of stuff so
it's it's really important to have
control over your health entirely and
not just be
in this place of you know you think you
got control but you don't
and the one thing about medical medium
books especially this one
is it allowed people to become so
empowered
that they were able to actually stop
things from coming their way
stop conditions from coming their way
they were they were able to stop eb
from causing harm and in the shingles
too which is also in this book and
so it's so important and then there's
like this book also brought to light for
the first time what bell's palsy was
which is shingles back pain that's
mysterious which is shingles virus and
there's over 30 varieties of shingles
so this book brought that information to
light
as well okay and frozen shoulder
colitis so it it broke the truth about
colitis which is the shingles frozen
shoulder which is the shingles
um bell's palsy with which is the
shingles back pain like sciatica which
is the shingles
and um so it's just so great i just put
some tomatoes in now i'm gonna put
i'm gonna put a celery stick or two in
i'm gonna do two celery sticks in this
one
small they're small celery sticks
sometimes you have a really big celery
stick that's all you need is that one
big celery stick
penny says i heard you can't heal okay
polythemia and with the help of your
book i was able to help heal my husband
incredible incredible that's so special
so amazing i'm gonna pop i'm gonna cut
an orange over here
and pop this in good to see you guys
coming on education
educating myself says the book was a
master class
and medical information you know it's
it's funny because
i keep on being told first of all i was
i was asked to write the books
i was asked by thousands of people
because you guys know that i worked with
over 250 000 people for over 30 years
right
and i was told every day by doctors
every day by practitioners to write the
books write the books write the books
and and i was like ah just
i got to help people i got to help like
i'm helping them now and they're like no
you've got to help millions of people
everybody needs an opportunity
everybody needs a chance so i wrote the
books and that's and that's what
happened
like the world changed the world of
medicine changed because of this book
the world of medicine
completely changed in chronic illness
because of this book
and um and so that was really special
but
but now i'm being told don't keep on
writing the books
create programs you know create programs
people all they have to do is spend two
thousand dollars for the program
they can learn from the program and you
can create multiple pro
programs you know two thousand dollars a
piece i'm like no i want this
affordable i want a book that's
really really affordable you can get
your life saved and bring your life back
i don't want to do that i don't want to
stop writing the books no matter how
hard the books are to write and do
i don't want to just stop writing the
books and create programs
so people have to pay two three thousand
dollars for a program in order to learn
how to heal it just doesn't seem
fair to me it just doesn't right now it
just doesn't it just doesn't feel right
so
the book's there it's affordable and
it's just
it's just such a great way to heal i'm
gonna pop in some orange in here you
guys
so i'm making the spinach soup which is
really a famous recipe for healing
it's one of the medical medium healing
tools you guys laur
uh lorelai hey what about tomatoes being
nightshades
what about them being nightshades
because that's misinformation out there
nightshades was a
theory basically because okay it goes
back to this book
i'm glad you asked that question it's so
important
before this book came out no one knew
what was wrong with anybody
so lorelai think about it okay you got
almost 100 years of chronic illness
right
people rushing to doctors not having any
answers
and um so a lot of theories were created
because nobody knew why anybody was sick
so then they'd be guessing games like
what if it's
these tomatoes because it's a night
shade
a spooky night shade
kind of vegetable fruit thing right
so that's one that was just a theory but
there's no science behind it
causing a problem there's no truth
behind it they've never been able to
link anything to it
and so like rheumatoid arthritis isn't
caused by a tomato
it's caused by epstein-barr virus so you
got all these people they're going into
you know functional medicine doctors
offices chinese medicine doctors offices
naturopathic doctors offices do's doctor
you know osteopathic doctors going in
there looking for help for years like
the 1960s the 1970s the 1980s
and the 1990s no one having answers like
why are we sick why are we sick
and then it's like all you have to do is
just come up and pull something out of
thin air
pull something out of somebody's you
know whatever and just all of a sudden
you're like you pull something out
and it's like night shades that's the
answer and that's why people are sick uh
now it's lectins that's why people are
sick well that's funny because millions
of people already healed
and they healed using the tomatoes they
healed using
potatoes they healed using all the
medical medium tools and foods that i
talked about
and lectins didn't stop them from
healing their diseases and chronic
illness and everything else
these are just these are guessing games
to when someone doesn't know why
somebody's sick
so it's like it must be the nightshade
it must be
the leptin it must be hmm
and maybe it's you know that vegetable
that makes people sick so people just
wanna they they just throw the guessing
games out
and the guessing games maybe it's
candida that makes them sick because
that was a complete
farce and i talked about the whole
candida mistake that happened out there
and
so and maybe it's the histamines maybe
it's oxalates
maybe it's that and and it's all a
guessing game and that's the sad
part so what happens is you get sucked
into that
you totally get sucked into that and
that and that's a problem it really is
um because if you really get sick
someday
and you're running from a tomato
basically you're running from a bee
a bumble bee and then you run right out
into a street and get hit by a bus and
you're mauled by a bus
because you're running from a bee and
the bee wasn't going to sting you
because the tomatoes not going to hurt
you it's just this is what they do they
set this i i think they
i think it's done purposely and by
accident kind of a both of a combination
out there it's like they just set
everybody up for failure it's like no
one wants anybody to truly heal or
something
um and where did if you had a problem
with tomato what was it was it really a
tomato like
it was it a ripe perfectly ripe vine
tomato like this
and you cut it and you ate a piece of it
and then something bad happened
or was it the tomato sauce that was on a
pizza
that was on with cheese and bad oil and
gluten in the crust was it that
was it some other was it ketchup
with vinegar in it was it that that was
used for something else you know what i
mean
because those are the things that will
get you sick it's the vinegar it's the
cheese on a pizza
that's what's gonna amp up the
epstein-barr virus
tomatoes are anti-viral tomatoes are
anti-pathogen they're anti-bug
and you know i remember teaching people
about how the nightshade confusion was
wrong from the beginning and it freed
so many people they can heal they can
eat potatoes and tomatoes
so matt says your books info
changed my life sue says false i used to
get
kidney stones now i have none of none
and eat all the oxalates especially
spinach
and crap spinach is an anti-kidney stone
uh you know fixer or whatever it's like
it's the anti-kidney stone
tool spinach is healing it heals the
kidneys
it heals the body it heals the
gallbladder but that's how
misinformation works out there it has
tons of it out there you guys
tons of it it's it's overwhelming now
you know medical medium information when
it hit the scene
uh i've been teaching it forever but
when it hit the scene in the
publications of the books and stuff
it was like it had such a leg up because
everybody's like fresh air
fresh air now there's so many tricks out
there and so many people getting fooled
in so many different directions it's
it's really sad when you really see it
now where do we start which one which
which book tasha
um i mean you're not you can't go wrong
with this book it's got all the recipes
in there it's got
protocols and dosages um
you can go to this book and then cleanse
the heel i mean honestly
this is a power pack right here the
cleanse the heel book and
the medical medium revised and expanded
i mean honestly
these these two right here um go to the
library get them for free if you want
you can do that too go to the library
you can get cleansed of heal for free
there
cleansing heal is also 51 off on
amazon.com right now i'm putting some
cilantro in here a few sprigs in here
right make sure when you get
this book okay that it's the new edition
revised and expanded so if you do get
this book
and or you get it from the library when
it comes out there and you don't get it
from amazon whatever
make sure it's the revised and expanded
the new edition all right it's got the
45 recipes in here i mean just
gorgeous the book is just so pretty
i mean it's got all the beautiful
recipes in here
i don't know if you can see that right
there
so anyway and i'm trying to protect the
book right now because i usually make a
mess
i get food on it all of it i'm trying to
trying to take care of it right now and
not mess it up
like when that book came to me i was
like oh my god i can't believe i have it
after all this time just put a little
orange juice in here
squeezing an orange
great to see you guys i'm glad you're
coming on we're going to talk about
triggers
with chronic illness triggers with
symptoms and conditions we're going to
talk about lyme disease
so we're going to go into that that's
where we're heading now
just making some spinach soup i want to
give you guys kind of a little in on
this of what i got going on here so
i got the cilantro i got the tomatoes i
got some celery sticks thrown in there i
squeezed some orange in there
um jamie
my husband has a horrible reaction to
onion and garlic
no doctors can figure out why um
depends on the reaction well first of
all um
i would stay away from onions and garlic
if he's having a bad reaction i would
stay away from them for sure onions and
garlic
can kill bacteria so bacteria
like h pylori it can kill bacteria
like streptococcus it can kill
bacteria like staph and what happens in
people's intestinal tracts it gets so
mucky in there you get a lot of staph
you get c
diff staph streptococcus e coli and h
pylori
so the even if you're not exhibiting
symptoms
there's people out there that have a lot
of e coli streptococcus h pylori staph
c diff in their intestinal tract small
intestinal tract
even in their stomach they have some of
it so when you
drop some garlic in there the garlic is
giving direct
kill-off so we're talking direct
kill-off
on that stuff the minute or the second
that e coli explodes depending
if it's got some toxins in it if that
bacteria like strep e coli c
diff staph uh h pylori has actually
toxins in it or some bad toxins in it
the minute those buggers explode from
that direct hit from the garlic right
and i'm looking for my garlic here it is
the minute that garlic goes down
and it hits those bugs and they die you
don't even need a lot of those bugs to
die you can have just a little bit of e
coli dye
a little bit of strep a tiny tiny bit of
strep or e coli or anything
if you you know if if they die then you
get all you get the reactions you can
get a lot of reactions okay
and that's people who are loaded with
all the different levels of bacteria
in their system right so we can do is is
how much garlic first of all i wouldn't
do
cooked garlic if i was somebody that was
really hypersensitive
because cooked garlic can still kill off
the pathogens too but cooked garlic
tends to be a little bit different
digesting wise i mean i would say
tiny bit if you're ever if you know if
you're ever up against something like
this but you want garlic you want onions
it would be a tiny bit
because when you use a tiny bit you end
up killing just
less you end up killing less of that
bacteria so you might be able to slowly
kill off that bacteria over time
and get to that point where you can
actually have garlic again or
stay off the garlic and onions right
and just change the diet so you're not
feeding those bugs let them die off on
their own
naturally over time i have a gut health
chapter
in this medical medium book right here
which is incredible gut health chapter
um it's so much information in here it
really there really is
and so you can do like the healing foods
make sure there's no gluten milk cheese
or butter
to keep the ice creams out keep all that
out of there
and there's protocols in the book too
just eating better like the 28 day
cleanse in the medical medium book
cleanse in that book can be really
helpful so that now you're killing off
the bacteria and i recommend that to
everybody and that's why a lot of people
healed
when you're doing the 28 day cleanse
you're starving
that e coli that's in everybody you know
i know people today they'll be like i
don't got any e coli in my system i go
yeah you do
of course you do i don't got any strep
in my system well did you have strep
throat before yeah i had a sore throat
and they said it was strapped back
when i was younger yeah it's still in
your system it's in your gut and
eventually it causes sibo and then you
get the sibo diagnosis right
so and you know people got that e coli
they got the strep they got the h pylori
people are loaded with this stuff you
know
the 28 day cleanse in medical medium
took away the foods that feed these
pathogens feed the bacteria and
proliferate this bacteria right
the 20-day cleanse took away that people
like getting their lives back on the
28-day cleanse
healing because they were taking away
foods that feed the bugs right so here
you go
that's your bacteria that's your e coli
that's your streptococcus
that's your h pylori that's your c diff
that's your staff
okay sits inside everybody's guts 28-day
cleanse
took away the food that feeds the
bacteria so the bacteria couldn't eat
anymore it's like wait a minute
this person's on the 28-day cleanse and
i can't find any food and i'm starting
to starve in here
and this person's cleaning up so i can't
even find old food that's hanging around
the intestinal tract
and then the bacteria is like where do i
go where do i go and it weakens and
weakens and eventually dies off or
gets flushed out and pushed out by the
20-day cleanse
and that's how people were getting
better that's one way they're getting
better from the 28-day cleanse
making the spinach soup let's talk about
lyme disease
let me put a little bit of spinach in
here
let me put a little bit of spinach let's
do that right now
honestly people being afraid of spinach
is heartbreaking
breaks my heart totally does you guys i
mean seriously
it's so sad that's misinformation once
again out there
michelle been tested and allergic to
tomatoes
missed so much there's a difference
between and i told a doctor friend about
this recently there's a difference
between
what a test says for your foods because
you can go
and get tested do a food sensitivity
test and they'll be like you're allergic
to tomatoes you're allergic to eggplant
allergic to strawberries you're allergic
to cilantro you're allergic to
some kind of weird ragweed you're
allergic to whatever and they just throw
all the stuff
in stuff that isn't even food stuff that
you would never eat in a million years
you're allergic to star and nice you're
allergic to
ginger you know they'll just do all the
stuff right and
meanwhile you're getting tested by a
system that doesn't know why you're sick
or doesn't know why anybody's sick
food sensitivities they don't know why
anybody's sick do they know why the
world's sick i mean unless they know
unless they're actually doing what
science research is now taking
taking all the cues from medical medium
books they're not going to know why
anybody's sick
so um so what i told the doctor friend
is like
are you and dr fred actually said well
my food sensitivity test says i'm
allergic tomatoes and i said to my
doctor friend i said
so if you ate a tomato what happened so
i gave him a tomato
and i said if you eat a tomato what
happens
say nothing nothing happens if i eat a
tomato but my food sensitivities
test says you know i'm allergic to it
like okay well that's really funny
because
um you can eat it and you're fine yeah i
could eat it i'm fine
like what else does your test say you're
allergic to test says i'm allergic to
blackberries
what happens when eat the blackberries
nothing i'm fine like okay
and what happens is those tests they're
not perfect
and they never were they never will be
it's different if you're eating a tomato
and your mouth is swelling up and your
throat's swelling up and you can't
breathe
look i don't want you to eat tomato if
you don't want to eat a tomato do what
your doctor says your doctor says don't
eat a tomato don't eat a tomato
i'm just telling you about my experience
with a doctor friend
who said well you know my food
sensitivity test is i'm orange tomatoes
i guess i shouldn't have um and
meanwhile you know last week or whatever
it's like
i had a pizza you know he was like
whatever uh nozilla when i first started
to drink celery juice
i had a lot of shivering and diarrhea
it was a sign that lots of cleansing was
happening i don't have any
any of these drastic symptoms anymore
because i have healed so much with mm
info
what that is is when you do your celery
juice and i got my juicer over there in
the corner can you guys see it i
actually just juiced
pretty recently before i started this
live and i drank my juice
um what happens is when you're doing
your celery juice and i just put a
little celery in the spinach soup by the
way
when you're doing that the sodium
cluster salt and celery destroy
pathogens so it looks like this so
here you go you got all these little
bugs in here right you guys know this
one right
it's my little friend virus right
epstein-barr
and bacteria okay streptococcus
so people are filled with all the
bacteria they're filled with all the
strep you start dropping celery juice in
there the sodium cluster salts start to
strip
down the membrane and that's what
happens the bacteria will have this
membrane all around it like this you see
this that's that's the membrane and
that celery juice starts to eat away you
see these little furry things that stick
up that stick off this bacteria
that's actually accurate bacteria will
have fur on it
some viruses will have fur on it that's
their first defense mechanism right
there
they have first sticking out of their
membrane that's what that's what happens
and so just to break that down
is is difficult all on its own but not
for celery juice celery
juice the sodium cluster salt starts to
break down that membrane
and and that's then starts to really
help
and julia my daughter's eczema
went away uh do his protocol celery
juice no eggs supplements
dot dot dot incredible incredible um you
guys have if you just got on here i'm
talking about lyme disease right here
out of medical medium i'm gonna read
some triggers too
so this book has healed tens of
thousands of people with lyme disease
when it came out and now it's hundreds
of thousands of people with lyme disease
since it's been out um this is the new
edition it's
packed with information even more i put
a whole book in this that's why
it's so big and now that's the whole bit
um so
this book the lyme disease section of
this book has changed the way doctors
see lyme disease
so it's changed the way they see it
because this book exposed the truth
about lyme disease that lyme disease
is viral not bacterial so okay
so this lyme disease is caused by
viruses not bacteria okay
and so that was what this book exposed
um and also what happened with this book
is it forced the medical science
of the world it forced them to abandon
the theory that lyme disease was
bacteria so they abandoned it
so medical research and science doesn't
believe lyme disease is bacteria
anymore now the lyme labs that your
doctor sends the tet
the blood to right
they won't abandon the idea
that it's bacteria because they built
their empires
on lyme disease being bacteria so you
got these lyme labs
that have made billions of dollars for
the last 50 years
40 50 years and they can't abandon it so
you've got the lyme labs
with then you've got the doctors that
are the old dogs now
the old dogs that believe that still
believe lyme disease is bacterial
you got them working with the lyme labs
but then
you got medical research and science
which is their boss
doctor's boss in medical research and
science is the boss of doctors it's the
boss of the lyme labs
that big boss doesn't believe it's
bacterial anymore because of medical
medium books so they took lyme disease
out of the bacterial world and they put
it now in autoimmune so now it's an
autoimmune they don't know what it is so
they
they're just like it could be viral it's
not bacterial
we don't know what lyme disease is
anymore and that's because of the
medical medium books now
antibiotics destroyed thousands and
thousands of women's lives now i say
women because they were mostly stricken
by this disease
not men and that's still like that today
now okay
so tens of thousands of women's lives
were destroyed because
antibiotics because the overuse of
bombarding their system with antibiotics
when their condition
wasn't bacterial this book
has saved countless women's lives
because they didn't have to
go through all that heavy bombardment of
that
old school antibiotic treatment for lyme
disease
they were able to be freed from that and
recover without having their life
destroyed and that's what this book did
the original one
well now this is the new new and even
improved because i added so much
information into it okay
now there's these doctors on podcasts
right now
there's some some of them famous
whatever there's doctors on television
with doing television careers
and they were responsible for the damage
and the life and the death of thousands
of women
going back many years of lyme disease
but see no one ever corrects anything so
they just kind of be
act like a chameleon and now they're
chameleon to another direction like oh i
didn't
i didn't run a clinic and give hundreds
and hundreds and hundreds of women
tons of antibiotics and destroyed their
lives that wasn't me
uh you know with the old lyme disease
theory they keep on they keep on jumping
from
old theory to new theory to new theory
to new theory to new theory
and they don't clean up the mess nobody
knows what they did now they're on
podcasts or have their own podcast
meanwhile they've destroyed so many
lives doctors from new england doctors
from around
you know the country around the world
now they're famous for their podcast or
something
and literally they have a wake behind
them blood on their hands
uh because i know i've been in this for
35 years i know
who screwed up everything
when it came down to that i know how
that worked people who lost their lives
i know the good doctors versus the bad
doctors i know
what happened in the lyme disease world
and it's it's really hell
and there's a terrible thing and what
happened so
this book has changed that for so many
women so they don't have to go that
route of being bombard
bombarded being completely just having
their systems wrecked with tons of
antibiotics not knowing that it's viral
and
being told it's bacterial and that's
what's incredible about the book so
and no one sees those mistakes no one no
one care who cares if tens of thousands
of women lost their lives
from lyme disease and you know who cares
because it doesn't matter
those doctors they never get like no one
ever says hey so you just spent
20 years bombarding you know women with
so much and
sarah says i was given so much doxy yeah
in boxing it was brutal
sarah that was the old way
and that's the way that now you'll see
these podcast doctors out there
that you know are doing their podcast
they got all this money behind them and
they're
they have a history of
bombarding women with antibiotics and
they don't even like they don't come to
the table and say well
made a mistake shouldn't have done that
i shouldn't maybe we shouldn't have gone
that direction
you know no and they don't just keep on
going with the
you know the theories and the bs and who
cares you know it's amazing
amy beasley explain why when a lyme
patient
takes antibiotics when they have um
why they have they die off or hurts
yeah absolutely i talk about it medical
medium book here
they're not having a die off when they
take antibiotics they're having a
reaction their nervous system is having
a reaction to the toxic nature of the
antibiotics now i'm not against
antibiotics okay and do what your doctor
wants to do but the point is
is that i'm asked this all the time by a
lot of people
and what happens is and i taught about
this for years and taught doctors this
too
herxheimer is a theory that there's a
die-off happening
you so you just think there's a die-off
happening but what it is
it's an adverse reaction to the
antibiotic because when you have lyme
you have viral inflammation to the
nervous system and when the nerves are
very sensitive i'll say it again
you have viral information inflammation
to the nervous system so the vagus nerve
the phrenic nerves
all the nerves in the body they get
sensitive as heck
so when something toxic like an
antibiotic it's driven into
the body whether it's through
intravenous or any other way
you think you're getting herxheimer but
what you're doing is just
hurting bad your nerves are hurting bad
hypersensitive nerves
from viral infections they can't handle
a lot of things
and that's the great mistake in the
industry but i would listen to your
doctor if he thinks you need to be on
antibiotics you go on antibiotics if
that's what your doctor wants
you know or whatever and and all that
i'm just saying that look you can always
take the book to your doctor
and and maybe educate him and maybe
he'll see some other things
but whatever whatever your doctor says
do um
but that's how it works with herxheimers
and that's how it works with the whole
situation
um anyway
talk about triggers in a second let me
just blend this up a little bit
and then we're going to go into some
triggers that's the next thing
so i'm going to make the spinach soup
let me at least do some blending
now you can use more spinach you can use
less spinach not a lot there's not
that much spinach in this one but
there's definitely some in there
[Music]
so
tammy can it just affect one side
of the body i have ebv shingles and more
it affects the left side from
from ear to toe yeah absolutely
definitely can affect one side
epstein-barr hasn't um
epstein-barr and shingles loves to
affect
one side in many many situations it just
does
i've seen bar can too
i'll tell you why in a minute
okay that spinach soup is blended
epstein-barr releases neurotoxins
some nerves will be more sensitive to
their neurotoxins than other nerves
what happens is if you've been under any
stress your adrenals will
release adrenaline and the left side of
the body
can be hit with more adrenaline from a
stronger adrenal which could be the
adrenal that's on the left side of your
body too
so when you're going through fight or
flight any kind of stress in your life
anything financial stress anything
you know could be relationships whatever
happens in your life
that adrenal gland pumps out more and
more and more adrenaline
weakens the nervous system a little but
you really can't feel that until the
epstein bar releases all these
neurotoxins and when the neurotoxins
land on nerves it's going to be whatever
nerves
are your most sensitive and they're
going to light right up shingles on the
other hand can focus on one side of the
body so
you know it that can happen too but
epstein-barr can
can do different things there's
different varieties
glad you guys are here
gotta pay attention when i cook when i
prepare foods
gary said i was really crippled with
many lyme symptoms
after a spider bite four years ago thank
you anthony for bringing me back let's
talk about triggers
let's do that you guys i'm gonna pour
this out in a minute
but i'd like to talk about triggers and
how it works
a spider bite can lower your immune
system
and when your immune system is lowered
because the spider bite is a trigger
when your immune system is lowered
now the epstein bar creeps up
cytomegalovirus hhv6 herpes simplex one
they can you know which is cold source
they can all creep up shingles can all
creep up
strep can even creep up right but
epstein-barr loves to creep up with all
that
because it just sits inside of us and
eventually kind of comes out and creeps
up
so i'm going to page 197 i know you guys
don't have your books yet i wish you had
it
had the book so amazon.com right now
that's where you can get it if you want
to know where you can get it right now
um barnes and noble too online
so right now i'm looking at triggers so
i'm in the trigger section right here of
lyme disease and it's really the
triggers for epstein-barr too
is there a list of recipes i came in
late yeah
there is uh in this book this is packed
i'm making the spinach soup from this
book yasmin thank you for coming here
i really appreciate it so in this
trigger zone here let's see if i could
find spider bite
so i'm looking right now um
but yeah so the whole thing is spider
bite to have it it's number 12 on the
triggers list
spider bites are actually much more
common triggers for lyme disease
symptoms than tick bites
accounting for about five percent of
cases from this list
all right if the bite leaves some of the
spider's venom inside your skin an
infection can result that weakens your
immune system
roughly one out of five times it also
produces a bullseye
rash okay it can in a lot of people i'm
reading
out of the lyme disease chapter right
here and
um so talking about epstein-barr
which is really an epidemic all on its
own just so you know so
let's talk about the triggers i got the
book open i want to show you guys so i
got a couple of note postage notes in
here as you can see
i'm in the trigger section of medical
medium secrets
i'm making the spinach soup i still got
to pour it out and i still have to taste
it
so the first trigger right here i have
here for epstein barr
is the pandemic we're facing now so that
pandemic that plague we're up against
now
is the first trigger the most powerful
trigger for epstein-barr so everybody's
epstein bars
can really get amped up from the
pandemic virus that's going around right
now
so if you happen to contract that virus
that's creating this pandemic that's
happening right now then
you've got a good chance of creeping
that epstein barr up
we're actually triggering that
epstein-barr up so
okay the current pandemic can challenge
the immune system
both by exhausting its reserves and by
causing it to overreact so what happens
when we get
sick from the pandemic virus that's
going around right now
it can trigger off by literally lowering
our immune system weakening in our
immune system
and making it overreact a weakened
immune system can in turn provide an
opportunity
for dormant viral infections to gain
strength and create new symptoms so what
i'm trying to say is
in from what i'm reading here is that if
you catch that pandemic bug going around
right now
right your immune system lowers it
weakens
and then any kind of low grade viral
infection creeps up
glad you guys are coming on all right
making spinach soup and reading about
the triggers right here
and so that's important to know
okay it can also lead to symptoms that
someone had previously experienced to
resurface so if you guys had
epstein-barr
if you guys had symptoms of epstein-barr
maybe not even knew it was epstein-barr
maybe had tingles and numbness aches and
pains
you know um ringing in the ears
dizziness whatever it is burning skin
then it's chances are those symptoms
could come back
if you get hit with that pandemic bug
so that's another thing too the pandemic
virus that's going around now is
difficult on the central nervous system
and people who have suffered with
neurological lyme symptoms are often
dealing with
or often dealing with nervous system
compromises already
can get triggered by this because hey if
you get a high fever from the pandemic
bug that's going around right now that
can trigger off the neurological
symptoms of lyme
if you've already were someone with lyme
so that's one of the biggest
triggers right now going on so you got
all these millions of people out there
with epstein-barr
they don't know how to fix their
epstein-barr they either struggle with
it they struggle with symptoms and
conditions that they don't even know
causes it right
and what happens is that
that they're going around with the
epstein bar they have it in their system
it's sitting there whether it's causing
trouble or not in the moment and then
they end up getting the pandemic bug
that's happening out there right
they get hit with that well then that
weakens the immune system and their
epstein-barr creeps up
and now they think it's a pandemic bug
that's keeping them sick after the fact
but really now their epstein-barr is
ignited
and it was published first here in the
medical medium book right
so um there's more information
here to read too so that's one
so just like the flu or the pandemic
bug here now it can prompt that high
fever which can heat and strain the
nerves
that are weakened so if someone recently
healed
those nerves can actually weaken from
the high fever
okay so the pandemic bug can create that
high fever
weaken somebody's nerves who actually
recently healed and now we're back
in the saddle again of having
neurological lyme
or having hashimoto's or having ra
or having cfs or having any kind of
thing any any kind of symptom really
so many different symptoms so that's how
it works there um
so yeah but but i want to talk about
blood draw extension
extensive blood draw as a trigger so i'm
in the trigger section right now
i'm going to cover that for a minute i'm
in medical medium if you just came on
here
the revised and expanded new edition you
guys got to check it out it's on amazon
the link is in description
you can look at look at that right now
so here's another trigger you have to
look out for okay
this trigger right here is a trigger
that we get in trouble with all the time
and we don't realize it it's extensive
blood draw
so when you go to your doctor to get
blood taken so
fasten your seat belts for this okay so
we get told by our doctor hey
you need some blood work let's go do it
you'll be fine all right i need blood
work because blood work's a good thing
right yeah
and they end up taking too much blood
and if you have epstein-barr or you're
already chronically sick with something
that's epstein-barr related
or epstein-barr caused of course like
cfs or fibro or
lupus whatever's going on in your life
or just say vertigo
dizziness focus some anxiety eczema
psoriasis and you're already dealing
with all these conditions right
and then you go to the doctor and you
get your blood drawn
they end up taking more blood right
from you than you need really taken from
you first of all
it gets thrown away at the la the labs
so blood labs throw away 95
of all that blood they take a little
sample out of each vial but
you end up losing a whole vial right and
sometimes people get a whole vial and
they'll take a bunch of things out of
there do a bunch of tests out of that
vial but still they throw away half the
blood easy
so they'll say hey you need five vials
of blood you know they come and
take your blood or you go to a place to
get your blood taken or you're at the
doctor's office to get your blood taken
and they're like what we're taking
they won't even tell you sometimes
they'll just take seven vials they'll
take seven vials
nine vials 12 vials of blood 14
vials of blood i talked about this in
the past where
where i've known people they've taken 20
something vials plus
and then some people die from that right
they die literally die from that they
get too much blood taken
they weaken they can't recover and they
get chronically ill and die
and it all stemmed from that big blood
draw right
so i talk about this being a trigger so
here you are
you're somebody that is on the edge of
epstein barr or you're on the edge of
getting a sickness of some kind okay
you're on the edge of some kind of
low-grade viral infection like
epstein-barr
or shingles and then you get the blood
draw
and they take too much blood and what
goes wrong with that
is they remove your immune system so
epstein-barr stay in us they live in us
they live in our liver
they live in our body they live in a lot
of people's thyroid and they stay
somewhat dormant they're not really
causing too much trouble
they're alive they're inside of us but
they stay kind of relaxed kind of in a
docile state
because your immune system keeps it in
check
too so your white count basophils
monocyte neutrophils are
keeping it all in check that's what
happens and
as you're sitting there living your life
your immune system is trying to stay
strong
and it's trying to keep those viruses
down and then you get a blood test
and they pull out too much blood when
they pull out too much blood
they end up pulling out your immune
system that was in your blood
now your immune system doesn't rebuild
overnight you all of a sudden don't get
a brand new immune system when they
removed it
so when they removed your white count in
your blood
that one time they took 10 vials of
blood and that all that
immune system went into that blood right
meaning went out of your body in that
blood right
then epstein-barr is like wow we got a
chance to now thrive
i'm looking for we got a chance to now
thrive because
you had all that blood taken out so now
the epstein barr is like
whoa the immune system's gone right now
a large part of your immune system that
was inside your bloodstream
keeping the virus from causing problems
is now removed
and that's why this is a huge trigger
right here is blood draw
so what i recommend and i'm going to
read this section extensive blood draw
that's a major trigger i'm talking about
that that's in the medical media book
right here okay
when a larger number of blood vials are
drawn
it can be stressful on the immune system
because the very immune defenses that
are keeping the viruses behind lyme
symptoms and other chronic illnesses
the viruses behind lyme and other
chronic illnesses
the immune system keeps them at bay
and now it's your immune system is being
drawn out of the body
when the blood is taken
you guys so i'm in i'm in the lyme
disease chapter chapter 16
16 of the book right here medical medium
just letting you know
and i'm going to tell you a couple other
things in a second
so here's how it goes um larger blood
draws
tend to take away a substantial portion
of a person's immune system that day
and it sometimes takes weeks to rebuild
those portions of the immune system so
here it goes you just had your blood
taken
now you need weeks to restore your
immune system but during those weeks
epstein-barr creeps up so say you're
somebody with lyme disease which is
epstein-barr infection
and you get all this blood taken all the
time your lyme doctor is getting all
ordering all these blood tests you're
getting all this blood removed right
i've seen this take people into grave
places with lyme disease
too much of their immune system is being
taken out and they decline and they
decline and they decline over the years
and decline
and the very thing that's causing their
lyme disease epstein-barr
creeps up creeps up creeps up and really
does a number on them
so okay so that that's important to know
too
it can take weeks to rebuild those
portions of your immune system within
those weeks that
that the full power of the immune system
is not present anymore to monitor the
blood the viruses
can get a window to strengthen and
proliferate infections can travel from
organ to organ with ease
that means your viral infection can
travel from your liver
to your spleen spleen to your pancreas
all because
the doctor's ordering too much blood it
doesn't even know why you're sick with
lyme to begin with doesn't know why
you're sick with some kind of cfs
doesn't know why you're sick with ra
doesn't know why you're sick with
anything hashimoto's and too much
blood's being ordered
so that's important to know infections
can travel from organ organ with ease
because they're not being corralled
by your immune system right and that can
lead to a flare-up of symptoms whether a
week or a few weeks
oh i didn't get my symptoms after i just
had all my blood taken but you get it
six months down the road
then you got all these new symptoms six
months down the road but you don't know
it's from the blood that was taken six
months before
i recommend doing smaller blood draws
over more visits
if you're struggling with lyme symptoms
or any other condition labeled
autoimmune i recommend no more than
four vials of blood at a time and even
consider
fewer if you're very sensitive a mistake
made by well-meaning doctors is to draw
a large number of blood vials with
sensitive people
that's just one precious piece of
information
in this book like when people say well
why do i need that book like why would i
need medical medium
new addition or anything uh that piece
of information can save people's lives
it can save them from years of chronic
illness it can ha
it can help them literally get their
lives back just that piece
so it's like what and this isn't in
their books you can't find this is
medical medium information i teach
doctors this stuff but you can't find
this in other books
so anyway there's chapters on anxiety
depression adhd autism
lyme ebv lupus fibromyalgia chronic
fatigue syndrome
adrenal fatigue candida gut health fruit
fear
menopause thyroid issues ra migraines
shingles colitis tmj frozen shoulder i
mean it the list goes on this book is
crazy and it's packed and um
so i made some spinach soup i'm gonna
actually pour it into a bowl
bear with me guys
miasha he only writes books he could
have created programs instead and change
hundreds it charged hundreds of
thousands of dollars for each program
the books are all under 20 if you can't
afford
the book you can go to the library it's
so true
i can charge programs two thousand
dollars three thousand dollars programs
ten million people around the world
world will
buy those programs at two thousand
dollars a piece put the math together
which ten million times two hundred
what's ten million times two two
thousand dollars for three thousand
dollars
it would be an insane amount of money i
don't want to do that to you guys i feel
like it's unfair or not right i know
a lot of people that would do that in a
heartbeat i don't want to do it
i'm not trying to say i'm just like you
know a great guy and i just didn't want
to do that to you it's
because i look at it if i was sick
would i you know what would help me
spend two thousand dollars on a program
and get a few bills and whistles and
then be broke
or a 20 book or 30 book 16
book whatever and get the answers i need
so i can heal
if that was me you know what direction i
would go and its bottom line is what it
is
so um put a little cilantro on top
couple sprigs
okay on top of this that's my spinach
soup right there you guys
i don't know if you can see it but here
it is um i'm excited
this spinach soup recipe has helped so
many people it's in this book
um i hope you enjoyed this
this facebook youtube live and
um have you guys checked out tick to the
last tick tock video i put out it's
actually really funny
uh made me laugh because it was a
blooper which means it wasn't supposed
to happen
and it did um you guys check out metal
medical medium podcasts at apple podcast
check out those 17 episodes so much
information there i have a neurological
symptoms episodes if you guys are
dealing with any nervous system symptoms
at all or anxiety or anything and i have
a new episode coming
i have a new episode that's on its way
the medical media podcast at apple
podcast
and it's gonna be a mind blower um and
the meditations on the medical media
podcast at apple podcast
are also mind-blowing to help you heal
you guys
um and i have new meditations in the
medical media book
i'm heading over to instagram going to
make the spinach soup again
why not i'll have two of them tonight
and then tiktok will be live at the same
time simultaneously
i love you guys and i'll see ya