left and right
what's the biggest
and greatest of all the sickness
neurological symptoms
tingles numbness on the body aches and
pains ringing in the ears pain and neck
pain in the head trembles vibrations
tightness of the chest you're at the
pulmonologist now you're at a specialist
now you have a neurologist anxiety
depression blurry vision brain fog
all burning tongue burning mouth pain in
the gums big pain in the teeth pain in
the back
feet tremoring legs tremoring restless
leg syndrome it's endless
neurological symptoms
are the biggest actually the biggest but
you won't hear that out there
I think it's suppressed I think the
information is kept down
I don't think
I don't think the industry the health
industry the medical industry wants
everybody to know that neurological
symptoms are the big bad wolf of what's
happening out there
it's where everybody's getting sick
everybody's has a symptom everybody's
struggling with something going on with
neurological symptoms
so I got the books in front of me I'm
doing a q a
I'm going to take a look at what's in
here too so I want to talk about
symptoms conditions these books
have saved so many lives throughout the
years
people getting answers when they
couldn't get any answers at all and
right now here's what's happening
there's millions of people out there in
the world that are just starting to get
sick right now just starting so they're
starting their journey of doctor
internist specialist
then neurologist
then internist then GP then specialist
then naturopathic doctor acupuncturist
specialist internist doctor
acupuncturist naturopath do chiropractor
back to do back to wearing the doctor
and they're just starting their Journey
and that's what's happening so millions
of people right now in the world are
just starting their journey and getting
sick if you guys just got on here I'm
doing a q a I'm taking a look inside
these books neurological symptoms are
dominating right now
they're the big ones crying fatigue
syndrome fatigue
mysterious fatigue all kinds of
different neurological symptoms people
don't realize something that medical
medium termed neurological fatigue so
many people are dealing with all of this
stuff
burning tongue twitching nose pain in
the nose pain in the ears popping in the
ears fluttering vertigo dizziness
balance issues where they feel like
they're on a boat but they're not on a
boat I can go on and on all day
panic attacks
anxiety
so many people are struggling right now
but they're just starting their Journey
newbies they're just starting to get
sick and they're Doctor shopping
practitioner shopping health coach
shopping
and they're going in the Merry-Go-Round
and they don't know
that they're actually answers out there
that have gotten people with hundreds of
symptoms better people that have 100
symptoms more than 100 symptoms
50 symptoms and they've gotten better
and recovered their life recovered
themselves through the information in
the medical medium books
so I'm opening up these books for a
little bit I'm going to talk about
symptoms and conditions
I'm excited to do so I want to be
helpful today in any way I can
because I know so many of you guys are
struggling and still struggling many of
you guys are recovering yourselves many
of you guys here just fully recovered
after doing years of medical medium when
you already were sick for 10 15 20 years
the medical medium books were this
bright light for the person
who's been sick for over a decade
10 20 years
and so because you find the answers
so I'm hearing symptoms and conditions
and I love this book here
this book is the brain saver book
now if you're somebody just coming into
this you'll be like which book do I get
that's a great book medical medium
New Edition is incredible live a rescue
another Incredible Book right there too
get them free at the library
you can do that
so
so many people
have problems
Beyond just say a neurological tingle or
numbness or an ache or a pain or jaw
pain or dizziness or vertigo or ear
popping or whatever so many people have
addiction issues that they just can't
get past
whether it's an addiction to caffeine
addiction to coffee addiction to
chocolate
addiction to food because you're under
stress
so so many people are are addicted to
flavor they're addicted to MSG they're
addicted to that
that excitability they get from food
that adrenaline surge
and then there's so many people that
also have skin problems like eczema and
psoriasis
psoriatic arthritis kind of combination
of both and then you get people who have
rosacea dermatitis and all kinds of
other skin issues too so
I'm looking right here and I'm looking
through symptoms conditions in the brain
saver book and I'll just run a few right
here by you this is interesting like I'm
just cutting through some of these
so anemia is in here how many people are
anemic so I just want to hit that a
little bit so anemia is mysterious
that's mysterious to the medical
industry being anemic right so one thing
people don't realize is that low iron
in the blood
a big part of that is low-grade viral
infection
some people have epstein-bars and other
viruses
Epstein-Barr tends to feed on iron so in
a lot of people they're dealing with
this anemia because they're dealing with
a chronic low-grade viral infection
and that's something that so many people
struggle with that they'll never get an
answer to but they'll never get that
answer ever
and they'll just be like dealing with
their anemia not know how to fix it not
know how to heal it
so I'm looking through here too for all
kinds of there's Alzheimer's I can see
that there's
um
there's anxiety there's anxiousness
arrhythmias a lot of people have heart
palpitations and heart issues that are
not physical in the sense where the
heart has a problem how many of you guys
have dealt with that like heart
palpitations right you feel like you
have a a fish that's flopping around in
your chest
good tachycardia and AFib
ectopic heartbeat heart palp so many
people are up against that all the time
this question what's your take on Lupus
and multiple sclerosis so if you look in
medical medium book one you can even
look at brain saver on that somebody's
asking about lupus
so I have Lupus in here and it talks um
it talks about that in here too and
multiple sclerosis there's a whole
section here in multiple sclerosis
that's a very important topic so what is
my take on it
my take is having an answer for multiple
sclerosis that's my take it's something
that you can't get anywhere else in the
industry and that's Epstein-Barr
Epstein-Barr is the cause of multiple
sclerosis now you might be somebody
though
and have seen this there's other people
out there that have had this where
they're misdiagnosed with multiple
sclerosis
and they have a flurry of other
neurological symptoms weakness in the
limbs weakness in the legs weakness in
the arms
all kinds of vibrations and spasms in
the arms ticks and they may get a
multiple sclerosis diagnosis but really
there's something else going on
but then there's multiple sclerosis
where
the nerve sheath
is physically damaged and they can see
that so there's that option to is that
there's that too that diagnosis that
happens for people but in these books
and in the medical medium new addition
right here
I talk about multiple sclerosis and the
details of it and then I talk about
lesions in brain saver
which are really important too in brain
saver protocols a lot of people have
lesions they get diagnosed with multiple
sclerosis but the lesion isn't causing
the problem
so the lesion
in the brain
on the nerve sheath on the spine is not
why they're actually having problems
they could be having problems for other
reasons
and so I go into detail on all kinds of
black spots white spots calcifications
in the brain all kinds of different Scar
Tissue problems people have in their
brain and brain tissue
I talk about stains in the brain
causing
um
causing dark doctors to actually
misdiagnose
multiple sclerosis or issues regarding
that but when it comes down to Multiple
Sclerosis if I was diagnosed with Ms I
would be taking it on like a virus
causing it
and I'd be concerned about Metals too so
when someone has
a diagnosis of multiple sclerosis
that's usually a combination of viruses
like Epstein-Barr and toxic heavy metals
and I would take those two wands
do what's right for you and what your
doctor tells you but that's what I would
do I'd go into the medical meeting books
learn about a multiple sclerosis
protocol
so let's see if we can find one these
books are just like vast textbooks of
information so let me see I'll go into
the protocols book right here
and actually you can go in here too and
find them
so there's a couple of places you can go
for multiple sclerosis you can go right
in here
things
so somebody said the who or linking MS2
I saw that okay down here I measure
hi have MS and have been using medical
medium information to heal just came off
my Ms medication and was able to heal
one of my brain lesions that caused
double vision that's wild blueberry
dreams
on IG
a lot of people first of all I'm proud
of you incredible you're using medical
meme information to heal your MS
lots of people have healed their
multiple multiple sclerosis different
lesions with with the medical medium
information it's all about chronic
illness it's all about
these very things multiple sclerosis on
page 68
right here
so I'm in medical medium book one
the new edition I'm on page 68 multiple
sclerosis
it is so packed with information this
chapter
it has so many details on how it even
occurs what it really is like for
instance I'm reading right here what
multiple sclerosis really is
medical communities believe multiple
sclerosis is an autoimmune disease
resulting from your immune system
somehow confusing areas of your nerve
sheath with Invaders and attacking them
huge mistake by the medical industry
sorry to say
but it's a mistake
it's a medical communities believe it's
your immune system being confused and
attacking your nerve sheath
as I say in other chapters this is a
philosophy that will hold back the truth
in medical research for decades the
human body does not attack itself
pathogens are to blame so it goes on to
how the Epstein bar creates multiple
sclerosis
and then there's sections in here like
healing from multiple sclerosis
it's packed so I'll read you a protocol
really quick a little bit of it Mitchie
says does it have epilepsy yes the Brain
book does
so in the brain books
I talk about epilepsy is here seizures
so if I had multiple sclerosis I would
take this book
right here
and I would look at the protocol and the
first thing in the protocol if you only
did this
the first thing in the protocol is
celery juice
if you're somebody and you're like well
I don't know if I have multiple
sclerosis but I have a lot of symptoms
like this said hey you can always go
this direction in this path but you also
can find your symptoms in the Brain book
specifically
so it starts out with fresh celery juice
work up to 32 ounces daily then work up
to 64 ounces if possible
so if someone has serious
a serious diagnosis and struggles with
multiple sclerosis
that's what it says here now look what
it says it says work up to
work up to 32 ounces that means you
could start at four ounces
inserted six or eight ounces
and that's what it says right there
and then it goes through supplements it
goes through dosages right here you'll
see there's a bunch of different
supplements in here and you could take
it where when you read the supplement
chapter you can see where you can start
slow you can start with one or two
supplements now I know there's a lot
of talk out there about take supplements
or not you don't need to take
supplements to heal stay away from
supplements you'll hear out there
but there's a lot of confusion like
which supplements are you talking about
because you're talking about swallowing
charcoal stay away from it if you're
talking about
you know drinking and swallowing Pearl
powder and Soviet sodium bicarbonate
yeah you shouldn't be doing it if you
talk about supplements that are filled
with natural flavors and citric acid and
all kinds of toxic ingredients sure you
don't want to be using that you should
stay away from it but
supplements are critical
for people who need to customize and go
further with their healing process
this person
is dealing with a host of problems so if
somebody gets a diagnosis of multiple
sclerosis or any kind of neurological
problem they're also probably dealing
with stress
Financial issues all kinds of different
issues
maybe even emotional mental struggles
all of the above
and so it is critical to
Venture into protocols if you need that
now I tell people they can use the
medical medium books and they can just
focus on like the mono
right the mono diet they can focus on
the monoclans they can focus on the
morning cleanse
they can focus on the 369 they can focus
on the 20-day cleanse whatever it is
they can start there or keep that and
then incorporate supplementation too
but I've seen live saved when using
supplementation
properly
in protocols that actually work I've
seen lives get saved problem is in the
industry out there's a lot of
supplements being sold
for a lot of stupid reasons
and so it's a dog eat dog world
there's a battle and a war out there for
everybody
and their grandfather to sell a
supplement
and what's lost is why are people really
sick really what protocol do they really
need
those are the things that matter just
having those details
um a couple different questions here too
someone said
yes please talk more about autism when
kids it's an epidemic and it's only
getting worse so medical meme
information
many years ago
broke the news about toxic heavy metals
in Mercury
in book one and long before that so I'm
in medical medium book one revised
Edition right here
New Edition and I have autism in this
book a whole chapter on it so let's
let's just go into that for a second
guys if you guys have time to sit here
with me I want to talk about some
different conditions I want to look at
some of your questions I want to be
helpful
I know I didn't finish about multiple
sclerosis but there's so much to cover
here and the informations here and I'm
hoping that I'm still getting
information that you can really learn
from and glean from
so let's
find
what's the best cleanse to do for Ms let
me answer that in a second and I'm also
going to find
I find the autism section in here
what I love about these books
is they're so packed with information
I see so many interesting things to talk
about I'm actually like
my mind is exploding right now is what's
happening
all right so ADHD
and autism
so you'll see right here down the corner
I want to read one little thing really
quick what causes ADHD and autism
a popular misconception is that ADHD and
autism are the result of a poor
intestinal environment so you're going
to hear that so if you have a child and
you're going to seek help they're just
going to be all about gut health
I'm not saying that can't be helpful or
not no judgment on any of it
but some current thinking goes that in
overproduction of candida yeast and mold
and non-beneficial bacteria are to
filling for children it's hyperactive in
attentive impulsive or anti-social
Behavior
and then improving intestinal Flora will
improve children's brain health and
alleviate their symptoms so every mom
goes down this course eventually if they
leave the conventional wisdom every mom
will get child with autism end up try
and ends up traveling down that course
this theory is a distraction from what's
really in play that's a bold statement
by SOC in this book right here I'm
talking about autism
anybody can benefit from cleaning up
their gut health even if they're unaware
how or why
in the case of ADHD and autism trying to
improve the intestinal tract environment
with probiotics and probiotic rich foods
is a good intention that's peripheral
you guys hear that that's peripheral
it it doesn't address the true
underlying cause of ADHD and autism
toxic heavy metals
the true underlying Beast of autism and
ADHD toxic heavy metals if you say oh
I've heard that already
you're welcome
I've heard that already you're not
telling me something new medical medium
why am I watching you you're welcome
you're welcome
Decades of my work you're welcome
specifically ADHD and autism are born
from primarily Mercury plus aluminum
that settles in the brain's midline
cerebral canal
which divides the left hemisphere
than the right hemisphere the Mercury
and aluminum can also be in other areas
of the brain sprinkle the bowel in
smaller deposits some even inside the
emotional center of the brain
it might occur to you that it's hard to
build up significant exposure to toxic
heavy metals in just a few years of a
young life
how did my child get filled up with all
these toxic heavy metals
how did it happen however
Mercury is a neurotoxin that slips under
doctors noses
does it ever most doctors are oblivious
to which Medical Treatments they offer
that contain mercury and if they are
aware of it they're either in denial
afraid to break traditional protocol or
they believe in the treatment and that
belief overrides their common sense
about the nature of the toxic heavy
metals medical communities are due for a
massive wake-up call about obvious
Mercury contamination and so what you'll
see now is functional medicine doctors
and different doctors now are testing
for Metals all the time it's like the
routine thing going on so a lot of years
of medical medium work and Publishing
books and getting it out there but it's
now about toxic heavy metals
Mercury is a great instigator of ADHD
and autism in children in the 21st
century Mercury is also responsible for
most seizure disorders so I just want to
answer that a little bit going into the
seizure someone was asking about that
seizure disorders epilepsy
until Mercury and aluminum are addressed
the conditions will continue to affect
millions of new kids each year
millions of new kids around the globe
each year
it's very easy for a baby to take in
toxic heavy metals from her or his
mother while in the womb and for a
father to pass along toxic heavy metals
at conception
mm info
that's because the parents have likely
accumulated Mercury over decades and so
did their mothers and fathers before
them and Mercury tends to stay in the
family both line generation after
generation in some cases for centuries
unless specific steps are taken to
remove it now that's I hate saying this
in the moment but that's original
medical meme info and when you see
somebody on a post somewhere
say you know like somebody that's trying
to amp up a crowd because there's there
are health coach or
whoever it is out there or influencer
and they'll be like Mercury can pass
from generation to generation but no
citation of family one medical medium
genetics are not behind ADHD and autism
now that's going to probably piss off a
few people right there me just saying
that but
it's so interesting and I talk about the
rest of this I mean it's so packed
there's so much information let's keep
on rolling though there's so much to
talk about so I want to be helpful you
guys
and so happy to be here if you guys have
a little time I want to just cut into
some symptoms conditions I was talking
about neurological conditions which is
ADHD and autism but multiple sclerosis
we were talking about too hello what do
you do again what to do against
depression luck of discipline
question mark
let's head into brain saver a little bit
for depression
depression is something that people are
um
they feel like they're prisoners of
depression is
is not describable
by anyone who hasn't suffered from it
truly
I know that so many people have been
through so much but in here I have a
protocol
for depression I have a chapter
and here's a protocol in here for
depression so let's hit that for a
little bit
what's incredible is there's a
depression chapter in
medical medium too as well so I'm going
to find
out where we are here I want to read a
little bit about this to you how many of
you guys are suffering from depression
I'm just curious can you just throw it
at me a little bit if
if you feel up to responding
how many of you guys are dealing with
depression
I'm looking seeing if you guys are
responding about it yet
so I want to read to you a little bit
about this disorder so it's page 266.
I love when someone says oh you don't
know the topic so you have to read out
of your own book
you have to read after the book I mean
it's that much information when we hear
someone has depression we often have a
sense of what that means
they may feel hopeless they may feel
like their existence is worthless they
may they may feel guilty even though
they haven't committed any crime nothing
they do feels like any accomplishment is
made you guys know that sense and that
feeling right anybody who suffered or
struggled with depression how nothing
soothes it nothing
makes it feel better
when it's there and it's in the way so
you guys are all saying yes you guys
have actually experienced that many of
you
wow and a lot of you guys have
experienced depression nothing a person
does feels like it's working you feel
lost
you feel even if you know where you're
supposed to be you feel like you're
still lost
I know that so many people feel like no
matter where they are if they're in the
right place or not their depression is
so agonizing upon them I see so many
yeses oh my God all you guys have all
you guys know what it likes is you know
what it's like suffer from depression
many people who have depression could be
around a loved one and they feel like
they're supposed to be somewhere else
because they're so lost they feel numb
did you guys ever have that where you
feel numb
at all with your depression
so I see many of you guys well a lot of
you guys have depression because you're
sick too you're sick for so long you've
been sick for a long time and you feel
actual like
oppression from that great sadness and
then a lot of you guys just feel
depression regardless you know what that
is
along with these experiences of
depression there can be an inability to
receive any relief
heard that for so many people there's no
relief
depression compounds a depression
compounds upon itself
because part of a person's Consciousness
knows they tried so many Avenues to get
relief
it's like a failure feeling like you
you're trying to get relief for your
depression you're trying to fix it
you're trying to get past it and then
when it fails it's like more depression
compounds upon that depression right it
stacks on top of itself
I know so many of you people have
experienced that
Lee Hines says I don't deal with
depression it is being exhausted all the
time so you're just in the exhaustion
phase all the time so let's hit that for
a little bit let's go into chronic
fatigue let's hit exhaustion I'm going
to go to Medical medium
put one new addition right here
let's let's see if we have something in
there
it's important to know that these are
not
just novelty these books are intense
comprehensive details information
become an expert learn how to heal
yourself
by the way brain saver has information
in the protocols brain saver protocols
has protocols it's really incredible so
I'll show you by the way so you know
I'm a kid in a candy store because when
I hold these
I mean incredible Jewels it's like the
information in here
so that's brain saver right there go to
the library get them for free if you
want or go to Amazon
that's brain saver protocols
just be prepared because you never
would ever have guessed it or known
until you crack into these and you find
out what's wrong with you you find out
why you're sick why you're suffering and
you find out that there's something you
can do for it
when you actually Venture into this it's
a freedom that's indescribable
I've seen so many people
at a place
where they finally get free and nothing
describes that freedom and that feeling
of knowing why they're sick what went
wrong
and how to heal so let's keep on
cracking a little bit into it
I want to talk about fatigue how many of
you guys had fatigue that was maybe
you're dealing with it now it's just not
because you're tired
you have fatigue that's just slowing you
down unexplainable you've been to the
doctor's forth can you guys give me a
little feedback on that if that's okay
face appeal Beauty says your book has
made my life better on IG
so I'm going to
there's adrenal fatigue chapter in here
which is incredible as well
this book is so packed with information
I'm going to go into hidden the hidden
epidemic I'm going to go to page 31
Epstein-Barr virus
um
I've seen Barbara's chronic fatigue
syndrome and fibromyalgia
I'm sure a lot of you guys with your
fatigue you've had that feeling of fibro
that pain that body pain maybe you've
been diagnosed with fibromyalgia so I'm
in this chapter right here Dr fine good
to see you as many times as I look
through the books I always find
something I have missed when I look
again
it's always like that it's the same
thing with me as well always like that
Frenchie league on IG says doctors I've
seen just don't understand because I
look fine on the outside so I can't be
suffering on the inside and they may not
find anything on the inside either
so you're suffering on the inside in so
many different ways and they can't find
an answer
the Epstein-Barr virus has created a
secret epidemic
we're at a place in time where the
majority of the world's population is
living with one or more of the many
mutations of Epstein-Barr virus and what
does it create since we're talking about
fatigue
chronic fatigue syndrome
and I talk about it all through here
this is
incredible resource let me just see here
okay there's a long history of women
kind facing denial that there's a
physical cause of their suffering so you
know I just read the comment right on
Instagram about you feeling like the
doctor doesn't see my problem I look
fine on the outside but I'm suffering on
the inside the first sentence to the
chronic fatigue syndrome right here in
medical medium new addition just get it
from Amazon the books are on sale
they're all inexpensive
there's a long history of women kind
facing denial that there's a physical
cause of their suffering it's the first
line in the chronic fatigue section
sorry guys
like those with fibromyalgia
people with chronic fatigue syndrome
often hear that they are liars
lazy delusional or crazy it's an illness
that affects women
in large numbers it's also starting to
take hold of men men are getting sick
with chronic fatigue in chronic fatigue
syndrome is on the rise it's becoming
common for young women in college to
return home mid-semester with the
condition unable to do anything to lie
in bed
I've seen that years ago it's happening
more now than ever before
unable to do anything
Contracting chronic fatigue syndrome as
a person in your late teens or early 20s
can be particularly devastating as you
watch friends move on with relationships
and jobs meanwhile feeling stuck and
unable to live up to your potential and
maybe you're not in that condition but
you have chronic fatigue syndrome and
it's still hindering you in your life if
you like your legs are like sandbags you
feel like you you literally you feel
like you're being held down like
gravity's pulling you down as you walk
so as you're walking you feel like
gravity is holding you back because your
chronic fatigue syndrome is so intense
and so strong
fly high in YouTube says Anthony your
podcasts and lives
is what keeps me going I'm chronically
sick for over five years and I'm in my
20s oh my God
it's been such a tough Journey but since
I found you I'm empowered and won't give
up don't give up fly high do not give up
do not give up
take your time go through the book
systematically
let the Angels help you go through the
Books open them up
and let the Angels pick the pages but
find find your way
here's something on Instagram right here
at home fitness says I used to have
narcolepsy
but healed because of your information
lemon water celery juice heavy metal
detox adrenal snacks no coffee and
hydrating fruit low protein low fat Etc
and you pulled yourself out of
narcolepsy
that's incredible
McIntyre 792 says I'm 24. 24 you're
young I'm 24 and slowly seeing results
after being on medical medium six months
so far to heal Tourette's
it's freeing to know it's not genetics
and uncurable like doctors told me my
whole childhood Tourette's is curable
Tourette's is healable Tourette's can
be reversed
I've had a doctor recently say that to
me a doctor said to me
aw Tourette's is fixable it's curable
that's what the doctor said to me
recently because he applied it to a
family member the information for
medical medium and the Tourette's turned
around Tourette's is in the brand saver
book by the way
brand saver protocols it's in there
the protocol and
tourettes is in here
for learning about it
narcolepsy is also in the brain sleeper
books Let's kind of crack into that for
a second
I know I'm bouncing around I was just in
chronic fatigue syndrome but I can't
help it I want to answer questions
there's so much information here I'm
trying to Pace myself right now you guys
because this is
a special day to go through this and
take some time thank you for having
patience and being here
so I want to find symptoms and
conditions really quick
which
I mean seriously
these books are so big
a b c d e f g h i j k l
okay
I think I see you comment there Jen says
no wait the call says the comment went
down we healed by Addison's the other
years ago medical meme information gave
me my life back and got me off steroids
unfortunately had a medical injury and
sick again but this too will heal
it will
here's Tourette's right here
guys don't mind if I count the alphabet
letters go through them
told you the information came from above
I am not a smart guy but the books
supersede Medical Science in so many
ways it's unbelievable the information
comes from above Tourette's syndrome is
caused primarily by Mercury and copper
Mercury and copper when you learn how to
get that out of your brain Tourette's
goes away
Tourette's syndrome is caused primarily
by Mercury and copper with traces of
lead impeding electrical impulses
in the brain here's how it happens when
an electrical impulse travels across the
synapses it's something like traveling
through a tunnel if it's a depositive
toxic heavy metal surrounds that tunnel
inside the brain the toxic heavy metals
narrow the channel creating a bottleneck
the electrical impulse traveling through
gets hung up practically stuck in a
short amount of time a fraction of a
second another electrical impulse
follows behind it this new electrical
limb pulse hits the impeded electrical
impulse and propels the impeded
electrical impulse forward this is like
unlike OCD where an electrical impulse
hits a heavy metal deposit and gets
propelled backwards in Tourette's the
copper mixed with lead that's
surrounding the synapsis conducts the
electrical impulses forward even as the
bottlenecking blocks the impulses
physically to some degree sometimes both
electrical impulses are even stuck
together combined and they shoot out
together and that's what Tourette's is
it's an electrical impulse
filled with information a thought and a
word you guys just got in there talking
about Tourette's so Tourette's is an
electrical impulse filled with
information
in that electricity in the electrical
impulse and thoughts
and emotions
and when it gets hung up
in that tube synapsis it shoots forward
out from being bottlenecked and when it
does
Tourette's occurs now there's different
varieties of threats
and in different ways depending on where
the metals are situated in the brand
so we're talking about Tourette's
there's so much information in here you
guys we could spend days upon days weeks
upon weeks and it's still weeks still
couldn't cover it all there's protocols
in brain saver that you can customize
for everything customized for Tourette's
customized I'm looking on here
in here tremors
vertigo trigeminal neuralgia it just is
endless
okay
ticks and spasms
tinnitus
and it goes on seizures let's talk about
seizures for a minute because I know a
lot of people know people with seizures
a lot of people suffer greatly with that
one so if you guys got a minute
internet nonsense of severe seizures
come from large deposits of heavy metals
rather than sprinklings
so
everybody has a sprinkling of toxic
heavy metals inside their brain
everybody
has a sprinkling of toxic heavy metals
inside their brain looks like Christmas
tree lights
okay sometimes there are even clusters
of large deposits although it's usually
only a cluster of two deposits when it
comes down to seizures
what creates these seizures is the
interaction of metal specifically in
alloy of mercury aluminum and copper
with all three of those residing next to
each other or sometimes even partially
forged together through excessive heat
exchange from past seizures most people
who suffer from seizures
severe seizures were exposed to all
three Metals at the same time
so I talk about with people that suffer
from seizures they talk about all the
details and it's really a huge piece of
information in here
but there's a protocol for seizures in
these books there's the brand saver
protocols
if I was having seizures
I would dive into these books
and I would start going through the
protocols
I would get the metals out of my system
out of my brain
and minimize those seizures over time
it can be done because it has been done
so many times for people
but take the books to your doctor ask
your doctor if it's okay and if if it's
right for you and then your doctor tells
you brain saver books
have seizures in here you can find them
in the brain saver books seizure and
protocol seizure and
here
information and material
epilepsy
Okay so
any of you guys ever had tinnitus
popping in the year raining in the year
I'm just curious on that right there
because there's so many people there
because a lot of people so I want to go
into this people who have chronic
fatigue syndrome
most people with CFS or fatigue issues
don't just have fatigue only
they have a little bit of dizziness see
that they have some tinnitus we have
some ringing and popping in the ear
they have aches and pains a lot of
people with fatigue chronic fatigue
syndrome will also have some fibro
and some tinnitus and some vertigo
when you look inside these books
if you guys don't have the medical meme
New Edition please consider it if you
guys don't have the brain saver
protocols book or the brain zero please
consider it
get the information become an expert
learn it
get yourself better
get yourself out of the woods
pull yourself out of the woods
with the information
change your life
baby Paris says you're over there on
YouTube
I say you left the YouTube comment the
other day day four of 369 advanced
doing this for my allergies they were
horrible this year proud of you Bibi
Paris amazing
and IG do you explain memory and inflect
loss at early age of 45
oh my god do I ever
do I ever how about memory loss
protocols how about protocols for memory
loss
seriously
they're here
incredible protocols for memory loss
Alzheimer's memory issues dementia
there's a dementia Alzheimer's chapter
but just because you have memory loss
don't don't go to that place
then that doesn't mean you have anything
like that it's easy to have trauma and
have memory loss
it's easy to have trauma in your life
and have memory loss it's easy to have
too many toxic heavy metals in your
brain and have memory loss
it's easy for that to happen
so
so much information in here I just
opened it up to microdosing
Erica asks any other languages on this
books these books yes
um almost in every single country in the
world
um could be in every country in the
you can find them publish
out there
but look go to medicalmedium.com take a
look at the international editions at
medicalmedium.com go to
medicalmedium.com
so I'm just going through
um
hey misguided hangover cures
there's so much information in here
medical medium website for so much free
information it's free everywhere on
medical medium website keep that in mind
it's very free it's all free over there
so let's head into memory a little bit I
want to go into there how many of you
guys are dealing with memory issues
I would love to know
my mind is free on IG doctors told me I
have a special type of rheumatism that
attacks my Muslims
they want me to get they want me to give
one year therapy with cortisone okay uh
after I start drink lemon water and
celery I got healed
okay
so the doctors told you to do one year
on cortisone
you did lemon water and celery
and it's gone
and you're healed
that's incredible
he's in front
and I'm privately
stay on the sellers you stay on the
lemon water
please stay on there
um Terry Appleman says no info is
detailed
and then it just no like medical medium
info no no info is detailed like medical
medium info comments Bounce Around
[Music]
all right
you guys seriously so much information
in here
I don't even know I'm speechless
Elizabeth says house some children
inherent symptoms like one mother and
other like Father symptoms yes passed
down for Generation after generation
through toxic heavy metals DDT radiation
other poisons and toxins and viruses FC
bar shingles hhb six hhv7 herpes simplex
1 Herpes Simplex 2 whatever they just
they get passed down
so metals and viruses and pathogens get
passed down it's nobody's fault
it's nobody's fault
but wait a minute
sometimes it's not just that sometimes
it's exposure exposure unexpected
exposure and I thought that I talked
about that I just read that earlier
what that means Beatrice
where did you go Beatrice Beatrice my
heart starts racing just as I'm about to
fall asleep what is it due to
also has unpleasant extra strong
Heartbeats
so
look
if your heart's racing that falls under
like ectopic heartbeat it falls under
it's not that but it falls under the
hole right you've got something going on
with the heart heart racing but you've
gone to your doctors your doctors didn't
diagnose you with afib your doctors
didn't diagnose you with ectopical
heartbeat or doctors didn't diagnose you
with something
so that's another thing all on its own
did you get a diagnosis from the doctor
you know telling you what it is it's one
thing to know
another thing is a lot of people have
racing
Heartbeats
racing pulse racing heart
I mean there's so many things people are
dealing with one is just falling asleep
is because you're calming yourself down
enough to feel the fact that that's
fluctuating I've had a lot of people go
through that in life where it's that
moment when you're laying down to go to
bed
right there another thing too A lot of
people have anxiety before they go to
sleep and it cranks up there's so many
reasons why people deal with that I'm
giving you a whole bunch of them because
I want everybody to have an option
something there's hundreds of people out
there right now watching this so I want
to make sure they can kind of find their
way with this a lot of you guys might
have a racing heart at different times a
lot of you guys might have tachycardia
aphid you might have heart palps
um
um all the different issues with with
their heart racing the heartbeat
and
so I talk about it in these books a lot
of people have electricity heart racing
it's electricity it's coming from the
brain stem coming from the brain down to
the heart
and racing the heart and it's not a
physical heart problem
a lot of people just have so much junk
in the liver that's another reason too
they get a stickiness inside the valves
I've talked about that for years
Palace he says my nephew is throwing up
10 times a day
no doctors can figure it out please help
that's awful
it really is what I recommend is take
the doctors take the books to your
doctors
had it backwards
take the books to your doctors
um
ask your doctors if it's okay
right if you can go there go look into
the books
customize a protocol
start with the basics take it to the
doctor and if the doctor is all right
about that so let's go into that so you
have a nephew that's throwing up so if I
had a nephew that was throwing up 10
times a day I would be going into
mystery vomiting mystery nausea
so that's what I would do so let's see
if we can find something these books are
jam-packed
give me a minute if we can
I'm going to start with this one
um
let's try to get there
mystery nausea is something so many
people suffer from
all right
it takes a minute you guys look for this
just bear with me these are massive
textbooks
I am not a professor
and I'm not the professor in Gilligan's
Island right
so I am not a professor at a elite and
an elite University
looking at this massive medical
textbooks right here
so I'm looking for nausea here it is
Mystery nausea
okay
Godspeed
ABC a b c d e f g h
i j
because I have to try to make you laugh
once in a while
it's under mystery nausea and vomiting
there it is I will because it took so
long to get here I will read and I will
be at your disposal and I will read a
metric disposal
you can throw me out if you need to just
throw me out mystery nausea and vomiting
when someone is experiencing nausea or
vomiting the first thing almost everyone
assumes is that it's a stomach related
issue
someone who visits a doctor complaining
of nausea will grip your stomach like
your nephew did I'm sure your nephew did
that will grip their stomach because
that's where they're feeling
uncomfortable
it's true that these symptoms can
originate from the stomach in intestinal
area when food poisoning our stomach flu
are behind the symptoms in some cases
stomach cancer can also cause nausea and
vomiting although in many cases they're
not symptoms of the disease most cases
of unexplained nausea now get this
foreign
most cases of unexplained Aussie and
vomiting have everything to do with the
central nervous system and nearby nerves
keep that in mind here all right when
you're dealing with mystery nausea
sensual nervous system
come on big guy
let's get over here somewhere let's see
if we can get you over here uh
let's let's try this here
central nervous system
so
if I had a nephew
that was vomiting 10 times a day
doctors didn't know what it was they
probably looked at tummy
colonoscopy endoscopy all of it right
I would be looking here
in the brain
central nervous system
right but wait
the vagus nerves which originate in the
brain stem
okay
multitasking here just bear with me
the vagus nerves which originate in the
brain stem are the most important nerves
regarding anything to do with the
stomach if the vagus nerves are inflamed
or irritated on any level whether up in
or near the brain itself or down closer
to the stomach the vagus nerves
affecting the stomach
do you see where I'm going
the vagus nerve affecting the stomach
the vagus nerves can go into spasm
nausea can occur
often the reason for vagus nerve
inflammation is a chronic low-grade
viral infection that's releasing
neurotoxins
take the book to your doctor ask your
doctor if it's a low-grade viral
infection
affecting the vagus nerve through
neurotoxin inflammation and what's
Happening Here is
in a nutshell the vagus nerve is
inflamed and aggravated and agitated
causing a heaving spasm to happen which
means vomiting with no
reason it's a mystery
Celeste Waldo says you're so amazing aw
you keep me going on my darkest days I
go back and listen to your telegram
audio messages I'll leave more I feel
bad and I'll leave enough of them in
other inspires inspiring Clips they give
me the lift I need to feel like I can
heal Celeste I'm so glad you're
listening to those I will listen to I
will admit sorry I will listen to you
that you're listening to this telegram
messages I will leave more
toxic heavy metals inside the brain
close to the vagus nerves you guys can
also cause nausea so toxic heavy metals
inside the brain
can cause nausea
brand new exposure to a heavy metal such
as mercury can cause nausea and vomiting
I would say to my nephew did you get any
new exposure I don't know about
you didn't tell me were you
I'm not saying your nephew does this on
here I'm just saying were you vaping
were you doing something that has toxic
heavy metal exposure
vaping is definitely an antagonistic
thing
no judgment for anybody who Vapes it's
not uncommon for someone to get all
their dental amalgam fillings removed
and be overcome by these symptoms
afterward D2 Mercury exposure causing
vomiting all the time
I'm just reading the different you have
to you have to find the piece that fits
to you it's here the answers are here
other Verizon Mercury exposure for
Medical Treatments can cause nausea and
vomiting too
a very interesting one right there
I'm not trying to read too deep into
that I'm just saying that's really
interesting other Medical Treatments can
cause mysterious nausea
further migraines and other headaches
related to viral infections or toxic
heavy metals can make their way to the
phagus nerve
allowing a baby syrup to be extra
sensitive
causing
some vomiting
when the brain experiences an emotional
blow whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa I know my
brain
has experienced some serious emotional
blows
it has
when the brain experiences an emotional
blow or upset that makes us sick in the
gut or heart that's all vagus nerve
related my vagus nerves I never try to
make this about me Anthony Wayne
from my face nurse taking a hit this
year
taking a hit
Rita Hanley says what book is that
and where can I get it because I have
some of the symptoms that may want to
and they may want me to take meds but I
won't and I wake up nauseous every
morning because I have vertigo and
um I have it every day
so thank you medical medium
okay
via vertigo you want medical medium new
addition you want that you can also get
yes the brain saver books there's
protocols for vertigo in both these
books meaning like protocols vertigo in
here you can see there's two brain saver
books
and then there's the medical medium new
addition right here there's vertigo in
this one you can go in here you can get
a protocol bring the protocol to your
doctor
bring the book to your doctor if you'd
like but there we go we're gonna go in
here
we're a mystery vomiting
sinus infections from strep that's been
the walls of the sinus cavities for
years can also cause chronic nausea as a
result of sinus nerves affecting facial
nerves and other cranial nerves
eventually placing pressure on the vagus
nerves
there are certain situations where
someone can have acid reflux due to a
toxic liver and overload of strep rates
pylori and the intestinal tracting sibo
and this can cause nausea too so I'm
giving you just a couple of rundown how
many people have nauseated
you so many of you guys probably have
chronic nausea
and
um
but you're not projectile vomiting or
vomiting every day a bunch of times many
of you guys probably have nausea right
it's this is packed with information you
guys
so let's talk about shock therapies
something mind-blowing and brain saver
Goldenseal shock therapy for UTIs acne
and all that too I want to talk about
that protocol so let's get into it
protocols book
propolis shock therapy
all right let's find the brain shot
Therapies
let's go let's go let's go
brain shot therapy
we're looking for br we're sorry we're
looking for shock therapies of course
you know the incredible thing about
these books is there's so much
information
okay check this out
it's a medical medium shock therapies
right here
I'm showing you guys
my family my friends
rely on this
medical medium shock therapies let's go
into this a little bit
you'll find that some of the supplement
protocols in this next
chapter call for optional and it shows
in medical medium zinc shock therapy
medical medium vitamin C shock therapy
medical medium lemon bomb shock therapy
medical medium golden seal shock therapy
medical medium time t-shock therapy
priceless
information you can't get anywhere in
the health Bowl on any level
life-changing information medical medium
propolis shock therapy medical medium
aloe vera shock therapy medical medium
B12 shock therapy medical medium
California poppy shock therapy
it's insane really incredible
so I'm going to talk about this let's
hit
the Goldenseal shock therapy
these are tools that move the needle you
guys these are life-changing tools I
can't say it enough I try to stay calm I
try to stay cool about it but I want to
scream from the rooftops I want to climb
a mountain high and stand on the top of
that mountain in the Alps or something
and I want to freaking scream my head
off on how we are so gang lucky that
these medical medium shock therapies
exist on this planet
and what they can accomplish and have
accomplished in my personal life and the
people I know and the people that have
used these shock Therapies ask your
doctor though before you do one if it's
right for you
let's hit the golden seal shark there
yeah
I want to go on a cruise ship
I really don't want to go on a cruise
ship but I want to go on a cruise ship
and I want to sit at the front of the
cruise ship like on the Titanic
right I don't want to stand there and
scream my head off about these shots
all right
well I don't want to be on a cruise ship
um okay suggested applications for
medical medium Goldenseal shock therapy
cold flu
sinus congestion allergies bronchitis
pneumonia lung infections acute cough or
chronic cough earaches ear infections
strep throat sore throat did you guys
ever have strep throat maybe you don't
even know you have strep throat you have
a bad sore throats you guys ever have
bad sore throat strep throat
sore throat runny nose post nasal drip
styes conjunctivitis
UTIs bladder infections
medical medium Goldenseal shock therapy
a god-given blessing I can't even tell
you all right UTI bladder infections
kidney infections bacteria vaginosis BV
pelvic inflammatory disease PID
yeast infections all varieties of acne
this is incredible
all varieties of acne cold sores fever
blisters
herpes simplex 1 Herpes Simplex 2
seriously shingles acute neurological
symptoms difficult menstruation Cycles H
pylori
staff MRSA mononucleosis
Goldenseal shock therapy directions
come in here
and it's right here
all the directions are in there
on IG miyamona says hi Anthony could you
say something about getting acne after
being two years on medical beating
protocols
okay so a couple of things
you can go and Shop in the grocery store
grab the handles on the carriage
it's loaded with streptococcus
streptococcal whatever however you want
to say I like saying streptococcus
and I know a doctor friendly call to
streptococcus or either or
it's loaded with strep all on the handle
of your Carriage load it
it's not just loaded with strap from
everybody wiping their ass
and having it on their hands
because quite frankly
I know a lot of people that only use one
sheet to wipe their ass and I understand
why
because toilet paper costs money
but if I wiped my ass with this sheet
my hand would definitely be soiled
so
everybody out there
has their feces on their hands
unless they're washing their hands
before they go into the grocery store
and grab the cart
which I highly doubt
there's gonna be strep 10 different ways
till Sunday
on that card handle
if you're not doing an alcohol rub on
that card handle
whatever
all you have to do is get that on your
hands and here's the problem
antibiotic resistant strips
strips that can put people in hospitals
are all over those handles and door
handles and carriage handles
it's easy to pick up a new strip on The
Daily
you can reverse your conditions heal
your Epstein-Barr heal things take the
metals out of your body and guess what
you can go and pick up a brand new strap
and get a new batch of acne or a UTI or
something else
so the tools in these books are to knock
down what you're getting
I know people that have healed with
medical medium information got into a
brand new relationship
with a new partner picked up two or
three new epstein-bars two brand new
straps
a Simplex herpes one and they went back
to drawing board again
I'm not saying you can't have intimacy
or you shouldn't have a relationship
that's not it at all nothing to do with
that
I'm just saying that the protocols are
here for life
life
a lot of people heal from their bugs
that they already have and then go and
collect a whole round of another batch
of bugs
acne protocol and cleanse the heel or
live a rescue golden seal is incredible
too which is in here cold and still
shock Therapies
liver rescues amazing for the there's an
African chapter in here
I mean honestly you guys should all have
the books
sure
probably shock therapy
incredible all on its own
my God probably shock therapy it's
another great one
um so let's talk about propolis shock
therapy ready
sore throat strep throat tonsillitis
sinus infections allergies lung
infections bronchitis pneumonia cough
post nasal drips cold flu
ear infections UTIs bladder infections
kidney infections fever itself do you
think AI picked that up
fever chills night sweats trigeminal
neuralgia gum pain mouth pain tooth pain
tongue pain migraines headaches shingles
bouts of neurological symptoms cold
sores fever blisters herpes simplex 1
canker sores and mouth ulcers
propolis
propolis shock therapy
incredible all on its own
anyway so what happens with a lot of
people
they'll um they'll also keep in mind
this this can happen too your immune
system is battling a lot of different
things inside your body so you're
somebody that's got a lot going on
you've got to strep from acne or you've
got a strap from strep throat from
childhood you've got uh you had
mononucleosis when you were a child you
have two or three different viruses you
have metals and you your immune system
is battling off that and then other
exposures right the immune system is
trying to gobble all that up and eat all
that up right that's what your immune
system is doing and then you guys
has your immune system's gobbling
everything up up and eating everything
up you're healing
you're healing
but when there's a lot to heal
anything can trigger you and tip you
back too maybe you had blood work done
and they took too much blood and you
didn't read the blood draw chapter right
here in this book
the blood draw chapter is critical to
read it so critical I can't even say it
so let me let me go in here and it's an
insane chapter it's just insane
yeah
so I got some vials of blood here I just
happen to keep blood sphere blood in the
refrigerator
should I just open the refrigerator I
happen to keep spare blood
and I'm gonna bring some vials of blood
here you think this is a Biohazard
is this a do you think this these
bottles of my blood or a blood or a
Biohazard
anyway okay so
what happens is that people
they're healing they're working on their
healing they're battling a whole bunch
of different problems in their health
they're battling bugs they're battling a
condition of some kind
that's caused by pathogens their immune
system is working really hard and then
they go to their doctor for routine
blood work and the doctor's drawing a
ton of blood out of them
and so you want to understand this you
want to know this because I'll tell you
right now I've seen this bring people to
their knees and bring them to an early
grave I'm not against blood testing I
sound like a broken record I'm not
against blood testing I'm not against
blood testing
but there's things you have to
understand about getting your blood
drawn and that alone can knock your
immune system back so if you still have
a strep inside you boom now you got acne
a month after you had your blood work
two months after you had your blood work
as your immune system drops
so it isn't just always catching new
bugs which it is a lot it's also
it's also your immune system dropping
for some other reason you have no idea
about because you weren't taught
Laura Christine over there on YouTube
blood draws messed me up before medical
medium that podcast episode is gold
thank you very much Laura
and the blood draw chapter in here is
freaking insane
please get the book for that alone I beg
of you walk into the library
and tell that librarian
to get you the book
or go to Amazon
educating myself glad to see you're
there educating myself you didn't get
fooled
you didn't get fooled
buy all the shenanigans that occurred
I was reading your comments and you you
were keen on stuff about all the BS and
you obviously I think did you research
on stuff about all that too recently
interesting okay see you guys
there's so much information here
I think what I'll do is inject myself
with this vial of blood
I found this in a garbage can by a
medical center I'm just kidding this is
ketchup
read and learn the info it's there for
you to become your own expert
read and learn the info
you guys
Jenna Lynn Garza said burning mouth
syndrome yeah
that's a big one burning mouth syndrome
let's go fine let's go find it what book
do I need
burning mouth syndrome
where where
uh let's go here shingles virus let's go
here this is one option right here brain
Savers the other option
there's a shingles chapter right here
critical
um
see where I'm going Bernie Mount
syndrome
and then in here too
so many books don't know what to do with
them
someday Dr Nesbitt will visit us again
let's just hope it's soon because I need
him to uh give me a break
um anyway guys
proud of all of you I did not get that
viable blood at a garbage can by a
medical center I did not
um I found that vial Blood on the beach
in L.A it floated to the shore
just kidding
it's my sense of humor is not always the
best
newsletter going to be some exciting
things coming up please stay tuned with
the newsletter sign up to the newsletter
if you don't get my newsletter
something's wrong then
so try to re-sign up to it or something
go to medicalme.com and figure out how
to do it but be on the newsletter
because I'm also going to be offering
light blast in the future check out
Medical medium.com
check your spam
for for my newsletter it seems to kick
out to everybody's spam be on the
lookout for telegram Twitter and Tick
Tock yeah yeah yeah I'm gonna actually
try to do that Tick Tock again
did you see what happened you guys
my account was like killer it was
amazing I had all these funny videos on
there
and it was incredible I had like 600 000
or 700 000 or something followers on
there and I was verified on Tick Tock
and the day of my book launch the
day of my book launched
they permanently Banned Me
when I showed the book all right
the night before the book launch
all right and uh
anyway guys
trying it again so I'm gonna do some
original unique obviously material
exclusive on Tick Tock we'll see what
happens and I'll try to do some also
stuff on telegram as well
once in a while I swear
I love you guys very much
okay listen
let's let's talk about this for a second
okay
something critical you have to
understand
and I know this runs through people's
veins
it's blaming yourself
blaming yourself
for any kind of adversity and any kind
of struggle
it's blaming yourself
okay now when it comes down to health
issues if you're struggling with a
symptom depression multiple sclerosis
anything we talked about nausea anxiety
seizures whatever it is we covered a lot
of stuff CFS
whatever it is not your fault
I can promise you it's not your fault
you have to remember that
that's critical and don't forget it it
gets in the way of your healing process
when you believe it's your fault
it interferes
it messes with your mind
it messes with your soul
if you're sick you're sick and it's not
your fault something happened
and it's about discovering why
and how to correct it and move forward
because your body loves you
unconditionally and it wants to heal
your body wants to heal and it loves you
unconditionally and you can't forget
that
you cannot forget that
don't forget that
and you're not a bad person you didn't
create your symptoms you didn't create
your doctor bills you didn't create
your compromises from being sick
you didn't create your emotional pain
and you didn't create your losses you
have to remember that and don't forget
this pat yourself on the back have
compassion for yourself critical
critical
I know
that it's not your fault that you're
sick or have a chronic illness or a
symptom I know I need you to know I know
I know SOC knows but I need you to know
I love you guys
I'll see you next time