cook a meal it's a recipe
from the revised and expanded
medical medium book one okay the new
this is gonna be the
the new release the new edition right
here i don't know if you can see that
or if the lights kind of shine there it
is right and
that's the medical medium revised and
expanded
um book that's going to be coming out
pretty soon you can get it on amazon
okay so check out for the link in the
description
and i'm going to be cooking that recipe
right there that you're looking at so
i'm excited about this so that's the one
i'm
actually going to be cooking for you
guys i'm also going to make the heavy
metal detox smoothie too
and that's why the blender blender's
right here and everything because you
got to get the metals out
and i talk about the toxic heavy metals
in
this book right here the medical medium
revised and expanded so new addition so
that's on amazon right now i'm excited
about this
this is this is a big deal because
there's 45 recipes in here now
in this new new edition which is
incredible and i talked about autism and
adhd
ptsd depression
toxic heavy metals and ir this is this
is the book that broke out
the whole thing about toxic heavy metals
being behind autism
adhd this incredible book that's that's
really saved lives around the world
right well this is the new edition
that's coming out soon you want to check
it out
you'll see the link in the description
um and so i'm going to be cooking this
recipe
right here which i'm excited about now
this recipe
is in this new release i mean in this
new edition book revise and expand it so
over 45 recipes in here too so just
letting you know
this is the 28-day cleanse menu plans
that are in here that were never
in book one to start with when this
first book released
to begin with and i'm going to talk all
about it as we're going along but i'm
going to be making this recipe right now
so you're in my kitchen you guys i'm
excited about this i got the pan right
here
pan's getting hot so i'm going to start
making stuff that i'm going to make the
heavy metal detox smoothie and talk
about
how to get the metals out of your brain
so you get rid of the bipolar
the mood swings you get rid of the
anxiety the depression the ocd
adhd all of it so that's important too
so i'm going to be doing a heavy metal
detox smoothie so i got a lot planned
right now for you guys
and so i'm excited about this anyway so
i just want to get some
some food going right here to start with
really quick so i got to get that
going in the pan right here i'm cutting
an onion so
hopefully you guys can hear me okay
so i'm making a recipe
that's in the medical medium new edition
so um i'm excited about this really
so i'm doing this as we speak here
cutting up some onions i don't know if
you guys can see this
um and there's a lot to talk about i'm
going to talk about
the damage that toxic heavy metals do
inside the brain
and why people have problems why people
are struggling so much so i'm definitely
going to cover that right there i'm
throwing some onions in here
right in this pan so it's it's a half
cup of chopped onions
i'm putting a little bit more in this
one just you know
i'm gonna add a little extra onion for
me today so i got that
so half chopped onion half cup of
chopped onions i got the onions in here
i'm gonna do some potatoes now
um got these golds these
incredible gold potatoes right here
three and a half cups
of potatoes and you'll see you'll see
the recipe
when you get this book and you'll see
the details on it all
three and a half cups
[Music]
of diced potatoes right here so i'm
gonna dice up some potatoes real quick
and get this in the pan going
[Music]
we're gonna do three and a half cups
it's gonna take a minute so if you guys
are just coming on here i'm excited
because
i'm making a recipe that's in
this revised and expanded medical medium
okay book right here
so it's on amazon links in description
so i'm cooking potatoes and onions down
right now
once these are cooking i'm going to make
the heavy metal detox smoothie
heavy metal detox smoothie has saved a
lot of lives
it's really incredible what it has done
over the years the advanced information
about toxic heavy metals that i put out
in the medical medium book book one
no one knew about and it's becoming kind
of like
law out there in the health field
because of the information in the
medical medium books and especially
medical medium book one it's really
amazing what has happened
so i'm gonna do about three and a half
cups of potato right here
[Music]
chopping them up and i'm gonna try to
answer some questions too you guys so
so it's not a lot to talk about
[Music]
it's got three and a half cups of potato
in here just about almost please do a
little bit more
and it might be putting one more in here
[Music]
so i'm making a recipe if you guys just
gotta got on here
from the new edition which i'm excited
about so i'm gonna cook for about
you know a few minutes to get these uh
to get these onions translucent
i'm gonna add a little bit of water in
this pan right here it's a little touch
of it that's all
gonna put the lid on it in a little bit
you add a little bit of water to stop
the uh
anything from sticking which is good so
i'm cooking this up right here
um so anyway i want to answer some
questions
so for some reason the questions are
stuck and they're not rolling up right
now but i want to answer a few questions
here
and see what's going on um you guys if
you just got on here this is exciting
right now because i'm i'm pumped about
making this recipe here
so this is really good there's no oil in
this recipe really important to know so
there's no oil in here
no radical fats in this recipe so that's
so you can do some healing because the
minute you put oil in that recipe the
minute you put fats in that recipe
then you're stuck all of a sudden now
the comments are moving up so that's
helpful
um so i could read some anyway so i'm
making a recipe out of this book
it's not the original book just so you
know
this is going to be the new release it's
the new addition revised and expanded
talk about it a little bit that's the
recipe i'm gonna be actually making
right now for you guys
i was gonna make the heavy metal detox
smoothie in a little bit
[Music]
so
so what's really cool about the new
edition as i talk about
what we're up against now i talk about
the plague that we're up against now in
this new addition so that's one thing
that you're going to find
when you do get the book there's new
spiritual information
there's new meditations in here there's
more essential angels in here and it's
really
this book already has changed the lives
of so many with this powerful
information including like the sun
bathing meditation
the sunset meditation so i added more
meditations too it's really
it's really exciting what i've done to
it so i added a book
to this book basically and
for a new edition you're not supposed to
do that and i broke the rules and i
added a book to it which is really
incredible 45 recipes in here expand at
the 28-day cleanse
and the menu plans dosages and
supplements
this book basically this book already
i mean what it's done around the world
right now
and then i expanded upon it is what
happened
so i mean i'm just really really excited
about you guys getting it
and having it in your hands i can't wait
for that day
um you know you can pre-order it now so
i'm making the recipe that i was just
showing you right here
okay it's a morning hash and that's the
recipe i don't know if you guys can see
it so that's
in the new book this is my manuscript so
this isn't the book itself but this is
my manuscript right here
um before i hand it in to the publisher
there's more information on chronic
fatigue syndrome in the new book more
information
about lupus there's more information
about epstein-barr
in the new book so i'm reading that
question right there
there's a depression chapter really
important one
migraines and headaches chapter thyroid
chapter
additional information there shingles
chapter and
like what happens is that people didn't
even know what shingles even cost like
what conditions
they just thought it was a rash and that
was it like a rash and that was all it
was
and shingles is a lot more than that
because shingles causes trigeminal
neuralgia now that's medical medium
information that's
that came from that book and and before
it colitis
anybody with colitis you know that's the
shingles virus that causes colitis
so that's something there that is
important to know
sciatic pain you know this whole sciatic
pain the nerve pain the back pain people
get
when they're just they're hurting
they've got the pain down the leg but
yet
but yet it shouldn't be causing them a
problem they don't have that much of a
problem with their disc or their lower
spine
and even when they get their lower spine
adjusted or chiropractor says the lower
spine looks good in all this stuff
it's it's still inflamed they can't walk
they got the worst sciatic pain that's
the shingles too so i broke the
information out about that
being shingles and i talk about the
different types of shingles and rashes
um so it's really really a power power
packed
book um multiple sclerosis i talk about
that too
and so when you get the new edition
revised and expanded
it's a game changer i put a whole
another book into this
it's really incredible so i want to talk
about lyme disease too a little bit
in a little bit right now i'm cooking
this up and
lyme disease is there's really a tragic
history with lyme disease
and i expose that tragic history
um and talk about how you know people
were
taken advantage of they dumped they
dumped antibiotics in people
just hundreds of thousands of people
back in the old
in the old days back 20 years ago 30
years ago they still do it now they just
pounded people with antibiotics made
their symptoms worse
pushed him into the worst neurological
lyme conditions
killed a few yeah killed a few
so the history of lyme is really great
it's terrible it's like the negligence
the mistakes made by
a lot of the old lyme doctors still
still being made with the new lyme
doctors
many of them and
the the wake
of hell and just just
negligence of people with lyme disease
being told it's bacterial
being convinced it's bacterial because
big pharma wants to sell the drugs
and has really destroyed a lot of lives
and i exposed it for the first time in
our history
medical medium book one and so um
that information is in here in the
revised and expanded
and i also release the truth about lyme
disease
how it's viral and
that original book medical medium book
one you guys
um millions of copies went around the
world it's the most popular health book
ever in history by the way so this book
right here is the most popular health
book
in all health history so um for years
running now
and because i expose the truth about
lyme disease how it's viral so what
happened though the power of that
what it did was it forced the medical
communities it forced
uh science of research to have to take
lyme disease out of the bacterial
category
so just so you know even though there's
still some some
lyme doctors trying to test for still
some lyme doctors trying to test for uh
lyme bacteria
science and research above the lyme
doctors have moved it out of the
bacterial
category so big pharma doesn't think
it's
bacteria anymore they put it in
autoimmune and the reason why they did
that
is because of medical medium books and
information because so many doctors
follow medical medium books around the
world
so um i'm gonna put the lid on here
this is what i'm gonna do
cook that up a little bit i'm going to
make the heavy metal detox smoothie
what happens with people with lyme
disease is they'll have they'll be high
in toxic heavy metals
and that's a thing anybody with chronic
fatigue syndrome
lupus chronic fatigue syndrome lupus
fibromyalgia multiple sclerosis they're
high in heavy metals
people with multiple sclerosis symptoms
neurological symptoms
high in toxic heavy metals and so metals
are a big
part of it it's not just pathogens like
viruses like
i've taught about all these years it's
um the combination of toxic heavy metals
and
pathogens um so that that's that's why
the heavy metal detox smoothie is so
critical and so important and that heavy
metal detox smoothie
is in the revised and expanded new
edition right here you get it amazon.com
is where you get it or
barnes and noble it's another place too
um you can order it
so let's talk about the the the heavy
metal detox smoothie right here do two
cups of wild blueberries
i got that so wild blueberries are
really
an essential part of this smoothie
keep that in mind really really
important part of that smoothie
like really critical so we got that in
there that's one thing there
and i'm gonna put a couple of bananas in
there
that's what i'm gonna do so
you guys just got on here i was talking
about medical medium book one
but they're revised expanded
talking about toxic heavy metals this
information in this heavy metal detox
movie has healed people around the world
adhd autism focus and concentration
problems ocd
the medical medium book one
had the smoothie in there the heavy
metal detox smoothie so
ptsd that too so we got the bananas in
there we got the wild blueberries
and then i'm going to put some cilantro
in here too
because that's one of the key critical
pieces
now in order to get metals out of
somebody and get them get
metals out properly you got to have some
other critical key pieces so
a spirulina that's a must but what i've
learned
about products out there is that if you
don't
have the right kind of product the right
thing is not going to happen
that's just naturally what goes on so
this is a spirulina the only one i trust
right now on the market
it's the only one and i'm not sponsored
just so you know
so i'm not sponsored by the company um
but this is the spirulina so this is the
vibragi spirulina vias and victor i am
as in mary e-r-g-y
and this is critic a critical part
of getting the metals out corella
doesn't work
never did corella is toxic it's got
problems it doesn't remove metals
i recommend anybody who's doing corolla
in my personal opinion i would never do
it
i talked about that for years and not
just any spirulina
so what you'll see is i used to support
pacific spirulina because it was the
decent stuff that was out at the time
since then it's been a lot of years this
is the best stuff
that's out there now that just
completely
rolls over any other spirulina so it's
got to be in the
smoothie and it matters what kind
you can get a really bad spirulina
really cheap spirulina or a low quality
one
and then we get in trouble so that's a
whole other thing
um so i'm going to pop some of this
spirulina in here for a second then i
got to watch over the
stir fry there so i'm doing the heavy
metal detox smoothie while cooking a
recipe
just going to move this around so it
doesn't stick this is cooking up nice
right here i don't think you guys can
see
put the pan back on there we go um
so just talked about the spirulina
critical part of getting toxic heavy
metals out of the brain
out of the liver in my opinion and from
the information i got from spirit of
compassion
and the heavy metal detox smoothie has
really really
not just changed lives it's saved
countless lives at this point now around
the world it's becoming
a staple around the world um
and i talk about that in of course the
revised
and expanded medical meeting book one so
you know guys you know what's funny it'd
be different if none of that happened
it'd be different if lives weren't saved
if millions of lives weren't healed and
saved throughout the years with these
books and this
information and the smoothie and
everything else and then i'd be sitting
here like
other people in the health field toting
things in toting products and tote and
stuff but
no track record of of thousands and
thousands and tens of thousands and
hundreds of thousands of lives saved
no track record of that you know of skin
conditions getting better and
you know adhd completely disappearing
and you know
migraines disappearing and stuff and a
medical medium information has that
track record
and i'm actually really proud to say it
because
it's incredible because no other health
community or no other health communities
no other health authors have that track
record of that many people healed better
recovered
with the tools or anything and but what
they do is they take medical medium
information they take the tidbits
and they sprinkle other stuff around it
so they try to get people some results
by taking
mm info throughout the years this is the
barley grass juice powder
here's the here's another thing about
the barley grass cheese first this is
the vimergy barley grass juice powder v
is in victor i
am as in mary er gy
okay and same thing with the spirulina
so
now you can use a barley grass cheese
powder doesn't mean it's gonna work
and grab onto the metals it doesn't mean
it's going to help assist
getting the metals out keep that in mind
a lot of people use barley grass
doesn't work at all so that's something
also to keep in mind
um but this is the best stuff there is
it's barley grass cheese powder i just
put a little bit of put a little bit
more in here and that's the vimeragey
barley grass juice better it's another
essential ingredient
to getting metals safely out you can't
get metals
out with just garlic you can't get
metals
out with just cilantro by itself so much
just won't do the job
it has to be a certain blend of
ingredients i talk about so
here's the atlantic sea vegetable dulce
right here
so it's going to go in the heavy metal
detox smoothie okay
just want to keep an eye on this right
here you guys
[Music]
so um so this is the dolls right here
that's another essential ingredient you
don't need a lot of it you can just do a
nice little strip
do anywhere from teaspoon to a
tablespoon okay
but i'm doing a couple strips in there
and that heavy metal detox smoothie
so i got that in there like i put the
cilantro in there you got the wild
blueberries in there okay and then
what i do is the wild blueberry powder
all right it's a vimergy wild blueberry
powder right there
and what i call this is blue gold is
what i call it
so i put that in there too additionally
now regular cultivator blueberries
cannot
remove metals cannot remove
metals i repeat a regular
it does even if it's organic a regular
blueberry that's organic
cultivated regular blueberry organic
will not assist in getting toxic heavy
metals out of the liver or the brain or
anywhere out of your body
it has to be a wild blueberry that gets
the metals out but
it needs also to have the company of the
cilantro in the same blend
or on the same day the dolls the
spirulina
the barley grass okay and you get the
wild blueberries and
you need the five critical pieces and
that's what you need
so i'm just letting you know um so i got
that all set up here or rigged
and then of course
gotta have the orange squeeze in there
you can put an orange in there
squeezing an orange in that's what i'm
doing
right here so i got a couple things
going on you guys just came on here
cooking a recipe from the new edition
that's coming out soon the medical
medium revise and expand it
okay which i'm talking about um
so i got that going on and put a little
bit more orange for me
i like having a little bit more orange
in there for me so
i'm doing that
there we go okay so i'm gonna blend this
up the heavy metal detox smoothie the
medical medium heavy metal detox movie
uh which has gotten quite famous out
there
glad you're in my kitchen with me
so i just made the smoothie right there
i'm gonna get a glass real quick
you guys don't mind grab one right here
heavy metal detox movie
people ask me what do i put in my heavy
metal detox smoothie like what spirulina
do i use i still get asked that every
day
that's why i'm also bringing it up so
just a reminder it's a memory visa
victor i-m-e-r-g-y vimergy.com i'm not
sponsored by these guys it's just the
best stuff there is
all their stuff is and then
the vimergy barley glass juice powder
emergency wild blueberry powder as i
showed you okay
that's the heavy metal detox smoothie
you got the wild blueberries in there
you got the cilantro in there and the
lenox sea dolls
that right there is saving lives every
day
i talk about it in the revised and
expanded
right here really important to know and
uh now i'm gonna start finishing up this
dish right here so just uh
i'm glad you're here i'm gonna try to
answer some questions too
well letting that cook up a little i'm
going to chop some stuff up
so i got some red bell pepper i'm going
to put that in here okay you can do
about a cup of it is good i might do a
little bit more i feel like that today
here's a heavy metal detox movie i'm
going to put it right up here i don't
know if you guys can see it
i don't know how much you can see
so i got some red bell pepper i'm
chopping up as we speak
you can dice it up in small pieces
that's what i'm doing for this recipe
this recipe is in the revised and
expanded
medical medium book i'll show and
showing you guys
[Music]
let's get some of these in here
so anyway i'm chopping i'm dicing up
some red bell pepper right here
that's what i'm doing
i'm gonna put a little bit more red bell
pepper in this one so i'm
inking out the seeds that's how i do it
easiest way to cut these
as you cut the top off just like that
pull that out right there so i'm just
going to put a little bit more of this
top one in
just a little extra
so i'm gonna do some broccoli too next
chops up some broccoli in here
so i'm cutting some nice pieces off of
here
back we're live so lost you guys
streaming stopped making the stir fry
right now
so if you guys were just on if you
weren't on before
making a recipe right here from the
revised expanded book
trying to finish it up trying to get
some stuff done
[Music]
chopping up some broccoli
that going on here
lost most everybody i think
[Music]
but hopefully you guys find your way
back chop it up some asparagus right
here
getting some asparagus on
good to see you guys glad many of you
guys are coming back on
back on right julie awesome so
nice everybody's coming back incredible
incredible
i don't know what happened we just got
cut off
right when i was talking about lyme
disease
interesting so
the world of lyme disease is completely
changed
it's now under autoimmune as i was
talking about before because of medical
medium books
people i think don't realize that the 35
years of medical medium information
getting out there
the amount of work that i've done
they don't realize how many things
are what they are because of all the
work that was done with medical medium
information
getting out there it's amazing so
the industry medical industry believes
lyme disease is autoimmune now so they
don't believe it's
bacteria because
of what we've done getting the
information out there medical medium
books
have saved so many people's lives with
lyme disease and it all started with
this book and it started with my work
even before that obviously decades
before that but
with this book and if you guys just got
on here
and you found this channel revise and
expand at the new edition
i'm doing a recipe right here
from this so um
i was also talking about the heavy metal
detox smoothie i'll cover that real
quick here it is
if you really want something to work you
have to have the right things you have
to have the wild blueberries you can't
have to cultivate it once okay
that's critical that have the atlantic
dolls that's the other piece there
you gotta have the vimergy spirulina
gotta have the best spirulina there is
to date on the market gotta have that
and the bar the grass juice powder the
vimergy the v
is the victor i am ergy fiberg.com
i'm not sponsored gotta have the right
stuff it's critical to get
someone better and i've known this my
whole life
if you don't have the right things you
don't have the right tools
you'll get somebody all the way
to where they need to be in getting
better like all the way
to where they need to be you don't get
them all the way there
and that's important to know um i'm
making
this morning hash right here this is a
recipe
i still have the garlic to pop in so i'm
doing that now so i got some garlic
right here so i'm gonna pop in one clove
i'm gonna chop it up
throw that in here too a little garlic
clove in here
so look you got the options got the
options right here you got
the chili flakes these are chili flakes
right here red bell pepper not red bell
pepper sorry hot chili flakes
and you got the paprika
okay you've got these two options to put
in there put a half teaspoon in this if
you want
so i'm making this morning hash it's got
the red bell peppers
it's got the broccoli it's got the
onions asparagus
and it's got the gold yukon gold
potatoes
spoiled potatoes right there it's
cooking up nice
um i'm gonna answer some questions too
we're gonna talk about stuff so
two things going on at once making a
recipe from the book so i'll give you a
little insight
45 recipes are added to this book photos
and all incredible to the revised and
expanded all right
um the angel section in this book is
expanded
which is really awesome meditations
chapter
expanded okay supplements and dosages in
this book
expanded on epstein-barr that's another
area too
really this book is is a whole
another game than it was before already
was incredible
to save lives and then took it to the
next level which i didn't think i could
but i did so i'm making a recipe right
now from this book right here which is
this
amazon.com or barnes noble um
so just made the heavy metal detox
smoothie too we're talking about like
heavy metals
you got anxiety depression ocd ptsd
um bipolar that's a whole other thing
there all
all of that well everything brain
related like that alzheimer's dementia
memory loss focus and concentration
adhd metals play a role
and what people are doing with their
metals is they're getting them out of
their brain they're getting them out of
their liver
this is a big part of this book
originally just letting you know you
feel that onions trigger migraines
no but caffeine does i know that
caffeine triggers migraines um
that's a big one right there for
migraines and
it's like i got a whole migraines
chapter in this book too
by the way and it all depends like so
is it you never had a migraine before
ever and then the onion causes it or it
gets triggered randomly with all kinds
of stuff like
you know stress triggering it and it
happens to be the day the onions are
happening or
something else trigger it or you know or
dehydrate it that triggers off migraines
i talk about how migraines get triggered
off
toxic heavy metals viruses cause
migraines i talked about that
and revised and expanded um book right
here the medical medium book
his link is in the description so you
get the right one chocolate's a migraine
creator
you can have chocolate two days ago and
have a migraine two days later
um and then what that migraine is is
chocolate withdrawal so it's caffeine
withdrawal from chocolate
so people don't realize is they go
through chocolate withdrawal
every other day every two three days and
they get triggered with all kinds of
stuff
they get triggered with everything so
that's important too
it's amazing that we're taught to eat
chocolate
and which is fine you could eat
chocolate all you want just know
that it's going to just create it's all
part of the addiction
you know it's it's really is the the
caffeine addiction this is almost done
and i'm about to plate it pretty soon
put a little parsley on top
if you're really hyper hyper
hypersensitive and you're cutting raw
onions
and the sulfur from the onion is so
cleansing
it's possible that could if you already
got migraines going going that you can
get like
something going on from that but it's
it's
not toxic but you know what triggers off
migraines really bad air fresheners
plug-in air fresheners scented candles
are you around any
scented candles at all because you can
be exposed to a scented candle
like a week ago and then be sick a week
later three days later four days later
scented candles especially so i'm gonna
actually plate this you guys so give me
a second
so i got a plate right here i'm gonna
just plate this up a little bit
so this is the morning hash it's got the
red bell peppers it's got the
beautiful potatoes it's got the broccoli
it's got the onions
there
um
[Music]
so i'm just plating it up
right here
i think it almost looks like the
photograph
that's in the medical medium book so
i'm going to show you in a second let's
see how close i got to it right
i think i'm pretty close to it
i think i'm pretty close to it so let me
just put this
over here for a second guys are in my
kitchen it's so fun i love it i'm going
to chop up some parsley put it on top
that's what i'm going to do so i'm going
to roll up some parsley right here
and get a chop up some parsley real
quick
parsley is really healing and
chopping up a little parsley
[Music]
i like to chop it up finely you can chop
you can just put a couple of sprigs of
parsley on this if that's what you want
to do
perfectly fine i like to chop it up fine
throw a little bit on top i'll show you
what i got
let's just drop stuff and here we go
that is it right there
that's the morning hash that's a recipe
out of the 45 recipes
in the new medical medium book the new
edition i'm going to put it right here
so you guys can see it hopefully you see
that
and
i'm hoping it kind of looks like that
right there
that's just look that's not what the
photo looks like in the in the real book
that you get this is just my manuscript
i'm just letting you know
that's what this is my manuscript so
this medical medium new edition
so and that's the recipe i just made
looks good does it look okay it's piping
hot i'll tell you that much right now
so you want to taste it i saw that um
so so cammy asks what candles are okay
it has to be a candle that has no
fragrances no fragrances
maybe a candle that maybe have an
essential oil of thyme or
a little bit essential oil or rosemary
essential oil of oregano
that could be okay something like that
but you but what happens is with
essential oil candles they also put
toxic stuff in it too so it says
essential oils essential oil candles but
it's also toxic they use toxic
fragrances
just keep in mind about that scented
candles are probably one of the most
destructive
um to the body and it's crazy what
happens is you'll see out there
as you'll see perfumes colognes scented
candles uh air fresheners are so
toxic right and they're so toxic
and at the same time there's all these
people in the health field using them so
you got all these people on instagram
all these people on youtube and they're
so health conscious and spiritually
conscious
and they're showing their health
products and they're showing their like
fresh meals or whatever they got
whatever they're showing and eating
and as they're doing that they're also
burning scented candles in their house
they're doing that
they're they're they have air fresheners
going on they got perfumes colognes
all kinds of stuff like that and i know
because a friend of mine
um walked into their friend's house
after not seeing him for a while with
everything going on right now
and went to go see him and this is a
person that's an influencer out there
doing stuff went to go see him and
hit like a brick wall of just scented
candles and all of that and it was so
toxic like and that stuff is so
dangerous so it seems like everybody's a
health expert
out there but they're burning their
scented candles they're doing this
they're doing that they're tanking their
caffeine
they're teaching other people how to use
caffeine to get hooked on caffeine
with the teas and the matcha tea and the
addiction of all of it and the caffeine
addiction and the coffee addiction
coffee drinks and the chocolate
addiction and
it's like that's what that's how it
works out there and
sure you can burn all the scented
candles you want i mean go ahead and you
can do all the caffeine you want i'm
just saying that these are troublemakers
and then all the new clothing right now
when you order new clothing any kind of
new clothing
it comes saturated there's very few
articles of clothing that come
without smell now it's saturated with
fungicides perfumes
colognes and people should start
complaining because
what the chemical companies are doing
right now is they're bombarding everyone
they're
they're you know how you know women are
worried about hormones
one of the big hormone disruptors
is all the chemicals and the scented
candles the air fresheners
the detergents the chemicals and fabric
softeners
the chemicals in all the new clothing
are hormone destroyers they're just
hormone
destroyers so what women are falling
victim to right now without knowing it
they don't know this
but they're being taught to like douse
everything with
perfume and clones stuff is highly toxic
and
actually throws all the hormones off in
the body so then you got to go to the
doctor and you got to get
constantly get your hormones figured out
and balanced and checked and
meanwhile it's all this stuff just
destroying you know the
it's destroying the very glands that
produce hormones in the body too so
fabric softeners laundry detergents
colognes perfumes scented candles
this is a big deal and there's heavy
metals in all of this stuff so
that's why it's critical to be doing
like the heavy metal detox movie
and but you'll see people doing spinoffs
they'll be like i'm doing a heavy metal
detox smoothie they won't say a medical
medium anymore and they'll be like
i'm putting corella in here i'm putting
this in there
and it's not even going to help anybody
has to be the right
blend it's critical um
has to be the right brent blend it has
to be quick like i said if you're going
to do the heavy metal detox smoothie if
you want
to be like looking out for yourself if
you want to make sure you're protecting
yourself when you're getting all the
exposure from scented candles and from
air fresheners and perfumes and clones
on clothes that you order or whatever it
is it comes
um you just you got to make sure you're
getting the metals out you know and the
best stuff does that and
that's that's what i've learned um so
that's the vimergy spirit lena i talked
about and the other stuff
and but you guys just do a little
reminder i just made the recipe
there it is i can't wait to eat it
actually um it's medical medium revised
and expanded new edition um pre-order it
amazon.com uh you'll see the link in the
description
get in the library if you don't want to
pre-order it get in the library when it
comes out
it's coming out pretty soon it's pretty
it's coming up pretty soon you can get
the library for free if you want
that's the dish i just made right there
it's hot and steamy
that's it i'm excited um anyway
i love you guys and i'm heading off to
ig and then i'm going to make probably a
different meal
on tick-tock after ig but right now i'm
going to go to ig make another heavy
metal detox movie on ig i'm going to
make another stir fry
not stir-fry morning hash recipe on
ig and then i'm going to tick-tock i'm
going to make something different
i'm going to answer questions thoroughly
on tick-tock so i'm letting you guys
know
i'm going to actually answer questions
thoroughly on tick-tock um
anyway keep an eye out for today look
out make sure you get your notifications
on
and like this video whatever if
you like it love you guys and i'll see
you soon