here we are so in case you didn't know
this is an Anthony William medical
medium you can not book these books like
these books and if you haven't you have
to these are Bible Holy Bible and I'm so
so so grateful here today to talk with
Antony about something that I'm very
passionate about
so Antony will you start yeah our life
this is your Elena Djokovic an amazing
person amazing individual she's doing
incredible things out there and health
she's doing all kinds of things in
wellness and it's an honor to have her
here because she knows medical medium
information she sees the people out
there healing she sees you guys out
there healing she knows your struggles
she knows what you guys are doing she's
she's got her eyes on that it's
important a lot of people don't see that
out there they don't see the struggles
and the suffering and they kind of don't
they don't understand it you Lena sees
it all that's why I love her we're dear
friends I have her here this is the
greatest day right now I can't even tell
you so we're here and you need a good
introduction of me that's incredible but
let's change it around you always see
the the Antony William a medical medium
Here I am she goes let's change this
around a little bit yeah that's the
process but this is amazing she's you
know you Lane is doing a lot of
incredible things out there she's got
the foundation I want to ask you about
that for a second novak djokovic
foundation which is really powerful it's
about children it's a zero to six
program where you're focused on ages
zero to six and making sure they're
eating better a better way is living
right so I'm the CEO of the Novak
Djokovic foundation which is working
with for the early childhood education
programs meaning we are opening
kindergartens and educating teachers and
parents and working with children to
making sure they have a better start in
life and that's how we are infecting the
future and all the knowledge we gain
through all the resources we have
because I'm married to the best
player in the world novak djokovic and
we use our friends and connections to
make sure we bring all the best
knowledge to all the parents and share
with them and then we came across antony
and it was such a random moment for me I
was on a wedding weekend with friends
and there is this girl reading this book
the first book and and I'm like who is
bringing this you know can chest scan
you know on the wedding weekend like
people are usually you know reading
novel something yeah and he's bringing
an x-ray and she was really reading like
properly and then she I was like what
are you reading and she goes like Elena
you won't believe it this is gonna
change your life in it and here it is it
changed my life honestly I am so
grateful for everything you do on all
the channels you do because you are
really working your butt off to reach
every single person out there there's so
many people struggling out there I mean
you know it's like a war zone out there
people don't realize that and I say what
am i living in a bubble and nobody's
sick out there so science of research
fixed everything so science research
must have everything fixed no one's sick
out there so but that's not true I mean
just in America alone over 250 million
citizens just you know 250 million alone
or suffering here you know it's
incredible my resolutions and and
honestly I was never in or I came to
this knowledge for me all the motivation
comes as how I can be the healthiest you
know what is the healthiest we can be
and then you talk about that and you
talk about us as people rather than
patients and all these symptoms we have
because I have plenty of symptoms that I
never qualify them as a part of
something because we're supposed to
think it's normal
yes I tell you guys out there only time
rate how many times I asked you about it
like yeah can you tell me what is the
healthiest I can feel today in this
society with all the toxins that are
happening around us you know we are
breeding in and eat
and what is the healthiest we can be you
know it's a lot more time the funny
thing is a lot more toxic now than it
ever was when you think about the cities
in the old days you know have you ever
hear like stories of you got to move out
of the city to get to the country this
guy right there on the left side saying
to me you couldn't you've got to stay
out of LA for now there is this fight
wildfire the wildfires yeah that's right
and there are so many people who didn't
go out of LA had to stay and breathe in
all the toxins and so how do they feel
now well you know it together wildfires
and then the fire retardant that sprayed
and all the dust and all the ashes and
so we're always up get something whether
it's that or any kind of anything else
that's just added extra stuff that no
one needs so ease it a solution to move
to countryside well you know what it is
though it's like the cities used to be
like I always say the cities are really
dirty and cities are dirty and go to the
country and that was many years ago and
I've never told you guys about this but
they talk about this but now the cities
are worse than they've ever been and the
country is also not good either where
we're always exposed to something every
basically there's no everybody's exposed
in every place it doesn't matter where
it is every country the city it could be
anywhere and so we have to take care of
ourselves we have to learn and take care
of ourselves that's the whole point it's
not that we're supposed to run and hide
it's not supposed to that we're supposed
to meaning never get it ever affected or
intoxicated by anything it's not that
it's just that where we need to take
care of ourselves we need to do things
and the medical medium information is
what I you know always read out there
and say look you got to take care of
your liver because it collects it all
that's why you like liver book probably
for me the book that I carry around a
lot even though it's the heaviest one
and is this one and luckily it's also
translated in Serbian so when I speak
with my friends and family I also make
sure I refer them to the book and trust
me you are big because if it's
translated in serve in translated in
surgeon I mean that's your ultimate goal
you want to reach those kind of people
because they are open to knowledge I
mean I'm saying
to everybody from Serbia don't go down
you don't go back to prospects either
Cosmo and I'm just telling them go guys
by the books I'm also speaking about it
also in on all my channels because for
me this is the knowledge I am I applied
to my children's lives in my life and
also my husband is using lots of those
now lots of that kind of knowledge and
it's a Holy Grail you know if you want
to feel energized and youthful through
life because we don't feel that way and
that's what healthy means yeah yeah when
we walk around with symptoms we think
it's normal it's a new norm new norm to
have endometriosis normal to have PCOS
fibroids in norm to have all these
issues
Divac diabetes new norm to actually have
high a1c high blood sure
you know hypoglycemia thyroid problems
so we walk around we all have
hypothyroid right and we walk around
with it and it's just it's the new
normal we're just supposed to accept it
and then we're supposed to believe
science that research has all the
answers for some reason so we're
supposed to believe in all the studies
and all the science is thrown around and
and the vegans have all the answers and
then the Palio's have all the answers in
the animal protein high-protein low
protein high fat they're not healthy
it's like it doesn't work that way being
labeled as vegan also brings out
different kinds of food that we eat that
are not the healthiest option for us a
fried french fries that's vegan food but
is it the best one for you so a lot of
vegans don't eat good that's a you need
right yeah yeah totally and this is
what's gonna happen because there is a
huge vegan trend that is actually
sending us off the rails because we're
gonna get even sicker because we're
eating lab food as well because you know
those burgers out there are sausages or
cheese you mean that the fake sausages
the fake means that I got all those
absolutely and last tried them they do
they do taste well but they feel bad
after and like my body does not let me
do those things
it's just alerts me straight on and I am
skinny but that's how I feel good not
about looking good it's about feeling
good and this is what people don't know
what it is well if a plant-based person
if the person who's doing the vegan food
right and they're eating all of these
fun vegan foods all the time and they
get their first symptoms or they get
symptoms they think it's because they're
plant-based so then they leave the
plant-based world they leave that the u
n-- is immoral then they had to eating
animal proteins again because their
doctor might say it's because you don't
have proteins it's because you're not
getting your proteins not getting enough
proteins but maybe they weren't eating
as good as they could have when they're
eating plant-based and I say that to
people who are paleo too or people who
are doing a healthy keto maybe it could
be even better because that's the thing
we could be doing a better job in all of
our diets that's what I try to do right
I try to get the information out there
so it's like hey if you want to be
plant-based you gotta do it
this way make sure you get this in you
and she's gotta stay strong on this we
got our celery juices by the way we have
that I'm not having anymore I had two of
these before the live started it's
enough I need to keep the pretty face
otherwise it's a lot of celery juice
yeah but so you know and yeah it's it's
no matter what diet we subscribe to a
belief system we get sucked into there's
information out there that you know no
there's information about what's really
causing our illnesses that I'm trying to
spread out there and you're trying to
spread that information out there
because you're doing that you're telling
everybody about this information and so
that when you're plant-based or vegan
you don't get scared when you get when
you're having a symptom and you're
thinking it's because of lack protein or
it's because I'm vegan or because I'm
not doing something right because the
chase for protein that is the properties
for proteins and that's brilliant
that's brilliant well you know I I
texted you a few weeks ago telling you
yeah a friend of mine a close friend of
mine was you know having some mystery
weighed his shoes and it wasn't it
actually the doctor sent to her to kick
out all the fruits and all the veggies
and just go for the meat and the fat
yes that's gonna be like her healing
okay so just go totally totally no carb
no fruit yeah because because it's
qualified as sugar and sugar is you know
making her sick sick and I lost it I was
like just let's let's keep the book out
let's start reading and then let's see
and the thing is how do you go against
the doctor
you know like doctors are advising or
certain things of course first of all
when you see the doctor today are they
actually looking as we would want to
look you know as healthy so then they
also come because of course for them
it's like they're constantly seeing sick
people and trying to help them do they
have time to keep up with all the
knowledge that is out there I'm so
excited you partner with doctors and you
make sure that they also get the access
to that because it's so important
they're the ones people come to when
they see people in the white coats they
are like okay this is the person that
will save me and it's true they're gonna
save us but in some really you know
dangerous situations like broken arms
and you know car accidents or things
like that are serious serious serious
but then for this everyday illnesses
that we carry on through life this is
what we need this information for
because we're fueling our body with the
wrong fuel yeah and and I'm so happy
what you've mentioned in so many of your
books is that being repetitive with food
is not bad for us no everybody speaks
about variety changing it off spicing it
up right they need the variety what do
you say about that look like it's okay
if you're doing where you're not doing
variety where you just do something that
works that's another thing too I know
that a lot of us want variety and I
totally respect that not or that right
and and I think people get bored fast
and they get pressured you get pressured
by people around them my family might be
friends and are you eating those
potatoes again those steamed potatoes
again are you eating that sounds like my
son loves it I think I'm saying hello to
all the moms out there because I'm sure
that your kids love potatoes and I am
you know my son also eats them for
breakfast like he just likes them you
know and I mean okay he eats a lot of
fruits and then she will just go at 11
o'clock for potatoes and I'm not gonna
stop him
because I know now because I've read the
life I mean this is something that is so
precious to me yeah because it doesn't
like I love the fact that would your
speak when you speak about the food
you're not only giving this nutritional
fact you're actually giving the soul
feeding fact that every every food we
eat is feeding our soul - with
information that is so crucial that's
why I connect with you because you speak
to my soul
well the wild blueberries those are
powerful for the soul I talked about
that in the book oh they're really
powerful really healing and and that's a
crime and that's good for the heavy
metal detox which is I'm using from all
the recommendations you're like this
like the mornings the delivery rest good
morning are you know it's kind of an
intermittent fasting isn't it yeah it is
you know it's funny but the heavy metals
is people you know don't they don't
think they have metals in them they
don't think they have metals in they
don't think they have mercury in them
they don't think they have Lumina mentum
you guys probably hear it all the time
because so many of you talk about the
metals out there arsenic lead cadmium
nickel but in copper but if you have
eczema if you have psoriasis you have
your gift copper coppers inside the
liver if you have twitches spasms brain
fog tables numbness you've got mercury
Mercury's in there you might be viral
too I talk about that all times you've
got mercury in there so if you got all
of that the brain fog if you have
sleeping problems mercury can be behind
that too it could be behind so much
confusion the way you know if we feel
like we're confused if we feel like
we're not getting our information across
we can't see we can't talk so clearly or
we can't think or we're getting the
brain fog in the way in your home like -
because that was something that I've
just a few months ago discovered when we
were our chef that was cooking for us at
that time was you know wrapping the food
in the aluminium foil
yes warm to keep it warm yeah and I had
the massive food poisoning without even
you know understanding why it was you
know and then when I realized that it
was the aluminium that was and we use it
every single day I grew up around like
my
I don't know my cousins were working in
a factory that was doing that you know
we taking that matter exactly and so all
of us are getting sick from all the you
know everyday use of shampoos and
lotions and perfumes and all different
kinds of things what I you know blows my
mind is the idea of going to the shop
and buying your new clothes and putting
them on and you are also poisoning your
body with that because somebody has used
a mold spray or something on it yeah
they use a fungicide all our new clothes
that we get oh we go out my new clothes
they spray it with fungicide they don't
give you the choice there's no town hall
meeting
there's no choices there or not we're
not giving that they just they just coat
everything with fungicide fungicide is
so toxic it goes to the brain it's
filled with metals and so that's what we
live in all of this stuff every day so
sure I mean we're battling where the
diet people are all fighting each other
you got like Paquito people are all mad
at the people who do a potato and and
you got the people you mean the vegans
are mad at the beet eater people and you
got all everybody's throwing all this
science at each other all these studies
all this what I call fake science but
nobody knows the cause of illnesses
nobody knows that when they buy new
clothes
it's loaded with fungicide nobody knows
that they're supposed to lower their
fats because they're taking out their
oxygen and because their oxygen is
getting you know less and less in the
body to fight disease so they're eating
all these high fats and all these diets
nobody knows any of this information so
then everybody stays sick they're all
getting sick so you might be vegan for a
little why it might be keto for a little
while you might be paleo for a little
while you might be doing some diet and
you're feeling good for a while go back
to the five years later you know you're
you might be doing on YouTube you're
doing youtubes for years ago and you can
follow the progression that four years
later everybody gets better from it and
then gets worse like I don't understand
it like so many times you do something
that is so good for you and you feel
good and you commit to it but then I
guess you have to take into
consideration if your body's changing
well there's a couple of things to when
we usually jump into something we're
usually eating worse before that so for
instance like if you go to a healthy
keto diet after being you know eating
whatever or more you know you're eating
more fast food or you're eating no
process you don't see the diet is the
new kind of high-protein diet but
everybody gets mad if I say I protein
because it's high fat and that's the
whole thing but it's really it's really
a lot of fat but the high protein diet
is a lot of fat
they're basically they're both filled
with a lot of fat vegan diet is also
high fat it's nice that yeah - that's
why there's keto vegan now but the yeah
but the keto diets is the high fat diet
yeah the cute guys the high fat diet
that's still high protein but and then
you know but you got the high protein
diet that's still high fat and then you
got the key you got the vegan diets that
are still high fat and all of this
delivery suffers deliver suffering see
the keto diet high fat or liver
suffering you do high protein diet high
fat your livers suffering you do you can
package it name it anything you want but
they all end up high fat diets they kill
the liver the liver gets killed you
knock down but people get better at
first because they're lowering they're
staying away from their chocolate cake
they're staying away from their waffles
they're staying away for their joy
things like I mean you get stress from
all this information like now knowing
that everything you do everything you
use it becomes so toxic for you so now
there is a moment of panic right
everybody's like oh my god but if this
is how do I actually live this life and
who do I trust and I mean so often
people say but in this organic section
there is like not a lot nice and looking
fruit or veggie and it all looks very
you know it's not appealing to people
yeah so they give up before even they
started because it's just not as yummy
looking as that strawberry that is like
this big or you know and so you were
stuck with this fear because now all of
a sudden knowing what's causing your
illness is the new creating fear in you
yeah and you are providing us with this
information and giving us alternatives I
love the idea of knowing that I can have
you know a piece of fruit in 300 ways
you know if well people are afraid of
fruit there's fruit fear Oh big fruit
fear out there big like big so eating
all my life fruit more than anything
else honestly it has given me life
anything else I've been doing maybe not
well what happens is the fruit fear is a
funny thing because if someone gets sick
they don't blame the egg that's fed
every virus and pathogen and bacteria
that causes their problems and they
don't blame the egg but they'll blame
the piece of fruit they have no one
really ate fruit so why is everybody
sick no one eats enough fruit and for
anyone even determined fruits the reason
why they're sick it's not even possible
isn't healthier I wish it was but it'll
still feed every bug in our body so the
cause of illness are pathogens and
toxins so you got the viruses of
bacteria that's your pathogens and then
you got the toxins and everybody has a
minim and it's it's like Russian
Roulette it's like it's like again it's
like a gamble who's gonna get sick first
who's gonna get knocked down and have
the pathogen take over and give them
aches and pains and fatigue and all
kinds of problems and or what Thompson's
are people gonna get intoxicated with
like what metals and what different
kinds of poisons like the you know all
the different fungicide on clothes and
the petrochemicals out there floating in
the air and the mercury that's falling
out of the sky so we get both the toxins
so we get both the pathogens and then
they both get they join together the
pathogens eat the poisons and then we
get sick and then everybody blames the
strawberry everybody's going to blame
the strawberry a very food that will
actually help you get better everybody's
going to blame it suggest more people
who want to change their life because
it's all about working out as well no I
think people want to lose weight or
people want to feel bad you know I've
been doing this for 35 years maybe more
than 35 years now and I've seen guys
that are like in top shape top shape die
of heart attacks just boom that's it 38
years old they're in the gym they got
their tabs they got their apps I know a
lot of athletes I've helped a lot of
athletes professionally over the decades
and you can just you get one injury that
won't heal you get you get something and
you know you get a heart attack or
something happens but there's there's
ways to heal things there ways that will
avoid that there's a way to heal
injuries the way that you know do the
body can heal but you got to give it
what it needs you got to give it what it
needs how do we know what our body needs
for a particular thing like say
or feel like I love the item I keep on
speaking about it but honestly for me
your books are really important guides
so for instance when we have an injury
when we for instance injured our knee
and that's an injury that's gonna heal
at some point right with all the
different things you're doing your
therapy and stuff and then after a while
it's gonna come back again and it flares
up when we are eating inflammatory foods
yeah so that's the weak point for now
forever in our body and that's where the
viruses and bacteria are collecting and
nesting when we when we injure ourselves
and we have a pathogen in us we have say
like a virus in us I've seen bar we
injure ourselves
the virus can go to that injury that's
why there's so many people there's
people who get knee surgeries and they
get up and they walk out they're fine
right after the knee surgery that
literally I talk to doctors all the time
about this they just get it they walk
same pertinent this other person gets
the same exact surgery same exactly
problem to the T everything should be
fine they should be up and walking
bright out and then they're swollen for
weeks and weeks and months and months
and now on steroids and swollen and they
can't walk good they need long-term
physical therapy and it goes on a year
of a knee problem because they had a
low-grade viral infection in their
system but we're do are you suggesting
for them like I know for instance my dad
when he had this injury that kept coming
back he would they were suggesting him
to use the collagen is that a good thing
or not really well you can't build up
your collagen by eating collagen you
can't no you can't fix your kidney by
eating a kidney you can't fix your eye
by eating an eye you can't you can't fix
your liver by eating a liver and you
can't fix your skin by eating skin you
can are you listening are you listening
collagen that he swears to God about it
like I feel like people generally
attached themselves to the solutions
that are not really solutions you need
phytochemical compounds that are like
for example in celery juice to create
collagen collagen is created by our body
it's created through fighting chemical
compounds mineral salts and other things
like that
that's what creates collagen lots of
antioxidants from like blueberries lots
of man you can't eat something to create
something that's that's actually that's
a thousand years ago that was the Dark
Ages with a C vitamin because we have to
you know drink C vitamin or eight those
are minerals and vitamins nutrients
that's what we use to create things so
we use vitamin C to create our immune
system we use we use minerals to create
tissue in cells we use all of this
creates but you can't you can't take
something like collagen that's actually
in our skin but you can't take a
collagen source another source of
collagen whatever that might be
consume it and think it's gonna go to
the skin all it's going to do is go into
your stomach and out your intestinal
tract then you go to bathroom and it
goes out and that's where it goes you
can't find its way to your skin it's
like it's like eating a sheep's eyeball
to try to fix your eyeball or something
it's like eating yes you know even
kidneys it's people you can be kidney
pie but that's what the kids were eating
in my country we were growing up it was
a liver and you know there's supplements
out there with actual baby I don't know
if they're still out there now I haven't
been looking at these varieties of
supplements but some of us out there
would bringing in it with brain so in
order to fix your brain and so you're
gonna eat brain supplements to fix your
brain it doesn't work like that see but
for some reason we can we get tricked by
propaganda by money by investments and
those investments going to collagen it's
such an easy sell like wait a minute my
skin will get better
collagen collagen let me tell you
something when you have the worst eczema
the worst eczema effort you can gobble
all the collagen shakes you want and you
can take all the collagen pills you want
you can buy into it and spend thousands
of dollars on collagen every other month
and your skin will even not only stay
the same you get so excited these things
but you know we need people like you to
speak to all of us because we've wanted
to live a good life but it's just well
you know what it is I'm not I'm not
afraid of whose feelings I'm gonna hurt
in the industries and that's what
happens see everybody else there they
got their afraid you know don't don't
hurt that
don't hurt that guy you know and really
it you gotta protect the people who
struggle and suffer you got it and you
got and it doesn't matter if anybody's
gonna you know water roast me like they
do all the time and that's what happens
we all know that I get I get hit more
than anybody else in the industry
because you can't make money off of
celery juice so I'm a threat see this is
actually healing people so it threatens
the industries because they can't
bankroll off of this this is the one
this is this is rogue knowledge you're
providing I'm sure sure so there's a lot
of silence out there you can find in
juice bars now the celery juice just not
HPP one maybe just go for your fresh one
but not a lot of money's made from that
but the bigger industries like the
college industry millions and millions
of billions of dollars now it's a good
trick it's a great trick because I'm
using the good supplements you were
recommending and I really think that's
helpful yeah yeah it's important you
want to be you want to ski you want to
build skin tissue you want to get your
skin nice and healthy you got to get the
celery geez you got to get the metals
out of your skin because that's what it
is the metals on in our liver and get
the toxins out of our liver and
everything well with all this he
provides out there you really don't have
to think anymore what's to eat
throughout the day cuz when you think
about you know compiling everything say
the the lemon water in the morning and
the celery juice and then after dad who
drinks some smoothies fruit smoothies
and then go for the heavy metal detox I
need some salad and the baked potatoes
and also rice is okay right or I mean
look rice rice isn't or pasta what do
you think about pasta come on Italians
we like well the lentil pot if you're
gonna do a pasta the lentil pasta is the
best one to do okay that's what my kids
eat if you're gonna do a pasta if
anybody out there wants to do pasta do
the lentil pasta the red lentil pasta is
even better yeah that's what I would do
and the red lentils Percy that's also
absolutely food that our bloating us
come on that's a big thing out there
everybody's complaining hoping there be
bloated to everything when I get bloated
when my skinny you know I look like I'm
pregnant I'm not pregnant
well it's the food I don't think you're
really bloated
when people are bloated they're like you
know what no not in the morning I'm not
after 32 ounces of celery honestly not
gonna happen but um but you know what
happens is the reason why people are
bloating because their liver stagnant
and sluggish that's what happens
I think it's fatty liver you make the
liver for everything everybody blames me
for everything I gotta blame something
else for everything okay because I'm
always getting all the secrets that
people don't know out there the truth
out there and they're all like no no and
you deliver is the guilty one in the
terms of bloating deliver is the guilty
one right there
we haven't supported it enough yeah
because we just we just let it get dense
and sick and it gets congested with
everything in there were no we're not
cleansing it within the process how long
does it take to clean because I've been
plan based for the past five years
thanks to my son thank you son because
he inspired me you got to tell that
story that's incredible yeah it's a good
story well my son is my biggest
inspiration in life and I mean my son
and daughter but my daughter my son came
first and he kind of started a cycle
basically I was trying to be the
healthiest I can be and knowing that
there is a little human being inside of
me I wanted to create this perfect
environment for him when we live in this
sick world we are bombed with all these
you know well wrong messages of what's
gonna make us happier and better and
healthier and so when I started
researching a lot on the what I can eat
so that I can when I'm producing milk
for my son he gets the best out of it
and and I've turned plant-based or vegan
well back then I was vegan and I was
very very like hardcore
on that and and that's what helped me
understand and what did I like why would
he what was the the idea about why did I
start talking about this now I love my
track well
to the jackleg well yeah you just flew
from another part of the world and
you're on one hours sleep but I'm glad
you're here
but the yeah the thing is with with
everything as you're telling story
because you became the plant based and
then the whole transition like how like
you are feeling better you're always
feeling better but when are you actually
cleaned from all the stuff you ate for
the past
I don't know 28 years that was in the
case in my life
and then others who are healing yes like
how long does it take his work when are
we actually gonna feel the best like
you've been doing that all your life the
reason why you have so much energy and
focus on this particular mission that is
so noble and so important and please do
recognize that because what we're doing
right now requires lots of energy like
I'm shaking from the excitement but he's
been doing this every single day and
writing books and sleeping two hours
maybe in the night just to make sure
that he refreshes and he is able to look
like this thanks to all the wonderful
knowledge who gets from you know the
source and the wonderful spirit that I'm
connected to too so yeah what you're
doing is just something that has
connected with me in so many levels and
give me the cry right here so I guess I
got a hold it back but that's the side
of you people have to see because really
the commitment you you give for this
like I generally you know you get sick
from people telling you they're sick oh
I'm feeling her pain here and there and
you know I'm every day waking up with
this and then we all get sick from that
and he gets to listen it and practically
and with so much attention and gives the
solution to people this is something
that not you don't get in them you know
doctor's office unfortunately you get a
prescription which is just gonna delay
another you know what walking delay
yeah I could put sickness on hold a
little bit but it gets routed deeper
inside yeah but this is the information
that actually gets you back on track and
gives you the the time for you to to
reset yourself and go back in the
driving seat and that's how I feel in my
life
like you have control yeah and that's I
mean I am addicted to control I'm a mom
you need to have control bottom line
healthy and live in a healthy world and
all of a sudden there are these soldiers
like yourself that are really fighting
for them peaceful wonderful planet and
I'm connected to that mission and I'm
speaking with so much love to all the
people who are following Anthony and
every single one who connected today to
here and just to remind you there is a
lot of things in the book that maybe you
just skim through go back to it because
I mean I might have you know spent a few
times reading each book because it
really matters like these are the fairy
tales I speak to my kids now there is a
whole fairy tale about kids you know
about the deliver deliver and all the
like toxins and stuff trying to get in
it's like you know no no and my kids are
liking those stories I mean I do make
them funny but some kids do cry from
those stories so it's it's it's it's an
interesting journey I love the idea of
teaching my kids from early on and not
only my kids but all the kids that we
touch through the foundation how they
can take care of themselves you know how
they can start this life and live it
despite everything that is around us
because that's not what makes us
unhealthy it's our choices that we make
we have a choice every single day to
choose the right thing to do for us in
the planet and that's what you've
provided us like I haven't found this
knowledge in many books and I've read a
lot of books on health this is these are
the books I come back to and I will
forever be grateful for what you're
doing I'm honored you know the
information in the books is it's not out
there it only comes from this source so
it's not like it's repackaged it's funny
because the health books of today and
I'm not trying to say that they're not
helpful it's just that it's the same
stuff but it's repackaged for the next
generation of basically people who start
getting health minded when whether
they're in their 20s or whether they're
in their 30s or when they're just
starting to get health mind it and
they're getting excited and they get
they get the books out there and they
get the information out there and they
read articles and they don't know that
that information was the same
information that was repackaged ten
go to the crowd before them and then 10
years ago to the crowd before them like
for instance he got the whole candida
thing that happened for 30-40 years now
they switched it to microbiome but it's
still the same package but they renamed
it and then then the newer generation
kind of comes up and they don't realize
that the answers aren't in there yet and
if they get too sick they'll find that
the answers aren't really there and
that's what happens it's like so you
know it's it's it depends on how sick a
person gets to realize and I noticed
that the older people who've been there
done that they've seen all the tricks
and games they've seen the decades of
tricks and games and they realize things
are repackaged so when they find this
information and we wait a minute this
was different than anything else that
exists out there the rest is repackaged
backed by money put out there and it's
still it's not getting people to that
next level of where they need to go and
everybody swear to it and there was this
just recent article I feel like it was a
maybe half an year half a year ago where
they published the information about the
coconut oil being toxic carcinogenic and
so you know you are you're everybody's
drinking coconut water coconut oil you
know putting on their face or or their
food and frying stuff with it and now
all of a sudden that's wrong and then
you're like where should I go to for all
the information and how do I you know I
remember texting you many times asking
you how much fat is too much fat like
and can we actually live without the
fact because it's in avocado for
instance everybody's been dying with the
fat mm-hmm we just decade after decade
after decade everybody's dying with the
fat so everybody is on fat just
everybody's on it doesn't matter you
know Megan's I'm not but you know what
but it's still good to have a little you
can have
I'm going your way a little bit of that
Mikado you can have some coconut oil if
you're into fish you can have some sort
of age you can have some really good
high quality fats if you're into animal
products you go for the highest quality
but if you go for bacon or pork you're
into the bad fat now but let me tell you
the bad I'm a very strong advocate for
clan-based so I wouldn't you know you're
all plant-based your plan I'm not I mean
you're so kind to speak about it in such
way this is you do know that people are
enjoying meat I love my meat you're hard
at work plant it was like because you
know there is not many I respect that
though because I've seen plant-based
diets literally take people out of the
depths of hell with their health
literally worse and pull them out of it
I've seen it pull them out of it
absolutely but the right people are like
saying okay now I'm feeling better so
I'm just gonna go back to what it was
before right so the plan based diet is
mainly to get you out of the you know
hole and then you go back to your meat
until you go back again in the hole and
then you go back to that so there's a
some maintenance diet yeah but it is a
maintenance diet he should be it is no
you can be plant-based anybody out there
plant-based I mean raise your hand
yep raise your hand if you're planning
to that yeah it's a powerful way to heal
stick to it you know if you're something
that you don't want to do plant based on
some other kicking everything lower your
fats but I tell people plant-based down
lower your fats you know that's the
thing is is I'm all about whatever
wherever you are with your diet you got
to bring your fats down because that's
where you'll get in trouble every time
maybe you're not gonna get your curves
you know because those magazines and
popular places are actually it's like we
could offer Kings really both of us we
have two chairs moving probably sit in
one and we do feel good I mean this is
like this is what we're talking about
actually feeling good rather than
looking good and I know there are so
many people out there who want to feel
good and there are ways and it's just
well no I I could go into the gym I
could go into gym three hours a day
we're doing some muscle maybe I should
go in the gym do
three hours they start building muscle
maybe I'll go and get some massages
everyday maybe I'll go and do yoga for
two hours day and I won't be able to
help anybody because I'll be too busy
taking care of myself but in doing all
that so forget right in the books the
writing the book sleeps two hours a day
so he can provide all the knowledge to
us so sorry I've had people I've had
people say hey look medical medium I
thought you'd be built I thought you
would have big guns ripped I thought
you'd be ripped and it'd be like you
want me to go that route you want me to
dedicate half my life into getting
ripped I can then I'll put off all the
work forget finishing these books forget
doing what I gotta do as a mother - I
can totally understand when you say you
don't have time for that because also
every mom out there I'm sure you're
struggling to find your yeah time yeah
it's hard to find time for self-care
it's really difficult for everybody and
then but there's people that they make
it their life you know you can see
people who are built it's cuz they made
that their life you know and that's
that's what you're doing but I can't
make that my life I can't be putting on
iron you know Lena I gotta just you know
stay toned I gotta stay healthy you know
sure just ride my bike well where did I
read you're like 28 year older than 20
been doing this for 35 years and I'm 28
no it's true they say I'm 28 because I
look so old when you're 28 I think it's
done I think it's out there on the
Internet I remember that I asked you
that like how do you stay so young and
and then it's like what what is it was
just so confusing obviously there are
lots of lies out there and there are
people who are trying to discredit
people doing good stuff and and I feel
for me the most thing the thing that
connects me is this soul feeling like
this inside of me feeling I don't
connect too many things out there like
that but I did to you and through your
books because you're a spoken word I
mean those you know to our nights are
like really paying off I mean they
touched me and people who are following
me and for not only me but my family
they're gonna you know also be connected
to that I'm sure and for for every
single person in this world if you
connect to something just you
stay true through it like I I connected
so much with you I'm so grateful to be
to their today here and also with your
community I'm sure most of you feel this
way and you should be here with me also
cheering him on the way you do or some
of the social networks because we can
see your programs everybody feeling
they're all working so hard they are
it's amazing I mean the support third
they're supporting other people they're
telling other people their I mean the
work that you guys are doing out there
is mind-blowing it's I talk about that
all the time you know wake up when I
wake up in the morning first thing I say
is what can I do for everybody what can
I do because they're doing what they're
doing and I I just I I just can't even
imagine what what kind of pain and fears
you're going through because all the
stuff that is helping you heal that he's
sharing like I've been seeing girls and
men like with the with the with the
worst psoriasis and eczema problems and
acne and and I've never had to go
through that but to connect with through
his empathic eyes and through his
empathic platform that is providing all
of you with such a you know resources to
heal and then see you heal as well and
you know have your clapping and like
blessings it's like there's not many
places in the world where you can get
such an encouragement well you know when
you're kicked down like so many people
are and you guys know you know people
you know family members and stuff and
there there are 10 different doctors
offices you know how to go into
neurologists they got all the different
symptoms and everything and they're just
struggling in any every way and and the
thyroid problems and they get different
diagnoses the skins you know having
problems or they get the fatigue that
neurological fatigue that I talk about
in all the books and everything works
your nervous system is so weak that
you're just you can't function you're
lazy like bags of cement you know and
and then and then you need you need
answers you need answers it's critical I
mean you have to get you should see what
you are saying I really know for people
like it would be easier like you don't
have to change so many habits you you
know have like you know all of the stuff
we've been told from the early
you know years on because our parents
didn't know either and our grandparents
didn't know none of us knew what we were
doing and now when you come here and
you're like yeah let's change this and
let's change that and let them you're
like oh but it's easier with that pillow
I'm just gonna take the pill
and that's where we are getting into
this you know but stay strong that's why
the communities are important that's why
this in particular is so important you
are doing and you're making an effort to
connect with them and there's no and
there's no ads there's no ads before
this this episode I'm dead right now
without the ads I really need to there's
no ads there's no this is this is
exactly this is a free channel you have
to sit there waiting for 20 ads to come
yeah I only have the celery juice and
lemon balm tea in front of me he didn't
provide me with any kind of cool stuff
no smart core it's rough we're rocking
it out I've got the best greeting ever
from Anthony and he really prepared the
wonderful table with lots of good food
and I made a photo of it so I'll share
it with you so then you can see how you
can actually treat yourself for the
lunch or dinner good ideas I mean comes
from straight from the source well be
here so you guys I want to keep on
taking care of yourself okay I think
we're gonna be wrapping this up we're
good we're good
well I can see people are actually yeah
I want to wrap it up too but I just
wanted to say that people are really
sending you some love out there
incredible incredible incredible thank
you for doing this honestly really it's
important for us to change my life it's
changed my kid's life it's gonna change
their you know kid's life Yelena's happy
to be here but I'm telling you to have
her here because you guys I mean she
really is a powerful voice like working
for you guys and that's the whole thing
and you know what happens is it's the
people that actually they understand the
other people that are struggling out
there they know their struggles they
understand what they're going through
and they care and they have compassion
she has compassion just compassion when
I'm through you oh my god you got way
more than me and then and then it's that
that matters in this world because you
know and
how many times that people are sick that
no one's supporting them like they start
losing their friends they start losing
you know they start losing friendships
and they get told that it's all in their
head they get told that it's because
they're lazy they get told you know and
their and their whole life becomes going
to their doctor's appointments and and
they really do struggle like so many of
you do and and I know that and I want to
change that we want to stop that like
Elena and I want to change that in the
world and and she's always working on
that and I'm working on that and I know
you guys are working on that too but the
whole point is is that we get it we got
your back and he got our little not
supporting him and I need that support I
need it yes you your power source here
um I love you guys thank you for for
joining us and hello to my country to
everyone really so many hearts are
getting so much love here it's crazy
I mean it's um that's how I feel about
all of them this has been an awesome
awesome time I can't believe it I just
blown away
thank you for coming on and thank you
for being here thank you alright
and I'm gonna click this off this we're
right here this is just like this here
we are